The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello, heroes. Those who have followed us through the veil, through the void,
and have come out on the other end as champions, you have completed the Maximum Fun Jar for 2011,
and we reached our goal with the help of you, and you, and you, and you, and you.
But not that guy in the back. Fuck that guy.
God damn it, Tave. Just once. Just once pitch in.
Did you say- Did you say Tave?
Tave. My friend Tave.
Is that short for Taven?
It's short for Tavian, actually. Tave-tion. It's like a-
I'm actually- I can't be mad at that guy. That poor guy with that poor name.
And listen, the English- the teacher at the community college isn't paying the bills like
it used to, and Tave-tion just likes to listen to the show. Who can blame him?
This is my brother. My brother meets a device show for the modern era. He's listening to us,
so he knows how to improve his own situation, so he'll be fiscally in a position to help out
next year when we call upon his aid. But let's not dwell on that. Let's dwell on
right now when I am Justin McElroy. And I am Travis McElroy.
And right now, I am Griffin McElroy. For the foreseeable future,
this is my brother, my brother, and me. So let's get right to the wisdom.
So if I, a dude, goes into the bathroom and all the urinals are taken, socially acceptable
in working order or otherwise, what am I supposed to do?
Wait around for a urinal to become available? Go outside again and try later? Take a stall?
If I take a stall, should I close and or lock the doors? Much obliged. Potentially harm.
Why wouldn't you close the door?
I don't know, because it's like you're sort of claiming that as your own, as your property.
You're, you're, you're staking your claim, and maybe you feel like you don't have a right to.
You take a wide dominant stance.
You're saying, hey, this is mine now.
I mean, there's, there, there's, if you'll forgive the pun,
there's, there's squatters rights that you have in a, in a bathroom stall.
If you post up in a bathroom stall, that's,
that's basically your apartment for the duration of your, your onesie or doosie.
Like I think, I think the moment though, that you're afraid of, if you're peeing in a bathroom
stall and then you walk out and in the time that you were in the stall, all the urinals cleared out,
you look like a douche when someone's waiting to poop.
And also everyone just thinks you're trying to hide your tiny dick.
Yeah. Why? What do you, what's your shame? What's, what's wrong with you?
As you walk into the stall announced, listen, this isn't because I have a tiny dick.
This isn't a shame thing.
All the urinals are taken.
And my dick's not even big. Like it's average.
I don't, I, listen, I have an average dick, but I need to, I like to say-
I just really need to pee.
Why don't you just wait it out?
Like what's the rush?
I think if somebody wants to shoot one, they will wait, they'll go around you.
It's not a big deal.
I used to be afraid of using the urinal, not because I have a tiny dick, but just because I
don't, I just don't want anybody to see my dick.
I'm like, that seems like if there's any, any given point during my day,
that I were to highlight as most likely to get my dick seen,
I would say that using the urinal is, is like number one, maybe number two on that list.
Right. And also you, you run the risk of splash damage.
Splash damage is bad.
And also I might see other dude's dicks and that, psychologically, that's, that's even worse for me.
So I used to use the stall.
I'm, I've gotten over that fear, but I'm sure there are other people who still suffer from it.
And to those people, I'm saying that you're, you're completely within reason.
Yeah.
The stall or just wait and use the bathroom at home like a normal person.
But like a human being.
Let's throw, slap a motto on this bitch.
Let's make it marketable.
Okay.
Yeah.
Go your own way.
I gotta get some rights.
What about this?
If there's no stall, you need to stall.
Okay.
Is that, is that, does that have some possibilities, you think?
That definitely has some possibilities.
I think no matter what, it's an intimate moment.
What you, what you do in a bathroom.
I can't think of an un-intimate thing that one would normally do in a bathroom.
And it's uncomfortable sharing that moment with other people.
So just, you know, it sucks.
You gotta get through it.
But stalls, I think, are the best place to do it.
Guys, I was lying in bed with, laying in bed with my girlfriend.
Sorry, Griffin.
And I asked her the age, if you could have sex with anyone, who would it be?
Oh, the age old, if you could have sex with anyone.
There is an age that you can have sex with people.
What is the age of anyone you could have sex with?
18, by the way.
Young enough to be legal, still in the prime, obvious.
Her answer was XBF or 50.
Because what's up?
Her answer was her XBF because it was so good and passionate.
I got cranky, rolled over and went to sleep.
She's now angry at me, saying it doesn't mean anything and it was no big deal.
Help.
Terry, Terry.
Is Terry asking how to get over this girl that he just broke up with because she said that thing?
This girl that he definitely, definitely just dumped.
See, the answer to that question is supposed to be like Shakira or Natalie Portman.
It's not supposed to be your friend Jeff.
Your fucking brother.
Like, no.
You're not allowed to do that.
And note to guys, if your lady asks you this question, the answer is her.
The answer is always her.
Can I get-
Crap.
Can I get you with red hair?
Is that-
Can I get you minus, let's call it eight pounds.
Like, I think right there would get you in the sweet spot for me.
You on a good day.
Yeah, no, she done fucked up, Terry.
And might I say, Terry, as one man speaking to another, what a moment this is for you.
Because it's rare that girls fuck up this clearly.
Like, this obviously.
Guys, all the time.
Like, if we get this question from a girl, I think the-
I don't think we'd be so-
It probably wouldn't be worth reading.
Her answer was a one-two punch, fuck you.
Because it like, it was so bad.
Fuck you, because it like, it was so good.
Like, number one, it was so good.
Like, fuck, I can't fuck like that.
Like, I can't fuck like Jerry.
I can't fuck like Jerry.
Like, I'm pretty good, but I'm not Jerry good.
Not only was it fucking good, it was passionate.
Those are the two key elements to good, good fucking.
Because it's gotta, like, there's gotta be technical ability behind it.
There's also gotta be a little something, a little extra spice, a little love.
A little bit of dance, you gotta know the craft, but the heart's gotta be there, too.
He was good at loving me.
Jerry was.
Back in the long, long ago.
Terry, I don't know what to tell you, man.
You done been wronged.
You've been wronged.
You need to be angry at her for the foreseeable future.
Yeah, why the fuck is she angry at you?
Why are you even thinking about this?
Jerry, Terry, Terry, Terry.
Oh, for the rest of your relationship, which I imagine will be about two weeks,
whenever you guys get into a fight, just yell at her about her mind fucking her ex-boyfriend.
Yeah, and you're with Jerry right now, aren't you?
In your heart, you're with Jerry still.
Not Terry, me Terry, not me, but Jerry.
I know it's confusing.
I know it's confusing, but you're with Jerry in your heart.
Recently, I was-
You want a yahoo instead of the thing you're doing?
Uh, yeah, yeah, that's why I started reading it.
This one was sent in by Nick Jensen.
Thank you, Nick Jensen.
Hey, Nick.
Hey, it's by Yahoo Answers user, Dean Windass, all right, who asks,
girls, what would you do if you accidentally sat on your ex?
If it was your worst ex and you went to sit down on a chair
and it was your ex's face that had been transformed into the seat of the chair
by some magic experiment gone wrong, when you sat down,
his nose went up your bum like this, and then-
Like what?
And then Dean Windass has included two parentheses,
marks that are facing inward to each other,
which I guess is supposed to be a butt crack.
My butt crack doesn't, I don't know, it's not beveled.
Is that the right word?
Although my butt crack is where I keep asides.
Yeah.
So there were like parentheses in that sense.
Well, what would you say when you realized it was him?
This is a survey.
Cool, cool.
Cool.
Hey, did you guys recognize this as a survey?
2010 census, I must have missed this one.
What would you do if your face was-
Like this is-
First off, I don't know where the first off is.
Your boyfriend's face was transformed.
Was the rest of him transformed into a chair too?
I mean, is that what we have to-
This is a left, right?
This is a person chair.
I'm thinking about that old lady from Doctor Who
who gets her face stressed out.
I think just that and let's just throw that on a love seat.
This chair looks like Jerry.
Terry, did you turn Jerry into a chair
and trick me into sitting on it?
I like that he had to add the extra component of
it's your worst ex as though if it were anyone else,
that would be completely fine.
Hey, honey, hey, sweetheart, if you could sit on anyone's face
who was turned into a chair by some magic experiment gone wrong.
And also their nose would go up your butt like this.
And you make parentheses with your hands.
Mine is George Lopez.
I like his comedy, but he also seems like a really good dad.
Yeah, and his skin is taut and leathery.
And I like a chair with some firm support.
George Lopez, your face is very comfortable to sit on.
Yeah, I'm not a fan of your work,
but I am enjoying sitting on your face.
It's like massage beads that taxi drivers use.
If I had a chair that the seat of which was composed
of George Lopez's face,
can I call it Beverly Hills Chair Wawa?
I think so.
I think that that would be more than acceptable.
Can I make a movie called Beverly Hills Chair Wawa
that's just a bunch of chairs instead of dogs?
Yeah.
I can do both of those things, but will I?
Probably not.
I'm a busy guy.
I'm afraid Stuart getting transformed
into a chair would actually be a bump for him.
That would be a big up.
To go from whatever he's doing now.
Whatever the fuck it is he's doing to be a chair.
So I guess that answers that.
What a fucking weird...
How about this?
How about this Yahoo answer?
What do I do when I read a question
from someone who's obviously insane?
Like obviously mentally unstable
that this is what they're pondering.
Diamond Mayweather responded and said,
I'd jump up, apologize, then move to another seat.
Well, of course.
Being more careful this time to check
to make sure it's not a person.
And then send them a polite sympathy note.
Jerry.
Cherry, I'm so sorry.
Cherry.
Please forgive me.
I'm gonna move over to that seat.
It's got George Lopez's face on it.
Which I believe my tuchus will prefer.
9 out of 10 tuchuses prefer George Lopez's face
to Terry or Jerry.
See, Jerry?
That's an area that Terry can compete with Jerry in.
Face comfort.
I have a friend named Badkins.
I think he's probably listening to this right now.
And he has this great pickup line
where whenever he's at a bar or a party
or something like that,
he doesn't do this all the time.
I don't want to make him sound like a grosso.
But if a girl comes over and is like,
hey, can I have a seat?
And he says, sure.
He takes his glasses off and wipes his face down.
I have to say, here you go.
This is where it goes.
Pretty good.
That's pretty good.
It probably never panned out.
It's still just rife with comedy.
Yeah.
Never worked.
Someday.
Keep the faith.
Recently I was volunteering at an event.
I hit it off with a girl I was working with.
I decided to ask her out to coffee
but put off to the last minute.
By the time I was going to ask her,
she was with a friend
and it felt weird asking her around her friend
and even weirder calling her away from her friend.
I didn't end up asking her out.
My question is,
were those even borderline reasonable
or just poor excuses and bad habits?
Thanks, Mitch.
I believe that.
Thanks, comma, Mitch.
Thanks, Mitch.
I think that those,
they seem like good excuses at the time
but I think that it would be just absolutely like bawling
if you just walked up and said,
listen, sorry to interrupt
and just asked her right in front of a friend.
I think it would show like huge confidence
and like, I think it would be a great start.
She would, if you got the guts to do it,
she's going to look awesome in front of her friend.
What person doesn't want that?
I disagree.
Uh-oh, that's rude.
What are you going to do?
Roll up there, be like, clam up.
It's me time.
Maybe not that,
but you know, just walk over and say,
I'm about to take off.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to see
if maybe you wanted to grab coffee sometime.
Who wants to be pursued demurely though?
Who wants, who doesn't want that passion,
that fire there?
So maybe just like run up and yell,
clam up and push her friend out.
I've been trying to wait.
I can't risk, you know, losing this opportunity.
I love you and I want to get married to you.
And then if she says no,
turn to her friend and say,
how about you?
How about you?
Yeah, maybe just the old eeny meeny miny moe.
I'm just laying them out on the table.
As long as they're out here,
would you like to pick them up?
I mean, as long as I'm laying them out for you.
Trying to catch a sweet baby by the toe over here.
Eeny, meeny, miny.
Who gives a rat's ass?
Let's both do it.
Let's go, ladies.
You and me, arm and arm.
Sex party, my place.
Show you my eeny, meeny.
You want to hook up to,
you want to hit up with CJ Maggies?
Let's hit the O'Charlies.
Get some, get some onion fringes.
Just get down.
But at the end of the day,
don't ever call someone away from their friend
to ask them out,
because you look like an absolute creeper.
Excuse me, just come,
just step over here real quick.
I have something private to ask you.
I'm not sure you look like a creeper, though.
I don't think that's fair.
I think that it just makes you seem like
asking a man out is something
you're incredibly embarrassed about,
and something that you wouldn't ever want anyone
to know you were doing.
I think it's creepy.
Hey, I have hemorrhoids,
and also I like you.
I like you very much.
Don't tell Debra.
Don't tell Debra over there.
Don't tell Debra, but we're in love.
She's got judgey eyes.
I hang out with six to seven people
every Saturday night.
It's a busy night.
We all go over to someone's house,
and then have dinner,
and play games and whatnot.
Two of these people are vegetarians.
When I go to their houses,
I don't mind eating their vegetarian nonsense,
but when they're coming over to my house,
should I have to go out of my way
to make some sort of vegetarian dish?
Or should I tell them to fend for themselves
as they would have done in the olden timey days?
Ryan.
It sounds like he should revise
the beginning of his question and say,
I hang out with four to five friends
every Saturday night,
and one to two vegetarian acquaintances.
Occasionally, after dinner,
they join with us.
What I love about this is the idea
of some sort of vegetarian dish.
Do you know what's a vegetarian dish?
Vegetables.
Like a salad.
That's vegetarian right there.
What?
First of all,
that's wildly wrong.
Everything you just said.
There's so much other food that vegetarians eat.
You're disqualifying yourself.
Do you eat salads?
Not everybody.
Yeah bitch, but like bread too, stupid.
Like what are you talking about?
Travis puts like chorizo sausage
on like two out of three meals of the day.
Your opinion when it comes to vegetarian matters
just don't count.
True.
What I'm curious about is
is how telling them to fend for themselves
in your apartment.
Like,
like hey there's some compost out back.
Like go nuts.
Go wacky back there.
Maybe grow some some bok choy.
You're gonna love it.
You're gonna love the fertile soils back there.
I think that if you're,
if you're picking a dinner
that you're gonna make for people,
I think that you shouldn't go out of your way
to make something for them,
but I think you should go out of your way
to make something,
not go out of your way,
but try to choose a dish
that would be easily convertible.
You know what I mean?
Don't serve meat noodles, for example,
would be right out.
That's a thing?
Yeah, sure.
Honestly, yeah.
Build your own,
like do a pasta thing
where you like you add whatever you want to it.
That way people could do like,
you know, meatballs
or they can just do the sauce
or whatever they want
and that way it fits everybody's lifestyle.
Do you think that Travis calls sausage meat noodles?
That's basically what they are
in a mind like his.
A beautiful mind.
Beautiful mind.
Like Russell Crowe on Russell Graham's movie.
What?
He did a movie,
it's called Beautiful Mind.
Oh, that one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't see it.
Yeah, somebody did.
Yeah, so I would serve something
that's like convertible,
that's easy to take the meat out.
Something easy to remove the meat from.
And I'd go with a syringe or whatever.
Don't like chicken cordon bleu
and just give him a pile of breadcrumbs
and some cheese.
You guys eat croutons, right?
Here's a bowl of croutons.
It's what you people eat, right?
Travis told me you guys just eat vegetables.
That's it.
But yeah, I would.
That's the way I would go.
Hey, Griffin.
Hey, Will.
You ready to take a trip with me?
I mean, I just,
I've still got the stink of the sky on me
because my plane just landed.
Your sky stink?
I've got a bit of sky stink still left on me,
but yeah, sure.
Let's go on a trip.
Where to?
The money zone.
Okay.
So we're there?
Is this-
We're there.
We're here.
Are we there?
This is nice.
I'm comfortable.
The chairs are much more expensive here.
Is this-
I believe it is George Lopez's face.
So what we want to talk with you guys about
is something that is close to mine and Griffin's hearts
and Travis, I suppose.
That's video games.
It's so rare we get to talk about video games here.
My brother and my brother and me.
And today we're talking about one called Kingdom of Loathing
or KOL if you're down.
Or KOL if you pronounce your O's weird.
If you pronounce your O's wrong, then it's KOL.
Now this is made by our friends at Asymmetric Publications,
including the creator Zach Jick Johnson
and the writer Josh Mr. Skullhead Knight.
Josh Knight, I don't think you needed a nickname,
but I think it's all right that you chose-
No, no, no.
That's his Christian.
That's his proper name.
His mom and dad named him Josh Mr. Skullhead Knight.
Josh Mr. Skullhead, all hyphenated first name.
That was his baptismal name.
That's the name he was given upon confirmation.
Sure, sure.
He was named after Pope Mr. Skullhead.
I don't think this is a hand-drawn stick figure graphics.
Right.
It has some surreal humor, some word play.
Don't let the stick figure thing turn you off
because these are some high quality stick figures.
Yeah, I mean, you could tell the definitions there.
Even though they may be stick figures,
you feel the emotion, you feel the passion.
How many pixels does it support?
Easily a billion.
How many megs of RAM car mine?
There's probably a lot.
They have tons of players.
I was turned on to this game and played it for a while
in college way back when.
It's been around for like eight years.
And it's still going strong.
Now, Griffin, I like online multiplayer RPGs,
but I don't have a lot of cash.
Is that going to be a problem?
It is going to be a problem with other parts of your life
because you need cash.
We exchange cash for goods and services
in this capitalist society that we all live in.
But to play cool, or if you want kingdom of loathing,
you don't need a goddamn motherfucking penny, bitch.
It's a free to play, a free as shit, I think should be the name.
Free as shit.
And it's free as fuck, like so free.
It's been in development for eight years
with literally, we're told, tens of thousands of dumb jokes.
We have not counted them ourselves,
but that is what we are led to believe.
I have played it before.
It is, it's funny.
And it's not funny in that way of like,
it's not like internet meme funny.
It's like, it's just funny.
Like it's a funny game.
And you know what?
Not only is it free, you play it in your web browser.
Like they could not have made this game easier to access
unless they came to your house
and put it in some sort of syringe
and like jam it in your eyes.
Johnny Mnemonic.
It's got a cool community
and you filled with a lot of neat people
and you can join them right now.
You can just push some buttons on your keyboard.
You will be whisked away to said kingdom.
Tell us the exact sequence of buttons, please.
K-I-N-G-D-O-M-O-F-L-O-A-T-H-I-N-G, period.
C-O-M, enter key.
Or kingdomofloathing.com would also work
if you're not into putting letters together.
But go check them out.
Yeah, totally.
And as a special treat for anybody
who decides to do a promotion on our show,
which if you want to do one,
email Teresa at maximumfun.org
and she'll give you the hot deets.
You get a jingle.
All the best jingles have an intro, right?
Which all the best jingles have a smooth, smooth segue,
which this is one of.
Let's see.
I didn't pre-pro this one.
This is not going good, I don't think, Griffin.
K-I-N-G-D-O-M-O-F-L-O-A-T-H-I-N-G, period.
I need adventure and sticks.
I don't have money to acquire the adventure and sticks
I talked about.
I'll go to cool.com.
I can't go to cool.com
because that is something else I'll go to kingdomofloathing.com.
Kingdomofloathing.com.
Check it totally out.
So, wait, wait, wait.
Yes, one of my closest friends is full of hatred.
She's a really great person and I just love her guts,
but it's hard to constantly be around such negativity.
Stay posy, our friend Justin Russo always says.
But anyway, don't get me wrong.
Every now and then it's nice to have someone to vent with,
but believe me when I say nobody wants that all the time.
I don't know if she gets off on bitching about people or what,
but lately I've taken to saying,
can we just not talk about this right now?
And it's like she doesn't even hear me.
She completely ignores it.
I've explained it to her before.
She just doesn't seem to realize that it's exhausting
to be around someone so angry all the time.
Like I said, she's a valued friend
and I just wish this one thing was different.
Suggestions, how to with hate.
Wait, no, no, let me try again.
Suggestions, suggestions, how to with hate.
This is rough, man.
I can think of one or two friends off the top of my head
that I just stopped hanging out with
because they just brought me down all the time
because it's all they talked about was negative shit.
That's not just one thing that's wrong with them.
Like if you are a categorically negative person,
that affects every single aspect of your life
and it makes you not pleasant to be around generally.
Yeah, a lot of times I think the only way to go
is like intervention kind of thing
because I don't think there's anything,
it doesn't sound like there's anything you're doing
that makes her hate everyone.
So it's not like a behavior you have to change,
but maybe going to where I'm like-
I don't wanna sound like a downer,
but I don't know how you intervene with that.
Like how do you tell somebody like,
hey, completely change your whole worldview, please.
You know how you got this worldview?
Can you just flip that?
Just put that to R for me.
Can you bust that worldview out and flip it
and then reverse it?
Well, I think it's a matter of saying to her like,
hey, listen, you might not see it
because you're so close to it,
but you complain all the time.
You might wanna take a look at like your mental process
and figure out why you're so unhappy.
And once you do, get back to me.
It's hard to be with you right now.
It's hard to be around you right now
because you are such a negative person.
And I think you probably owe them that.
I think you owe it to them to say,
listen, I just can't take the negativity all the time
because that'll get up in you.
That will affect you and affect your day-to-day.
It'll build a home inside you.
Absolutely.
It's like that giant song,
make a little bird house in your soul,
except it's not a bird house.
It's like a shit house.
It's like an outhouse.
She's pooping in your heart is what I'm saying.
And you'll get septic if you let her keep doing it.
Especially if like everybody else sees that too
and all of a sudden now you're also getting associated
with the negativity because you're with her all the time.
So there's a certain amount of like,
it just seems like a really like negative influence
in your life on a lot of levels.
In fact, you know what?
It's so negative.
I say, let's go on the next question
because it's bringing me down.
Yeah.
I feel like I'm getting my heart shit in now.
Why are you shitting in Ditto's heart?
Come on.
Don't shit in his heart.
Look what your friend is doing now.
You need better reason to cut ties?
Shitting Griffin's heart.
That heart's already full of blood and egg yolk.
Griffin, you got a Yahoo for me?
I got like four.
How about this?
I guess this one was sent in by Metal Gear Jim,
which wasn't his Twitter name.
That was his actual name on like on the email.
So maybe it's by Yahoo Answers user John who asks,
could I take Tyra Banks?
John is five foot five, 130 pounds.
And I don't work out.
My GF just said that I wouldn't have a chance against Tyra.
Hmm.
What's the scrappiness?
Is his scrappiness?
It doesn't include his power rating.
Yeah.
Or anything like his special abilities or anything like that.
But I gotta say, even if you were about six inches taller
and like 20 pounds beefier and you did work out,
have you seen how fierce Tyra Banks is?
And look in her eyes.
Plus, there's just her large like collection of knives
that she carries on her person at all times.
Well, yeah.
But we're talking about modeling.
You're just like hand to hand like.
Yeah, yeah.
We're talking about a backstreet brawl.
No chains, no pipes.
Just the fists of a man named John
and the fists of a supermodel named Tyra Banks.
Are there any holds barred?
Let me check.
There is one hold barred.
Okay.
You can't say anything mean about her eyelashes.
Oh.
Actually, that's her weak point.
She's really sensitive.
You also can't bring up the time she spent in Paris
modeling with her mama, going from agency to agency,
trying to find someone who will take her under her wing
because she gets very emotional about that.
She went through some shit in gay Paris
and I think that that hardened her to like-
People tell her,
I've heard her say that, just like that.
Can you translate?
Can you just click Google translation?
I used Google translation that said,
you can't do this.
We don't believe in you.
You have bad eyebrows.
You have bad eyebrows?
Was that the word?
Listen, I know.
That's how they say it in Paris.
The eyebrows, I love your ears.
Listen, Tyra Banks will come at you like a fucking Wolverine.
Not like Wolverine from X-Men,
like a rabid Wolverine
and also kind of like Wolverine from X-Men.
Like both Wolverine from X-Men
and like a rabid fan of Michigan.
But on the bright side,
like the next day when you see your friends
and they're like, oh my God, what happened to you?
You be like, oh dude, Tyra Banks fucked me up.
She's got reach.
First of all, she's got reach on you
because she's a tall, beautiful lady.
Her being beautiful has nothing to do with her reach.
I just wanted to go ahead and put out the opinion
that she is in fact an attractive woman.
She's got nails probably, right?
That's safe to assume.
They're probably sharp and just the fierceness.
We can't stress the fierceness enough.
Once you're down on the ground bleeding
like a bloody heap, she's not gonna stop.
She will literally kill you.
Do you think that he could take Tyra Banks
if she were in her fat suit?
Oh, no way.
Are you kidding me?
You could kick her down a flight of stairs
she wouldn't even notice.
Could you take her in her hobo suit?
Yeah, her hobo suit, yes.
Tyra also should be noted has a weave,
which is basically bionics, right?
Unfair.
Man-made integration.
Good news, John, you won.
She got disqualified.
She got disqualified for the use of bionics.
I like my best friend's girlfriend.
I'm not a total douche,
so I'm not gonna try to steal her or anything,
but I wonder how I could stop being interested in her.
I can't talk to her just like another friend
and I can't stop seeing her because of my friend,
says Salazar.
Why are you cheating on your best friend?
Why are you such a...
No, no, no, I see what he's saying.
I get it.
And I don't hear what he's saying
because it sounds to me like he's inception cheating
on his best friend.
Like if you're dreaming about her,
like that shit's in your mind and that counts.
You lost already.
Salazar, I have a suggestion for you,
and that is to try to find faults with her.
Like focus on the bad stuff.
Out loud.
Because sometimes out loud,
try to say like,
hey, you got shoulders like a quarterback to her
and you can just really,
just sort of throw a pipe bomb in there.
Not literally, of course,
although, I mean, problem solved.
You've got, you've got eyebrows just like Tyra Banks.
You've got T Banks,
I brushes and that's not a compliment.
I don't know what your,
your eyebrow culture is in your area,
but it is not a positive.
I hear what you're saying,
but unfortunately she has no faults.
Oh, so she's so perfect.
And Salazar is in love with her
and maybe she's in love with him too.
And maybe they have to break that sacred bond
so that they can be happy for the rest of their lives.
Or maybe he could imagine her pooping
because maybe you can imagine her pooping.
See, I didn't want to say that
because we have a pretty strict
non-scatological rule for our show.
But if you can,
if you think I will break that rule to help someone,
but guess what, dog?
What if it,
what if you flip it and you imagine her pooping
and then you love it?
Oh God.
Now you have a crush on your boyfriend
and you're dirty.
No one likes you anymore because you're dirty.
Salazar, you're, you're on a tightrope.
I think you should just keep on walking
until you make it to the other perch.
I think you're doing it.
You're already,
well, you're already ahead of the game
because you've already like made the decision
that you're not gonna,
you're not gonna try anything,
which is great.
So, you know.
That's good too.
But if you've like,
the harder you try to not be in,
like, have you never seen a Renee Zellweger movie?
Like the harder you try to not be into her,
the harder you're gonna be into her.
The best thing to do,
and it sucks because it sounds like,
you know, a non-starter,
but you need to just stop thinking about her.
You need to just, it's not gonna happen.
It's not a thing.
He loves her, Travis.
Listen, Salazar,
have you considered going to her front door
and ringing it?
And also the boyfriend lives there too.
And she comes down and you have a boombox
and you're like,
say it's Carolers.
And she's like,
it's Carolers.
And you hold up signs
that actually tell her how you feel.
And then when you walk away,
she runs up and she kisses you.
And she says,
Merry Christmas.
She runs back inside and you're like,
okay, I guess I'm not in love with her anymore.
Hey love, actually,
that's a stupid fucking conceit,
by the way.
That's a dumb part of your fucking stupid movie.
I love you so much.
Here's this big romantic gesture.
All right, kiss you.
I don't, we're done.
I'm out.
Peace, dip.
I'm out, 2011.
I'm out.
I'm done.
Salazar, do all those things
and maybe it'll work.
Yeah, if you learn how to control the human heart,
you get right back to us, friendo.
Hey, would it be out of line for me
to ask your girl for her number
after only the first time I meet her?
What's happened to me a few times
is that I'll ask the girl
if she wants to grab lunch sometime
and then give her my number without asking for her
since I feel like I'm putting her
in a less awkward position.
But most of those times,
they never get back to me,
waiting by the phone.
If you feel like you're putting her
in an awkward position,
why are you speaking to this person?
Like it should be a pleasant thing
to like plan dates and exchange phone numbers.
Waiting by the phone,
you got something to offer.
This isn't a two-way street.
You're not putting anybody
in an awkward position,
offering a chance to go out on a date with you.
You're fun.
It is the year of our Lord, 2011.
Yeah.
Everyone's already connected as fuck, right?
I'm connected to every single person
in some way,
some ways more tangential than others.
Just ask for a fucking number.
It's not like you're asking her
to like move in with you.
You're not asking her
to like get life insurance policies together.
Is that a thing you can do?
Yes.
I don't know.
Just ask for a number.
What's the big deal?
Maybe you'll call her.
The thing is,
is like giving her your number is really passive.
Like it doesn't cause anything to happen, you know?
But getting her number is an active step
that shows interest
and that you then, you know,
can control the situation
instead of sitting at home
waiting for them to call you.
If she doesn't want to give up your number,
then if she doesn't want to give her a number,
she's not down.
Yeah, she ain't down.
She's just trying to get it to end,
get the time to end.
And so then you don't have to worry about it.
Like if it's okay to ask her for it or not,
because if she's not down,
then you don't lose anything.
Like you're not going to fail
because she said no.
And you go, okay, well, I tried
and you walk away
and you move on to the next attempt.
There is not everybody right now
go into your mind Inception style.
Get rid of the fear of being turned down
because you know what?
That can't hurt you.
Nobody ever died from it.
You get tougher and cooler.
I'm still afraid of it,
but that's only because I'm batting a thousand.
I'm pitching a perfect game.
You've never been rejected so.
I've stolen every base I've tried to steal.
I've baseball metaphored every baseball metaphor.
And I'm afraid that one errant pitch,
one errant baseball
will fuck up my whole streak.
Yeah, I understand that completely.
I get it.
And also I'm just like a really polite,
like nice guy.
I'm not saying that to my own horn
is just the real talk.
And I don't want to put a lady in a position
where she has to come up with an excuse
not to give me her number.
That's fucked up.
When I say it out loud,
it sounded more fucked up than it was in my head.
Well, then I don't want to be like,
I'm just so busy with work right now
that I can't give you my phone number.
I think we should all just enter into
a social contract with each other
that it's okay for a guy to say,
hey, can I get your number?
And it's okay for the girl to say no.
Yeah, see if the girl said no,
if the girl said no,
then I would be like happier than she was like,
well, I don't know,
because my aunt bloop, bloop, bloop, bloop,
like lie, lie, lie, lie, lie.
If you lie to me, I just feel bad
because I made you lie.
I made you say it,
and now you have to go to hell.
Peace out.
Waiting by the phone,
I think you should also probably get a little bit better
at figuring out people are in,
if people are into it,
if people are feeling your flavor,
because I'm not sure you are super great at that yet.
You'll get there.
Also, girls don't call guys.
Sorry, that's society.
You got to get on the hunt,
get on the hunt, pursue,
pursue a figure and passion,
and don't wait for her to finish her conversation
with her friends.
Also, asking someone if they want to grab lunch
is a passive thing that friends do.
Ask her to dinner,
ask her to a movie,
ask her on a real date.
Ask her to hold lunch.
Hold, ask her to have sex with you today.
Hey, I've got a Yahoo answer.
Do you want to hear it?
Sure.
Yeah, of course.
It was sent in.
This is incredible.
It was this exact question was sent in
by both Mike Bachman and Jacob Locker.
You two get married.
Two heavy ass hitters
in the Yahoo answer submission game
that we all met.
We met both of them at Praxis this past weekend.
And I suspect they love juicing.
They're probably juicing.
They're probably on a little bit of some
anabolic steroids just to get their humor muscles toned up.
They are as handsome as their submissions.
I will say that.
This question,
it was, it's written by Panda Coley who asks,
is this weird for brothers?
It's right in our wheelhouse, right?
No, sure, I guess.
I'm going to say that now.
My twin brother and I take baths together
because my mom wants to save money.
Smart, right?
We are 17 and it seems a little weird now
compared to when we were young.
Do you think this is weird or not?
What are those ages again?
They're twins.
So we're assuming that they're the same age.
Although it would be even weirder if they weren't.
Like I'm 20 and he's eight.
They're 17.
Why is it taking you this long to wonder if that's weird?
Hey, mommy.
We both can't fit in the bathtub anymore
because we have grown human adult bodies, mommy.
Hey, mommy, we're full grown humans.
There's no way that you can stack us in here
like Tetris blocks that we're not going to touch.
Your, our parts will touch.
There's no bathtub big enough to have a naked shower
with your 17 year old brother.
That's fat.
That's a fat.
It's not a shower.
It's a bath.
When you, when you take a bath,
you're making soup out of your, out of your grossness.
You're making soup out of your-
If I ever open like a, like a bathroom fixture store
and I sell like-
Or a soup store.
I'm going to advertise my large tub
as big enough for two full grown 17 year old males.
The problem is when you're in a, when you're in a bath,
which is already pretty gross,
you're just making broth.
You're making Todd broth or Zach broth.
I'm making-
You're making your own gravy.
When you get, when you get Tony up in there,
that's officially a stew and that's unacceptable.
Okay, wait, wait.
I have this all figured out.
The mother is not a weirdo.
The mother started selling Todd and Tony stew.
Yeah.
Like when they were little kids
and now she doesn't know how to cut off that revenue stream.
This is oaky.
Somebody's been playing soccer.
This is getting better with age.
I love this stew.
You have to give me your secret recipe, Tammy.
I can't.
It's a dash of Todd, dash of Zach,
and just like a whole bunch of weirdness
that they are never going to recover from.
Just can't recover from this.
You can, you can really taste the scarring.
The two things that aren't going to recover from the stew
are your hunger and Todd and Tony.
Those are the two parts that will,
that will never make a comeback.
What's the age?
What's the cutoff?
Can we come up with this right now
and then we can send it to Panda Coley
and just be like,
you need to turn your mom into the fucking police.
Five.
Yeah, five.
You think once you come off the T,
like once you come off,
I would say once you're off the T,
not that I was on the T at five, come on.
I'm saying like off the T,
off the brothers lap in the bathtub,
you fucking weirdo.
Get off of there.
I would say that as soon as you're old enough
to no longer need a spotter,
like if you're afraid of like drowning in the bathtub,
make sure there's someone else in there.
Okay, but wait a minute.
Wait just a second because that life is like a recursive.
It's like a snail shell.
And once you get to be like 80,
you need a spotter again.
Can we start throwing 80 year olds in the same bath?
Yeah.
Yeah, and they shrink too.
Like they get better.
They do.
Old people are basically Shrinky Dinks
that you put in the bathtub
and then you got a full-
And you look at their Shrinky Dinks.
I can debate the number as far as age a little bit.
I can give you some wiggle room, no pun intended.
But if, I have to put a firm wall on pubes.
In fact, the T-shirt says,
if you see a hair, you can't be there.
That's the rule for me on bathtubs.
Like you can't, at that point, no dice.
What about, can we put an old dude
and like a baby in the same bathtub?
Like an 85 year old.
Well, but then I feel like that's unfair to the baby
because if the old man goes down,
what's the baby supposed to do?
Baby can't save that old man.
He doesn't have the lung strength.
What if we get a baby, an old man,
and a 17 year old all up in the same bath?
And then you gotta get them all across the river
from one bath to the next.
The baby, the old man will eat the baby.
Yeah, no question about that.
He's confused.
The 17 year old will eat the grain.
You have two rafts, go.
Go, solve it.
Hey, I wanna hear Griffin's last question.
But first I wanna say thank you
to everybody we met at PAX East this weekend.
You were total sweethearts.
We saw so many My Brother, My Brother, Me shirts.
We saw our friend Brentalfloss was there.
He put on a great show.
And you guys were all so nice and genuine.
It made me really look forward to April 17th.
What up?
Because it's my birthday.
We'll be in Chicago and we'll be doing
My Brother, My Brother, Me live
opening up for Jordan and Jesse Go.
What's up?
Are you there?
Yeah, I should say so.
Tickets are gonna be way affordable.
They're gonna go on sale soon, I would imagine.
We'll let you know.
Follow us on Twitter and keep checking Maximum Fun.
That really is my birthday, by the way.
And we are gonna go out afterwards and get silly.
We're gonna get slizzard.
We are gonna get our wastey faces on.
We're gonna get our dicks wet.
I don't know, because we're on a water slide.
We're gonna make it so wet.
We're gonna go to the old town ale house
and we're gonna go on a water slide
because those are all over the place here in Chicago.
Yeah, just streets are littered with them.
I rode a water slide all the way from O'Hare to my apartment.
Keep it, keep it.
Keep your focus on My Brother, My Brother, Me.
nbnbam.com, nbn, at nbnbam on Twitter
and we will let you know about tickets and everything
but it's gonna be off the chain, off the hook, off the chuck.
So right.
If you wanna get in touch with us,
go to nbnbam.com right there and text.
You'll see our email address.
We have a voicemail that you can call.
What's that number, Griff?
It's 203-nbnbam1.
Yep.
And you can call us for questions and stuff.
Again, we can't thank you guys enough
for your support with Maximum Fun Drive.
Holy shit.
We had a couple of people who, you know,
groused a little bit.
Most of you were just so generous
and gracious about the whole thing.
Seriously, it's the best.
If you donated and you haven't listened
to all the other shows,
now is the best time to do so
because you're supporting them.
They're your shows.
Go listen to them.
Go give them a listen.
Subscribe and shit.
I don't know how podcasts work.
I just make them.
That's all there is to it.
Hey, Griffin.
Hey.
I'm ready.
Oh, one more time just to remind you.
Go check out kingdomofliving.com
if you haven't.
Go do it right now.
It's free.
It's free as fuck.
So fucking free.
Do it.
Oh, man.
How about this?
So this one's sent in by Jackie or Jaqui Ronan.
There's a Q and a U in there.
I'm just spitballing.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Zoraz.
Who says Quidditch for dogs?
Is this true?
This is Justin McElroy.
This is Travis McElroy.
This is Griffin McElroy.
This is my brother, my brother and me.
Kiss your dad's square on the lips.
Keep your heart, three stacks.
Keep your heart.
Hey, keep your heart, three stacks.
Man, these girls are smart, three stacks.
These girls are smart.
Play your card.