If you change your mind, I'm the first in line Honey, I'm still free, take your chance on me
If you need me, let me know, I'm gonna be around If you got no place to go when you're feeling down
If you're all alone, when the pretty birds have flown Honey, I'm still free, take your chance on me
If I do my very best, I'm an angel
That's it, step one, talk like Bill Clinton
Maybe a fellatio goof
My fellow Americans, blow jobs
Is that good? Is that a good impression?
You are gonna call that number
You will call that number and it will not be accidental, it will be drunk
Maybe not today, maybe not tomorrow, it'll maybe be a year from now
When you're real sad and lonely on Valentine's Day and you just call her at night and you go, hey, hey Debra
We haven't spoken in about a year
I thought we had something special together
Oh man, the whole episode, huh?
This is former president Bill Clinton
I'm a ghost now, now I'm a ghost who loves blow jobs
I love blow jobs, balanced budgets and hauntings
Griffin, yours sounds more like Don Nott's
The secret to Bill Clinton is you gotta sound like a ghost underneath a bunch of blankets
That's the secret
I love Bill Clinton
And if you felt a little undertaker in there
Oh yes, it's me, former president Bill Clinton
Blow jobs
We're like milk, we're zero scoops
We actually cool other people's love when they drink us
Just to be in our presence kills other people's love
Yeah, we're the opposite of love, whatever that is
They need to come up with an opposite of love
How about it, wordsmiths?
Happy love
Even with all your science, you still haven't been able to come up with a word that's the opposite of love
Yeah, it's pretty despicable
You know, you think about Shakespeare
Shakespeare created eyeball, he created the word puking
Green-eyed monster
Skim milk, obscene
Luggage
That's all created by Shakespeare
He couldn't come up with the opposite of love
Pinterest?
He did not
He did, he was talking about someone, I think it was in Two Gentlemen of Verona
Where he says, her practicing her sartorial craft
She had a lot of Pinterest because she had a lot of interest in pins
And then the other gentleman of Verona responds
It's not that she loved her, he opposite of loved her
He did, he didn't
Then he vomits and blacks out for six hours
It's his longest play
As a result
In lots of theaters they cut that, they trim it down to three hours of vomiting and blacking out
Well you can usually just turn it into a dream ballet
That kind of conveys the time
Or you do a War of the Roses kind of thing
You're like, hey buckle in audience
Yeah, purists do the whole thing
This is a three hour song about social networking platforms
I am Barbacane the Tumbler
Lord Steven of LiveJournal
I don't know what's happening
I would like to have been there on this day when this girlfriend asked this guy how much he loved her
And he responded, I don't know
I have to go to Yahoo Answers
A hundred?
I literally can't quantify it
How big is a house?
We have an opportunity here, not to equate it to another metric
But to come up with our own metric
That we can think about how much money we can make off of that
If we sold that shit to Hallmark and we just said like 50 billion
Throbs
Throbs is so good
I'm mad that we were going to have this whole riff and Travis just nailed it right out of the gate
It's throbs, obviously
It's sexual, but it's also heart related
Okay, so zero throbs is just utter indifference
And negative throbs is that hatred or does hatred have its own
Now what is hatred?
I'm sorry, I forgot the goof
Hahahaha
I'm not even going to do your throb goof now because you ruined my goof
Please don't take this out on the money making opportunity that we have in front of us
Once a season I get a goof veto
And I'm using it to veto this goof as a punishment
For you unintentionally killing my goof
This is like a goof end of Reservoir Dogs
Hahahaha
Travis is cutting a goof ear off
Just dancing
Fuck
Say your dumb thing about the throbs
My internal critic is Rupert Giles from Buffy the Vampire Slayer
And whenever I have no matter what entertainment or media I'm taking in
He's always disappointed in me
That's not a goof
I feel guilty all the time that I'm not reading books
Hahahaha
Sometimes for me it's Wanda, sometimes it's Maggie, sometimes they're together
I would watch that buddy comedy all day long
They made it, it's called Taxi
Hahahaha
I don't have an internal critic
Is that normal?
You have a lot of external ones
Hahahaha
I get ballots
This one was sent in by Graham Wetterburn
Thank you Graham
That's a good name Graham
Yeah it's by Yahoo Answers user Raj who asks
Why does Dilbert's tie curve up?
Hahahaha
Scott Adams said in an interview with groundreport.com
No one really knows, including me
Dilbert started as a doodle before I knew he would be famous
I don't remember what I was thinking the day I decided to curl his tie up
WikiAnswers' search tells me
A. It's a metaphor for his inability to control his environment
B. He's just glad to see you
But IMO. A mini hurricane surrounds him and keeps flapping his tie
To all Dilbert fans, what do you think?
Hahahaha
Oh god
Who thinks about Dilbert this much?
Apparently not even Scott Adams can be troubled to figure out why his dumb tie is standing up
He's too busy hating women
When you ask the sexist creator of Dilbert
Hey what's the deal with the tie?
He's like fuck it I don't know
Stop pursuing that line of questioning
Why is his tie sticking up?
Cause she didn't cook it long enough
Hahahaha
In the kitchen
I'm Scott Adams
Why is his tie sticking up?
Why are you not having kids?
Get out of my face
Scott Adams
Hold on, I really think this Scott Adams character is going somewhere
Why don't you workshop it and come back
Hahahaha
Justin's going to go workshop his Scott Adams character for a couple minutes
Travis and I are going to goof on the original cue
But Justin's going to go off
Hahahaha
You guys go forward and I will dip back in
In a little bit with some more Scott Adams
Let me give you a setup
It's Scott Adams in a pet shop
That's run by a woman
Good good
Okay
I also like the person who ever said number two
He's just happy to see you
Dilber's just got himself a tie bow in there
Nothing weird
He's got a tie-rection
I think it's suggesting that Dilber is so bound to his job
That his tie has literally become a part of his body
And when blood flow increases to the tie
It forms a fully erect phallus
And he has a really curvy wiener
Yeah
Just like a hook, like a fish hook wiener
It's just a half chub
If it was a full chub, his tie would be sticking straight out from his neck
Why are these poodles so expensive?
Must be your time of the month
Well, there he is
Hey, Scott Adams, ladies and gentlemen
Hey, what's next?
What's our next scenario?
Scott Adams is an astronaut going to the moon with a female astronaut
Okay, I'll check you out
This is the kind of question, right?
That somebody doesn't just ask
Well, they did ask it
No, but I'm saying this isn't like
Oh, it just popped in my head
They've stared at Dilber every Sunday
Here's a few excerpts from my thesis
My master's thesis
What's the deal with Dilber?
I mean, there are a couple of answers from people who say
Adams is also hinted that the tie may just be displaying an aversion to him
We may never truly know why Dilber's tie does what it does
Dilber's tie doesn't do shit
It's not a real thing
A dude draws it and he doesn't know why he does it that way
There's no deeper truth
I just heard Justin inhale sharply
Which makes me think he's ready to give us his
Scott Adams goes to the moon goof
Why are you even coming, Angela?
The moon's made of green cheese, not malls
Yeah
I'm Scott Adams
The first opus was a little stronger
And he's also starting to mutate a little bit into the Wolfman
Can I have one more?
Oh, God
I need to redeem myself
Scott Adams is getting married
Okay, got it
DiabloAnswersUser? responded to me
I think that Dilber's tie curves up to give him some individuality
He works at one of those office settings where he is really just another number and paycheck
Nobody's special
He can be replaced at any time and nobody would notice
I think Dilber's tie makes him stand out
Even though nobody really comments on it
Hey, I think you're projecting a little bit, bro
Yeah, maybe just a touch
And maybe Dilber's there and Angela and accounting just doesn't want to talk to him
Even though he's a super nice guy and he offered to make her dinner
And that's why his tie curves up
It's hard, man
He just gets repressed by his triangular boss
And his dog talks
Which is pretty cool
His dog talks and his cat is like an evil scientist
I haven't read it in a while
But there's an intern or something
And they're real
Do you remember we used to have that Dilber screensaver?
Yeah, the Dilber desktop games
Man, when I was nine, that was a jam
Yeah, we played some real dumb shit
Hey Justin, you got that goof ready for us?
For all that you are
And all that you will be
And all that we will be together
I do
Want you to get in the kitchen and make me some hamburger helper
I got it
Shit
Is this the first lie bowl we've ever done?
If you guys could adopt one celebrity
Who would it be?
Obviously, not Dilber Godfrey
He's going to keep you rolling, right?
With all the zingers
But I don't think that
The rest of it would make up for it
Ian McShane
Okay
What would Ian McShane be like, Travis?
Mostly he'd just shuffle around the house
In a bathrobe cursing
Sounds pretty good
Wouldn't that be awesome?
And just have friends over and be like
Don't mind my Ian McShane
Don't let him climb on your lap
Ian, down
Down
I'm going to go with Giamatti
Oh
I imagine him hiding up in the corner of the ceiling
And just spot him with a flashlight to get him down
Don't look at him, it's a challenge
Giamatti
Do you know what the problem with having a pet Giamatti is?
He's a Pokemon
It's Giamatti
Giamatti, go
You're so skittish
Go
Giamatti is the human equivalent of a comically large rabbit, I feel like
Oh crap
Justin
What?
You got a celeb?
I'm not going to adopt a celebrity to make any goddamn sense
They're people, they live in houses
They are human beings
I don't understand
I don't understand the question
And as requested
As promised, I should say
We have got a jingle
That is
Over a month in the making
Don't fucking talk about that
And it's been something Griffin has been sort of working on in his spare time
In his off hours in the basement
Five weeks
About 35 minutes of work on it
Yeah
Just hours of tinkering
He just wants
Sometimes he'll say, can I hear it?
And he'll be like, he's not ready
It sounds tinny
Bring up the speaker
It's got hand claps
It's got bass
It's got kazoo noises
It's got layering
It's going to be amazing
Here it is
Put your soap in my soap
And we'll both get clean together
It's got a divot for your pleasure
You gotta use that soap
Don't you waste your soap away
Buy yourself some bars today
Yeah
Don't let your skin get dry
Stack soap, don't use no lye
Stack your soap into the sky
Buy yourself a little hope
A little hope with Stack Soap
Stack Soap
Get yourself clean
Buy yourself a part
That's where you'll find it
Get it on Kickstarter
It's going to smell so fresh
Soap
Wow
I hope I win the Grammy this year
for best soap song
Just to take things a little serious for a second
but not too serious because we'll come up the other end
The last time that we all went to Golden Corral
was the first Christmas Eve after our mother passed away
We decided that's the time we've got to get in there
and gnaw on the beef hooks
That's going to turn us around
We were like, we'll go out to dinner for Christmas
and didn't think of the fact that it's fucking Christmas
and everybody in their right mind is closed
Everybody's closed so there's one place that's open
Motherfucking Golden Corral
Well don't worry guys because it was the closest restaurant
to the cemetery we had just visited
Pretty good choice Golden Corral
How much does this restaurant cost to eat at?
Everything
Do you want to know the saddest part?
We weren't the only ones there
It was full of people getting their holiday nosh on
None of them were quite as in good spirits as us
Nobody made eye contact
You could tell the holiday magic was there
because a boy would come up to the beef hook
and a man would scoot over a little bit
Come on Junior
Come on
Get on in here
I've already gotten through the pre-gristle
Really tuck into the meat
All those boys over there
They just made a terrible life choice
They probably could have made spaghetti at home or something
Just slosh your sauce
and count your blessings
If I go to Italy and talk with an Italian accent
would I offend the Italians?
I'm going to Germany, Austria, and Italy May 23rd for 11 days
I just wanted to ask
I talk with an Italian accent but don't speak Italian
Would the Italians find that offensive?
I can't imagine
Why would they?
I think they'll find it flattering
They might think they're having a stroke
Why do I understand?
I don't understand what you're saying
But it's Italian, it's got to be
It's got to be Italian
Look at you
He's an innovator
He's a pioneer of the Italian language
I don't understand any of it
You douchebag
This you doucher
This is either like
You either are planning on doing this
Which is bad
Or you already speak with an Italian accent
But you don't speak Italian
And your name is Kevin
So you're not from Italy originally
Do you know why people have accents?
Do you know how that happens?
Because they're from the place, Kevin
Jesus, Kevin
Kevin, you are from Nebraska
You speak with a Nebraska accent
A Nebraska brogue
I've never been to a foreign country
But I have to imagine
That it would be the same
As if anyone from Italy
Rolled up to America
And was like, now I'm going to speak with an American accent
Like
I don't hope for that
It wouldn't be a thing
It would be like, como esta
Mi amigo
Donde esta
La biblioteca
Donde esta la biblioteca
Biblioteca
Que tal
Mi amigo
I sound like the DNA strand
Yeah, you do
Dinosaurs
Mi amigo
De
Ñe
Es
Es tu amigo
Oh my
God
Donde esta
Thunder Lizard
Bien con migo
A Jurassic Park
Que es tu nombre
Mi nombre es
Jose Hammond
Que es la problema
Mi amigo
Tassara Tops
I wish I knew more Spanish
But I don't know any
I know how to ask for the library
Or maybe bookstore
I know how to say bathroom
And Mr. Ian Malcolm
Oh
Baby finds a wife
Es verdad
Christ
Yeah, oh god, don't do this
thing, Kevin
I have recently embarked on a year long
personal crusade to shed a bunch
of extra LBs
I've got a lot to lose, so I've broken it down
into 20 pound milestones, so I have goals
to plan against. And the first one is coming up
soon. In general
I fit the heavy set ponytail, bearded
nerd stereotype, so recently had
the idea I should probably mix it up at each 20 pound
milestone. Cut my hair, shave
my beard, start dressing a little nicer
Do you guys have any other ideas for potential
me changers, health
style or otherwise, that's trying
to rock it in Rochester
First of all, good on ya
Yeah, I love this question
so much I could faint. Getting it in 20
does. 20 does
you were getting it
I love the physical appearance
and caring about all that. Make sure that you're
taking care of your mental
self as well, so maybe on the next
milestone, you try
something, you know, food
or beverage related that you've never tried
before, something a little adventurous, and maybe you find
that you have a
great palette for wine, or
you really like Italian food, you know, something
new. Wait, hold the
fuck up, Travis. What are you
are you saying?
To reward yourself on this quest
to lose weight, what you should get
into is wine and
Italian food? Okay, let me strike
that. Oh yeah, I lost 60
pounds. Time to go to the OG and gain
it all back. What about
carb up and slurp down? I will have
all the fujule
Let me see all the fujule that you
got on your shelf. Well, just let me introduce
myself. I'm fat again
Then
can I say art?
Yes, not only
can you say art, you should have said art
the first time. I'm going to double back
and say art. You can't.
You can't. I can't. You guys
edit out your shit all the time.
He's
right about that.
He is not wrong. So let's say
rather than food and beverage, let's say culture
and maybe
go to a museum
or go to see a ballet
or go to see a symphony, something, you
know, that maybe you're not
normally into and you just want to check out and see
if maybe you dig it. You guys are thinking
so small scale.
I am
amazed at you. This guy
is offering us a chance. Every
20 pounds he loses, he can
totally and completely
reinvent his entire persona
so much so that
his friends won't recognize him.
You lose 20 pounds, cut your
hair, shave your beard, wear
sunglasses constantly, and
say your name is now Roz.
Lose another 20 pounds,
maybe you
go hit the tanning bed constantly
and you bleach your teeth
and then you change your name again to Brock.
Or the Brock.
Or the Mr. The Brock.
And then next time, you're going to
be really fit. Maybe get that asshole
bleached and let's see if we can't get a porn career
going. Lose 40 pounds, bleach that asshole,
regain 20.
Where are you at now?
Your friends don't know which side they're coming
from. Lose 40 pounds of fat,
regain 20 pounds of fuck
muscle. Get in there. What is
that?
It's what you
use to thrust. It's the
thrusters. It's your
thrusters. I just gotta get
your thrusters going and your afterburners.
I learned these.
I'm going to take you to hyperspace.
Try a barrel roll.
It's bad news.
Our shields are failing.
Girl, girl.
Fire up the tachyon cannons.
Oh man. I need some
more dilithium crystals, by which I mean
meth. Of course in that case
it would be fuck meth. Because it's the meth
that you use for sex.
I learned in school that
every muscle is a fuck muscle or you're just not
doing it right.
What class was that in?
What school were you going to?
Health school.
You dummy.
I saw an episode of Morrie recently
where Morrie likes to cure people of their fears
by something Morrie believes in called immersion therapy.
Where he
is like, I know you're afraid of band-aids.
We're covering you with band-aids.
Wake up. You've been covered with band-aids
this whole time. There was a lady
who was afraid. Her big
fear? Tigers.
And Morrie brought a tiger.
That's a perfectly reasonable fear.
Can we all keep our fear of tigers?
Can we not be afraid
of tigers? That seems like a super
good one.
Deborah, just keep in mind that the tiger
is just as afraid of you as you
are of it. Oh, no. It wasn't.
Sorry, you're dead.
They're acting like it's a problem
because I can't even look at
Frosted Flakes. Don't get Frosted Flakes.
Don't go to Frosted Flakes.
Get the off-brand
toasted flakes.
And don't go to Exxon.
I think that's pretty much it, right?
Don't go to any Bengals games.
My day-to-day exposure to
tigers is actually pretty low.
I don't have to see a
tiger if I don't want to. You know what?
Thinking about that, mine might be a little bit too low.
I'm not sure I'm getting enough vitamin T.
Everybody's got some
needs, and
everybody's got some wants.
Extreme
Restraints' catalog of sexual
products will fulfill both of those
things for you.
So visit extremerestraints.com
and
get
an electroshock paddle that goes
on your balls.
Is that a real thing?
It should be.
I'm
going to request that you put a real product
in there.
Go to extremerestraints.com
and buy a ghost
that you can fuck every night.
That's
not a thing. We need a site
called Extreme Restraints.
Go to extremerestraints.com
and buy a sexual
fish tank.
You're
doing an ad for
extremerestraints.com.
Go to extremerestraints.com
and learn about all the good chicken
Popeye recipes
on the forums.
Holy
inaccurate. Everything you're saying right
now is a bastardization of this product message.
This is by Yahoo Answers
user marymaryx30
who asks,
how do I improve my scorpions?
My
scorpions are okay, but not the best.
How do I improve them? I've been
struggling with them for months.
That's it?
That's so important. That's the context?
Best at what?
By the way, when I said that it was related
I meant completely
diametrically. Best in what
capacity? With scorpions
you have four basic
criteria for
judging their quality.
It's their four danger zones, right?
Yeah, the four danger zones you've got to worry
about. One, exoskeleton.
Yes.
What kind of chitin is he working
with? Can we improve it?
How's your chitin? Is he getting enough vitamin D?
That's huge for chitin.
D is, I say, I've
always said that. What's that motto
you always tell people and you have it
cross-stitched up on the
hanging up there in the den above the fireplace?
What is it?
It's
you gotta have D
if you want
if you don't
don't shed your
don't shed
that chitin.
Fuck!
It took
it took our mom weeks to stitch
exactly that, but Griffin
was very... And she was not a
swearing woman. Yeah, she did not
enjoy swearing, but Griffin was very
specific. So armor.
Armor, that's number one.
Second, of course, claws.
Does it look like a little
crab? Do I know if scorpions
have claws? How are the
pincers? How are the pincers?
Number three,
obviously,
pointy tail.
What's in there?
Who knows? Caramel?
Poison?
I injected some caramel into all your treats.
I'm the best scorpion ever.
And then what's the fourth
one? Heat coming off the genitals.
How is its
genital heat? Also, can you find my
scorpion's genitals for me?
Can I make a 1980s movie called
Genital Heat? I've been over this
motherfucker's thorax with a fine tooth comb.
No genitals to be found.
If you see a scorpion in your
house, your very
next stop is
an open house.
Century 21.
Pardon me.
This is a lovely open
house. Thank you for having me. I'll take it.
I cannot sell my old
house because the scorpion lives there now.
It's his now.
I'm gonna try to charge him taxes
on the sale, but
I don't know how- scorpions don't have money.
Can we improve the
mass marketability of these scorpions?
You guys are missing the obvious
answer. What? What's that, Travis?
Steroids. Travis, I don't
think that- Wait.
You're running away from me because you want to make these
scorpions, like, super
beefy? I don't know that they have
beef. Right.
I don't know that they have beef to
embiffen, you know? I think it's just
just skittering- Well, not yet.
Skittering claws? You gotta get them on
a regime. It's all
chitin and- On a regimen.
It's chitin and just hate in there.
Maybe you could paint their
shells like hermit crabs.
See, I like that. Paint the scorpion
for kids.
This is what I'm talking about.
Can we make scorpions
the new Furbies?
Of course. Just a tiny
cork on their stingers.
That would be adorable.
And rubber bands
on their claws.
I think scorpions are so hateful that
if you cork their tails and
rubber banded their claws, that they'd, like,
learn to bite.
Yeah, they'll grow fangs. Or learn how to use a gun.
Or just become really spiteful.
Use their words to hurt you.
Looking fat today, J-Man.
Hair's looking a little
thin.
Not as young as you used to be,
J-Man. So he turns into
little juice.
It's an old parable. It's an old story
of the frog and the scorpion.
The frog gives the scorpion a ride across
the river, and halfway across,
the scorpion starts calling him, I don't know,
stupid and stuff. And the frog starts crying.
He's like, why are you such an asshole?
And the scorpion's like, it's in my nature!
But then does he sting him?
No.
Because he's got a tiny cork on his tail.
He just batters him with the cork.
He's like, you like that? Ow!
New line of frog-safe scorpions.
Each one is $20.
Who is the first to buy?
God, can you imagine
a frog with a scorpion on its
back, and the frog is also
full of hate? And then like,
you get that lethality
of a scorpion with the mobility of a frog?
Well,
we're done. Oh, shit. And the frog
is secreting some sort of hallucinogen.
So the scorpion is just
freaked out.
The frog has a really high credit score,
so he's able to like, get a house.
Why would that be a thing?
And one of them is played by Ray Romano.
Oh my god, the frog is Ray Romano.
Ugh.
Oh, and the scorpion's played by Tim Allen.
We've got a hit! Listen, this has been
the least productive
meeting we've had about Madagascar 4 yet.
And I think we need
to go back to the drawing board
and really see where we went astray.
We have a theory that it's when we introduce
scorpions.
They ruin everything, including
our Madagascar 4 production meetings.
I'm reading more of this Yahoo answer,
and I think that a scorpion is a yoga position.
Oh.
Moving on.
None of that was helpful to this person.
You don't know.
You throw it at the wall, you see what it takes.
They might have found something in there that was useful.
Here's what it takes. Scorpions.
Their feet are like needles.
Hey, brothers.
There's someone
really into yoga
that's been screaming at their iPod
for five minutes.
You dumb motherfuckers!
I'm not saying like, lying like
I'm not.
I've got a real hearty penis.
No, I'm not.
I'm not talking about lying like...
It's like a can of Senka down there.
He's talking about lying like saying things like
no, I'm not afraid of masks.
Yeah, right. Pretending like I'm not afraid
of the robot woman from Superman 3.
Should that come up in casual conversations.
Oh, you know who I like?
You know what never scared me?
The HBO logo they used to show
for the movies in the 80s.
It never really scared me.
You're the ever loving shit out of you.
No big deal. It was pretty frightening.
Hey, y'all. Thanks for
listening to our Best Of episode.
As you all
might have guessed, if you
follow us on other social channels, there's
a good reason for why we don't have a regular
episode out this week and that is
that Vine is shutting down
and I'm just really struggling with it.
Yeah, that's the story of the week
and Vine...
I miss it so much.
I miss it so much. I learned so many
valuable lessons from it but now it's just like
what's the... like comedy is dead
kind of. Yeah, comedy's
over. I miss
it so much because you know what was nice about it?
It was easy. It was so easy.
Six seconds, one and done.
One good
toot. Yep.
And that's a viral baby.
It's viral content.
No, the real reason why we don't have an episode this...
Oh, we do have an episode this week but not a normie.
Is that
Travis and Teresa had a baby.
What? Yeah, I'm...
Oh, you're not just finding this out, are you Justin?
No, I knew that. It was just a little joke for the show.
See, and that joke was the perfect length
of time to go into Vine.
Yes, both
baby and mama are doing well.
It is a girl.
These are all things that Travis said I was allowed to announce
on the show, which is very exciting.
Her name is Bebe.
Barbara Lee McElroy and we are
so, so, so happy for Travis and Teresa.
And so we're doing this special
episode. I guess another programming note,
that Casper special that we were
talking about doing is going to be not
on Halloween, because that's today.
Yeah. But we're going to figure this out
sort of as
we go. So we ask for your patience
and we're going to keep churning out the content
for you. And
again, congratulations to Travis and Teresa.
And
I guess my condolences to myself.
Yep.
Is this before the show or is this
in the middle of the show? No, this will be in the middle. Okay, great.
Well, that means that we're in the middle of
the money zone and it's time to
go there
and be there. Are we there? Dude, I've
been there for the past two minutes. Like I've been getting
paid this whole time talking about Vine going down
and my new great niece.
Well, that is a, well, she's just
your niece. No, but she's great
though. She's not. Okay.
This is the perfect opportunity for me to tell you about
a bowl and branch. Getting a great night's sleep
is easier and more affordable than you might think.
Griffin, you don't need a new
expensive mattress or sleeping pills.
You need to change your sheets.
Think about it. What's wrong with mine?
That's what your skin is touching.
These are a bowl and branch
means luxury linens and
you're not paying anything. And like what language does
that translate to luxury? Just
language of brand.
These are wonderful sheets.
Luxury sheets can cost $20,000
I bet, but
in a store. But bowl and branch are not
going to cost that. Not even close. They're like a
couple hundred bucks. They'll let you try them
risk free for 30 nights. And if you don't love them, you
can send them back for a full refund. That's
right. You have nothing to lose
and they come beautifully packaged
in signature boxes that make you feel like
a proper little fancy
person. Also, these sheets
can't be torn up.
They can't be burned. They're indestructible.
They are indestructible. They are the
golden fleece. They're
all made of golden fleece. So when you sleep
on them, every night that you sleep on them, your
life expectancy increases by one year.
Just to keep that bowl and branch
executive list of this from jumping out the window,
I should mention that no, these are not indestructible
sheets. They're just regular
levels of destructibility.
We have to say that.
They're not like more destructible.
Yeah, legally we have to say that, but
you guys know.
You all know what's up.
Bowl and branch is going to give you $50 off
your first set of sheets when you go to bowlandbranch.com
and use the promo code MYBROTHER. That's
$50 off your first set of sheets. Go to
bowl, B-O-L-L, and
branch.com. Promo code
MYBROTHER. They double your
proficiency as a lover. You can last
twice as long, go twice as hard.
Alright, you do yours now and I'm going to
throw shade at you the whole time. I'm not
throwing shade. I was a hype
man for this product. That's all we're doing here in the
money zone. I want to tell all y'all
about Wink. I know you're hearing that
thinking, who's this new customer?
I don't trust them. Yes, you do trust them
because it's Club W.
They've evolved. Somebody
used the
leaf stone on Club W
and they've evolved into Wink.
Amazing. Wink is
well, it's a lot like Club W.
They are going to help you
find the wine that is going to be
personalized to your palate. They're going to deliver
it right to your door.
It's called Wink now and that's spelled
W-I-N-C.
I know you hear that and you think
that's not the normal way
it's normally spelled. Well, no.
It's a new name. It's an improved look.
Here's the important part. Still the same
amazing wine company introducing you to
wines that you're going to love.
Fantastic.
Tell me more. I will.
Just calm down. I'm kind of flying by the seat of my pants
right now. Everything has changed.
My whole world has changed. Vine is gone.
I've got a second niece. I've got
two nieces now and you guys didn't even think about
how hard that's going to be for me to keep straight.
Now Club W is called Wink.
It's not spelled with a K. It's spelled with a C.
That's great. I just need
a minute. Okay? Okay.
Take your time. Wink.
They work directly with winemakers
and growers from all over the world to create delicious
wine and they deliver it right to your door.
They have 100% satisfaction
guarantee which means if you don't like a bottle they send you
they will replace it with a bottle that you're going to love
no questions asked. And that means
questions like but you drank the whole bottle
and you stuck a note inside that said yum yum
I sure love this.
We're not going to ask that question. We're not going to
ask you about that. We're just going to send you another bottle
no questions asked. Whoa.
The best part is that Wink is going to offer our
listeners 20 bucks off right now
if you go to Try Wink
that's Try with a Y
Wink with a C
dot com slash my
brother and they will even cover the shipping.
Think about that. You get free wine personalized to
your palate delivered right to your door. Try
Wink get 20 bucks off and
complimentary shipping right now when
you go to Try Wink dot com slash my
brother. That's Try W-I-N-C
dot com slash my brother.
I want to take a
moment to
mention to you
about a new podcast. It's called Driving Miss
Wiki. Driving
Miss Wiki is the name of this
podcast. It is recorded as the host
drives home
where the host's passenger
I wish we had more information
about that. I know. I want to actually
take the unprecedented step
of actually clicking research
to the website and researching.
Nope. It's taking too long.
I can't
figure it out.
Come on Justin. Hop on Nexus Lexus.
Let's crack this shit.
Driving Miss Wiki is the name of the podcast.
It is recorded on a drive
as a passenger reads to
the driver who is also the
host. A Wikipedia
article and they discuss them.
Past episodes
are not episodes. That's not a word.
Wow. You've had a lot of trouble reading this message.
This is actually your second attempt at it and you
fucked it up just as bad as the first.
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. I'm just saying it's noteworthy
how bad you're doing.
Is Travis the glue that holds this fucking
boat together? Has he been holding us together
this entire time? The show is called
Driving Miss Wiki. Let me tell you about it.
No God. No. Not again.
Some of the
topics they've discussed included the company
of Merchant Adventures, Marshall
Island Stick Charts, Prague, Texas
and Caruncles.
Those are of course
uncle cars.
Cars that are brothers
to other cars
that have sexually reproduced.
Your hosts are Parker
and Mary or Marie
perhaps. Let's go with Marie.
Yeah. So I found that out
through some research
and you can find their podcast at
drivingmisswiki.com or
by heading over to iTunes
and searching for Driving Miss
Wiki. I also want to
shout out this
message for Tuna
and it's from
Twin who says happy 30th
birthday to my PIC.
PIC.
Thank you for showing me the wonderful
world of podcasts especially
my bim bam. I can't wait to record
our competing comedy advice
podcast and put these clowns out of business for good?
You the best and I like you
a lot? How could you?
How could you do this? Did want
to get this one on
or around July 2nd
so
pretty good job I thought.
On that note first of all
fucking step up to the plate.
If you want to step into the terror
dome. If you think you're capable
go ahead because you
know what? Feed my
Frankenstein. I'm hungry. Yeah come
on. Come on. Step
up. Many have tried some have failed
bring it on.
Also want to say on the subject of us being
extremely late on Jumbotrons
there's been a freeze on
new Jumbotron messages
so if you wanted to get a message on the show you
haven't been able to for a while because all our spots
got done filled up. They're going
to open them. This feels like
weird to talk about that our listeners are so
like down and so supportive
that they have flooded us with
Jumbotron messages. If you want to get a message
on the show they're going to open up
spots in 2017
on November
28th. That's Cyber Monday.
They're going to open up. I
say they we don't actually sell
the Jumbotron spots. Max Fun handles that
for us and so they're going to open up some spots
in 2017. If you want to get a message on the show
November 28th Cyber Monday
those messages are going to
those slots are going to open up. So
if you want to get a message on the show next year
which is like your earliest option
go go hop on
maximumfun.org slash Jumbotron then
and good luck.
Good luck.
Anything else bro. Oh God they
just announced today
and obviously we knew about
this the the CISO show
that we did. My Brother My Brother and Me
TV show has a release date.
Yep February 23rd 2017
is when that's going to air
and I think I really think
you're going to like it a lot. Yeah we've been watching
some we've been watching some episodes and they're
they're they're good man. I'm really
really proud of it and happy about it.
We made them so we're biased.
I know but like I'm so I'm so
excited for everybody else to see them. I
really think this is going to be one of those situations
where I
I'm not embarrassed of a thing
that we made which is so rare
so rare.
So that's cool.
Anything else before we let people get back to it.
Not that I can think of.
Thank you all for sticking with us for this
best of episode.
I just like
sort of blanket like we have some
filler Eps prep for all the shows
so just expect
I guess a little bit of
what's the word I'm looking for.
It may not be. I don't know if disruption.
Yeah I don't know what like the next
it's because we expected these
babies much closer together.
So I don't know. We don't know exactly
how this is all going to
go but I think it's going to be
just fine. It's going to be just fine.
We are
again so excited for Travis and Theresa
and just expect like
especially once Rachel and I
have our baby in December
just like expect this podcast to just be
like three fucking Tim Allen's
three fucking Ray Romano's just laying
it down completely
inaccessible to all non dads
and they're doing all right.
You're not a dad. You're locked the fuck
out of this humor because it is all
all the way down baby
all that humor. So anyway
I stepped on another leg
go like shit that you
guys are not going to like at all
anymore. Like you're going to fucking
hate it. That jumbotron problem is going to
resolve itself. Yeah we're going to be done
with this show. Yeah it's going
to be guys it's gonna be
shit.
Anyway happy Halloween.
I'm Bez and I'm Theresa and we
host the weekly comedy podcast
One Bad Mother. We celebrate our moments
of parenting genius as well as
our failures. Just like
we're going to have hot dogs and I'm like
no we're having fun everybody loves hot dogs
and it just like smashes that thing right on my
chest and then I'm just crying in the middle of like
kids space while people are like literally dancing with their
children. Parenting can be sad and
painfully funny at the same time.
So join us each week as
we admit that this is hard but we're getting
really good at it. Find us at
maximumfun.org or wherever you download
podcasts.
It's two words alt
tab. Alt
tab. Now what does that mean. That's
shady though when you see when you
walk into somebody and you're like is
that a dick and then it
flickers really quickly. Whoa whoa whoa how personal
do you think this is going.
They're live streaming a bris.
I assumed it was like
I assumed it was like they were looking at bee dogs.
Travis no
one except you
looks at bee dogs. R has
ever looked at bee dogs. I think in
Colombia bee dogs is pretty big.
When you say bee dogs no
one knows what the fuck you're talking
about. I think you guys
will find that many people know
what I'm talking about. No one knows
what bee dogs are except you. I think
that bee dogs is a pretty big deal.
I want to see how much
I will tell you that no one knows
what bee dogs are.
I think you'll find
that bee dogs are pretty
popular. It's like listening to
Mariah Carey kibitz.
When you bring up bee dogs it makes
everybody sadder because they don't know what the fuck
you're saying. And it's
time for them to learn.
Hey guys I want to talk to you about
bee dogs. No, no, no. Fair enough.
You're not using our show as a
platform for spraying your madness.
What themed party can I
have for Halloween? I want to
attract lots of lovely ladies.
Oh behave.
Oh no. All right Griffin I'm
going to have to take this question away from you.
Okay. Can you
please paste the text into
our Skype window.
Okay you just typed fuck
you.
That is enough.
What themed party
can I have for Halloween?
I want to
attract lots of lovely ladies.
Oh behave.
That was miserable.
It sounded like Austin Powers had a stroke.
I did.
Oh behave.
Can I
say something? I think this person
has their heart set on a theme.
I think the
theme has been decided.
Guys I don't want to get outside of
the question but
is it possible that this person has just chosen
to live an Austin Powers lifestyle?
Oh here.
Can I share
the top answer?
Please. The top answer
from Yahoo Answers is
Rock Titan says
it's
April.
Oh he's the
pragmatist. Oh that's great.
This Yahoo
Answer is sent in by Diane.
Thanks Diane.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Jared
Ancharski
who asks
I got arrested for smoking weed
and my court date is soon.
If I come into court in a karate uniform
am I good?
Am I okay here?
In what context?
Will the judge make my punishment lenient since he knows
I do karate?
Exactly.
If he knows you've got your karate game right?
Additional details.
Since they know I do karate they'll know I do
other activities besides chill around
and smoke so will that help or no?
See this
it's like an onion this question.
Now this
only works if you do a fashion
show. So you come in your karate outfit
and then you come in your horse riding outfit.
This is a hard hat.
I do construction things.
And also I'm a milkman apparently.
Someone give me a hammer.
Boy was I ever lucky to get
Judge Samo Hung.
He's been very lenient
about my gi.
Samo Hung
was one of the karate guys
on Walker Texas Ranger.
Go on.
One of the karate guys on Walker Texas Ranger.
I could have gone for Chuck Norris but I feel like
his
I think the thing
Chuck Norris is a hanging judge.
Everyone knows that.
Is there anything this gentleman
can wear other
than a suit
that he says I heart judges.
OK but that's
that's probably not going to do it because I think
I don't think you can wear any shirt that says I
heart anything on it and then I heart judges
a lot. People don't what about a sarcastic
maybe a Judge Reinhold
mask.
Hey listen judge to judge
are we cool. Am I good.
I've got this Judge
Reinhold mask and a karate gi.
Are we going to waive these charges
or what. Can we can we work that
into our catchphrase vernacular.
Am I good.
Anytime you say
something terrible or faux pas
just real quick. Oh shit. Am I good.
Am I good.
Hey I came to court in a karate gi.
So I'm just going to go. I assume
the charges have been dropped. Uh huh. Am I good.
I just
I just chopped your gavel in half.
Am I good.
What's that smell.
It's not weed. I promise.
To what extent
does the color of
belt that this person has
all the difference in the world.
OK.
I mean either way you chop it
if he's got a white belt
he's not going to a intimidate the judge or
be impress him with
the amount of time that he has spent in karate
chopping class. You can get the
white belt blue belt brown
belt yellow belt all within
like a week and a half if
you pay and if you slip a few you know extra
hundo's to your sensei.
From what I've seen
there if you were to graph my
respect for people in
the martial arts it's a pretty
steady curve up until you hit
black belt and then it
branches pretty radically
in two different directions where
on the one hand I am
for some of those people
I am like wow really
odd by the dedication to your
craft and then the other people
it's like just
put on just get a job
put on a suit and
learn how to play lacrosse and
please get your life together.
It just strikes me as one of those things that in my life if someone
were to say to me oh yeah I have a black belt
the next two words out of my
mouth are prove it.
I don't know
what that entails I don't know if that's like
chop through this wall or fight me
or what it is but there's something about someone
making that statement where I'm like
oh yeah prove it.
Chop that horse in half.
A black belt is really only
a value add to a person
when nobody knows
that they have it.
If I got a black belt I wouldn't tell
fucking I would go take my classes
in another state.
So that people would. What classes?
Oh karate classes. Karate classes.
And then when I came
back and like if shit came down
and I did a chop and a kick
and a man died then people would be like what?
I'd be like oh don't worry about it.
I would never ever admit the fact that I have a black.
Spray your jacket to the side and show them just a
little glimpse of black belt. Because if
I ever said the word out loud to somebody oh I have
a black belt they're gonna make all kinds of wild
assumptions about me. Right.
Which are probably all going to be true. They're going to be
very true. But I would rather
not be subject to that.
Do you think that when you get the black belt itself
it's reversible?
In case you want to wear brown shoes?
Idiot.
So this is why. This is your
outfit okay. You come into court.
You're wearing black dress shoes
a black belt and you have a tie.
You go to the judge and you say
am I good?
As you can see
I'm in my formal gi.
Am I good?
This is my dress gi. Am I good?
I have a funeral to go to.
I'm gonna karate chop the
coffin in half.
I can't believe you'd hold a karate master
here.
You don't know the lightning you're bottling
up here. You can't put
me in a cell. I will not be responsible
for the damage I do
if you lock me in a cell with another person.
I'll whittle their bones down
and make a ki. I can't be
responsible. I don't know that karate
is the kind of thing that you can do if you're high
on that sweet sweet dojo.
If you're rocking dojo
I don't think that
your skills are going to be as
high as you want them to be.
No
Three puns intended.
Yes and no.
To the outside observer
you will be very bad at karate.
To your own perception
you will be on a fucking
kung fu other plane kill
bill style.
Body parallel flat to the ground.
You against the crazy 88's
just losing your mind, chopping off
limbs. Mortal Kombat
fly through the air bicycle kick.
You're just laying on the ground
and rolling about. You're
listening to 311 and you're eating Starburst.
I got a
FTP login you can check
out. You're gonna love
my files and folders.
Don't go too many trees deep
cause it gets weird.
Stay in the index.
Let's just say stay in the index.
If you find yourself four or five folders in
just unplug your
computer. Just pull this string and I'll get you
out.
You need Joseph Gordon Levitt to give
you the kick.
Unless you don't like horse assholes.
Get Joseph Gordon Levitt to give you
the kick.
This yahoo was sent in by
Liana which was
sent to her by her friend Keith.
So thank you both people
in this arrangement.
Many
boffins died to bring us this yahoo
so let's really enjoy it.
It was asked by yahoo answers user
Geof who asks
is it okay to draw on a dog
with magic marker?
Sometimes when my
stepdad Ron grounds me I'll write
messages on
my dog. He is white with
washable marker and send him downstairs.
Just little messages like
if I need food or about how much I
hate my stepdad Ron.
My mom
said it would make the dog sick. Is she right?
So many
more problems with the best stepdad
name ever is Ron.
Got some dog mail for you Ron.
Fuck off.
I hate you Ron.
I hate you so much. Come here Mr.
Perkins. What's it?
Aw man.
That really helps. That hurts myself as
I'm trying so hard. That hurts my Ron
esteem. I don't like that one bit.
Can you give me the
question one more time Griffin? Is it
okay to draw on a dog with magic marker?
Sometimes when my stepdad Ron grounds me
I'll write messages on my dog.
He is white
with magic marker. Just little messages
like if I need food or about how
much I hate my stepdad Ron.
I'm imagining like a Yorkshire terrier
like bounding down the stairs running up
to Ron and it's like a message on him
like hey Ron I smell that chili. What the
fuck? You're such a bastard. I'm super
hungry. I got a message for you
Ron. I'm a dog.
And also the person asking this question
is 32. Yeah.
God damn you Ron.
Now listen to me Sparky. I want you to go
upstairs. I want you to find Ron.
I want you to just wiggle in front of him.
You gotta make sure he reads this. It's important.
I've been trapped under this bookcase
for two weeks. I gotta get some
pasta up here. I'm so hungry. Also tell
Ron fuck you Ron.
If Ron wants to rescue
me tell him to fuck clean off. I hate
Ron. Tell him to send my mom
and ask if my mom is back
with my fruit roll ups yet.
I sent her to the store
20 minutes ago for fruit roll ups.
Mr. Perkins you look kind of sick.
What happened?
Is it the markers?
Is it your skin? It's you or me
Mr. Perkins.
Maybe you learned how to talk English.
Stupid dog.
Poor Ron.
What a fucking
sick bird. He's just trying to watch Extreme Home Makeover
and all of a sudden the dog
trots in front of the screen. It looks like a drawing of a knife
stabbed and an arrow
that says Ron. This is you Ron.
This is what I want to do to you. Look at the dog.
Oh Jesus.
It says I love you Ron. I'm my dog.
Oh he rolled over. It says no I don't.
And it says fuck you Ron again on it.
With an arrow towards the dog's penis.
Tyler I thought
you were going to come pick me up from work.
Did you not read the dog?
I said fuck you and fuck your job.
I'm not coming to pick you up.
And also that we were out of eggs.
Did you tell mom?
I wrote it on the dog Ron.
What else do you want me to do?
I can't force
the dog to stand in front of you all day.
Please just read the dog.
You used all the paper for your stupid
novel Ron.
How's that going Ron? Did you find a
publisher yet?
In this economy Ron you might as well
self publish your stupid shit.
Put it on Kindle.
I've got a Tumblr dog.
Where I just put messages. Why can't you get a Tumblr dog?
Can we
make it a new law?
Sort of like in Game of Thrones
if you're a bastard your name is Snow.
Can we make it that the second you become
a stepdad your name just becomes
Ron by law?
Legally speaking
I now pronounce you wife and
Ron.
It's not even your name so much as
like Earl.
It's like an honorary title but his name is not Earl.
You're officially like the Don
of this house.
You're the Ron.
You're the Ron Don.
So let's see.
You've got to get WednesdayWolf.com
the imps.org
mobrulesgames.com
and indiegogo.com
Actually Mob Rules Games
I already busted one out for them.
I will give them a final draft of that
come the end of this promotion.
Don't take this the wrong way.
The imps and WednesdayWolf.
I like the idea of Daymere pile of
watercolor donors.
Start there.
What does that cover?
That covers WednesdayWolf
and the imp.
It covers all three?
They all want money.
That's the connector. Everybody wants money.
Here we go.
Hold on.
Let me take a try.
Build a Daymere
pile of
watercolor donors.
All these businesses need funds
to operate.
You can help WednesdayWolf
the imps don't
take the wrong way.
That's almost what it's called.
But I ran out of words in the verse.
Go give them some cash
to chase all of their
dreams around.
I like how it ended on some of that unresolved
dreams of
dreams.
I don't know guys.
Build a Daymere
pile of
watercolor donors.
You need to give
these people lots of cash.
That's how the market works.
They take your money and turn
it into goods and services.
You can take those services
to the bank.
While they take your
literal money to the bank.
Visit
WednesdayWolf.com
the imps.org and don't take this the
wrong way's website which you can probably find
on google.
Fuck.
Make sure to join us at
McGillicuddy's deck for
party on McGillicuddy's deck.
To the sequel.
Party your deck off at
McGillicuddy's.
Get your deck wet.
Come get your deck wet with $2
washer splashes all night long.
The hottest
babes. The hottest guys.
The drunkest children.
The wildest monkeys.
The craziest poop throwing monkeys
you've ever seen. And good
news ladies. Margaritas
are just $3 all night long.
Monkeys get in free till
midnight.
Hey monkey it's 1230.
Come on in anyway.
It's McGillicuddy.
21 and up for male monkeys.
18 for female monkeys.
I don't even know if monkeys live that long.
What the fuck.
Half man half monkeys will be submitted
for study at
research institutes nationwide.
So
summer's here. Summer's here
again. Do you guys wanna
yahoo answer? Yes.
Yeah. This one was sent in by Josh
Papow. I haven't
decided if it's the kind of question
that we could get
in trouble for reading yet.
Okay. Yay.
Thank you Josh. So yahoo
answers to your question Mark who asked
really freaked out my girlfriend. Need help?
As a teenager I suffered
from severe depression
and formed a strong bond with the character
Garfield and his outlook.
It's sad but
reading
Garfield anthologies obsessively was
the only thing that made me feel normal.
And it eventually took on something
of an erotic fixation.
Oh no.
And I think you mispronounced
normal.
Reading Garfield books obsessively made me
feel normal.
To avoid feeling like a sicko
I drew pictures of Garfield with
a woman's I think a Pamela Anderson
circa 1991 body
and Garfield's head.
These drawings eventually evolved into
erotic fan fiction starring Garfield and myself.
In my head Garfield still
has a woman's body but someone
reading the stories would think I'm having sex
with regular Garfield. I killed
off John in a jealous rage.
I didn't touch Odie. I enjoy his
companionship and don't mind if he watches.
What the fuck?
The stories are your pretty basic wish
fulfillment stuff balanced with a
self loathing rants.
Yeah pretty basic stuff.
Nothing out of the ordinary here.
I've been doing this near daily for years
and I have a substantial amount of writing in a folder
I keep buried in eight different folders.
My girlfriend stumbled
across them by accident when they came
up in a search and is pretty freaked out.
How can I show her I'm just a
normal guy with a weird outlet
from my psychological problems and not
some kind of sicko. And then they
included a sample of some of the erotic fiction
and I didn't think I would ever
say this on this podcast but it's too
gross to read out loud.
Guys I know different
strokes for different folks.
We've all got something
buried deep inside that you
never ever ever want
anybody to know ever. Now I'm not
saying mine would be as weird
as putting a woman's body
on Garfield's head but it's
pretty fucking weird. The secret
to not getting made fun of
is that you can't tell the entire
world which is on the
internet. This is a secret
you can never. You're embarrassed your
girlfriend found out so you decided to put it on
the internet? How bad are you at
internet? You can't hide a yahoo
answer in folders.
No. Cause I found it.
I found it and I know it forever now.
Yeah. I'm just
if Jim Davis ever saw these drawings
I think he would literally fucking die.
I think he would fucking die. I think his
heart would explode in his chest and he would die.
He would say my baby! And then he'd die.
Hey real quick. Just for a second.
Let's play devil's advocate
here and just like get ourselves in
this guy's head space and just like imagine.
No I'm not. I don't want to do that at all.
Come through the door.
We're gonna step into this
guy's mind. What if I die
in this dream? If you die in the dream you'll be
stuck in Garfield fucking limbo
forever. You need Joseph Gordon
Leavitt to give you the kick. Yeah yeah.
He'll kick you in the head until you die.
Give me the kick. I'm ready.
Which
would you
come on
which would you prefer?
Pamela Anderson body and Garfield
head or Garfield body and Pamela Anderson head?
If you had to
party down on one of those bad
boys
which would you go with?
Additional information. The Garfield head is wearing
sunglasses.
Garfield
body suction cup hands or no suction
cup hands?
Either or.
Whichever would be more
pleasurable. Is Odie there
and is he just jerking it so
right? Odie loves what he sees.
Either way
Odie's down.
Odie is down to clown.
Justin do you want to pick first?
Well Griffin
you ask the questions so you have to answer.
Fuck.
I'll say
if it's Bill Murray's voice
Pam body
Garfield head. Travis?
Oh no I've already killed myself
in this situation.
Can I
throw Travis's body at the corpse
and buy myself enough time
Travis's corpse at the
creation and buy myself enough time
Here's the problem though. You throw it at Pam body
Garf head. Who's that coming up from behind?
It's Garf body Pam head
and it is
very upset.
For many reasons. You have
in your inventory a dagger
and a shield.
Open doors are
west and north.
Okay can I
I am going to go
with Pam head
Garfield body but Lorenzo
music voice.
I have a thing
with the real Ghostbusters so
I think that would be enough to get me through it
and also
You're worried about finishing?
I can't
You also changed Pam Anderson's
voice to Garfield's.
Now listen if I have
I have too much respect for Bill Murray's
work. If it's Lorenzo music
But you could have left Pamela Anderson's voice
Why does it have to be Garfield's voice?
I don't see why Pam Anderson's voice is not going to come out of
Garfield's head.
And I
find Larry the crash test dummy
to be a very soothing sexual influence
So if I can pretend
that if it's Lorenzo music's voice
and I can pretend it's Peter
Venkman of the Ghostbusters cartoon
or Larry the crash test dummy
or perhaps even tummy gummy from
Disney's Avengers gummy bears
How many other cartoons can you ruin for me right now?
I can't
That's all Lorenzo music that I'm aware of
He's probably something else
That thought didn't even
The thought of what would be the most
sexually pleasurable
That didn't even cross my mind. This was pure
survival instincts
I've got all of these pizza shaped disks
left over from my Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
sewer boat
Just the disks. I got rid of the boat
but I've probably got 150 of them
Right. Different years
If you come over to Travis's house
he's coming to the pizza disk room
and he's showing you
the ones with small factory imperfections
and that kind of thing
Basically all I did was just stable them to the wall
directly. There's no
furniture in the room. There's a body
but I don't ask about it
There are five
people right now who just threw
down their iPod and ran into their
attic like, where's my fucking pizza launcher?
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Dad! You promised
You said that
if I kept up my GPA that you wouldn't
throw away my pizza launcher
What do you mean I'm 32?
What do you mean you died 7 years ago?
Dad! How long have I been asleep?
Dad!
I think that old man was a genie
I think I got a genie curse
Dad!
I don't know what you want
He says he's governor
What's going on?
I used to be Zac Efron and now I'm Steve Buscemi
Help me!
Dad!
I've got adult
balls and no pizza launcher
What gives?
Dad!
I wanted my suit to fit over the counter
What's going on?
They said I couldn't
at the store
Is that a
problem you would like to?
I can't find
Jost on the shelves!
Dad!
I've been without electricity
for a week
and while I was without
electricity I started reading books
Oh, I see
Okay, so this is books, man
This is educated
Justin
This is your brain on books
This is what they do
So in your mind this is what educated people sound like?
I
in circles
I am in electoral circles
This is what my friends
and I, this is how we speak
Justin, I want you to know
I picture you right now surrounded by bookcases
but your brain has swollen and you just have like a giant
forehead
Tell me
I have become top heavy
but without electricity I was not able
to watch my programs
I was not able to play video games
and I was forced
to read and now I've been exposed
to all the great culture
of the world
How
How sallow is
your skin? Can you give me some sort of
salowness rating?
It looks like an orange fruit
by the bottom
Did you get
a book jaundice? What happened?
No, he was just reading books and eating
carrots the entire time
As they ran out of power they had to eat their
stock of baby carrots
I was forced
to eat the butterflies I've
preserved over the years behind
glass
Nutritionally devoid
but
surprisingly very pleasing
to the palate
Yeah
All that voice wants to do is eat something
beautiful
So this is our advice program
My brother, my brother and me
will dole out
intellectual
conversational
advice
You're hearing like hard right, what is this voice
doing? I think he's just
turning into a condor also
It's
bucking underneath me
Bucking wildly
It wants desperately to go scar's guard
I won't
let it. I'm holding on to the reins
as sadly as I can
Oh god it's devolved
into Ed Grimley. Somebody help me
This final
yahoo was sent in by Earl Parsons
Thank you Earl. It's by yahoo answers user
Sky who asks
If I die
Is there yahoo answers in heaven?
Oh shit I'm Justin McElroy. I'm Travis McElroy
I'm Griffin McElroy
This has been my brother, my brother and me. Kiss your dad
Square on the lips
Keep your heart
Three stacks
Hey keep your heart
Keep your heart
Man these girls smart
Three stacks these girls smart
Play your part
Do you live in the fictional city of Chicago?
Do you love amazing
podcasts like Max Fund's own
Lady to Lady, Minority Corner
and Bullseye?
Do you enjoy insightful interviews with talented
actors and comedians like
Duane Kennedy and Andre Royo?
Don't miss your chance to be part of podcast
history by attending the first
ever Chicago podcast festival
Lady to Lady and Bullseye
take the stage on November 17th
and Minority Corner performs on November
18th. Tickets are on sale
right now. Visit Maximum Fund
dot org for more information
and to grab your ticket today
right now.