Hey, you've already been out here, you've already experienced this crowd.
I'm very comfortable with the energy of this room.
That's why I switched into my Tybee Island shirt.
It's island time.
Yeah.
So that's that's code for I can say fuck now.
I feel like this is the this is not only the nicest building we've ever performed in.
This is the nicest building I've ever been in.
And I'm I'm like 80% sure that's the first time anybody's ever said a curse word in this building.
Yeah, not the last.
No, most certainly not the last.
Uh, this is my brother.
My brother and me in an advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle brother, Travis McElroy.
And I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
Yeah, just once.
I want that to be met with silence.
Yeah.
Can we get ask you a favor?
Yeah, sure.
Can you just scoot?
Yeah, can we get more monitor?
We're literally so far away from each other.
This gigantic, beautiful stage.
I'll save you.
I know this looks weird.
Like, why are those three guys in the picture you took?
Why are they so close to each other?
They have the whole stage to their auras have to blend doesn't do that fleet with Mac.
Can we can we start the podcast off by just detailing just how many times we've just completely
fucked up being in Canada, just like from literally the word like I made you guys promise
this wouldn't turn into like the can you believe it's different like the Canada, the Canada
the Canada chapter of the big john's bathroom reader but like holy shit we have screwed
up literally everything can see the best example I can give is when we crossed the border and
everyone in the car was amazed that suddenly things were different right it was like holy
shit I can go 100 miles an hour yes Canada rules that we saw a gas station and Travis
was like it's 119 that's crazy and Justin was like no that's not even the good part
Justin said well yeah they would have no reason to use gallons it's pints what and everyone
in the car was like oh yeah yeah it sounds about right yeah in my defense the guy at
Hertz told me that got you we had uh we have a theme on our program sort of a recurring
gag that uh we don't know how to find marijuana anymore and we made it something of a tactical
error in performing shows in places where it is cool as a cucumber and as easy to get
as cucumbers are yeah to just buy it so uh we we met some folks last night and one of
the gifts that we received a couple of times was jazz cigarettes yes yes was weed now this
is very exciting to us hooray because we're not cool very cool it was very cool the only
thing was we realized we're crossing the Canadian border that is not cool and pre pre-tension
set in like this is the idea of like tomorrow this will be a problem yeah so we needed to
smoke all of this tonight we didn't we didn't we got we tried we got close got sleepy but
here's the thing right we were so like i wanted you don't say we it was you you were no leading
up to the event we were all very worried about border crossing like they would peel back
one of like the floor mats and just find a weed yeah that we had forgotten about and
then we would go to like guantanamo bay this paranoia didn't just extend to marijuana and
marijuana-based products uh i didn't we have little meat sticks for our baby that i threw
away because i know you couldn't bring meat that's the level of like by the way you guys
are missing out on so america is we had to get out of there because it was getting pretty
real uh but we do meet pretty good and i can't believe y'all don't get to to sample that but
i was so worried about like i had all my paperwork when we get to this border and i
i am now using that term loosely dude at the border travis gets out it says there's seven
of us and he hands them the three passports that he had and he said uh only got three here
and travis reaches back and hands him the rest of our passports and then he looks at our passports
and then we drive through so he did not corroborate the alcohol in there and i was like i don't think
so no no no it went like this do you have any tobacco or alcohol um no
that did not warrant a check the fact that one of my passports is for a baby the dude did not
even look in like is that a baby so when he was like turn off the engine and step out of the car
we just like jessica everybody out which which which do you want us to go to american jail or
canadian jail please god put me in the direction of the nearest jail could not have been less
interested did not like we couldn't like i i imagine travis like leaning back the man needs
four more passports dig dig out four more from our box give me american passports give me four
four more a little bit of accent work from our box of passports uh also we were streaming carly
ray jeffson's new album emotion on the drive-in no no listen listen no listen no listen no listen
is yes great out of i agree best out of national treasure national treasure carly jeffson oh yeah
y'all would definitely be into her anyway streamed it i got a text message from my old buddy at&t
like hey bud um uh you've charged like a hundred dollars of roaming fees because you forgot to buy
an international plan uh was it worth it and my answer is yes of course emotion is the greatest
album possibly of all time let's let's do some anybody uh let's listen for the first time not
listen to our show before and they're just kind of here on a whim should i raise your hands okay i
want to i'm trying to make better you know we don't do i realized this while i was explaining
fucking anything and then we just talked about carly ray jeffson for 30 minutes like y'all cool
like i don't we don't do a lot of like looking at you you know what i mean like yeah now i'm
looking at you you know how many people here um didn't have power when they left their house
fuck i will be your power let us be your power you'll be warm with us you're safe here you won't
be you may not have power but you'll be erotically charged that's my guarantee that's the justin
mcgroy guarantee anyway it's an advice show as you've almost certainly surmised and uh let's
get into it my boyfriend and i found over here what's up dog pound dog pound nice y'all in the
middle are cool too my boyfriend and i are moving in together today and i have serious concerns
about our breakfast out situation in the future his usual mo is to order the biggest most average
breakfast they have on the menu that is the travis mcgroy special and not like a huge burrito
or omelet or whatever but just the item that boasts the largest amount of eggs bacon hash browns
and toasts how do i explain to my boyfriend now that we've moved to the big city he should branch
out into other delicious breakfast options that's from very excited in vancouver very excited are
you here you're here oh that was the saddest uh egg man are you here no he is here can you just
raise your hand it's kind of a you don't want to put your egg your egg boyfriend okay egg man can
i tell you you're right and she's wrong oh there you know what's really hard to fuck up eggs bacon
and toast yeah really hard to mess that up you know it's really easy to mess up great burrito
yeah eggs bacon and toast yeah listen but crepes are great listen that's true but like breakfast
is like one of the most utilitarian meals of the day right it exists i mean don't get me wrong it
can be delicious i've had great ones miss ower over here somewhere i know breakfast can't be
awesome but mostly it exists so that you're not cranky by 11 a.m yeah right you could say that
about all meals though if you think about it that's true griffin my the reason i celebrate
eggs bacon and toast is that is as a tactical choice if you don't necessarily know what the
day shall hold it is the best tactical breakfast option you can make there are many times you will
look who in this room and i do want to see a show of hands on this one who in this room has looked
at a breakfast or brunch menu and seen the french toast and thought fuck i'd like to eat some french
toast but then realized that the rest of your day is about that fucking french toast as soon as you
consume it's like well catch you guys at three and have you ever seen someone finish a breakfast
burrito like finish it not like they the kitchen slices it in half to say and this is the garbage
job they everybody at the table gets excited when somebody else gets the french toast because
there's like i know they're gonna have some bites left at the end it's gonna get into breakfast is
crazy i mean if it makes you happy then i think go for it i think this is this reminds me of the
question we got out of the guy that only ordered chicken nuggets at restaurants and it's like
fucking stand in your truth and chase your bliss that that is true there's not like a forum where
he orders eggs bacon and toast and the other restaurants were like steven again again like
they don't know the waiter doesn't know so oh this is it tell him to do it like this every time go
you know what i think i'll try the eggs bacon and toast tell me what tell me about the tell me about
these um is it edged oh but con continental interesting how wonderful do you guys want to
yahoo uh yeah uh about 14 people sent this question and i don't know if they were good
there was some collusion going on uh it's by yahoo answers user janine who asks someone just went oh
janine janine asks what would happen if i hugged and kissed kissed the grinch dude
y'all interrupted me hey do you guys have the grinch over here
we should have made sure that before uh what would happen if i hugged and kissed kissed the grinch
do not delete please i'm a girl and i simply love the grinch how would he react if i hugged and
kissed him do not delete please is this uh pre or post uh the song the who's singing the song and
he's like our love what song are you talking they do they sing the one that's like
wahoo okay hold on i misunderstood you are talking about the grinch not like is this
grinch post transformation or pre-transformation not was this question submitted before the grinch
was released because yahoo answers was just a twinkle in mr jefferson yahoo's eye back in 19
whatever whatever no i mean are you talking about like i really like the bad boy i can change him
grinch or do you like that he even carved the roast beast grinch you're you're saying it's like
she wants the bad boy does she want that bad boy grinch all ladies love the bad boy grinch am i
right fellas yeah am i that's good guy grinch is just getting friend zoned
i just carved the roast beast and all i get is a handshake
oh i cannot believe she's had this much of a problem with this question being deleted yeah
so i look at the related questions and the top three nope scratch at five are what would happen
if i hugged and kissed the grinch so this person has been on uh the warpath and some yahoo moderators
like not again no how many times no i think we've just discovered is that mrs grinch is a yahoo
moderator there there is a mrs grinch and she is very active on yahoo not my husband no way kiss
kiss of my man how dare you he's my husband i love him his heart's too big there's only room for one
in here i'm a big lady well there could be room for three if there was room for one before no
well griffin uh sorry but that would argue that there was room for one in his heart before it grew
three sizes and i think we all know that there was not before he did not feel love in the way
that we do i'll be back with you guys in a second because he had max who loved him sure and he did
not care for max he was very no debate there but then his heart grew for sure and he gave some
roses to him so now his heart is barely big enough for a small definitely definitely i have more in
my published work backstage my roommate carelessly ate my last can of soup when i texted him about
it he replied with an honest apology and explained that he buys the same kind of soup
you may thought it was his fair enough i typed the following message in my phone no worries
however as i hit send he sent a second message saying that he would replace my soup for me
my no worries ended up being sent before i received his second message but it showed up
in our conversation is happening after so it looks like i said no worries to the idea of him replacing
my soup oh man it's the third time i've read this fucking question okay is there any way i
can express them that i still desperately want that can of soup without it sounding like i'm
reneging or is the order of operations etched in stone that's from souples in canada's seattle
this question is a fucking high stakes thrill ride are you here are you here souples yeah i
just have a quick question i can't hear you so just like raise your hand you said no worries
has there been a response from him since then they haven't they haven't spoken great you are
in the clear you just need to now post well some worries i love okay you need to understand in the
mo if you had called us when this happened in the moment within the first 10 minutes there is
something that we could have done but you've come to us so late i cannot imagine a reality where
you're like upon further reflection this is why we put the emergency hotline number out there
right which is 911 oh fuck is it different here that's not a joke what's your what's your guys
not one one tight no can i tell you something good to know jic good to know those numbers still work
here did you guys know that they have green flashing traffic lights here i've driven through
dozens of them i've stopped at half of them because i don't fucking know
everyone's laughing and clapping like i got it wrong so now i know what's wrong
will you just go then why is it flashing what is that to indicate
it's pedestrian control so they see those green flashing lights are like
no he's coming the pedestrian no the monster he's a pedestrian that's how they signal
get the fuck off the streets the pedestrian eaters coming what was the question something
something something soup soup wait wait wait follow up quick follow up what kind of soup
whoa game done changed this ain't no broth that's not a soup that's a meal
oh i didn't realize it's a hearty question oh my my my the plot and the soup
you're going to have to take his soup well when he least expects it when he's while he's eating it
no he has to turn like oh i forgot to get my wine and then the soup's gone he's sorry he's having
a little wine and soup the homemade soup dish homemade wine can you engineer a trip to the
grocery store and then when you pass the soup you're like uh why don't i have you here i just
wanted to uh circle back i feel like there's this wait there's a wait what
can you run up to the mic real quick because we're not gonna be able to hear you just yeah
oh shit no you're up there no they're stairs oh okay leap this is how law should have ended
yo yo yo what's your name okay so um since i sent that email uh i ran into him at a friend's house
and he said hey uh when you get back home i've replaced your soup for you and i was like great
awesome thanks that's a good dude got home on the kitchen table was a can of chili
that was on sale
flag on the play
so he got you broke ass not soup
soup hey i replaced that soup for you you get home
i got you uh i got you a chair no it's
desperately not i thought you were going to say you got home and there was just a bowl
of soup sitting on the counter there you live this person yes still yes
yes griffin has some advice that he used to give people a lot he doesn't you know it doesn't work
here because imp you the advice is just pack your bags and move away but but but but but
this motherfucker stole your soup you can't pack it up yeah if you move away now you're just gonna
have a line of roommates out the doorway to steal your fucking soup the words out there soft this
is what you need to do you need to swallow this down you can't swallow down the soup is gone
and you need to forget about it until the opportunity arises and then you are going to ruin
his life oh shit maybe it's 10 years from now maybe like he brings like he's went on a date
and went well and he was like i've got some soup back at the house and they come back and like his
day just you're gonna steal the deal i'm gonna steal it here with a little campbell's chunky and
then he gets back what's that there's just the note you open it up and it says i took your soup
enjoy your cold empty life good luck having sex without soup can't be done
that's that's that's love line every episode you got soup
oh you're good to go uh thanks for your soup thank you thank you superman
here's a yahoo here's the yahoo cinema jacob locker thank you jacob coming out of retirement
jacob locker it's by yahoo answers user tim who asks how to kill time in a cheap and sleazy motel
i'll be stuck in a sleazy motel for about 30 to 45 days
it sucks yeah you know what now that i think about that's a long stay yeah it's a long
and also a very vague time for 30 to 45 days yeah that could be 50 percent longer
you never know how long it's gonna take for the police to stop looking for you
you they're an unpredictable bunch cops it sucks it's noisy almost all the time and the
guests are creepy and grim looking no en suite bathroom bed bugs yes
yes bed bugs almost certainly yeah uh i can't afford other options right now suggestions
30 to 45 days gotta kill time the first time griffin read this question i thought he was
saying like on the matter of a suite bathroom the answer is no on bedrooms no no bed bugs wait so
bed bugs yeah yes we can he shares a bathroom yeah yep he's got his own bed bugs yes
the other guests i don't know why he puts that in close are grim looking ghosts
he might be in purgatory yeah sure yeah everything about this question leads to but you've always
been here right or he's in the movie identity uh can you spend the 30 to 45 days digging a tunnel
into the bathroom because that fucking sucks that it's not connected to the place where you sleep
or maybe just reno the place flip that hotel yeah yeah 30 to 45 days you could get a lot
done a lot out of that oh you're coming to stay at our hotel you're gonna want to be in 10
yeah trust me there's a zen garden in there yeah they have a koi pond uh marble cabinets
some built-in bookshelves it's real marble countertops let's turn this into our cabinets
are not a thing my little cabinets is the height of a luxury i'm very disappointed the two of you
that i have to call myself on marble cabinets that's in a morgue but not anywhere else you know
what you can start a morgue business you start a more big here's another thing you got 30 to 45
days time to bring back the concept of a hotel detective we got a lot of young people here
happened at the motel six but this guy in room four is coming for the crime and he's
monk from that show monk he's in the new show tony shalhoub has seen better days tony shalhoub and
monk too the sequel to monk he's in a hotel room there used to be a literal job that existed as a
hotel detective where you just were on call if people lost their keys yeah or like needed to
follow somebody i guess there also used to be a show called monk and a show called rescue rangers
and both of those are pertinent suggestions you must understand all these things or nothing else
will make sense all the best jokes require 30 to 45 seconds of backstory just a footnote at the
bottom hey true believers this is the reference read another question just i'm feeling like this
is going to be a real club banger my husband steve and i got married at the end of july and
of the wedding day i posted one picture on instagram i don't have facebook i get it okay
and i do and i'm the bad guy i get it anyway i know how i know and i don't have tv i know i get
it no it's fine i don't blame you i know how annoyed some people get about having too many
pictures of the same thing on instagram so i didn't want to post more than that of your wedding
now that we're about to get our professional pictures back for the photographer would it
be okay if i posted one or two more selected photos that's from jacklyn fearful of flooding
the feed in the frozen north jacklyn jacklyn you hear jacklyn jacklyn i heard two different
ones come from different points of the audience can i you're the nicest person on the internet
uh in fact that you're you're bad news actually it's not flattering uh you're too nice for the
internet i'm gonna need to revoke your internet card for your own good jacklyn get off the
internet you're soft do you know i can't handle it out here there's a lot of i'm sorry if you've
never heard this word shit on the internet and it can get really bad it's rough out there i'm
gonna need you to stop internet you just can't internet anymore because that's a sad that's
a sad truth is yes there are indeed people out there who'll be like pictures of your own wedding
again that's the third one i've seen in 10 minutes fuck your wedding can you okay wait i i have a
i have an idea can you photoshop your wedding photos to make them possibly about something else
maybe you have like chili dog tuesdays and it's like but you're it's also a wedding photo but
like just secretly about your wedding but mainly about uh making a throwback thursday i hear those
are popular did you serve hold on this is important did you serve chili dogs at your
wedding what are you talking about it could be the equivalent of chili dogs could be regular dogs
that's okay uh you serve poutine don't buy into the stereotype jacqueline yeah
i wanted i side note i'm very excited to try poutine why i am here yeah i'm so sad i gotta
leave i gotta leave early and i'm meant to eat poutine and do you have any early morning poutine
dispensaries anyone have some in their pockets or their their poutine vest do you have some
blue jean what the fuck do you are you fucking kidding me this motherfucker has fret no fretro
shitter open it up verify evan has brought us some poutine hold up no cancel the podcast wait
shut up evan who's the depression four oh perfect that's the perfect travis uh what do you have in
front of you i want to clear okay so what i've got is a bag of ruffles they have ridges put an
asterisk next to the episode title the happiest griffin's ever been followed by the most they are
a poutine flavored ruffles my favorite thing about this bag is down here in the bottom corner where
it says simulated flavor we want to be straight with y'all this ain't real poutine we had a great
gift it's a great gift this is oh good it's our snack demo segment that we do on every episode
the reason i got so excited is the thought of somebody having just loose gravy on them at a
comedy show you want me to good delicious i'm not gonna those two will bullshit you i won't
bullshit you i'm the the real flavor scale sorry everybody i can't do it it's not very good i don't
like it i really do it i weigh into it you just don't have a refined palette like me and scraps
i do you have another yahoo uh yeah we got it you tasteless bastard
give me another one of those bad boys yeah dig into it great cool audio gently um this super
crunchy installment of the yahoo segment was sent in by jacob locker again thank you jacob
it's by whoo it's by an anonymous yahoo are you guys dialed in or what oh yeah for sure for sure
for sure for sure it's by an anonymous user no name will calm evan asks you did evan asks
how come some ghosts are cool and some are jerks
i've been in a number of places where the vibe was weird and people always got negative from
being around it then sometimes i'm in places and it's really positive and again it feels
weird but it's supportive while in the negative experience you hear and see weird stuff you get
to sleep faster in positive ones but how come some buildings presence can be negative while
others positive so they walk through the positive one and they're like whoa whoa something i should
take up stand-up comedy yeah that's probably why most people take up like stand-up comedy
go go i felt a cold spot and also i love you too yeah why okay it is hugely upsetting to
me the idea that i don't care if the ghost is positive or negative they said you get to sleep
faster yeah i do not need to go to sleep with the idea of a ghost like i'll be here all night
and forever find my bones and the best one but listen only when you get around to it no rush
no rush dude i know you're busy chill out dude i'm a new ghost i've been only on the game for
like 20 years i know you're trying to hit 30 in destiny just finishing up my dude i'll take over
you go to bed i'll grind for you get you some gold bro your kd spread is a joke let me patch this up
for you why is this person yelling at me on the headset does that happen in video games yeah
definitely listen i'm confused by the question in so many ways but they say a number of places
the vibe was weird this makes me think like the literal building is a ghost like the building was
murdered in a high passion and has unfinished when you tear down a building and it still had
stuff to do like i still had hats to sell i was gonna be an orphanage just give me time
you know you put one orphan in a building you're a weirdo
you put a hundred in a building it's an orphanage i don't get it
i guess some people are cool and some are jerks right and then they die and become ghosts that's
usually how it works that's the thing i'm actually more worried about why there would be ghosts who
are cool yeah where those who are jerks yeah that makes sense to me i'm angry i'm dead i can't do
shit i'm but a ghost who's just like hey man you know what are you gonna do jkl or jkd jkd just
keep dying just keep dying like a ghost is like you know what i've made peace with my situation
this is me i'm a hollow bastard that's the problem though you can get too complacent yeah that's why
they're stuck they're too nice you gotta be hungry to get off this coil you gotta you gotta work put
the work in it's getting fucking dark no i mean i'm just saying it's another you want to do like
ghost crossfit pain is weakness leaving the body that you left when you died how is there not
already a crossover show of like haunt ghost haunting shows and intervention and it's like
listen ghosts yeah get your shit together you've been in this house for five for 500 years time to
move on what's your unfinished business giving a shit what a thrill it is to be back in america
the land of the free and the home of the money that is made of paper and not plastic
that really got that really got to you huh yeah i've been carrying around 40 canadian dollars i
think that's why i'm so miffed about it i've got 40 canadian if you're listening this and you need
40 canadian dollars and you want to mail me some american dollars let's work that out i think that's
illegal folks we we were planning on putting this episode on hold for a little while uh gonna save
it leave us a little bit of uh uh what we in the industry like to call padding uh but then justin
what happened yesterday what's up infrastructure my my electricity was out for 12 hours power shit
the bed um it was my fault because i went grocery shopping yeah it's it's it's guys it's just every
time we put out a new episode over the next let's say two months just consider that to be a miracle
because now travis is at a wedding so he's out of time like it's just our schedules are just
ridiculous i know you think of us as your friends that live in your ears but we actually have like
like we got shit to pop let's hit some ads let's get some money i want to start things off by
talking to you about the underwear that i'm wearing right now you know it's me undies you
know this you know this to be true me undies.com is committed to making the world's most comfortable
underwear and guess what mission accomplished right now we're offering you 20 off your first
order when you go to me undies.com slash my brother and if you don't love them your first
pair is free let me tell you this i wear them at every live show i need that i need that crutch
it's performance enhancing garment and i need it uh what if you what if i don't want to pay like
as much as everybody else pays do you mean like 20 off like i just said yeah okay maybe um i mean
you're gonna pay a lot more for things than you need to if you don't pay attention in this life
justin but i'll go ahead and say it one more time 20 off your first order go to me undies.com slash
my brother if you don't love them your first pair is gonna be free the uh i all this commerce has
gotten me a little bit of a rumbly in my tumbly griffin well i'm not gonna solve that for you
you are gonna solve that for yourself how by reading the advertisement uh we're gonna head
over to naturebox.com slash my brother it's listed in this ad copy as a vanity url because that's how
we do we're so vain we gotta url for our own use from snacks like peanut butter nom-noms or sriracha
cashews or uh my favorite lemon tea biscuits uh naturebox has over 100 delicious snacks to choose
from that get delivered directly to your doorstep it's such a treat too because i'm usually hungry
when a box gets there i'm like oh hell yeah i was hungry anyway yeah and these don't need a lot of
cooking or preparation just rip it grip it and dip it in your mouth dip it in your mouth but then
don't undip it don't leave it in there just leave it uh they got new they're gonna have new flavors
for you to choose from every single month full of flavor without any of the junk if you go over to
naturebox.com slash my brother our vanity url you can get a first box of hand-picked snacks sent
directly to your doorstep now they have written here in the ad copy and this is quite possibly
the most beautiful sentence i've ever read head to naturebox.com slash my brother to unbox a world
of taste and possibility yeah harness the energy of these snacks this variety of snacks i got a
message for ann davis from ellenor who says hi mama i'm pretty tickled to have a mom so cool
that i can send her a message via the mcroy's maybe i'll be home when you're hearing this
let's go for a bike ride or get eg's or watch some k dramas or whatever it's neat to get to be your
daughter love ellenor is k dramas what does that mean uh kevin kevin dramas or dramas drama centered
around people named kevin those are really good what's your favorite kevin drama right now yeah
second heaven not second kevin that's interesting i would think it would be second seventh kevin
that's my favorite uh that's a good that's a good family dynamic yeah i love that all those
kevins let's check in on uh this next message is for kevin and it's from kevin and those are just
fun pet names i just whipped up for laura who this message is actually for and it's actually from
dave uh and dave says to laura happy belated birthday to my favorite sister don't tell jen
you introduced me to my bim bam and even took me to candle nights now you've been featured in a
live episode farm wisdom and on the jumbo tron the hat trick triple double uh love you miss you
happy birthday oh that's nice love kevin love to hear that kevin just two kevins do we owe laura
some money because it sounds like she's contributed a fair amount to this show
no i think we've given her more than enough in return that is fair uh folks listen we're doing
a live show this weekend i know you're listening to a live show now and you're like how can i get
up on this if you live in la come see us the la podcast festival or la pod fest as you probably
don't live in la statistically speaking statistically speaking you don't live in la good
news you can go to la pod fest.com and you can pick up a streaming ticket that means you can watch
uh my brother my brother and me live streaming uh you can watch we're also doing adventure zone
uh on sunday you can watch that streaming you can also watch all the other shows that are gonna be
there giant bomb cast uh worst idea of all time yes please fuck yeah uh so so many other good shows
uh the the ticket costs 25 bucks the streaming ticket costs 25 bucks uh we can save you five
bucks off that if you use the coupon code what is it brother brother brother i gave the wrong
coupon code on adventure zone what'd you say i said adventure it's actually i fucked up because
i do that shit alone and i didn't have you guys fact checking me anyway use brother or zone whatever
chase your bliss um what else do you want to talk about thanks john rod and all we do that in the
show we already thank john roger yeah that's it i think we might be good cool let's get back to
the jokes we should um we should take questions from the audience from the audience that's a novel
idea uh can we bring the house lights up or is that as bright as it gets or it's just bright on
stage maybe if i compare oh yeah there they are uh yeah here ma'am right here so well before we
can take your question okay um here are the rules now we've never met is that correct this is true
i always true you are what is this um okay so uh first things first no bummers uh keep it short
what else what are the other just that just that okay honest to god if you break all the other
rules and you don't say a bummer like i'm cool with our transaction thank you very much uh now
ma'am what is your name i'm riley okay uh how's things pretty good pretty good um so
today's my birthday happy birthday whoa hold on can we all sing happy birthday to riley legally
legally legally we can't legally we can't but everybody in the theater can make up their own
10 second long happy birthday song i want to hear i want to hit well you can't record it so
this will just be for everybody here ready the recording will stop now all right all right and
the recording will begin now so riley great one travis thanks griffin what's your question riley
so now that i'm basically an adult no right okay um i noticed that you all don't have jobs right
right but somehow you still make a lot of money so here's my we're making some learnings and
i don't want to accidentally get a job right so how do i not get a job like you all
you think you'll just wake up one day like shit it's nine o'clock what happened i gotta be
somewhere that's how i got that's how i got my first job i walked into the tcby on eighth
avenue and they're like hey can you hold this scoop for a second i was like yeah sure i could
ah no
that was great i actually did get my first few jobs accidentally because my dad was like you
know they're hiring a blockbuster and literally here's the thought i put into it i like blockbuster
when it applied 16 years old didn't even occur to me that like
well it sucks i gotta be there all the time and i'm not making honestly that much money
um and i stole a copy of fight club and got fired
fight club what are you gonna do what are you gonna do happens the best of us uh rilo
might i suggest making money on the internet yeah yeah yeah real top notch it's really easy
here's what you do one be mark maron well can you do that by as a thing
done bye everybody uh and uh yeah it's all the you know what in this day and age
jobs are what you make them oh no people no i disagree no no no people no no no disagree
let me finish this thought and see if you don't go with it let him say this dumb thing
take the thing take the thing you love yep just keep doing it no but ask someone to pay you for
it wrong one and two are good but three is not good just ask someone and they'll go i mean i
do have money yeah that's how the world works so so did that does that help um not really but
fair enough okay thank you riley uh who else has a question yes yes rachel rachel sperling has come
to all of our shows there's one right there rachel sperling game recognized game
crossed crossed the border to do the hat trick was it what can i ask what can i ask question
was it worth it what is what we're right the doing all of the travel yeah
yeah where's the conviction okay what's your question rachel okay uh i work at a popular
grocery store in a not very large town you're telling me you don't look up yahoo answers for
a living you just made our advice you're right it looks stupid so when i'm out and about in town on
my own time and i run into regular customers that i'm friendly with uh-huh how can i politely
extricate myself from the conversation because i'm not being paid to be nice to them right
then how do you have how do you have can i tell you the thing this is this is literally a thing
like i have heard from so many bartenders where like they'll just be like in the neighborhood
where their bar is and meet the person that they want tips from so they're very nice to them and
it's like hey how's it going while they're like walking a dog and it's tough because you'll see
them again how do you when they come into the store how do you know the people that come through
like i've been working there for a long time and it's like a neighborhood store and you speak to
them and i speak to them it's like oh it's celery steve conversations yeah yeah well that's what
you can i hey how's the gluten intolerance going that's right that's that's that is less superficial
than 90 percent of the conversations i have oh shit this is what you do you use the knowledge
you have of their purchases against them until they get uncomfortable and stop talking to you
in public how's the infection clearing up hemorrhoids still a thing huh but a lot of
laxative last time is that taking care of itself where are you going see you at the store
but then won't that just be equally awkward next time i see them at the store no because you have
to do it like not pointedly you have to do it so like if you do it if you do it enough times no
one will come to your lane and you'll just have like the most chill shifts ever pop open a can of
bud light lime marita and just chill no i'm sorry if i'm sorry no if i was at a store and i saw one
lane where only one person nobody else in the lane was drinking a bud light lime marita that
is i would i would run not walk to be checking out there the cool cashier the coolest cashier
ever rachel sperling thank you so much i saw that hand go yes you sir yes yes yes you've done it
you've done it you have the best hand here hold it up for me again thank you yes perfect
and keep it up spread those fingers a little oh yeah the symmetry meaty palm yes all right yes
is that how they make them up here would you like the question yeah please what's your name
to me you're just two floating hands buddy
okay my name is brady hi brady hi uh my question i'm a substitute teacher okay so right now i
still i'm trying to lock down that permanent and i want to know what do i need to do when
i go into these schools to get the attention of my bosses without wearing like miss frizzle sweat
shirts like with why is that not an option that's me like number one like thing one yeah
i'm gonna turn it oh shit is there anyone in here who's the principal
um shit yes shit that's a tricky needle to thread trav also i live two provinces away
oh and what is that i don't know what that is yes that like
from what i understand you guys have just like six big fat states
no like hold on let's let brady teach us now yes substitute for the complete lack of education
about oh the metric system uh traffic lights just the whole kit and caboodle
okay so there's 10 provinces what did i say six yeah yeah but there's probably four they're like
i live in one of them according to probably most of the people in this room
sis whoa brady don't act like that in the teacher's lounge it's just it's saskatchewan that's where i live okay i like that one
that's good because i was just about to say what a great province that probably it sounds a lot
like sasquatch yep i like it cool i like it too you know what you could do brady you could uh
pull a stand by me i think his name on that movie lean on me it's lean on me uh lock
what lock the doors from the inside to keep drug dealers out and then you tell the principal like
did you see i shut off the fire did you see what i did i shut off the fire escapes i locked on the
doors so the drug dealers can't get in it wasn't a licensed activity but i'm trying to show initiative
i saw a buzzfeed listicle the other day oh you just know this is gonna be a good story
sorry i saw a buzzfeed listicle the other day and it was like these 23 sexy substitute teachers make
us wish they were permanent teeth this is not a fucking goof by the way this is a realistical
which i thought was fucked up these guys are just trying to do their job can we not says
the guy who just objectified in substitute teacher's hands for three minutes he spray
keeps gesticulating though here's here's what you could do brady uh the next time your class is in
session get all the kids to stay on the desk and be like my couch my captain but you know
but wait to do it until the principal comes by so just like just stay put wait i'm willing here he
comes here it comes i bet that those movies and tv shows are misleading and when a principal sees
a substitute teacher working real hard they're like no that's exhausting yeah i want to teach
your cousin does the shit and then drinks during lunch so you can maybe try that yeah maybe give
less shits yeah okay if the teaching thing doesn't work out you got all the money you
need right there on the end of your wrist my ladies and gentlemen brady brady thank you so much
uh wait i got it you ready yes yes yes come on down
a lot of licensed music not fair use
hello hi hello hi i'm fancy sorry fancy that's great and a great introduction to yourself i'm
fancy now what's your and what's your name fancy oh okay got it from episode 196 oh sweet okay
what's up well unfortunately exquisite fancy delight never took off i'm sorry but anyways
my question and i did send it to you but just in case oops um it got lost in the mail that's okay
okay a couple months ago friends and i were out for dinner and an enormous argument erupted over
the habits of men who go to the bathroom were the worst by the way yes especially
in a lot of ways were the worst especially in that specific way well that that was the
female's opinion but among the males there was a huge argument about whether you unbuckle and
undo or whether you just undo and whip out at you mean at the urinal yes not like the sink yeah
yeah because that's more clear cut yeah but anyways now this argument has spread among our
friends and every party we would go to there are raging fights and it started to spill over
into the girls because there was a listicle on buzzfeed what the fuck see it's ruining everything
yeah this one was about where you put how you put your bra on the 27 hottest substitute dogs
do most of them put the bra on by like stringing it between two surfaces and diving just running
through well naturally awesome i assume everybody's doing it awesome my question is
what can i do to distract people when these arguments start it's thank god thank god that
that was the question and not so what is it you whip it out you unbucked because we're in like
i would not have answered the question otherwise because this is like a classic opera house
basically and i cannot talk about my bathroom stuff you don't want to bum them out that would
be too easy if you're just like how about all this stuff going on in the middle isis am i right like
you can't do that i think they know what isis is in canada sure sure but you i'm saying don't do
that well you did you did you did do just that um you could get something better going like cake or
pie that's more divisive okay raise your hand who's cake who's pie it's not even a thing you
guys not have cake in canada yes they too but we have completely run face first into the big john's
element um why is this cultural imperialism by the way what we're doing up here yeah okay i just
call it manifest destiny different thing my dude i don't think so um the reason we're not doing a
good job at answering this is that i didn't know that there was a debate about the other thing
and but talking about that would be counterproductive wouldn't it that would
kind of be like your worst nightmare so we'd be adding to the problem oh no this is great
you force the two sides to cross are you so it's like you make the women discuss whether you should
unbuckle and undo you make the dudes discuss how you put on a bra and then you just watch the chaos
yeah some fancies just want to watch the world burn that's what i've always said fancy ladies
justin i just justin i want to congratulate you on not doing your michael kane impression i know
it's like your favorite thing in the world no no problem i'm glad i could help by not doing it
we get another i saw that hand in the middle go up first yes you pointing to yours yes yes yes you've
done it no no shit yes but now we have to do both of you yes green shirt you first yeah you're next
day stay ready get ready stay stay locked hey hey what's up hello hey hi so i live with wait
what's your name my name's dean dean what's up it's a good it sounds like an onomatopoeia that i
like like when a little sparkle goes off all right what's up uh not much cool cool yeah any big plans
for the rest of the day do you want some ruffles or don't you give away my ruffles dean hit me so i
live with my twin um we don't look anything alike and whenever people see us arriving at events
together or leaving events together they assume that we're dating uh oh shit that sucks oh no
that's very bad that's the worst it could be is your twin so bad
oh i think what doesn't mean is we're not weird dean that sucks dean i'm sorry dean
dang damn how about how about like a shirt that says like i'm not with stupid
because that's also funny yeah yeah it's a good icebreaker is your twin here no well
shit you would never date somebody with such bad taste in podcasts is this worse than if no it's
worse than anything dean i thought about it super quick could you do staggered entrances
staggered entrances but don't talk to each other at all during the event that's important what's
your twin's name hana hana hana um i don't know why it's still very bad you're just gonna have
to stop hanging out yeah you guys had a good run you gotta burn that bridge i don't hang out with
my siblings and it's time for you to nip it in the bud dean does it help i'm a hologram dean
i mean does it help at all that we haven't said anything helpful but just like we're giving you
some level of commiserate like that's we don't usually do usually we like try to help out a
little bit or at least say something funny but that's just bad you do get a power move if they're
like are you two together and you're like that's my twin that person will give you anything you're
higher wait why did you bring your twin to the job interview i don't know but it worked but you owe
me now boss steve now i'm the ceo thank you dean thank you dean yes come on down come on down
keep clapping i can't abide silence hi hello what's your name elisa elisa which has something
to do with my question actually okay good thank you for the preface so my name is somewhat hard
to pronounce i didn't have any problem with it i did it perfectly when you read it how's it spelled
it's spelled like elisa with one s okay so with a y or an i with a y a l y s a that's a trap and my
last name is somewhat hard to pronounce it's don't say in the podcast that's too much information
we kept not the word i just said i communicate as many of us do through email sure i work in a
business where word of mouth is super important and i meet people who have heard about me through
somebody else or they've gotten an email from me and they think my name is elisa and it's really
awkward for me to try and sure fix so my name is starting to get out there in my business which is
really exciting but it's not really my name yeah right elisa what do i do i so we have the last
name mcelroy and people have been pronouncing it mckelroy my entire life or mclory is a really
popular way or for whatever reason it's very difficult here and so i've got into the habit
when i say my name which i know people can't spell i will say mcelroy m c e l r o y as soon as i say
it so when you meet people start training yourself to immediately say elisa as you meet them like ah
hi i'm elisa say your name right off the bat don't give them the opportunity to mispronounce it
because then it's weird yeah but if they're just like wow elisa's really forward in her introduction
let me try and ease your pain with this and this is gonna sound cool but i want you to really dial
in with me here you compare to some of the other questions tonight it sounds like maybe count your
blessings because there's no listen i want you to really think about this because there was that guy
who didn't have his soup and he was very sad and then there was a guy with the just beautiful
flawless hands and i forget what his thing was about and then dean's thing was the worst that's
true by and large you're doing okay yeah maybe try to get more permissive about it just all
right so you you prefer elisa right that is my name that's like the main crux of the whole thing
okay you prefer elisa what if you open yourself up to some other possibilities
maybe there's a personality for elisa tell people call me elisa call me elisa just don't call me
late for dinner and then stare them dead in the fucking eye until they turn and you are in control
what's ironic you're actually 45 minutes late for dinner and they have fucking nothing
so did that help
thank you elisa i feel like maybe we've run out of steam a little bit
this has been really really fun yeah i thought we came to canada for this give yourselves a hand
uh we want to say thank you uh before anything else to the chant center yeah this is an amazing
venue they've been really really cool and uh also like y'all yeah yeah y'all got put through the
y'all got put through the ringer yesterday and the fact that you're here makes us feel very
good they looked at what we did and looked at this room and said okay it's hugely irresponsible
but i'm glad that they did it we have to scrub the walls to get our goof stink off of it
uh thanks to billions uh who who booked this these these shows for us yep we wouldn't do
these shows if it weren't for them um i want to say thank you to uh uh teresa and riley and
sydney and charlie uh sydney of course is part of sawbones thank you that was that was one of
my favorite episodes of sawbones ever and also great that you opened up uh the show by saying
by the way a third of you have this horrible horrible cat yeah uh without the like without
them uh helping us and supporting us we would not be able to be here and do this uh and thank
you to rachel thank you both rachel mcgrawley and rachel sperling yes thank you to all rachels
thank you to john roger in the long winters for the use of our theme song it's a departure off
the album putting the days to bed um i don't want to make you all jealous but he played at our show
in seattle it was pretty neat yeah and he's here tonight no he's not allowed in canada he rocked
canada too hard uh thanks to maximum fun it's a podcast network that we're very proud part of
yes they've got a lot of great shows at maximum fun.org thank you to uh thank you to emily carol
who did this amazing poster for us that is available for sale to you you can take one home
tonight actually you're getting also a great price because we charge 10 for it in the us
and because of your money situation you can get it for cheap you get it for cheaper technically
so you got that going for you nice yeah let's talk about currency valuations
what's the yin trading at
y'all i want that final yahoo to shut it down griffin you know what i mean
this final yahoo was sent in by ira ray are you ira ray who wants to know it's good
it's by yahoo answers user udavir who asks which is the biggest planet in the world
my name is justin mcelroy this has been my brother my brother and me kiss your dad square on the
lips one more time before we let y'all go i want to say thanks again to me undies they're dedicated
to offering the most comfortable underwear if you go to me undies.com slash my brother you can get
20% off your first order put these on your jeans put this in your face it's nature box you can
order hundreds of great tasting snacks go to naturebox.com slash my brother to sign up for
a sampler box of great tasting snacks see ya maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned
listener supported i'm jesse thorn i'm jordan morris the federal government has millions of
dollars in programs and opportunities that you need to seize today you're a taxpayer right well
then you've got it coming thanks to uncle sam you can learn to get grants for education learn to
ride a llama print money the old-fashioned way force your dog to stop being so rambunctious
make a souffle that sets and stays set mount the heads of your enemies on spikes grind your own
corrective lenses using just rock salt and diamonds for all of this and more drop us a line
don't wait right now jordan jesse go 123 itunes street or wherever you download podcasts