The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it
Also, this show isn't for kids which I mentioned only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening
What's up, you cool, baby?
Ah, it's better, it's better with you
My life
This is true
Ah, it's better, it's better with you
My life
Ah, it's better with you
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother, my brother, me and advice show for the modern era
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy
And I'm your middle-est brother Travis McElroy
Wow
Feels good
It feels good, it feels real good
And I'm old man 2021
Oh, oh, oh no
Wah wah baby, it's 2022 here
Wait, did that baby just beat that old man to death?
It did, it's 2022, this is Griffin, this is sweet baby brother Griffin McElroy 2022
Is that what happens every year?
This baby is naked and it doesn't have a name
It's covered in blood it sounds like
It's covered in old man blood
When was the last time we recorded my brother, my brother and me?
Quick quiz
Before Krimi
I think it's before Krimi
It's before Krimi for sure
It was the first week of December maybe?
It's been weeks since we recorded, we're fired up, we're ready, we're excited to welcome 2022
Yes
Which we're not going to have to call it that much longer because we're about to pick our annual theme
This is an episode that I look forward to
If you haven't listened before, this is a great episode to get people started with
Is it?
Yeah for sure
I love this podcast, these guys do a half hour of clumsy wordplay at the beginning of every episode
Fight about nothing and then move on from there to talk about McDonalds
Let's just start it off
Yes
20 didgeridoo
20 didgeridoo is bad
Let's start it off by, and this is also tradition, going through previous years
Yes, yes, yes
2010, 2010, Zolo, of course
Ridingless, correct
2011, 2000 in heaven, get right with Christ
Okay
Then we had 20 does
Big swing
20 does, getting it
A simple, it's so rudimentary, I love how simple we started with it before our palette expanded
20 dirt, dig it up, get it out, that is of course 2013
That's good
2014, 20 forward, sounds like a, I don't know
We really played fast and loose with the idea, I think we've like
We've grown up
It really codified in 2015, okay?
2015 was 20 grifty and the con is on
That was the best, right? We're not going to top that
You know what else I was reflecting on, a challenge, is that the years in the first decade we did this
I'm so old
The first decade we did this, the sounds are all the same
Yeah
I was returning to a lot of established themes this year, trying to find more rhymes for 20
But okay
Then we had 2016, building bridges, we look back on that one pretty shamefully
Yeah
Oh boy
Maybe our biggest whiff
That might be the biggest ironic one we've ever done
If that could have been grift teen, that would have been really good
Yeah, that literally could have fixed some shit
20 serpentine, keep them guessing, zag on them
Very good
Collaborate teen, stronger together
I feel like we had a lot of so-so ones until we hit 2019, which was Frankenstein teen, become the monster
Right
That one might be the most potent, I think that we had done
That was a powerful one
That was a good one
Then we had 20 funny, fill your life with laughter and love, which then became 20 honey down to bee'sness
That's right, that's right
I'm so bad
That's one of the few slash years that we had
Yeah, and then we had, of course last year, 20 big dog run, no boats about it
Fuck, that was a good naming, last year's naming episode was a good one
I don't know that we're going to top it this time, but that is what we've done so far
How many names do you guys have in front of you that you cooked up?
None
I'm coming in hot
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
Oh my god, that's too many
I have five
Wow, that's a lot, okay
Okay
Because also, I'm just going to, I'm 38 now, when we started naming years, of course I was 25, now I'm 38
A lot of these are bad, I'm just going to, right off the top of my head
Okay, a lot of these are bad
A lot of these are just thought generators
Yeah
Thought starters, yeah
So, I want to throw out kind of a big conceptual one that I don't think will necessarily merit further consideration
But I was excited about it
Two, two, two, two, deuces are wild
And what this is, it reimagines a future where we've been hurtled 200 years into the future
Okay
Right
Two, two, two, because we're not going to make it there, Ovs
Two, two, two, two
Now, hold on, do you mean just us or the planet?
Just us, just us
The planet will make it
We'll figure it out, we're humans
I might make it, Justin, you don't know
Two, two, two, two, deuces are wild
I think if it's just deuces wild, I think deuces wild
Deuces wild, yeah
I like deuces wild because the year that we are currently in, not 200 years into the future, does have a considerable number of twos in it
Right
But not all the twos
I just want you to get that one more two
Yeah, not all the twos it could have, to Justin's point
I mean, I understand that time travel would be a big conceptual thing
I'm embarrassed at this one and I don't want to talk about it anymore
It sucks
Travis, let me sort of traffic cop this a little bit until we sort of get our rhythm
Travis, do three in a row of your worst ones real quick, just so the audience doesn't have that sort of Damocles hanging over their ears
Okay, okay
Twenty hoo-hoo, let's learn about owls
Not even, like not even in the ball game
Just go, just go
Twenty hooty-hoo, let's learn about outcast
As a parry, they're good
Next, I'm not even going to put these on the Google Doc, but keep on rocking and rolling
Third, twenty boppity-boo, be the magic
So you're not even, you have eschewed twenty as a rhyming
I told you they're not good
But I could say like Carl Daniels
No, they all rhyme with twenty-two
Hold on, wait, Justin's just introduced a really powerful concept that I wanted to stop and make sure we take a beat, okay?
And that is that, have we been hamstringing ourselves by needing to rhyme and also not giving the year a real human name like Carl Daniels
It wouldn't be powerful to be like, fucking Carl Daniels, Carl Daniels sucked
Or, if we're being optimistic, man, Carl Daniels was the best, wasn't he?
Carl turned it the fuck around for this nation of ours
If I could say, I think, oh my god, to send jokes out of the room
I think we do need to limit ourselves to the rhyme, because it's one of the few things, if we open the palette up that much, we'll never crack this
I think the restrictions make it important
There's so few things that people can rely on anymore, I think they need to rely on a rhyming year theme
That would be my argument
Instead of it being, just one last thing though, instead of it naming the year Carl Daniels, can we make it possessive and just make it Carl Daniels' kickass year
And then all the Carl Daniels' out there, just know that they're gonna find a 20 on the street every day
Well, what if we make it a rhyming year, but the tagline is, a good year for Carl's
A great year for a great Carl
It was a good year for Carl's, and make it retrospective right out the gate
I'm gonna go ahead and keep suggesting this, and it will be relevant every year this decade, to just do 20 cummies to
I hate it
And I still haven't learned really what that word means, aside from context clues that it does involve
Do we let Travis do one more bad one, just to get a story
Travis, why don't you get, are all eight of yours bad?
There's one that I really like, and it would be kind of a different direction for our year of protection
Alright, let's have a beefy one, let's have one that we can really sup on
20 whoopty-doo, who cares
No
No no no no, Justin
No, I don't like the nihilism of that
No no no no, but let's fucking cross-examine it, don't just shit on it
You're right, okay, you're right
20 whoopty-doo, who gives a shit
Oh, I like that better, yeah, who gives a shit
We've given the years in the past powerful, powerful dragon shouts, I would say, of mottos and names
And what fucking good has it done so far, right?
Correct
Like we, certainly we look to Big Dog Run, and we think like, I could be stronger
But at the end of the day, you know, Omicron wasn't like, whoa, look at all these big dogs, let's get out of here
If we, if we like, don't necessarily look at the year, we don't quantum lock it
Is it possible that we could have, like the end would justify the means a little bit
It's interesting that 20 Big Dog Run was our most stationary year
Both physically and, I would argue, professionally
Just a real
Emotionally, psychically
Yeah, just keeping it between the navigational beacons, you know? Just trying to stay on course
What I also like about it is you could treat it like a genuine question
20 whoop-de-doo, who cares?
I do, I do
I care
I'll answer that call
Okay, I want to, I want to put it on the, well, you know
It's on there, it's on there, Travis, you're not in this Google Doc, so I don't know what the fuck you're doing right now
That's more important than this
I'm listening and paying attention
Yeah, so where is the Google Doc?
I shared it with you, to your email
Where?
To share with your email
Okay, I'm in it
Okay, I'm going to throw out one of my, one of my better options
Alright, let's have it, let's have it
Okay
20 Yummy Stew, something's cooking
What I like, my argument for this is one, it's fun to say
I like there's an exclamation, I put an exclamation point in the notes just because like phonetically
Like it felt like you were kind of excited
But I do like having a punctuation mark in it
No, no, no, see the thing is you can delete the punctuation and then it removes pressure
What I like about this is like we can get to the end of the year and like nothing has happened
But it's like, I don't know, it feels like something's cooking
Something's cooking
Yeah, it's definitely, it's definitely I in apostrophe, I won't accept that G
Something's cooking, now can you make it a question and make it 20 Yummy Stew, what's cooking?
What's cooking?
So then it's a little more interactive, a little more actionable, that's my worry
That's bad because if, you know, due to climate change, if wildfires continue to be the sort of clear and present threat they were in previous years
I think that that
That would be in poor taste
So then I guess you're also against 20 Yummy Stew, what's cooking good looking? Is that too much?
Yeah, I don't want to harass people with the name of the year
I feel like the only problem with this Justin is that in the last, let's say six years
I have, there has not been an event that has been sort of a slow building moment
That has been a good thing that we're all wicked looking forward to
Do you know what I mean?
It's not like, oh man, there's a sinkhole that's very, very slowly opening up somewhere in South America
And it's very slowly consuming this community
But what's that coming out of it?
It's taste stations and they're back
Like there hasn't been a thing that's like
I'm pretty sure taste stations are back
Something's cooking
Now can we go in a different direction where stew
Cream savers are back
Cream savers
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Where stew is a sort of mixed up bag of ingredients
Is there something like 20 Yummy Stew, toss an onion in
Toss your stuff in
I don't think we need
I like people to sort of read their own context into it
Beyond the sort of like basic setting of expectations
I feel like that's where we're at
What do you do if something's cooking?
Well it's just like something's cooking, you know?
Travis is saying there needs to be an act
This is an observation
We need a like
Let me tell you a tagline
Mix it up
What about 20 Yummy Stew, mix it up
Well I've got a tagline that I'm pretty excited about
20 Yummy Stew, put it in the pot
Huh
Okay, what would that be?
What you have, what you've got, put it in the pot
20 Yummy Stew, let it simmer
Let it simmer is again like I don't
That's a very passive thing
Put it in the pot
Take what you've got
But what does that mean?
I'm trying to
We're talking about it
Instead of asking, just turn that beautiful thinking brain on
Put it in the pot
What do you have?
You have something special
I have something special
Put it in the pot
Oh, it's a stone soup scenario
It's a stone soup situation
Okay, stone soup
Now I get it
So we're all adding something
Put it in the pot
I just like how that sounds
That's not bad
Don't be embarrassed about that thing that you have
Just put it in the pot
That idea, put it in the pot, let's see what happens
Maybe it'll be good, maybe it won't
20 Yummy Stew
Okay, Trav, do you have another one that you'd like to offer?
Griffin, does anything
I got something that's been coming through my head
because I was thinking about this
Is it about cummies again?
It's not about cummies this time
But I will, sorry, I will add 20 cummies
No, I hate it
I hate it so much
And it's a different one
So just hang on, you ready?
20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20
Try that out
Try that out for size
Wait, that's it?
I thought that was a build up
No, the name of the year is
20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20
What is that for?
Try it out
You should have written some down
Why are you trying to break
We have so few rules and conventions, Griffin
You should have written some down, Griffin
But you should try saying it out loud because it feels good
20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20
It does get me pumped
It does
Yeah, but I have had to institute a
we don't chant for things rule in my house
Okay
So it does
I can see it would be a little bit hypocritical
It would be a little bit hypocritical
because of how often my two children instigate each other into pounding the table to ask for candy or whatever
And this feels a little bit insightful, like inciting
Okay, all right, it's on the list
How about 20 funny shoes
20 funny shoes
They don't got to match all the time
Right?
I'm trying to think of something with shoes
20 funny shoes and odd pairing
Ooh
Ooh, something different
Ooh, an interesting pairing
That would be cool if in past years we've been like, believe in yourself
Or work with others
Or build those bridges
And then this year we're like, wear different shoes
You can do this
This you can do
Shoes not match
And then that would be great because then you would see somebody on the street with not matching shoes
You'd be like, that asshole listens to my brother and my brother and me
Yeah, that's like an international sign of
Just wish we could monetize it
That's the problem, we don't sell shoes
Not yet
Okay, listen to this
All right
20 Venti Brew, oh that Java
Oh
When you say it, you have this way of saying them afterwards that really sucks the fucking air out of it
Give it a little bit of panache
Let me try it again and you listen and imagine I came up with it and not you, okay?
20 Venti Brew, oh that Java
It was fun to say like that wasn't it
Yeah, that's pretty good
It was kind of fun to say
This is what I like
Maybe this year I could just get bigger coffees
Maybe that's what we've been missing
That's pretty good
What about
I don't like how Starbucks has kind of co-opted the Venti thing
I hate doing that
Wait, from you?
When you guys go to Starbucks
I say large
Large, right?
Yeah
A large, thank you
Yeah, like a human
What about
We just kind of brew blue right past it
I feel like it's on there and we'll circle back to it Justin
I don't want to spend too much time on it ruining it
I like brew
Brew as a verb I could get into
I don't know about Venti and having it be like a witch's brew
I guess we are getting back to something's cooking or put it in a pot
Yeah, that's true
What about 20 skies of blue, anything's possible
Whoa, I like that actually
Skies of though
Skies of blue is interesting because one
Wow, what an incredible
You are opening up the possibility space for us to fail even more powerfully
Yeah, yeah
Than we did in 2016
I have two options and it's either whoopty-doo, who cares
Or skies of blue, anything's possible
I only have two settings Justin
I see that you didn't add 20 skies of blue, anything's possible to the list
He'll add it, he'll add it, it's a good one
One, I don't know why I'm adding all of the things
Because you didn't come up with any numbers because you didn't come up with any names beforehand
So this is your contribution, your secretary, your stenographer
There you go, you're keeping the minutes
Let me hit you with this
I don't have a tagline for it but it seems like it's right for any tagline we could want to put on it
20 coming through, clear the way
20 coming through, emerge into your power
Emerge
Part 20 coming through, emerge
Oh shit, that's good
That's pretty good, I like that
Imagine that on like a big projector
A big, what are those things called that you put on the lights to make it appear?
A gobo
A gobo, a big gobo that just says emerge
Emerge
20 coming through
That's powerful as shit
20 coming through, emerge, I really like it
That's really doing me right
This is the episode, by the way, most of the episodes we record in a given year
The one where my let's not accidentally make a cult radar is up
Oh, you don't want to
I did just imagine a crowd full of people, this is by the way after we whipped this COVID shit
Just in an auditorium and the three of us
For some reason we're dressed in all white and our shoes don't match
And there's a big sign behind us that says emerge
As people chant against my rules, everybody's chanting emerge
Everybody's going 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20
To the outside observer, we have made a cult for sure at that point
For sure, for sure, for sure
I also want to take a moment to celebrate us because in making this procedure public
We open ourselves up to, I mean literally every year
Multiple people telling us they wish we had done one of the other things that we talked about
And sometimes even suggesting other things we didn't say
This is interesting, in previous years we have opened it up to suggestions
And this is just us this time
I did not consult the crowd
Oh, you didn't need to
Plenty of people emailed them in and tweeted them
I would say also in our defense we have never gone with the audience suggestion for this
Because that's a little too important a decision I would say
It could be trademark
Yeah, that's a big thing too
Otherwise you're not going to get classics like this
Yeah, like 20 runny goo
No, no, I was leaning into a real great slide
You're not going to get classics like this
20 sun tee view
Porch life
You're holding the sun tee, right?
And this is your view from the porch
And you've got a sun tee view, porch life
Now I think the one problem with that, Justin, is I don't know
I don't think any human being has ever said, look at this sun tee view
What is sun tee? I don't drink tea, what is sun tee?
Sun tee is where you just make slow tea in the sun
You let the sun heat up your gross water
So it's not a thing then, right?
No, it's a thing, what do you mean it's not a thing?
Sun tee?
Yes, everybody's googling this
You put multiple tea bags in a picture and you put it in the sun
Oh, you're right, you're right
You put it in the sun
Okay, sorry
Did you just Google it?
Yeah, I Googled it, I'm sorry
Where's the trust, you know?
Is there something with kazoo?
No
Banjo kazoo
Banjo 20 kazoo
That was a really good banjo kazoo
20 Scooby Doo
No
All right, is it the time in the episode where we take a step away and say
What do we want to embody?
Well, have we put up all our suggestions?
No, no, no, no, I think this will help spread a little fertilizer around on the feet
It is important to me, kidding aside, it is important to me that it be somewhat either motivational or aspirational
In a way that gets you pumped for this year
Because I don't want, everybody, this is one of the years of your life, right?
You don't want to assign it to negativity this early
You will get there for sure, but you got to start fresh
But let me add this, because I agree with you, I do agree with you
But is there a way that we can embody, because in the past I feel like we've embodied like a naive kind of hope
Is there a way now that we're doing like a, this is a mature, this is a, it's still there, right?
This is hope for sure, but this is a cautious, powerful hope, you know what I mean?
Yeah, that's interesting, Travis, because I would say a weakness of
Skipping 2020, which I think we can all agree, that year's motto, both of them were complete fuck ups
2019 and 2021, we have become the monster and big dog run
Like those are both very strong, but it was also like, get the most powerful and aggro
And that like, I don't necessarily think that's us
There are very few times in my life where I'm like, let's become the monster, baby
Because I'm, we are, we are, we are meeker than that, I would say
Two thirds of us definitely are
Yeah, so instead of it being like, let's go baby
Have it be like, maybe don't be so timid
Maybe don't be as timid as you usually are and take a shot, you know?
Like, not like, get it and win the game, but like, get in the game
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah
20 something new
It's just not, it's not very clever
It's not specific, there's not enough specificity to it
Let me hit you guys with this
Yeah
Because I've been saving it, this isn't my last one
Oh fuck
When it came to me, I was like, oh, mama, like that
This is so exciting because this could either be the moment where Justin says the thing that like
Well, I have one more, Justin, do you want me to do?
Please do yours
Okay, 20 looky-loo on the horizon
I don't like the phonetics of looky-loo makes me feel bad
Okay, okay
I don't like saying it
That means something
Yeah
Did you guys watch that Beatles documentary?
Because it's dope, because they'd just be like noodling, like Scooby-Doo-bop-bop-bop-bop-bop
Hey, is this anything?
Scooby-Doo-bop-bop-bop
No, that's not anything
What about this?
Get back to where you once
And it's like, oh fuck, you guys just wrote get back
That's the moment we're at right now when Justin's about to say the thing that's like his get back
Okay
20 mummy crew back from the dead
Huh
20 mummy crew
What this is about is two things
Okay
One, back from the dead
Yes
Okay
Yeah
Well
Fair, right?
We've been ground down to a paste
Yeah
But it's also about, so it's about coming back from that
But it's also about community
Oh
Because you look at anybody else that's with you, they're a mummy too
You're in the mummy crew
What about 20 mummy too?
20 mummy crew back from the dead
The idea of mummy crew, obviously Justin, is one of the best things you've ever sort of generated
Yes, correct
One of the best pieces of content you've ever created
It's up there with your two children who I love very much
20 mummy crew
The idea of us, instead of calling our audience Mbimbambinos or, you know, Mbimbambnation
The idea of them just being the mummy crew is so fucking strong
I tell you, I don't like having the word dead in the motto
Because that feels a little bit
We're back from the dead
Yeah
Right
Not why, but I do think that there's something, maybe it's 20 mummy crew, rise again
Or 20 mummy crew, straight out the tomb
Is that better?
Better than dead
20 mummy crew, arise my love
Hmm
That's interesting
Something for the Baptists
20 mummy crew
Sarcophagit it
Ooh
If we hadn't already done getting it, I would
Yeah
I do love, by the way, the juxtaposition of me saying maybe tone it down to a more reasonable, let's not be so timid thing
And then Justin was like, alley-oop, 20 mummy crew, rise from the dead, back from the dead
It feels, also Juice, can I tell you a genuine concern of mine
And this is something I had a few ideas that I immediately shot down in my head
It feels a little bit like the Post Malone Jägermeister commercial
Where he's back at the bar and it's empty and the bartender's like, it's empty because of COVID
But then he's like, dummy, we're better now
And he walks out in the street with a bottle of Jägermeister and then the place is packed
And he's like, we worked hard for this, let's celebrate
And then it's like, a month later, it's like, uh-oh, I'm gonna cry
No, don't
I worry about it being like, 20, rise from the dead, baby, it's back
Go buy a Toyota truck, Toyota Nation, because we are here and we've waited long enough
Okay, okay, okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Along those lines, 20 mummy crew, lying in wait
No
Right, because the mummy's there
Way too passive, way too passive
Way too passive
I want something that says, we're not doing it now, but we, ooh, moments notice, you know what I mean?
If you want that, then get 20 yummy stews, something's cooking
Mmm, can we do 20 mummy crew, something's cooking
20 mummy stew
20 mummy
I'll be, can I be honest?
I feel like, of the things that we have
I feel like, I love the tagline, put it in the pot, a lot
I like the concept of mummies though
It is equivalent in my mind to like, don't hide your light under a bushel
Put it out there and let it become better
By becoming more fragrant and mixing around with the other stuff
To me that, and maybe we're getting, maybe that's trending a little too close to collaboratine
But even put it in the pot feels a little bit more achievable than go find a collaborator
So 20 mummy stew, 20 mummy stew put it in the pot?
20 mummy crew, together we rise
That feels, again, we're getting close to like a presidential campaign
Well
For mummies
I have been waiting to announce
20 mummy crew pyramid dreams, is that anything?
Ooh
Now we're getting into cult territory again, I feel like if we start leaning into pyramids, like symbology and shit
20 mummy crew
Under wraps
No
20 mummy crew
Wrap it up, it's about safe sex
That could be fun
I think if you don't, here's what I would say, if you don't have something about resurrection in there
Then, mummy crew stew
20 mummy crew
Sounds very strange
Yeah, I guess so
Mmm
Um
20, oh shit
What if, guys
What if we get really, really focused
Okay
On
Bringing back
Brendan Fraser's The Mummy series
And so 20 mummy crew
Is us
Really pounding the pavement
To get Brendan Fraser's The Mummy 4
Yeah
Yeah, it would be the fourth mummy
Off the ground
But you have to not count the Tom Cruise mummy
No, of course not
Of course I don't count the fucking Tom Cruise mummy
And we're bringing back Rachel Weisz, I don't care
Rachel Weisz
Now Justin, you say it's unattainable, but I would argue that it is more attainable than us all becoming big dogs
I think if Brendan Fraser
I think if Rachel Weisz hears a knock at the door
And she opens it and Brendan Fraser's standing there
Yeah
She puts on her coat
And walks outside and follows him, no, like, no words exchanged
Just like, yes
Correct
Yep
It's time
I don't, I don't, I don't want to do this
You don't want to bring back
No, I don't want to bring back
This is going to be the one
Brendan's doing a lot of great work in a lot of different fields
Yeah
So, so good
I don't want to disrupt him
In Doom Squad
Now here's the thing, Justin
I want you to just brace yourself that this is going to be the one that everyone is going to be like
I can't believe you guys didn't commit to bringing back The Mummy
The original series
I don't think so, because most people, we are
The funny thing about that is we are
A hundred million light years from having the juice to get that done, a hundred percent
It's not even close
And most of our listeners are probably even more unable to bring back The Mummy
I think everybody working together
And you know what the other problem with that is?
Even if we do it, it doesn't benefit us enough
Okay, first of all, Justin
I've watched The Mummy
All you got to do to bring back The Mummy is like disrupt The Tomb or some shit, right?
And then the movie, mostly The Mummy brings itself back
What about, okay, 20 Mummy Crew, a Nox and a Moon
What do you think?
Is that anything?
Is that like a spell?
No, that was the name of the woman
It could be badass to have a spell in our year slogan
That like makes a magical thing happen
You know, Travis, you just said
20, 20, 20 viewers skew!
Let's meet Kevin Smith
That's attainable
That's fun
I feel like Travis said something not realizing the power inside of his incantation
And that was disrupt The Tomb
20 Mummy Crew disrupt The Tomb
The idea of like, of taking these sacred, you know, idols
Shaking them up a little bit
Disrupt The Tomb
Let's try something
Now there is a lot of colonialism associated with that
There is a huge, there's a huge
It's unthinkable, unthinkable that you would even suggest it
Wait, we're canceled mid podcast, we haven't even published
No, it's NBC guys, they canceled us again
Whoop
Alright, don't disrupt The Tomb, fuck
20 Mummy Crew
20 viewers skew
Buried with cats
20 running
Running is something, running is a word that could potentially go in there
I mean 20 running crew
That's nothing Travis
20 running shoo
20 running goo
20 running shoo?
Guys, you guys feel like we're in the weeds right now?
This is where I feel like our power lies
Is deep in the trash heat
When we just start saying
20 cunning shrew
What?
Like a cunning shrew
It's okay Justin, this is part of the process
This is how we get to Big Dog Run, you know what I mean?
Wait, what about 20 Mummy Crew emerge?
Emerge
Escape the grave
20 Mummy Crew, shame the grave
Shame the grave
It would be dumb if we just had a year of unabashed hedonism
20 Mummy Crew, death is only the beginning
Oh man
Maybe we should go to the money zone just as like a palette cleanser
And when we come back have sort of fresh eyes
And then we'll read through them again
This will be the whole, okay great
Great, actually, that's actually a great idea
Yeah
Cause I'm looking at this list guys
And it's maybe our worst list ever
But I think maybe we're just too close to it
I think we're way too close to it
It's better with you
Bombus
Boom
Watch your language
It's right there, Bombus
The mission is simple
Make the most comfortable clothes ever
And match every item sold
So when you buy Bombus
You are also giving to someone who's in need
You guys, I'm wearing Bombus socks right now
Whoa, me too
What?
Yep, you can tell cause of how comfortable I am
I'm not wearing socks cause I stepped in something wet earlier
And had to take the wet sock off
Oh man, that's the worst
Did you know what the wetness was Griffin?
Or was it mystery wet?
Rarely do I know what the wetness was
Oh, that's the thing man
I got two dogs and a potty training toddler
It could be anything
Okay, they also make shirts and underwear
And oh my god
These are incredible
It's my favorite shirt
My favorite t-shirt
It's made by Bombus
I said it
Everything they make is soft, seamless, tagless
And with a luxury, cozy feel
And they're made from stuff like marino wool
And pima cotton
And even cashmere
Which all sound so fancy
And make you feel fancy
And so they're perfect, cozy, winter layers
Go to bombus.com slash my brother
And get 20% off any purchase
That's B-O-M-B-A-S dot com slash my brother
For 20% off bombus.com slash my brother
Oh, time to level up
Oh yeah?
Hey gamers, level up those clothes
Hey gamers, it's time to level up your fashion
A lot of people think that we might get to leave our houses this year
It's impossible to say
But you want to be ready
When we're allowed to leave our houses
There's going to be a rush in the clothing stores like you wouldn't believe
But you could have your fashion already ready to go with the power of SitFix
It could be already ready already?
Yes, you could shop at a store that just caters to you
Call it Ted's Threads if your name is Ted
Or call it Stitch Fix because that's what it's called
Rich Fix
Rick's Fix
They got a new thing, Stitch Fix Freestyle
Oh Justin, I'm too far into rhyming
Oh no
No, no, no
Yeah, you got to disengage that part of your brain
You can discover and instantly buy curated items based on your style
Your likes and your lifestyle
So you know that they do the stylist thing at Stitch Fix
And I love that
But Freestyle lets you go in and say like, I need this
This is me
I need this
And you could shop for over a thousand brands and styles
Personalized to your size and fit
There's no subscription required
They offer free shipping, returns and exchanges
You can get started today by filling out your style quiz
At stitchfix.com slash my brother
That's stitchfix.com slash my brother
To try Stitch Fix Freestyle
stitchfix.com slash my brother
You're in a theater
The lights go down
You're about to get swept up by the characters
And all their little details and interpersonal dramas
You look at them and think
That person is so obviously in love with their best friend
Wait, am I in love with my best friend?
That character's mom is so overbearing
Why doesn't she just stand up to her?
Oh God, do I need to stand up to my own mother?
If you've ever recognized yourself in a movie
Then join me, Jordan Cruciola, for the podcast Feeling Seen
We've talked to author Susan Orlean on realizing her own marriage was falling apart
After watching Adaptation, an adaptation of her own work
And comedian Hari Kondabolu on why Harold and Kumar was a depressingly important movie for Southeast Asians
So join me every Thursday for the Feeling Seen podcast here on Maximum Fun
I'm Lisa Hanawalt
And I'm Emily Heller
Nine years ago, we started a podcast to try and learn something new every episode
Things have gone a little off the rails since then
Tune in to hear about
Low stakes neighborhood drama
Gardening
The sordid, nasty underbelly of the horse girl lifestyle
Hot sauce
Addiction to TV and sweaty takes on celebrity culture
And the weirdest, grossest stuff you can find on wikipedia.org
We'll read all of it, no matter how gross
There's something for everyone on our podcast, Baby Geniuses
Hosted by us, two horny adult idiots
Hang out with us as we try and fail to retain any knowledge at all
Every other week on Maximum Fun
Baby Geniuses, tell us something we don't know
Is there a new one on the list?
Yeah, there's just this new one right here
Someone put that on there
What's it say, Griffin?
22 the Dew brought to you by Mountain Dew by Hot Blast
You know, it's funny you say that
I was actually thinking, I wish we would sell the rights
Like the branding rights, you know what I mean, to this thing
Oh, that's fun
I wish we did that
Well, this is a cold shot kind of selling it
Where we would name it that
And then get retroactively reimbursed for it
Yeah, and it would need to be a brand
It couldn't be like 20 Long John Silvers
No
Enjoy our crispy fish
Okay, just to sort of expand our mind a little bit
I am on rhyme zone looking at three syllable rhymes with ew
I did that as well, yes
Okay, so there's some stuff in here
Just like 20 BBQ, 20 Black and Blue, 20 Brunswick Stew
20 Brunswick Stew, that means even less than some of the ones we already had
I have two, can I throw out two that I thought of just as more thought starters?
Yeah, sure, sure
20 Cordon Bleu, Cookin' Fancy
Okay
And 20 something blue, Tie the Knot
This is interesting, we're getting even farther
That's fine, Juice, we have to get perspective, you know?
God is watching us from a distance, 20 Deja Vu
20 Broader View
20 Point of View
Is nothing
Meaningless
Now, 20 Deja Vu, one more again, is not bad
Let me, I had a thought while I was recording the podcast
Yeah, sure
2020 Dew, Second Chances
Huh, here's what it is
2020, we messed up pretty bad
As a species, we whiffed it
It was going to be cool too, like that number was really a cool number
Yeah
But 2020 Dew, what that suggests is, let's try again
Let's try again
You can do 2020 again, but better, Second Chances, 2020 Dew
Okay
20 Debar Dew
It's also kind of continental too
Yeah, sure
You know what I mean? Kind of fancy
Yeah, because what it is that you are saying is, to translate, just for our friends who don't speak French, is 2022
Yeah
Right
It's also, Justin, if I may, would be the laziest one
You may, you may, you may
It's the laziest one we could have possibly done
No, actually 2022 would have been lazier, and that was my initial thought
But I kind of do like 2022 as a name
Like TOO?
No
No?
TWO, the number
Huh
That's cool, I like that
Is it?
Let's do it again, let's try it better
2022, a year of sequels
20 Pikaboo, here we are
20 Pikachu
20 Pikachu, electric mouth
20 electric boogaloo
20 Pikachu, don't evolve
Oh
That's kind of a fun
20 Rendezvous, good evening
Oh
This is a phase that I think we go in where we see how hard we can whiff
20, no I'm sorry, 20 Rendezvous, good evening, it's very good
20 Rendezvous, hello there
20 Rendezvous, on the veranda
20 Rendezvous, I see you there
20 Rendezvous, to the veranda
To the veranda
20 Rendezvous, a nighttime affair
20 Rendezvous, a night to remember, and we just do it like a senior prom
All you need to do is have one good night
Just one good night
Just have one good night
Then at all of our live shows we'll set up a photo, like set up a prom photo booth
And we will have all teams a night to remember
Guys, I'm kind of hooked on 20 Rendezvous, a night to remember
I think it's very close
I think a night to remember is a little
I think it's hitting like a walk to remember, maybe it's just 20 Rendezvous, a walk to remember
A walk to remember
No, Rendezvous, I like the class the night to remember brings, it also sounds like we're picking a prom theme
Which is very fucking to me
Enchantment in the evening
20 Rendezvous
Enchanté
Too hard to spell
So is Rendezvous
Yeah, we need to talk about that for a second
Do we just want to expect people to learn
How to spell Rendezvous
How to spell Rendezvous, okay, nobody look
Travis
Griffin, spell Rendezvous
R-E-N-D-E-V-O-U-Z
Incorrect
Say it again
R-E-N-D-E-V-O
Griffin
R, I know Travis got the first five letters right, R-E-N-D-E-Z
That seems like a weird pick
You sure you want to go with Z
R-E-N-D-E-S-V-O-U-Z
It's R-E-N-D-E-Z-V-O-U-S
Oh, so I was right and you were
Yeah, but if you could be shaken from it, you didn't know
Yeah, you didn't have it
You were guessing
That is tricky, I do feel like it robs it of a little bit of
But maybe this would be something that we could concretely take away from it
Is that everybody would learn how to spell one word
That is true, that is an actual thing
I'm working on spelling restaurant right the first time every time
And so having that like, this is not only a good, obviously great motto
But also a powerful learning experience
Okay, earlier in this very episode you did say that you wanted it to be motivational or aspirational
This is
What does 20 rendezvous, a night to remember mean
It's like saying, hey, make the most of it, grab this opportunity, this is a night to remember
What if it's during the day though
We could even make it more specific, which is like out of 365 chances
Have like one night to remember
That doesn't feel strong enough
I feel like 20 rendezvous is good
I feel like a night to remember could be stronger
I am shaken by the spelling
Okay, alright
I'm a little bit shaken by the spelling thing, it robs it of some of its power to me
Now we could, let me just, one more thing
Just if we wanted to do perhaps our biggest cold shot ever in 13 years
Fuck
20 rendezvous, meeting in person
That's cool, yeah there's nothing wrong with that right now
Yeah, loaded, a little bit loaded
How about this
20 Jenny Sue, you get on out to that corn patch and feed them piggies
Now, okay
So once again, just cause, 20 Jenny Sue
You get on out to that corn patch and feed them piggies
Yeah
20 Peggy Sue
20 Jenny Sue, cause it rhymes with 20
No I get that
20 Jenny Sue, get on out to that corn patch and feed them piggies
20 Peggy Sue, ooey oo, I look just like Buddy Holly
Maybe, 20 ooey ooey ooey
Does 20
Wait, is that it? Wait, wait, wait, was that it?
Ooey ooey ooey
20 ooey ooey ooey
20 ooey ooey ooey, that's a spicy one
20 ooey ooey ooey, yummo
20 ooey ooey ooey, a spicy one
Oh, 20 ooey ooey ooey ooey, doo wop's back
Uh, 20 switcheroo
20 switcheroo, 20 switcheroo
Ah, no, that doesn't, that doesn't, that doesn't, that doesn't, that provides no direction
What about 20, 20 tried and true?
20 tried and true reads a little patriotic
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
20 Dr. Drew, he sucks now
Oh, okay, so that would be a good way to get to 20
Yeah, we just, old stuff kicks ass though
20, 20 you should sue, get justice
20 more bamboo, it's sustainable
20 kangaroo, put it in the pouch
20 kangaroo, jump on it
20 started-oo
No, that's actually too motivational
Yeah, yeah, yeah
That would be on the front of a planner that I would purchase
20 revenue, maximize your earning potential
What about 20 racing crew, it's about family
20 more fondue, make it cheesy
Yeah, now I like that that implies that in previous years we've had some fondue, but this year it's 20 more fondue
Turn it up
20 Sudoku
20 Sudoku, line them up
Can I tell you right now, I feel like we're never gonna find it, even if we find it we won't know it, and it's the worst episode we've ever made
Yeah, this is our lowest again
And this is, I feel the electricity right now because I believe you said that exact same thing last year right before we came up with 20 Big Dog Run
Oh, oh, oh, okay
20 Pay Per View, all of our episodes cost $1
What if we did one just for us this year, it was like we've given you guys 11 good years
This one's called 20 Pay Per View, and all our episodes cost $1 now, you have to put it into your phone
What about 20 Miss Construe, say that again
What was that?
More for me and you
No, 20 Miss Construe
20 just for you
I feel like there's a lot of people in America that are already living that life
Yeah, that's fair
Yeah, yeah
20 not for you
20 New Tattoo
Ooh, I, okay, okay, okay, let's, let's
Let's take a breath
Now, 20 Big Dog Run, great
Frankenstein Teen was the entire thing, is there something funny bamboo, funny big bamboo, funny
20 monies through, time, crypto, time to become a crypto lord
20 Santee View
Oh yeah, now we're getting somewhere
I got it
Oh boy
Oh shit
20 Rise of Groot
Get back to where you once belonged, get back
Coming this July
After many delays, we will finally be treated to it
Despicable Me 4, The Rise of Groot
It's Minions, The Rise of Groot
Oh, okay
Nice
It used to be called Minions 2, and now it's called Minions Rise of Groot
That's better
20 Rise of Groot
20 Baby Shoe
For sale
Never warned
Why did you keep naming them?
Oh, sorry
It was, do you know that this movie was supposed to be released on July 3rd, 2020?
That's why I think it's so powerful
Because by calling the year 20 Rise of Groot, we're saying that this film will absolutely be released in theaters this July
Yeah
No bones about it
What about 20 IOU, we will give the next year a much better name
20 IOU, one good year name
20 IOU, one hour of your life
Let's do this, we'll go back through the list real quick
I actually am warming back up to Carl Daniels Kick-Ass Year
Yeah
Okay, so just taking a look at the list, we got
Carl Daniels Kick-Ass Year
I'm gonna leave it in, I wish the name was funnier than Carl Daniels, but here we are
20 Whoop-de-do, who cares, I still, I can't get on board with that
20 Yummy Stew, something's cooking
Or 20 Yummy Stew, put it in the pot
Put it in the pot
20 Cummies, ew
20 Cummies 2
20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20
Yeah
Tony, Tony, Tony, Tony
20 Venti Brew, oh that Java
20 Skies of Blue
20 Coming Through, Emerge
20 Runny Goo, what?
20 Runny Goo
20 Runny Goo, 20 Sun TV, Porch Life
20 Mummy Crew
20 Do The Do, brought to you by Mountain Dew Baja Blast
And then Griffin kind of abandoned his posts
Cause I feel like 20 Rendezvous, still merits consideration
20 Rise of Gru
I feel in my heart, my heart's telling me
This can't be fun to listen to
That Mummy Crew is
See, I'm still on, I'm still stuck on Yummy Stew
I like the
I'm telling you guys, 20 Mummy Stew
20 Mummy Stew
20 Mummy Stew, do what thou wilt
Wait a minute, no this is powerful
Is there a motto that we can do
That is like, you guys have, you all have
Flown, flown away from our nest
Like you don't need us in
Oh, 20 up to you, the power is yours
20 up to you, 20
Oh man, hold, oh you're so close
20, 20 up to you
20 it's in you, the magic's been in you all along
The magic, 20 it's in you, the magic is
The magic comma specifically
20 up to you, what are your ideas
20 up to you, fill in the blank
No, see that's like, that's like you're no better off having heard it
You know, like you're exactly where you started
That's like coming to the oracle and the oracle's like
I don't fucking, I don't play Madden, get out of here
What do you think is gonna happen
What do you think, I don't know
Can't see the future, what am I
20 Mummy Stew, people used to eat mummies
Is there something, is there something instead of stew
Can we swap brew in there
And is there a word that's like
I'm imagining a bubbling pot
And people putting their stuff in the pot
And not being afraid to put stuff in the pot, like they're gonna ruin it
And then you get out of that, you get like a soup or a potion
I don't even know what you're asking
Like a witches brew
What are you suggesting
Is there another word
Is there another
Yummy mummy stew, yummy mummy brew
Yummy mummy stew
Yummy mummy
Yummy mummy brew
From Budweiser
Yummy mummy is a trademark
So we can't, that's owned by the General Mills Corporation
Dammit, cause that was gonna be it too, shit
Yes
Yes Griffin
20 new shampoo
20 new shampoo, gotta try something
How about this, 20 new shampoo, gotta try something
Something's gotta change
The stakes, the stakes
20 new shampoo, something's gotta give
The stakes are low
20 tummy goo
What's that on your, what do you got on your tummy
The upset tummy crew
20 old U2, you just listened to Joshua Tree
That's good
20 no taboo
Oh Jesus Christ no
That could be problematic
20 no taboo
20 in review
It's the 20 that sucks isn't it
This decade's gonna suck to me
This millennium is gonna suck
This millennium, I'm gonna say 20, I want 30
Can you imagine if we were in the 30s
We could do like
Oh you could do like dirty
Dirty everything
Flirty
We gotta make it to at least the, we got dirty, flirty
Shirty
Squirty
Squirty tummy goo
I would give you that
Are we skipping
Squirty tummy goo
2023, off the rails
2023, take a pass
2023, looking forward
Can we go back to 20, 20, 20, 22, 22 deuces wild
What if we just called this year the deuce
Oh the double deuce
2022, ballet time
Let's see, let's get abstract
We have been recording for so long
Yeah
Okay
M-M-X-X-I-I
Mix it up
Is there
20 bigly chew
I feel like that's where we were
Wait
Bigly chew
20 breaking through
Emerge
But that doesn't feel, I can't get excited about that
Not as much as 20 kangaroo put it in the pouch
And we could do a mascot with that one
We could have like a mascot that's a kangaroo
We could call him Jack, but not that kangaroo Jack
No, a different one
20 talking to, sit down
You're fucked up
Sit down
We need to have a talk
Look he's talking to
Meme
Okay, we could just do this forever
You know what I'm saying?
Like we were very close with 20
I feel like 20 rendezvous, a night to remember
Is the most powerful one that I have experienced
That is the one that got the biggest reaction from me
That one gave me the chill bumps
What's it mean though?
I told you Griffin
No, you didn't
It's a night to remember
Make the most of it
What's it mean though?
It means that when a slow dance comes on
Get close
20 rendezvous certainly hits the lips good
A night to remember isn't any, it doesn't mean anything
Can we take 20 rendezvous and make it more like secret spy kind of feeling
But it's like if we do shows this year
Then 20 rendezvous and night to remember will be very powerful
Well that is a good point
But what about 20 rendezvous trading secrets?
What? No
No
20 rendezvous, there's been a murder
20 mummy crew, wrap it up
Now I already said that and make it about safe sex
And we just kind of get right past that
Yeah, just kind of
20 rendezvous
Get organized
Organize
Do it
Seize the means
20 rendezvous, stronger together
Seize the means of production
20 rendezvous, seize the means of production
Why would those two ideas have anything to do with each other?
Well you're rendezvousing
It's like this is the year where everybody unionizes
20 rendezvous
20 rendezvous, strengthen numbers
20 mummy crew, strengthen numbers
God, now I'm back to liking mummy crew
I know, 20 mummy crew
The ties that bind
20 mummy crew
The ties that bind is not like
Not everybody, I want it to be something everybody can do
Sometimes you make it too hard
It requires collaboration, that was our mistake in 2018
20 mummy crew, weigh your heart
20 busting through, oh yeah
Oh that's cool
Oh yeah
Aid
Cool aid
20 busting through
Oh yeah
Now that feels dangerously close to
We're hoping to be reimbursed
20 we've been sued
By the Kool-Aid Corporation
Okay, right now for me
It is between 20 rendezvous colon something
And 20 mummy crew colon something
20 what's this do?
Mysterious buttons
Now I just listed two options Justin
And what you did
Say yours again
20 rendezvous something
And 20 mummy crew something
Something
To me if we can find
It's like the last Tumblr to click in place
Is the thing that goes after them
Not the year name
Right
20 mummy
Is 20 mummy crew too close to Frankenstein team?
I'm actually fine with that
This is part of
In the iconography this does worry me
Because we did a lot of monster imagery
We did do a ton of monster imagery
But they didn't say
They weren't like oh we've already got Boo Berry
Can we do Count Chocula?
I'm actually liking 20 rendezvous more
Because it's like
It's got like sort of a sexy adult energy
Yes
We've never really done that before
Fuck it would be funny to just have a prom theme
Thank you
And not have it be aspirational at all
But just have it be like the vibe of the year
Can we do that?
Can we define the vibe of the year
And not necessarily the objective?
Sort of like you're saying like a tonal
A tonal motto and not
20 rendezvous a night in paradise
Because here's the thing
When we tell people what to do
One doesn't do anything materially to improve their lives
Or two they don't fucking do it
Yeah
How many monsters do you think came out of 2019?
Not a lot I would say
But if we say 20 rendezvous a night to remember
And then somebody
It just has that energy in the ecosystem
That could do something
I think 20 rendezvous is it
I think let's jazz it right now
To find the right tagline
Because I just don't think a night to remember is it
Okay
Okay listen
The etymology
If we can talk etymology
Sure
It comes from the French rendezvous
Which translates to present yourself
What about like 20 rendezvous show yourself
Like this is your
What's it called
Not a cotillion but like where you
A debutante ball
Yeah
That has some trouble
20 rendezvous
20 big debut
20 rendezvous have a ball
20 rendezvous
Now wait I'm actually kind of enjoying big debut
Well okay but we did big dog run
I don't think we can have big in the name of it again
Yeah
Okay
20 rendezvous
Time to conspire
Okay
20 rendezvous
Meet me meet me in the dark place
20 rendezvous adult home
20 rendezvous clandestine moments
20 rendezvous a secret kiss
20 rendezvous where the shade of the evening meets the secret
That's cool
20 rendezvous stolen moments
20 rendezvous a kiss for us
Oh yeah
20 rendezvous every kiss is a gift
20 rendezvous
A kiss in the shadows
I'm hating this the more we say it like this
No no no 20 rendezvous is good
I have a foothold now
An emotional and mental foothold on 20 rendezvous
We are going to say something in the next few minutes
As that tagline that's going to make us laugh
20 rendezvous stolen passion
No 20 rendezvous hidden passions
No I want it to be like not romantic
I don't want to be summing up romance for this
20 rendezvous safe tonight
20 rendezvous making memories
Did you say safe tonight?
Like the
Yeah the eagle eyed cherry
20 rendezvous fight the break of dawn
Oh I like that
I like that
Until the sun comes up
20 rendezvous until the sun comes up
That sounds like we're telling people to go out there and pork all night long
20 rendezvous all night long
20 rendezvous slapping bodies together
How about this 20 rendezvous the night is young
That embraces things and it's like we're just getting started
Yeah but it also is very low pressure it could be like should we start this puzzle
The night is young
I think we have time to finish this puzzle of three kittens playing in a basket full of yarn
It's got to be something about the night huh
It feels like it because no one's like hey do you want to have a coffee rendezvous
That's not what they say Griffin
Oh the twilight meetings twilight passion
20 rendezvous meet me in Vienna
Oh we'll always have Vienna
20 rendezvous remember Fiji
What about
What about and just imagine it in your head before you start generating
Don't just wait for your turn to talk really think about this okay
20 rendezvous fancy night
I like that I like that
20 rendezvous like that's these that is the concept we're trying to get across is a fancy night
So why not just say 20 rendezvous colon fancy night
A night of fancy
A night for fancy
You're you just one of just I was letting you have room to breathe and you had to iterate
20 rendezvous a night for fancy folk
A fancy night
What about 20 rendezvous I haven't seen Marcus in years
There's a story to it now
20 rendezvous a night to remember is is is I mean
20 rendezvous there's only tonight
20 rendezvous a fancy fantasy fantasy
Fancy takes flight
20 rendezvous fancy takes
20 rendezvous fancy takes flight
Because that could mean like things that has been like you just you're fancy like you
Like you whatever catches your fancy like you let it take flight
That's good in so many ways juice because it could mean like fancy takes flight is nothing
It's a new concept that kind of sounds like flight of fancy
And so when you say it that's not that he's saying like just like live your dream
Skip like live the dreamscape realize realize the dream right
But it could also mean like let's have a let's have a nice dinner tonight
Patricia fancy takes flight fancy takes fancy takes flight now in let's call
Can we call it?
I want us to just one last thing
I want us to imagine a conversation that we are having in a show where we would say
To confirm a thought we had just said like a man 20 rendezvous
Fancy takes flight as a as a as a thing that could like confirm what we think
I think then you could say like well that fancy flying now like I think it's more of like
Like I was the fancy takes flight to me is like if you've got a win
This is 20 rendezvous your fancy takes flight let your fancy take flight is 20 rendezvous
Rendezvous with you. What was the French again presenting yourself presenting your 20 rendezvous
Fancy takes flight
I like Griffin you said in a really wonderful emphatic way just then I just like fancy takes flight
Fancy takes flight takes flight. Come on
This is the year in which fancy takes flight
It's 20 rendezvous man. All right, call it. That's it 20 rendezvous
Fancy takes flight. Fuck. Holy shit. I feel so bad for Rachel having to edit this episode
No, no, she won't have to test it. I think it should be can I say I think it should be
No, God, no. Oh my God. Okay. How on earth I have to go pick up
How did this go so long? I have to go pick up my daughter in school. Let's wrap it up in 30 seconds
Okay, really quick. If you have HBO Max we're on an episode of fungis. It's called too many grandpas
It's in season three. I think you're it's if you like us and you hung in this far
You will enjoy this episode fungis is a very very good show and I'm really proud of the work that we did in this episode
It's very fun. It's a great showpiece for mr. Travis McElroy
We're all in it and it's really fun. And one of the grandpas is named Glimph, but it's not
We have merch at mcrormerch.com new pin of the month. Everybody has a night for me through see which sales for which benefit the center for reproductive rights
We have guppies want me blink sharks fear me sticker
There's a ton of stuff on mcrormerch.com and thank you to montaigne for these for our theme song
My life is better with you and thanks for making some fun. And here's a final thank you to Rachel our editor
Thank you to Rachel our editor for doing the Lord's work on this one. Here's finally Yahoo
Hey, it is sent in by the rock and it was asked by Jeremy
From the Pearl Jam song and Jeremy from the Pearl Jam song asks
Hey, does is there a toilet blue that is that you can play fortnight on blip blip blip blip
Okay, that's gonna difference my name's just about you know, I'm Travis McElroy. I'm Griffin McElroy and as always
Kiss your dad scrub lips
You
Maximum fun org comedy and culture artists owned audience supported