Please welcome to the stage your max fun favorites. My brother my brother and me
Don't get it twisted this rap shit is my
Fuck what you heard. It's what you hear it
Listen it's what you hear it listen. It's what you hear it listen
The McElroy Brothers
Don't give it to ya. Fuck wait for you to get it on your own.
Go deliver till ya knock knock open up the door it's real
With the non stop pop pop I'm stainless steel
Go hard getting busy with it
The McElroy Brothers
Got such a good heart that
Make a mother fuckin' wonder if you dead. Damn right
The McElroy Brothers
I was worried it would break the flow of the song
But it sounds super natural
I think it sounds better
Girl Talk actually got in touch with me
Like teach me your secrets
Hi everybody
Is it okay if I lead things off?
Wow okay. Sorry but
I just wanted to bring up before we started
Because it would be a smooth transition
Three different people have come up to me this weekend
And told me that they had horrible dreams about me
So
If anyone can lend any specificity
To the terrible way I'm apparently about to die
So I can look out for it
Omen's importance
You can introduce us now
Hello welcome to my brother and my brother and me
An advice show for the modern era
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy
And I'm your middle brother Travis McElroy
I'm your baby brother Griffin McElroy
If you've never listened to our show shame on you
Yeah
This is an advice show where we help people
We have been here at Mc...
Well hold on
I have a PowerPoint presentation I've prepared
To help this guy...
Fucking brace your asses
This was my first PowerPoint presentation
But I think I really nailed it. Here we go
Okay
Now
Is that
Helvetica?
It's a nice tasteful Helvetica I think
Some nerdlinger here probably knows what it is
Come on
There we go
One nerdlinger was a conservative estimate
Yeah
No smokers
Fourteen thot experts
That's MaxFunCon
So we uh
Did something funny happen to
Were we going to talk about something? I forget
Funny shit happens at camp all the time
Yeah
How has everybody
Else's MaxFun been so far?
MaxFun
That's easy
Raise your hand if you forged
A lifelong friendship this weekend
Lifelong friendships?
That's a lot
That's pretty good
I saw some people not raise their hands which bums me out more than
You have like three hours
For our radio listeners I would say like 90% of the people
Raised their hands but that 10% was like ah come on guys
There was probably a moment where somebody
Raised their hand expecting the person next to them to raise their hand
You didn't
We didn't it seemed
I thought okay
Um
Do you think people get like friendship
Desperate at the end of the party like I drove
All the way up this fucking mountain
It's like last call
I'm not leaving this party at midnight until I find
Someone to be my best friend forever
We wanted to mention
Before we leave the camp
Chat segment of our show
The extended well thought out camp
Chat segment
We will be doing some questions from you the audience
In the second half of our program
So try to think of something
That we can help you with
Don't be a bummer
Nope
Keep it light, keep it fun
And make sure that we remain the center of attention
Did nothing
Did nothing talk worthy
Happen to you guys this weekend camp wise
The only fun moment I had
No
My favorite moment so far
Was Friday night
I was hanging out and I saw this gentleman
Who I was just amazed he was so funny
And I was like you know he should be a comedian
And it was Kyle Kinane
Um
And I did not realize that until Saturday
And I'm just really glad I didn't
Walk up to him like hey kid
Keep those stars in your eyes
I see something raw in you
Something I can mold
I got a pocket
It's a real launching point
We can make you a star
Are we able
To talk
Cause there's this ubiquitous thing that I feel like
Everybody experiences at Max Fun Con
Um
But it involves regularity
So to speak
No I don't want to talk
Is anybody else deucing like a rock star
Like it's your full time job
Is it the altitude
I honestly don't know
What is going on
I can overrule this hold on wait I can save us all
Press the button that we can't
Ah camp is gone
So we were at if you want to discuss it more
Come find me after the show and we'll talk about poop all day
You won't find him
He'll be in the bathroom
So we stopped at
LA Hotspot
Roscoe's Chicken and Waffles
The Englewood location
We stopped at the authentic one near LAX
I'm not sure they all seem
Pretty authentic to me
So we ate a big meal and then as we were leaving
We spotted this flyer
Griffin do you still have it with you
I do I don't want to hold up the unsavory parts of it
I'm sure you LA locals
Read it every week you're all
Subscribers
It's LAXpress it's a
Massage guide
It's a massage guide it's what they advertise
Can you fold that half
So yeah
There's a woman in it and she's
We don't want that
We don't want to talk about that because it's gross
The whole flyer is grody
There are full length
Features that are just ripe with
Grossness but there are a few
Pretty amazing things in it
Now keep in mind every page of
This flyer is filled
To the brim with
In
Invitations
Sort of enticements
To the flesh
Honey pots of
Sexual delight for money
Basically except for
These pages
First of all there is a
Full page the entire
The entire rear page
Is dedicated to four movie
Reviews for this massage
Guides in house
Movie critic
I assume
That's a gig you work your way up
To spoiler alert he hated
All four movies
Where's the nudity
I think there's probably nudity
In at least two of these movies
So that's the first page
It gets weirder from here
There's a picture of Brad Pitt
The story above this is not about Brad Pitt
It's about people you can have sex with
In the area that you live
And thank god that right up in the top corner
They've labeled it just in case
Who
This guy's going places
And the piece de resistance
Yeah I actually just wanted to point out
There is an ad on the adjacent page
That is advertising women as silky
Which I did not know
Seems more like a fabric softener
Ad but here
Okay so here's the last one
This is not bullshit this is just one of the pages
So what we're working with
Are audio fans
Our listeners at home are probably just like
It's a butthole it's definitely a butthole
I know I've listened to this show before
It's a ghost horse butthole something
This is Mackenzie
Again still like listeners at home
Like oh man oh no
What's wrong with Mackenzie
It is a
We are talking about a kitten
Sweet precious and I would say
Appropriately horrified
Kitten
This is an advertisement for a local
Animal shelter
Looking to get rid of this cat
Which seems like the most inhumane
Thing ever because this is the
Grossest this is
The grossest publication
Diagram of people who are going yeah I definitely
Want to have some sex and also I'm looking
To adopt a kitten
It's just one circle that says lonely
So anyway
That was the flyer that we found it's time
To get into the vice portion of our program
This is our wheel wheel wheel house I guess
This is where this and talking about
Porn advertisements
Actually that is actually kind of
Our wheelhouse also thanks
So
Here's our first question submitted to us by
A reader earlier
Today I bought lunch at a local bakery
And as an impulse purchase I bought a
York peppermint patty at the register
However despite paying for the candy I accidentally
Walked out without taking the snack
Out of the jar what's worse
I didn't remember that I had abandoned the candy
Until long after the deli had closed
Meaning that if I want to retrieve
The patty I actually have to go back
A full business day later and
Embarrassingly explain my mistake
What is the protocol in these
Situations do I return
Tomorrow and let them know about my
Error or is this a dollar I'm simply
Not going to get back that's from snackless
In San Francisco let me tell you
One thing I know for sure you're getting that
Fucking patty
We are going to get through this
Together
This is a this is a great opportunity
I think to steal
Because you can steal with a clean
Conscious it's yours it's just living
Without the peppermint patties
He did pay he exchanged currency
For goods and services
He just put it on layaway
I got the remaining 37 cents
I'm ready to get the sensation
What if that was this dude's steez
In that he just sort of went around
His town and just sort of
Planted seeds of like next
Time he's in this convenience store
He can be like I need to
You know get a pack of cigarettes and also
You owe me one York peppermint patty that I did
Purchase a while ago and then he has a little surprise
Treaty wasn't expecting review the security
Get the security camera
I did pay for this
That's going to be hard to convince him
To give you that though
Because he's not going to remember your face
There's people in there trying to scam
York peppermint patties all the time
I know how this
I know that you probably get this a lot
But I want to get the sensation
And I did pay for the sensation so just
Give me the patty already you think it's a big patty
These are the big ones one of the small ones
For a dollar you're getting a full
Size patty right one would hope
There's not a joke here
I'm really would like economy
You guys the economy
The joke
We're doing a little bit more observational stuff
This time yeah we're working
Out some new material on this supportive
Crowd you
Want to Yahoo yeah I do thought there'd be more
Meat on the peppermint patty bone yeah me too
I thought it would be funnier for longer but no
So when you guys ever
How do York peppermint patty you guys
Know I'm talking about right behind alley
So we actually have
Another resource for people
That we help
From the Yahoo answers service
Where people submit
Nigh anonymously submit questions
And then we find them
And then we help them whether they
Want it or not so Griffin what's our
What's our first this
Answer was asked by Yahoo answers user Gerald
Who
Asks just Gerald is funny
I guess it is
Context that he's a Yahoo answers user
Paints it paints a real nice picture
Gerald asks
Is it safe to drink my brother's sea monkeys
I
Told
My brother that if he doesn't get back my vintage
Motley Crue t-shirt I got from my uncle by today
I was going to drink his sea monkeys
But he didn't believe me and he didn't
Give it back yet and said he won't
I think I should stand my ground and drink them
But I don't want to die or catch a disease
Or something
You
That I like that stick
To it of this though that's the kind of that's
The kind of gumption this nation was built on
I don't want to drink your weird babies
In water but I'm going to
I want that shirt
He's not going to
Get the shirt back to ultimate we're talking about
We're talking about punitive damage I
Think if you watch a man
Drink your water family
Right in front of you
That is a man who is capable of anything and you will
Give him whatever he wants
I have a particular set of
Skills actually just one it's drinking
Your babies especially
If you don't do it all at once if you just like
Slowly sip and go I'll keep going
I love this
Gerald has informed
Us of what his brother's hierarchy
Of favorite shit that he owns
Is and apparently
At the top of that is a Motley Crue
T-shirt that he is not willing to part with under any
Circumstances and then right behind
That is his sea monkeys and
It's like that dude is beyond punishment
Isn't he?
He's like he's too sad
To fail at that point
I think brother of Gerald has made
A serious miscalculation just
Strategically because he has a pretty clear
Vulnerability what with those pets
And a big tank of water that's made of plastic
I mean you don't even need a brother to drink those
A stiff wind and your whole sea monkey
Or just the passage of like
Six days because that's really all those guys
Have in them. Some of them get very full
That's where shrimp come from. They have bad hearts
Sea monkeys have bad hearts
It's all the inbreeding. Yeah it's true
That's real look it up
What else are they gonna fucking do? They're not gonna
They can't like get out. They can't hold down a job
Maybe it's the best if he does
Drink the sea monkeys. Okay now wait
They would be killed I presume by the stomach
Acid right? Oh god you better
Hope so. Yeah. Or else
You're gonna have a fucking inner space scenario
Happening. You are gonna have an
Inner space on your hands
That's what happens
In that movie. Yeah yeah
Martin Short drinks some
Baby prawns and Dennis Quays like
Don't worry I got this
I'll take him out buddy. Don't worry
I got this prawns. This is inner space 2 where he
Doesn't shrink down. It's a very
He's normal size
Wait okay hold on wait
Are you saying
Martin Short
Full grown Martin Short in inner space
Is
Has a full sized Dennis Quaid
Okay we'd have to write
Some sort of sci-fi in the script because we'd have
To shrink Dennis by at least
25 percent. Or
Grow Martin Short. Exactly
Martin Tall
Stupid
Low hanging fruit
Idiot
Is that as bad as it's gonna
Get today. God Christ let's
Hope so
I
I think it's safe. I just don't think that
You don't get your shirt back
And you're queasy. And you're both gonna
Know that that happened for the rest of your life
You'll always be able to. That's a thing. Yeah and
You're gonna have sea monkeys controlling you from the inside
That's terrible. It'll be like inner space
You know. Hey if you guys
Inner space jokes
How about the next question Jeff. Okay
Hello brothers
McElroy. This one is actually submitted by
Somebody who is in the audience assuming
They are not hungover or dead
Hello brothers McElroy are you
Having fun at Mac's Fun Con? Me too
This was written before
Mac's Fun Con right? This was before Mac's Fun Con so this is
A big leap
What should I name my car?
It is a 2011 Mazda 2
Hatchback in black. It's very
Cute. I thought I could
Go for a while without naming this car when I first got
It but I've had some bad luck in the first year of my ownership
Broken windshield in the door, punctured
Tire while driving on the highway, broke up with my boyfriend
So I think not
I didn't
Write that. So I think
Not naming the car might have something to do with this
If it helps I name my last
Car Sally Ride
Sincerely
Lisa W. Lisa W are you
With us today? Okay well we'll do our best
Are you blaming all of your bad
Luck on the car? You really think it's the car's
Fault?
Is it a boy car or a girl car?
You didn't ask?
You gotta check, look at the car fact
When it talks
I always wondered what those were for apparently
It's for having your car sexed
What color is it?
Black. That helps. Hatchback
Call it Hatch Black
That's not a good name
What?
Griffin what have you
Have you had a car that you've named in the past?
My 2006
Toyota Matrix. I call it
Trixie because Trix is like in it
It's not funny but
I just answered the question you asked me on stage
Can you call the car
Jason Mrozda and then
Cause those words
Are almost the same
That's actually not bad
How do you feel about Jason Mrozda?
That's pretty good. Hold on
Do you love the music of Jason Mrozda?
Can you learn to?
Can you open your heart
To Jason Mrozda and let him
Just sidle on in?
You gotta jam a cassette
Cause I assume that your 2011
Your car that was produced in 2011 has a cassette
Jam a Mrozda cassette in there
And then get like a butter knife and then
Really wedge it in there and then that'll be like
The permanent soundtrack for Jason Mrozda
It's a super good idea
I worked at a Borders that was exactly like that
24 hours a day
That's not a joke
How about a Yahoo? Yeah sure
Oh this will be interesting if the call and
Response works out
This one was sent in by Ira Ray
Are you Ira Ray?
Wow it works
That is gratifying
It was by Yahoo Answers user
Sammy who asks
What are some simple mysteries that I can solve?
Be serious
My dad said to start
It's misspelled start but it's hard
To pronounce it
Small and build my way up to big mysteries
Like spirits in houses, hauntings, etc
I need to know
Some simple cases, please and thank you
One of the more mannerly Yahoo Answers
Yeah I like that
Don't start with Encyclopedia Brown
Those were way hard for me still
I cracked one open recently
I'm 32 now, these should be
I'm cut to 20 minutes later
The first Battle of Bull Run couldn't have been this
Because the sword said on that
Love those books
Didn't make me any better
At mysteries though
I think your parents have to plan the mysteries for you
I don't know how old this person is
I hope not too old
You gotta get an early start on the mystery game
It's like being a gymnast
You can't start young
What could start as a small mystery
Could unfurl to be like
Gangland violence
Drug trade
Just like a national treasure
He's trying to find the constitution
And then it turns into a whole thing
Starts out with him doing a tricky sudoku
And by the end of it he's just wrapped up
In a fucking John Voight shoot em up
That is the problem
If you've ever read any
Mystery, it always starts
With what appears to be a simple mystery
I don't think you can definitively say
This is gonna pan out
To be very simple
Because what if it's like that sweater
You start pulling that yarn and then it's just
There's a whole case here
Then you have the mystery of the unraveled sweater
Your mom is super pissed off
That her sweater is fucking gone
And she's like here's a mystery
Mystery solved
That was simple
Let me look at some clues
It's a pretty good clue
When we were little
When we were kids
When we were smaller
I don't think Griffin was born yet
Can we not tell the story then
This is BGM
Before Griffin McElroy
Travis and I had
Discovered food coloring
So we filled
Every drink we could get
Our hands on with food coloring
And then we decided
To see what effect it would have on the carpets
And then
And then our mom came down
And I just
Wanted to tell this story because that seems like a pretty
Easy mystery for her to solve
So if you could set that up for him
Just put some food coloring on your mouth and on the couch
And then sit there and wait
And I think that as his parents
It would be pretty easy
That was also just a really good bit for the family
Circus fans in the audience
Not me
People who don't like all the blue humor we usually do
And just want some Dennis the Menace-esque
I don't think there's anything wrong with being
Tasteful for a few minutes
I've been pushing to get us to be a little
Cleaner and I think that was a great start
What did you guys think?
We don't
That was muted
That was definitely muted
You want to do another question
It's actually my turn
Oh wait
Don't worry I was
Not allowed to do that
Yeah
No sad libs
No
It's the worst
Whoa
You guys know I can't improv
I can't just make it up
There's just a story
When you improv mad libs it's just shouting
It's time
For a break for some farm wisdom
Farm wisdom
Here's a song that I just wrote
I think he just did the Hot Pockets
Farm wisdom
It's a song that I just wrote
Come on and get yourself a goat
There's two more verses in there
In that beautiful head of yours
Maybe not
Farm wisdom
This comes from
Here's a bit of wisdom
If you see a skunk or possum
During the day or any nocturnal creature
You shouldn't approach it
It usually means that there's something wrong with them
And that they're sick
That sickness is usually rabies
Farm wisdom
Here's a song that I just wrote
In what scenario at any time of day do you see a skunk or a possum
Like oh I gotta get up on that
Hey little guy let me approach you
Don't worry it's nighttime
This is totally cool
I'm gonna adopt you and teach you to pick pockets
Come hang out with me
The only way I approach a skunk is if there is a larger skunk behind me
That's it, that's all
You guys ever seen a raccoon
Like in real life?
Yeah they're dicks
There was one on our balcony once
Not a joke
Obviously
Clearly not a joke
How about an actual question
Okay let me actually
Let's help somebody for once
My cowork and I have been dating for the last year
You wanna start over?
Can you edit that not Griffin
All of you
Up here
And set that out
My coworker and I have been dating for the last year
Since I don't answer to him
And he doesn't answer to me
There is no rule in it
However we've done our best to keep it on the DL
To avoid gossip
Recently when we were put
When we put in matching vacation requests
My manager put two and two together
And figured it out
My question is does there need to be
An I know you know conversation
If so how do I broach the subject
Of our not so new relationship to reassure her
She hasn't been duped
And reiterate my good work ethic
And loyalty to her
And the company that's from Exposed
Wait so the fear here is that the manager
Found out and went why didn't you tell me
I'm so hurt
I thought we were close
We go to Margarita Tuesdays every week
You gotta not do it at all
Is the right answer
Because it's not her fucking business
I guess it is
It is her business
Literally it's her business
Finances and profit margins
I think one of my rules is
If you want to
Convince someone that you haven't been
Hiding something from them
The time to tell them is not
After they discover
That is a tough
Sell if you can pull that off
This is apparently a simple mystery
That somebody can solve
There you go
Here's the thing
You are just going to deflate
Your boss if you come out and tell her straight up
Because either she's very satisfied
With herself that she fucking cracked
This da Vinci code
This sexy sexy da Vinci code that's going on
Right under her nose
It's going to diminish the sexiness
Of the whole thing to be like
Yeah we are together
And it's not a sexy dark sexy secret
Say sexy more
I'll get to it
I want to space him out
I mean they have to know
You have to tell them
But I do think it sets up an unrealistic
I don't have an end of the sentence
Is there a way you can say it
That acknowledges the fact that they already know
That you are dead
Say oh yeah we are going on vacation together
We are brother and sister
And we have been hiding it
From you all this time
We are related this whole time
We are the same person
Surprise
You are missing the obvious answer
That doesn't sound like us
I know you have to admit it to everyone
Come clean but then stage a big fight and break up
Re-hide the secret
Double back on your secret
It's sexy again
Maybe this time you invite another person
And just keep growing the sexy
It got weird
I got halfway through that sentence
No no no no
It's too late
My new thing is
This is a secret improv
You can take this one if you want
If you don't have a joke
Just say you don't have one
And then wait
Another joke will find its way
Onto your path
In a very organic manner
Sometimes I start a sentence thinking I have a joke
And I realize I'm just saying
Literally the next word
Conjunction
Article
Is there a subject coming up?
Just keep the ball up in the air
Mr. Conjunction fuck it
Roll with the punches
How about another yahoo?
Yeah sounds good
This one was sent in by Ira Ray
No I don't do it twice
Yeah
It's by yahoo answers user
Wewalkalone
Who asks
You are sitting
Registering for yahoo answers
You know what's sad?
Is that the O in alone
Is like a special character
It's like the O with the slash through
Like a no smoking sign
I don't know what that's called or what its purpose is
Tilde
It's an interior tilde
Which intimates that
Somebody else already registered
Wewalkalone
I bet there's probably a few variations on that throughout
Wewalkalone asks
How do you ask a girl out to breakfast
Without it sounding like you want a one night stand?
This is
This is a tricky needle to thread
Additional details
She loves waffles
And basically most breakfast foods
Is that any additional details?
Yeah that's it
Okay so that does tell you something about our character
I mean you could go the blunt approach
And say I want you to have waffles but not sex
That's how actually I order it
I hop every time
Me? I'm going to have
I don't look so good
I'm so hungry we waited a long time
I'm going to have waffles but not sex
Please do not try to have sex with me
Keep it under your apron darling
Is he wearing
And also some berries
And no sex
Some sex, some light sex
This is my fourth time at IHOP
I'm willing to entertain it
Do you still have the bottomless sex?
The bottomless sex?
Wait
I get it
Okay
If this guy is worried
That she is going to
Assume that post breakfast
He is going to want to have sex with her
That it seems like a fallacious
Thing to be worried about
Because nobody has ever
Eaten waffles and then been like
I feel like ready to get down
People in this room are fucking chock full
Of cheese blintzes, nobody's looking around like
Who's going to be my 11 o'clock hook up?
I wish I was napping
I wish these three brothers would be quiet so I could take a
Theater nap
Griffin actually wouldn't let us
Me and Travis have cheese blintzes
He said we wouldn't be funny if we ate those
He said we'd be too full
This is not a joke
Griffin has gotten super protective of my diet
The whole time I've been here
He's been really demonstrative
Justin kept getting
I don't want to put you on fire
Justin kept getting salads
And then just like
Eating around them in such a perfect manner
The salad would sit unmolested
Like in the perfect shape that he put it
On the plate
And he even addressed the fact like
Maybe next time salad
I thought about a salad
I want to be the sort of
I look around
I look around at everybody here and everybody's getting salad
Like they like it and I just think I want to be
I want to be where the people are
Eating that salad
And seeming to enjoy it
People are getting salad
With their own volition
Like it has a flavor that they like
And I don't know how to process it
So I just get some salad and then I get embarrassed
Because I eat everything else because it all tastes better than salad
You're so much of a salad
Salad noob Mario
But you know you don't walk back with the salad on your plate
To throw it away and then go we tried
He's wasting it
So that's good
He thinks oh that's salad that somebody else doesn't have to eat
You're welcome the rest of the world
Oh god I've been waiting
I hope the salad bowl will be empty
Those stars
Actually aligned yesterday there was no salad
Gotta rough up
The first time I got no
I did not realize
Here's my salad in expertise
I got no dressing
So just a big pile of
Leaves and then
The next time I grabbed
Something that looked like dressing and was
Olive oil so I just kind of coated it
I wondered why you were doing that
I don't know what dressing is
You were doing like a fancy flourish
Like a subway sandwich artist and I was like what are you
That's not for that
For a time I tried to get into salad
At restaurants my lovely wife
Can attest to this I tried to get into salads
At restaurants by asking them to bring
A side of pizza sauce
What was the illusion that you were
Chasing there like it's
Tomatoes
Did any waiter ever act like that was
Something anyone else had ever done
Oh yeah pizza salad
That's actually right there on your sides
Is it possible for you to serve the salad in like a
Bread bowl but like just flat and triangular
And like if you want to melt some cheese on there
And let's get a light on the leaves
You can I want pizza
Can the leaves be from a pepperoni tree
Anyway Justin didn't eat a salad and I had to develop
A system of reward points that he could
Exchange for dessert
I would be eating a bite of salad
And Griffin would say I
That looks like about 80 cookie points
You need 100 cookie points to get a cookie
So you can either have 8 tenths
Of a cookie now or you can finish the last
Two bites of your salad
I'm 32 years old and it worked
On me like a child
God
Help me if I didn't just alright come on
Salad you don't like me and I
Don't like you let's finish this
So this is the part of the show
Where we are
Going to take questions from the
Audience wait it hasn't started yet
Sorry hold on
This is the part of the show where we will
Take questions from the audience
Just remember our original
Disclaimers how are we going to do this because all
We have now is a mic and a chair
I don't want
I don't want him to share the spotlight
Can you guys like get the chair but put it
On the ground
Can somebody
Who has I guess we will just
Raise your hands
Is your question a bummer
Is it a bummer
How can we help
Hey
Just take the stage
Take the stage
What's your name
My name is Greg from Omaha
And I have
I have a question
It's going to start bummer it gets better
God damn it Greg
Greg what did we say
Is it going to have a
Bummery finish no no no
Hopefully no
So about eight months ago
I got out of a long term
Relationship
How long term
Nine years
Listen
Pull it out of the fire Greg
I was I was I was
Cheated on
Dumped for another person Son of a bitch
Come on Greg
Colleague and a colleague
In the community I work in
Since then total like
Recovery sandwich situation
Named it up
And
Like Vietnam
Like ex-girlfriends in the trees
Come on
Two promotions dating again
Yeah
Greg but anytime I hang out with
That like that group of people
The like fellow colleagues in my field
That know about that
Situation I feel like I get
Looked at like I'm like a kicked puppy
I want to know how I can shake
That Greg I got bad news
For you it was a bummer
A hundred percent fucking
Start beginning middle and
I literally said the phrase a kicked
Puppy every fucking sentence had
An element a taste of bummerness in it
Somewhere I look we learned about pie
Making yesterday and they said you have to have butter
All through the crust and you had bummer all
Through the question the bummer
Melts to leave flakiness
You
Could just walk into the room go I'm good
Yeah that's what people who
Are good always say
It is disheveled
And it's bedraggled as you can possibly
Look and walk in the room I'm doing
Guys guys hey
Don't cry for Greg don't look at me like that
Yeah I'm good
All for that
Without anybody asking that's important
You got to lead with hey I'm good
I'm doing fine hey why
Do you want to shake it why don't you parlay it
You get parlayed in one
A promotion maybe
He's already done that twice
Okay so you've been you're already making it work for you
For your promotion no I'm sure you're very
Talented at what you do yeah it was a pity promotion
Yeah nice
That's good Greg that's the way to pick up our
Spirits yeah now you're
Guilting us now it's about you
It's because of excellence yeah there
In your field what field is it
Maybe we can find some humor in there
It's got to be somewhere right
I teach poetry and theater okay
Okay what okay
If I may what
Emotions are there in that job
They give you more kids
There's ten more you're doing
This year you get a desk
Greg I think
That you you I can
Understand why you think that the good news
I think is that people
Will always think about
Others a lot less than they think about
Themselves so if you
Just do Greg
Just do Greg for
A few more weeks I think how long
Was the relationship nine years
Okay three more weeks
Do Greg three more
Weeks and people will
Inevitably move on to their own problems
They cannot keep in their head
Actual facts about other humans that
Long they have to just let it slip out so they can
Remember the lyrics to the new
Song
They're hard to memorize because they're not
English
Greg
Yeah yeah so patience
Patience Greg
This too shall pass
Like okay go said
Should I do the dance from that video you definitely
Should not do that
Thanks Greg
Round of applause for Greg he really put himself
Out there even though we expressly
Asked him from doing so
Anybody
Who's hand
Went up first I'm terrible at this yeah
Yes we got time for everybody I'm going to help everyone
In this room it's not like we have to go anywhere
I'm going to break these fishes and loaves up where
I was going to Jesse how much would it cost us to lock
Down Lake Arrowhead for another day
Just he's not going to answer that
Probably an astronaut that's fair that's good
Good instinct hi what's your name
So I'm Laura hi Laura
From the Midwest I hide
The Midwest all of it well most
Of it she's a rambler
It's true Ohio
Iowa Michigan
That's it you touched you touched
Them all what's your what's your what's your question
So my question is if you're
Cheap and you say don't want
To check your baggage how might
You get your rocket lube past
Security
I'll tell you no no no
This is great because this is a universal
Question everyone's worried about right now
Because you're not leaving it here
You finally got
Lube without having to buy it from a store
You're never
Letting it go this is the loophole
Or making it
Making it yourself out of coconut
Oil
You don't really have to make anything you just
Use the coconut
You go to Target and you buy
The travel pack of empty
Three ounce bottles and then you just split
It into multiple three ounce bottles
And then you actually have to say I'm putting lube
In these and then you line them
Up on your nightstand so when people come in
You'd be like this is my collection
There's single server or you could do
Like the bandolero of just lube
Packets
Lube of sexual
Lube this is
Of a lubricant that one uses during
Love making this is gonna be gross
Do we know if the bottle is under
Like do we know if the bottle is
Under over three point six ounces
Yeah it's four ounces
Okay first off you gotta drink some
This is gonna be
Simultaneously gross and too forward
To bring up to a stranger but if you are
Going to hide it in a cavity it will be
Super easy to do so
Cause you have what you
Have what you need to do that
And the problem with the bottle itself
Is that you can't use that bottle
Because can you imagine
That TSA security screening guy
Dressed down by a superior just to be clear
We're keeping an eye out for
Terrorist threats and the bottle said
Rocket lube
Nothing set off any alarms there
That maybe it is right that's what you use
On the missile silo to make sure
That the rockets come out as soon as possible
Right through there
You could also just
Do it in little baggies do you have any like
Zip lock baggies she was cheap
She didn't want to buy things let's be clear
People answer the question
I don't think they let you just put loose fluid
And zip lock baggies and bring it on airplanes
I don't think you can
Fucking do a makeshift capri sun
And be like no no no it's cool
Maybe like soak a towel in it
And then wring it out when you get home
Haha that's great
The perfect crime
Is it though
Is it the right
The problem with any solution here is you have to be
Ready with an answer because you cannot
Go to the screener and they say
So what are these and you say well there's several
Small baggies of lube
I have many pistons at home
Which I need to keep
Working in their most efficient state
They're sex pistons
I hope we've helped
Yes thank you very much
Who else
Elliot come on up
Just complete silence
Through the just no talking
Namaste
Hi Elliot from London
So fancy
Hey Elliot what's your
What's your not bummer question
So I have a flatmate
He's a lovely lovely guy
Remate
I'm just translating for people I wasn't correcting
Let's have one non completely
Xenophobic show this year
Who's afraid of Xena
I've been sitting on that
Joke for three years
Oh god
So he's a
Lovely guy he's got a job just like I do
Same wage and all the rest of it but
It's like living with a
Toddler that has a career
In that he doesn't seem
To understand the concept of
You know cleanliness and
Not leaving marks all over the walls
And
Wait a minute are we dealing with a
Harold and the purple crayon situation
Is he imagineering
No he's sort of like
The grubby marks around light switches
And leaving stuff on camera
Holy shit
He's eating peanut butter with his hands
Why are you rooming with pig pen
The problem is I've known him
Since we were 12 and I can't
I can't sort of you know
Leave him in the lurch and stuff like that
Otherwise a lovely guy
I've tried every sort of pleasant conversation
That you can have with a lifelong best friend
Without this sort of thing
How do I get him to you know be an adult
You could try cookie points
Cookie points would be good
Bath time points I guess
Bath time vouchers
They serve bath time vouchers in this magazine
Ellie give me a sample like in the conversations
You've had with him what's the tenor of those
What's the general tone
Well they've ranged
Yeah right
But generally it's along the lines of like you know
If you clean things up now
It will be easier than cleaning them later
And I won't have to yell at you and try and be your mother
You don't use that tone though
I don't but that's what I'm thinking
Did he have like when you were growing up
Did he have a nickname like Grubby Hank
This one's on you dog
You don't live with Grubby Hank
You go out and hang out at bars with Grubby Hank
You don't bring him into your domicile
His nickname was Scruff as a child
Same principle
But the cleanliness thing wasn't the thing
Until I actually lived with him
Oh no he just had a beard when he was a child
Basically yeah
You gotta move
Don't move
I'm rethinking it I was rash
I'm sorry
I mean
You were his last shot you know that right
Like his parents done fucked it
Yeah that's done
You were his last shot at having a normal life
And you've gotta sit him down
And grab
Don't touch him
I was gonna say grab his face
And it's like oh is that jelly
Did you put jelly on your face
I keep little tubs of those
You know those alcohol hand washes around
Just because
At like a barbecue restaurant you just hold on
They're just everywhere
Let me tell you
People might not know this
I'm kind of a messy person
How the fuck would they know that
They don't live with you Travis
They know your fucking voice
They don't know your mannerisms
I'll post some pictures
We rarely leave in the sound of you
Tripping over a milk carton
The argument if you clean it now
It'll be easier than cleaning it later
Is false because cleaning it later
Is inherently easier because
It never comes
That's his entire attitude with everything in life
And I don't know
Have you considered leaning into it
Getting super dirty yourself
Getting on the British version of
Hoarders whatever it's called over there
Just shitting all over his bed
Don't shit on his bed
What the fuck
You gotta think about mass
And you gotta think about volume
Hoarding is a volume game
You wanna have stacks of shit
Not shit shit
And then the money that you get
From being on Hoarders
You can buy a maid or a nanny
I don't think they pay people to be on Hoarders
Yeah if you're on Hoarders
They pay you like a Hoarders stipend
Get like an appearance fee
They look at you and say
Don't spend it all on crackerjack paraphernalia
Boink
Do you think that the
Hoarders guardian angels that come in
They're just like oh yeah your shit's super fucked up
Later bye
Have fun with your whole situation here
I think a good twist on Hoarders
Would be if they left all their stuff together
In a specific location
And then gave them a clue
And then it turned into like the Amazing Race
You can get it all back
It's all waiting for you
Whatever you do make it fun
Round of applause
How we doing on time?
What?
We're doing good
Who else has a question?
Oh wait hold on
Let's do a Yahoo answer
Let's drop in and just
Remember my password
This Yahoo answer was
Sent in by Christa Whalen
Thank you Christa Whalen
It's by Yahoo answer's user Janine who asks
Financial aid at Hogwarts?
Does Hogwarts provide financial aid?
Or do I need to submit the wizard
Equivalent of the FAFSA?
So this raises some legitimate questions
I think if you don't have financial aid
At Hogwarts it's gonna create
Sort of like a class warfare
It's just a rich get more magical
You know situation
It's you gotta have financial
Like I imagine they never really touch on this
In the books or the movies
But I imagine it's an expensive institution
It's a fucking castle
Right
Most castle based schools require
A large sum of money
I'm gonna ask you guys a question
I've been wondering for a while
It's slightly off topic
Perfect
There has to be one Slytherin kid
Who's like cool
Who's like nice
Who's sitting there in the conference room
Just be like you guys are dicks
Harry's okay
The four house based system
Of Hogwarts
Creates it's own class warfare
In and of itself
You got the one percenters in Slytherin
You got the
I just don't know what the Hufflepuff people are up to
They're just a bunch of fat babies
That's all I can think of
When I think of Hufflepuff I just imagine fat babies
Waddling around doing magic
You know why are there only humans
Another terrific point
There are only humans going to Hogwarts
We know that this world is populated by several different races
Intelligent races
There are fucking centaurs in the fucking backyard
Like hey guys can we get some magic too
And it's like yeah that'll be 200
Currency
200,000
Knots
I think
Zenny
You're welcome
You know there was one ogre
There was one ogre kid that got admitted
And just like
Tried to pick up a beaker of magic
And smashed it in his hands
Nevermind I'll see myself out
I'll walk through the wall
I'll telecommute
I'll just go to Hogwarts online
Hogwarts online
Oh man what a bummer that would be
Like oh shit
There was a fucking
This crazy wild troll got out
The second wizarding war
You missed some shit man
No I was eating this hot pocket though
Gmail servers went down and I missed my final
It's like literal
Phoenix University
Cause magic
Alright let's help somebody else
Help you
I apologize for sweating through
The shirt I'm wearing
It's hot up in this comedy lodge
Are you apologizing to me? Yes specifically
Hi I'm Sarah
Hi Sarah I'm Justin
I just got a new job that's work from home
And I was wondering if you had any advice on
How to do that
Sister if you can figure it out
Let me know
Can you afford to hire six to eight people
To just be around you
I've been working out of my home
For
Four years now
Just my home
It's just me and my cats
And your wife
And my wife
Well no I mean during the day
I pay someone
I pay someone to clean the house
Just so I have visitors
FedEx man is my best friend
Get okay
And get your boss okay
With the fact that your first year
You're not going to do very good
You're going to do a super bad job
At your job
All the things you like are at your house
They're right there and most importantly
Your sleep zone
The place where you do all your sleeping at
Yeah it's a rough
It's a rough transition and it really did
Take me like a year and a half before I was
Meeting my quotas so to speak
Structure is really important
I know it seems like well done with pants
But you really
You got to set a pants schedule
You do have to set a pants schedule
There's a primordial gene inside of you that's like
I don't have pants on so just fuck it
Let's watch a whole season
Of the amazing race today
I can't even wear sweatpants
Because they send a signal
To my brain that's like take it easy brother
That song 5 o'clock
Somewhere is about me putting on sweatpants actually
Love his music
So do bad for a year wear pants
I'm not saying do bad for a year
I'm saying you have no other option
It's a really tough transition
What do you do?
No that's fine actually
My employer is here too
Oh fuck
I always knew someday
The advice would come back
Circus closed
What is your job?
So I work for Make That Thing
Which is a subsidiary of Topataco
Okay
I imagine that most people there
Work from home unless there's a
Is there a centralized office for
There is but it's in another state
From the one I live in
Are there a lot of remote employees
Or are you more or less
Will they notice that you're
Not wearing pants?
They haven't noticed yet
Nice
There's a robot
That's at the hospital in my town
That has a
This is the beginning of my favorite
Tom Waits song
There's a robot
That lives in the hospital
Near my town
There's a robot that lives
In the hospital near my town
And he has a
He has a TV screen
On his face that is his face
That's his face and there's a doctor
I'm not making
I'm so excited to see where you go with this
This isn't a joke
It was on a commercial I saw
There's a
There's a doctor that lives
The doctor's on the TV
And he rolls into your room
And he has robot arms
And everything is a robot except his face
It's still a robot
It's a remote robot face Justin
You know it's not his actual
It's not his actual face
Pulled in a ghastly manner
Over
Does he have a pill dispenser?
No? I made that up
It's like a
It's like a gashapon machine
You put in a quarter and maybe you get the
Maybe you get the treatment you need
So he does have a pill dispenser
I'll edit that out when she said that he doesn't
And you could
I guess what I'm saying is maybe do that
Which part?
Good question
That is going to be
I imagine there's a lot of pranksters in that office
And when you're not there to fend those pranksters off
And all you have are robot appendages
Oh yeah they're going to TP you
And you won't realize it because you only have the one camera
Guys be honest
Am I covered in toilet paper right now?
You will have robot
Which model of robot you get
If you get a terminator robot
Then what?
Is there a rest of the goof?
No that would be terrific
Dangerous and kind of scary
What about a Johnny 5 robot?
What about an iron giant? How big is the office?
That would work
It's a fucking big office
You guys are doing pretty great
Vacation request
Softball sign ups in the break room
Aye supervisor
Supervisor
I'm going to start crying
I'm going to cry too
He just wants to be a hero
He just wants to be in charge of some employees
Did any of that help?
Oh it was great
No you fucking dropped the mic
That was a baller move
Put DMX back on
Play it off
I think we have time for maybe one more
One more person needs help
That's Joe Dan right here
Come up to the stage
Quicker
I like that
Cut across
Oh flavor
I like your style Dan
What's your name?
Holy shit that was amazing
How did you?
Raise your hand if your name is Dan here
So your odds were pretty good
Bad
All the smokers are Dan
I'm smoker Dan
My friends call me
What's your story smoker Dan?
I recently moved in with a friend of mine
Is he really dirty?
Because we just did this one
Actually I was going to ask a question related to that
Because I'm on vacation
And I don't know how to keep my house clean
When I'm not there
Because he doesn't do it when I am there
But no that wasn't
We've done that
Wow I like this pivot
We should learn how to do this
Days after moving in
He had a falling out
With all of our mutual friends
Can I ask what he did?
Was it so much of a dick move
That you don't even want to
I have no idea
It's a simple mystery
Sounds actually pretty
If only you could ask somebody
There has to be some material witness
Time to look for clues
The way he says it
It was the thing
That finally happened
I don't know what the thing is
My question was really
How do I go about maintaining those
Other relationships
Dan there is no reality in which we can answer this
Without more insight into what the action was
That you were trying to defend
What if he killed a guy?
The only story
He's told me is
Him and his friend
They had a podcast
I already fucking despise this
Fuck them where do they get off?
If you plug the podcast in
I'm not going to say it
Jordan and Jesse go
They were doing a movie review
Of Iron Man 3
They disagreed and it turned into
A life fight
Are you fucking kidding me?
We've all been there
It's a fickle thing
That I have a hard time
Taking seriously
Because it's dumb
All of my friends are fighting
Can I give you some advice that I haven't given in a while?
You need to pack your bags and move the fuck away
Because this whole group of friends
Sounds eight
They have that quality
He said mean things about Iron Man 3
Hey, come on now
I haven't seen it yet
If that was really the
Realistically
That's what your roommate is telling you
And the other ones are like
He shit on my bed
Did he say he didn't like Iron Man 3
Because it had black people in it?
Because that would be
Cause to say
I don't think I want to be friends with this dude anymore
There may have been subtext
I like Iron Man in that movie
He reminds me of your dad who I had sex with
I disagree
He does not remind me of my dad
People ask me how to build an audience
For their podcast
That would be the best fucking episode of anything ever
Just let it roll
Just let it play
Watch it all crumble around you
Yeah, all new friends
Start over
You're young, you got a lot of time to rebuild
It's a rebuilding year for you, Dan
I guess that's how I ended up here
We got bad news this year, but great news next year
You're gonna feel great
You made a bunch of new friends here, so you're gonna be fine
Move in with them
Who's got room for Dan?
There's one hand
How many people do you need to live with, Dan?
Round of applause for Dan
Alright, that's all the proper advice questions
Yeah, that's all the proper advice we have
Before we wrap this show up
In the only way we know how
We want to say thank you so much
Seriously, this is even earlier than we did it last year
Which was still pretty early
And I know you guys had super late nights
Behind the curtain
It felt like a lot of people were up really late last night
Saw a lot of auras
Thank you guys, seriously, for coming
And thank you to all of the other
Presenters and performers and everyone this year
Let's do one big round of applause for everyone
And now one just for us
I can't applaud
For people that have sent me to a
Three day panic attack
And I'm confronted by genuinely talented people
Oh, he's like really funny
He has jokes and things, oh shit
Oh god, oh god
He's worked at this, ah shit
So last year we
Closed the show out with a bunch of
Final yahoo questions
Layered delicately
So delicately
Over Vanessa Williams
Saved the best for last
We're not going to do that this year
No, we're doing something incredibly similar though
We are going to
Read the final yahoo answers
Yeah Nick, if you want to go ahead
Over the best last day of camp song
Possibly of all time
Should we stand up? Can we take these out of the thing?
I don't think we can take them out of the thing, we can try
They move
That's awkward
Should I start?
Go ahead
Do you have to mentally add the prices
If you work at Subway?
What do you think of the idea of people
Evolving like Pokemon?
Can spiders have fun?
Is it possible to break your
Titty bone?
Is the movie Jumanji based on a true story?
Are a kangaroo's fingers flexible enough
To pick up a can or a magazine?
Why don't we go
Does the Pringles guy remind you of Frederick Nishi?
Nishi
Notice there are no photos of
Notice there are no photos of Jesus with a hat?
Think about it
Two and two, add it up
Where can I find Gordon Ramsay fan fiction?
What is the opposite of being a gynecologist?
How much does Africa cost?
How do I tell my parents that I am a horse?
If you have a gun rack on your bike
Then you might be a redneck
I was washing my car
And my neighbour came out and said
Washing your car huh?
Billing ball
I said nope, just watering my jeep garden
Here's your sign
Ladies and gentlemen
Get her done
I am Justin McElroy, wear the blue collar
This has been my brother, my brother and me
Kiss your dad's square on the lips
Music