The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to My Brother, My Brother and Me, an advice show for the modern
era. I'm your oldest brother Justin Tyler McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother Travis P. McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother and 30 under 30 media luminary Griffin McElroy A.
A is my middle. A is my middle initial. Turn around every now and then I get a little bit
nervous. My Brother, My Brother and Me 360. We've done it. We're all the way back at the start.
So it's like a geometry joke. Okay, so we've circled back around or like a fully immersive
interactive experience. Well, it's both Travis. We're back to the beginning, which means
just a lot. We're just going to use challenging terminology for everybody that isn't a straight
white dude. What's the audio quality going to be like, you ask? Oh, it will be unlistenable.
It's gonna be hard. Yeah, it'll be hard to recreate that. I'm gonna go put my expensive
mic sort of dip it in a toilet for a bit and then continue using it. I should recreate sort
of the original WAV files I was producing. Back at the beginning as if we never left My Brother,
My Brother and Me the beginning. What was that? Hey, here's a trivia question for you.
What was the first question ever on My Brother, My Brother and Me?
Was it shampoo and a shower? Yeah, maybe. You don't know. You shouldn't have asked it if you
didn't know it. I shouldn't have asked it if I didn't know it. I completely agree. Now Justin,
where does the 360 immersive like fully VR experience? That's what I want to know about.
Can I plug this into my fucking Google cardboard that came with my New Yorker magazine and be in
it be in the room be in the studio turn to my left see the big big box of sickness tissues I've
got going look to my right and see the I've got a roll of toilet paper over here just in case I run
out of sickness issues. Can people experience this at real time in their Google cardboard?
That's the plan. We're still the tech is still sort of in its in a nebulous infancy. We've got
until tomorrow to figure it out because we're recording on Sunday. So getting the 360 experience
I think is obviously the biggest challenge we're facing currently. Well maybe we can maybe we can
like audio it a little bit and I can say like well right now to my right I'm recording on my desktop
but to my left I'm shopping on Amazon for Father's Day presents for myself and I'm eyeballing the
portable air conditioner I had to turn off so as not to actually make it sound like our first 10
episodes right yeah and every second that takes by makes me sweat more and more it was the air
conditioner saying all the problematic stuff yeah that air conditioner oh boy I've got the AC and
definitely not PC yeah I've got the first question you ready yeah my brother my brother comes to us
from the potato the underscore potato on Twitter god that sounds bad yes I want a larger follower
account but I'm finding it difficult to get more than two in a day this was our can I do start a
bunch of accounts and have them follow each other oh that was a good one good job good job question
fucking social media like acumen that was really what we fucking kicked it off with hey listen we
did okay I mean like you can't you I do I did have a lot fewer followers than I do now so something
here is probably pretty good um what are you all boys doing for dad's day I'm gonna play um a lot
of computer games and for one brief hour pretend like my life now isn't at the whim of my seven
month old daughter and that I can actually make decisions for myself I'm trying to get to that
captain underpants oh yes I'm trying to get over there another dreamworks franchise I want to
celebrate the entire sort of company output um I gotta get over there I tried to get over try to
get over there and my excitement I had two big buckets of popcorn two big puppets and you know
I kicked the door open into the theater and they asked me to leave right there and then so maybe
I'll try again a little more subdued contain a little bit contain it who's your do you guys want
to talk about a dad that's important to you not our dad obviously because it's the easy one but
a dad that's important to you like in media or like in real life like my friend steve's dad or
something I mean if whatever you want to do a dad's important to you it's the only sort of but
not our dad no no no I mean our dad's the most important dad he's a great dad and a very special
father but I feel like we talk about him and his funny injuries every father's day like it's time
to cut his butt open use a maxi pad it's a big bandage you know basic stories like that still
be on those phones though there's still me well no not on his butt bones because the the I believe
it was a window screen cut him wide open butt fell right off so dad that's important to us now
on our dad who poured kitty litter and bleached down a drain and knocked himself out for several
hours right right right right right right it's convenient about the it's convenient about the
butt thing he puts his wallet in that side of his pants he sits normal now it all bounces out
because some of the butt fell out when he cut himself right right that was yes I'll start I
guess dave hester from storage wars we get to see some of that relationship unfold and entangle on
the show with dave jr and I don't know I mean not a traditional great dad I guess um but he has he
has a catchphrase and everybody loves that for a good dad and you know passes on business acumen
passes on the family business at all times I am I am I am fucking rolling on that suda
so fucking hard I'm on that suda 51 so hard that like I'm being hypnotized watching my own
waveforms appear on the screen in front of me it's gonna be a fun record I want to talk about Dave
Thomas okay wait which founder founder of Wendy's America's dad uh here's some cool he wants to
know some cool fucking things about Dave Thomas oh yeah uh he was he was adopted he started a
foundation for adoption um he worked at Kentucky Fried Chicken and the colonel tried to lure him
into um a tryst a big pan a big pit full hamburgers and he was like you know me too well
colonel no he was he was uh uh he he listen he founded Wendy's this is huge agreed found
a Wendy's in Columbus Ohio go to the first Wendy's I think it's closed now but um found the
first Wendy's extremely successful but didn't graduate from college right get this he quit high
school uh in fact he didn't even finish high school but he found just a rose that keeps blooming
I know but get this you ready yeah he was so successful after dropping out of high school
he was worried that people would use him as an example for why you shouldn't finish high school
so he went back to high school in like yeah in 1993 he went to coconut creek high school
after founding Wendy's this motherfucker went back to high school it's great got his GED it's amazing
let me pop right in can I get can I pop into the cut real quick whatever you got is it about how
he how he didn't wait for the draft of the Korean War he volunteered for the army well that yeah
now did he have kid did he have a kid did he have children he had four children okay
I just want to pop in I just want to pop in there because we are talking about great dads
and he's America's dad he's the father of the Wendy's franchise and he's father
of of he's like a a surrogate father to kids that want to quit high school yeah and then find out
that um and here's just another factoid this isn't really related but he made a cameo appearance as
himself in bionic ever after a reunion tv movie based on the six million dollar man and the bionic
woman so that's kind of a cool thing about Dave Thomas and that would be I do not have any context
for that scene but I'm assuming it's a pretty cool scene yeah if for some reason Dave Thomas shows
up as himself I cannot fathom what happens in that scene but I'm very excited that it exists
do we know anything about Dave Thomas's politics oh Jesus hold on um I mean he was rich so that
probably didn't not great maybe but I don't know I don't know about his personal politics
I'm not here to talk about Dave Thomas's politics I'm here to talk about how he went back to high
school to inspire kids to finish school I think that's inspiring uh looks like he's pro-choice
he's not anything he's passed away but the fine um so advice so this is an advice show and um
we help people with the real issues that are going on in their lives back in the early days
we used to do a lot of like benign shit you know what I mean because we were afraid to get our toes
into some hot water um but with it's 360 so now we're back around to really um well soak in these
toes soaking these toes in the hot water like race sex politics nothing's off limits because this is
my brother my brother he 360 here's our first question how much cream cheese should I put
on my bagel and that's from cream cheese confounded um and it's you know what
it's a pretty good question yeah I guess so it differs from where you go to where you aren't
it's because you go to an airport and you get a bagel at an airport and they give you
a thimble a borrower full of cream cheese the littlest cup but you go to a new york deli hey
they get fucking crazy it's like they've got a bunch of cream cheese and it's like
brewster's million style they have to get rid of all of it in order to win the treasure or something
here's the thing when it comes to cream I see four options with your cream cheese application
hold on you faxed me over a chart here let me yeah listen I put a lot of thought all right
I'm reviewing it option a you have your open face cream cheese on both sides of the bagel option
right two different halves both of them cream cheesed option b you put cream cheese on one
half you make a sandwich out of it option c cream cheese on both half sandwich out of it this is
double cream cheese you're gonna dribble and it's gonna be you're gonna get a lot of like
is that cum no it's not it's cream cheese I did it I got I flew too close to the to the bagel sun
and option option four and this is my preferred option just a container whatever a big lump of
cream cheese whatever a dollop of cream cheese however you prefer to measure it out and then
you break off pieces of the bagel there we go scoop the cream cheese with it that is your
cream cheese palette and you will dip your brush and then spread it into the canvas of your mouth
correct I I think that cream cheese is actually a pretty good measure for where you're at as a
grown-up oh when I was a little kid no cream cheese butter and jam for me please mother butter
and jam and then maybe a scoop of clotted cream as I got a little older I had basically the thinnest
possible layer of cream cheese and then as I got even older and I started to appreciate that gooey
salty cheese I started thinking like I could take a little bit more of this I can handle some more
and so I would be eating a bagel with a pretty substantial amount of cream cheese and then from
out of nowhere some adult like a real grown-up would walk past me and be like you know some of
us are putting locks on it and it's like I'll never get there I'm never gonna get to a point
where like oh that's a good amount cream cheese maybe a fillet of brine salmon on top of that
you know they're doing some capers on there too which are just I cannot fuck with capers in any
way but like to think of a breakfast where I'm gonna put a fillet of brine salmon on my cream
cheese no way it's unthinkable it's unthinkable it's unimaginable I'll fuck with some mocks though
I don't know why I said it's oh I think about it a lot and capers are really just like olives that
couldn't quite get there huh it is tiny salty just like little uh you know like pop rocks
only for salt instead of sugar that's what caper is they're just weird sick peanuts yes if you
really unpack it um I prefer Travis's method it's just like I have um some tooth problems bottom
left my the whole bottom left quadrant of my mouth just doesn't behave I've gone to see the dentist
dentist says it's all made up and I say it's he says you're just thinking too hard about it just
to eat your eat your fucking food uh it's all goofed up and so every bite of food I take is is
it's it's precious because it could be the last so I want to perfectly measure out each perfect bite
every bite of bagel that I take is like a little amuse bouche and I just have a hundred of them
and it's perfectly creamed and I'm good I'm good to go I'm ready to go anytime I have the opportunity
to do that with my food I will chase it anytime I have the opportunity to have a sort of dunkaroo
method I'm going I am going to chase that 100 percent of the time you touched on this Griffin
but I would like to circle back around when I'm getting deli in New York like a New York like they
say a bow bow hey what is what you know how they do it yeah what is with the the literal like down
comforter of cream cheese that I have to like nosh through to get to the bagel inside what is
going on over there it makes it makes me think that you're supposed to take some of it off and
save it for later like it's like this is for tomorrow's we don't we don't know if you have
cream cheese at home so this is for tomorrow's and possibly the day after that's bagels it's a three
day cheese well what most people don't realize about the economy of New York City is the like
the cost of living is very high like a beer is like twenty dollars and you know like rent is of
course very high everybody knows that and it's like twenty dollars yeah right it's like twenty
dollars and the sandwich is like twenty dollars and the balance is that cream cheese super cheap
like yeah one cent a pound so like that's how they keep like that's how New York is able if
you took cream cheese out of the equation everything will become so imbalanced in New
York City that it would literally sink hit me with this hit me with this it's a city on the go
city on the go city on the move everybody's always always moving and going from business
meeting to business never sleeps never never sleeps getting a cab go from one business
being the fucking next business meeting you've been home to check on your kids or your dog or
whatever and forever they're gone they're gone they're gone they're gone they're on the go too
they went to upstate New York they're out give me a cup give me a cup of mine you see baby stay out
this baby stay out that's all it is so listen how come New York's food is like universally
a big sloppy mess you can go and get a big wet slice of za and it's gonna dribble and drizzle
all over you get a pound of cream cheese between two round boys and that's gonna get all over you
you eat a big the coney dogs coney dogs don't get me started there's two different types of dribbling
and drizzling that you can do all over yourself what is it you're on the go and you're on the
move and everybody's just fucking sticky and and and wet and covered in condiments all the time
what's up New York that's why that's why Griffin they need it as an excuse to stop like that's how
you know your day is done in New York it's like well I'm caked in ketchup and cream cheese and
syrup and whatever so now it's time now it's time to take a breathe you've been out on the
big streets making mud pies and mom's calling you in for the day exactly you've had enough
maybe though let me hit you with this maybe that is you ever heard the term tourist trap
maybe it's pretty literal in this sense like oh you ate the food well you're stuck and I can just
zip right on past you hey no problem New York more like no fork because they don't use they
don't even use utensils for these big messy foods no fork city do you guys want a yahoo
sure in a no fuck minute this one was sent in by this was sent by Amelia Burger thank you Amelia
it's yahoo answers use even the apples big the big it's a big and you know it's wet it's juicy
inside you know it's juicy and it's been sitting up there long enough that it's also like really
soft so you're gonna bite it and the texture's not gonna be right sorry trap sorry uh stop the
podcast uh it's been up there where do you think the apple is it's on top of the empire state
building that's why king kong climbed up there to get the tracks yeah he needed that apple
it was worth it was worth a thousand bonus points that's fine fine did you not think
I'd have an answer for that Justin oh of course of course uh Kevin Zach asks more like Big Snapple
it's been a while oh it's been a while I'm glad it's back oh um wow this website's not good
Kevin Kevin Zach the man so nice they named him twice asked how do we make apple juice more
relevant to adult consumers our company's been pressing apples and making apple juice for
generations all of the apple juice we make is Griffin I'm gonna stop you I'm gonna stop you
I think you're tripped out on Sudafed we did do this question last week did we no it was brought
up in the twofer part at the end of the episode but we didn't do it right but you said the thing
was that just a preview of things to come yeah now we're gonna do it we didn't we didn't talk
about it did we so I don't remember this at all so wait hold on it's been 360 episodes and this
is the first one in which Griffin actually said a yahoo last week that we are actually going to
talk about the next week that's the way we've always done it this wasn't the final this wasn't
the final I'm losing my mind I mean I am too I'm literally not lucid right now um how do we make
these fucking juices more relevant to adult consumers it's good it's a good topic do you
want to not do it no I do I do I just I wanted to be the human tweet that we were going to get
okay Travis McElroy is the human tweet here's the thing do you know what the people love these
days can you let me finish the fucking I thought you finished it oh god no you don't you interrupted
him you I don't even remember all the apple juice we make is pure uncut shit fucking send you to
space all the apple juice we make is pure not from concentrate pressed from local apples and sold
shelf stable not chilled we sell our apple juice in four different pack sizes one liter a best
selling format format five pack seven ounce juice boxes and 128 ounce jug and a 46 ounce bottle
primary consumer of apple juice has traditionally been kids concern around the sugar content of
juice along with the aging population in the households having fewer kids has led to apple
juice declines in recent years apple juice is loaded with health benefits that are irrelevant
to adults yet it has never been directly targeted or promoted to them the pure and local nature of
our apple juice is on trend with the today's adult consumer note solutions with alcohol are
not compatible with our brand so think of something else to say Justin and Travis yeah yeah yeah
actually if I could if I could speak on that for a moment uh I went through Taco Bell drive-thru
on my way home from the airport because there's not a lot of options and I liked eating it also
and um to other I prefer it to other options when many options are presented often that is the one
I prefer to eat with my mouth and uh it's cheat day buzz off anyway I ate there and they have a
new option there um that is Mountain Dew spiked I had a moment that I was so fucking excited
about Mountain Dew spiked lemonade that Taco Bell finally it's a one-stop shop well you can get
everything there at three in the morning now after you've been drinking you can now get
drunk drunker yeah and here's the thing it's non-alcoholic and it says you have it says on
the sign does not contain alcohol and I just wanted to say to Taco Bell this is sort of like
a mini Munch Squad diversion I guess if you have to specify that a product does not contain alcohol
maybe it's time to go back to the drawing board on what you named the thing like if you if you
were to have like um we've got a new thing it's apple juice with cocaine and then at the bottom
of the screen it says does not contain any actual cocaine it's probably like time for a new name
yeah back to the drawing board here's my idea for apple juice apple juice here's the thing
you know what people love these days they like beverages that claim health benefits
while also being delicious okay but you can't just say that you can't just be like it's healthy
it's got to be like makes your brain more powerful and gives you the energy to have sex good and
stuff like it's got to sound extreme like coconut water is a thing just make apple water just call
it apple water talk about like it'll make you live to 140 or whatever and you can say whatever
you want because by the time people crack down on that we're on to something else just make whatever
bogus claims you want it's like a moving target yes I this is what Don Draper would do just
fucking call it like sex juice and tell people when you drink apple juice your boners are better
and you look better and everybody enjoys having sex with you more and you'll go for like sting
time and everybody will be impressed with how good you are at sex because you drink some apple juice
when you're down to pound get the fruit that's round and now in a bottle it's sex juice it's
made entirely from apples and other natural ingredients like pan-x which apparently makes
your wiener bigger learn the secret that bees have known for centuries apples make you better
at fucking hey you ever see a horse turn down an apple no you ever see a horse's shlong it's
amazing apples definitely make you good at sex and make it bigger and better for you and your
loved one you heard it straight from the horse's mouth and then when people are like hey that thing
you said about apples and sex isn't true you say well the horse did say nay it's right in there
that's the asterisk could you just put some chunks in there oh my god like orbits like
like people love that what's that like bubble tea but instead it's just chunks of apple that you
have to sift through i don't love that sort of stuff it's sort of like a virgin sangria is what
you're discussing people love filter feeding yeah they love when they're drinking and then they have
to do work yeah and they can push the apple juice out through their baleen you know what i mean and
then just keep the chunks and you get a little snack um i tell you what would sell it for me
can i tell you and this is a fucking this is foolproof okay on my way to wrestlemania last
year and that's an important part of the story i went to stop to bucky's got a big thing a minute
minute time minute time apple juice i think is what it's called and a big big bag of sugar-free
gummy bears and blasted through them both and then they blasted through me with some
just chart topping loose stools just just some some real next level stuff um and so like my idea
is to have them do some sort of eternal sunshine of the spotless mind on me so that i can ever
or because i think here's the thing i think the sugar-free gummy bears are the ones that threw
the party inside of me but the apple juice was certainly a guest of honor and it's going to be
hard for me to sort of divorce it from its role in the festivities um so whatever they can do to
sort of just get that out of out of my mind um so i can enjoy the taste again i'll take my question
i answer off the air uh real talk those fucking little glass balls also that they had on uh boy
meets world and i think on like martin little glass balls they just pull out of the fridge
and i know we've talked about those beautiful globules but like i would drink anything out
of those are you kidding me i'd feel like i'm a fucking diablo 2 barbarian just chugging a
potion getting ready for battle you know what i mean with your toilet i i think the thing that
apple juice is gonna have to overcome is the fact that it is entirely sugar i mean it's just pure
sugar and adults are a little more savvy about that like if you want me to drink something like
if you want me to drink a 12 ounce glass of apple juice you're probably gonna have to do better than
a fucking half cup of sugar in the bottle of apple juice that i'm consuming that's lunacy
yeah no adult's gonna buy that maybe stop making it or you could do like tropic canada's with their
tropican of 50 line and literally just fill half the bottle with water that's what they did and
they're like it's better for you now it's like well i mean yeah yeah yeah in a blend i could
enjoy at home that's why i i've long advocated for gatorade to make a lime that's just called
gatorade weak and it's just watered down because sometimes a gatorade is just too much and you pour
half of it out and you fill it with the water and it's like ah this is exactly the level of
beverage that i desired it's gatorade week it won't it won't help you in sports i love you
i love you gatorade g2 is already a thing and that exists and they done did it they done did
they gotta go now i do love the idea of gatorade for once sort of toning their brand down instead
of just escalating and escalating and escalating until it's just like randy moss eating his way
through a car door to get at the gatorade extreme like that is sitting in the the uh sitting in the
cup holder inside you're looking pretty down what's that you've got eight sonnets to finish
before class tomorrow we'll pound one of these it's gatorade week it's not going to keep you
up too late and it's going to fuel your neurons with a mild amount of electrolytes just this is
the commercial i see just me sitting on the couch i grab a gatorade i take a sip and my face just
kind of goes like oh and it's like too much we totally hear you sorry about that we put too many
electrolytes in there here's a cup dump half of it out now try this we put some water in the
gatorade you already had but we charged you for it again oh that seems fair glug glug glug oh
that's perfectly miles i'm ready to take a nap please enjoy our sleepy time chamomile gatorade
for poets for poets and soft types brain thinkers i see you're having a little trouble adjusting
your cravat this morning well maybe you need to fuel your brain and cravat tying fingers
with gatorade week that bonsai tree's not gonna prune itself it's like the cool side of the pillow
in a bottle i work in a hospital and today i went to a subway down the street for lunch i
they didn't capitalize it but i'm gonna assume that it was a restaurant and now i'm i'm one of
the night people and i like to enjoy i think you have to say i went to subway i think if you say
a subway that is a different thing that's different i had my headphones in listening
to my bim bam while i was eating and while i was walking back to work i took off my headphones when
i walked to the door and apparently a doctor had been following behind me and asked me what i got
from subway okay um i had no idea who this doctor was and i just responded that i got a meatball
sammy he told me his favorite is the chicken teriyaki and continued to tell me that the
previous week there was a special where you could get lobster at subway then he just walked away and
didn't say anything else i don't know what the hell just happened to me please help that's from
confusion cincinnati um you just had a conversation like yeah it's just it's just you may congratulations
i mean you made small talk you made it everybody a deep deep connection i mean he was lying
so like i guess that that would be a confusing part he was lying correct oh my god subway did
have a lobster sandwich oh my goodness golly gosh so that's all that happened to you i mean this is
more this feels more to less like a question to me and the bim bam 360 kind of about a triumph
like i had a conversation with someone i made benign small talk for a couple minutes and then
we parted ways they didn't like what usually happens in our questions like try to sell me
a skeleton or grab my butt or whatever like you just had a regular interaction with somebody i
think that's glorious but it's not something you need our help with you did it congratulations
360 you all finally learned how to fly please teach us when you get a second now you do a
podcast and we'll listen to it what's your favorite subway sammy though i used to fuck
with the chicken bacon ranch but can't 30 39 30 i can't have ranch anymore i had a weird
realization the first time i went to a subway that wasn't in huntington west virginia and
tried to find my favorite pizza sub on the menu and not a nationwide experience i think the pizza
sub i think you could probably gen one up they just make it there for you you would get that
they you came in and ordered it one day and they're like i guess we'll put some marinara
on some shit and cheese it and okay here you go little small boy we love you very much
very good job i guess that's not a national thing i don't know they're very big in west virginia
though i don't know they're every west virginia subway i don't have a favorite i just like walk
in and say surprise me okay they're all good i've never been disappointed i used to this is true
back when i was a young man who didn't know better used to get the tuna sub the tuna sub at subway
oh what a mistake that was that's the one that they make with the tuna salad in subway right
yeah that's the one that they make begrudgingly are you sure yeah yeah it's sort of a hesitant
scoop that you get on that one uh like you'll get a half scoop of it i'm just trying to limit
the risk here when they go to hand it to you they'll jerk it back click and they're like
are we on a prank show please don't do this to us they said you order it and they say ah trying
not to get somebody to not sit next to you on the bus today huh very clever there are safer ways to
do this sir uh let's get the money some my brother my brother me that's right this podcast is supported
in part by casper an online retailer of premium premium obsessively engineered mattresses for a
fraction of the price up the price of what i don't know it's not in the copy point but like think of
something else and it's less than that think of a big price no you're wrong or or you might have
thought like sixty dollars and that is too low that's actually come on it's it is a mattress
it's like be be fucking serious and don't you like 801 because the person next to you said 800
that's cheap that a fucking oh it's the worst casper uh they the box you get from casper should
not contain a mattress but it does and that's the first sin of casper and it's really there's
several sins though they should not be this cheap that's gluttony i think is one of those
it's our and but and the other sin is they've defied god and made a box too small to hold a
mattress that does hold a mattress when you open it just like expands out and the sin is everywhere
it's like what i what i always imagined in cartoons when they like had an emergency raft
and it was like a little envelope and then they pull it unfolds that's basically a casper mattress
um except it's not funny it's just comfort well it does kind of make a funny noise i guess yeah
kind of makes this like so far yeah that's very quiet one though there's a risk-free uh trial and
return policy you're not going to want to do this but you can try sleeping on a casper for 100 days
with free delivery to the us and canada and painless returns now when they say that that's
a lie because you are going to have to stuff it back in that mattress and you're not a wizard
so you're going to be at that for the rest of your days um that's not sure i'm sure there's
another way of getting the mattress back to them uh and these matches they're made right here in
the good old us of a our listeners can get 50 towards any mattress purchase if they go to
casper.com slash my brother and use the promo code my brother that's all one word at checkout
and it says here also terms and additions apply i would like to tell you about i beat you to it
i would like to tell you about a service i call blapron because i'm a man on the go i don't have
time to say blue apron anymore so i shortened it to a mess a messy sticky new yorker exactly i gotta
go go go i don't have time to go to the store and figure out how much of what ingredient i want and
how to cook it and what ingredients are required for what recipe and what recipes are and where
they live i don't have time for that but blapron formerly blue apron but now rebranded by me
Travis McElroy not officially by them can't say that enough blapron sends you the ingredients you
need to make delicious meals with instructions on how to make those meals so even if you don't know
how to cook or what to cook blaperon's got you covered and that's for less than ten dollars per
person per meal they deliver seasonal recipes along with the pre-proportioned ingredients
and you get to show off for your your friends your family or even just yourself maybe surprise
yourself with a delicious meal because damn it you're worth it yeah upcoming meals include a
low taste style vegetable tostadas with summer squash poblano peppers and cilantro rice and
and peach honey glazed chicken with mashed sweet potatoes collard greens and Thai basil by the way
if you are a radio or broadcasting professional and you are looking for the two words that have
the most plosives per word in it you could not do much better than poblano peppers oh yeah take that
people at home it's listen to my it's a one two three four punch and you can check out this week's
menu and get your first three meals free with free shipping by going to blue apron.com slash
my brother do not go to blaperon.com that is nothing yet but blue apron.com slash my brother
you'll love how good it feels and tastes to create incredible home-cooked meals with
blue apron it hurts to say so many syllables um so don't wait that's blue apron.com slash
my brother blaperon a better way to cook blaperon does go to blue apron.com now it does
excellent oh did you you can did you just get it yeah i just got it if you go to blaperon.com
it goes to blue apron.com slash my brother so you are good there just go to blaperon
you're welcome blaperon you're welcome blaperon um i have a jumbo charm message this one's for
trella and it's from logan who says happy anniversary to my favorite person thank you
so much for all the amazing years we have had so far and for introducing me to these wonderful
brothers here's to a bunch more years to come uh and that is this supposed to go up now it's june
20th yeah yeah we did a good one um congratulations on your love and for all the amazing years
it was i like to know how many years please include that in these messages because then i
add it to the leaderboards we have an ongoing leaderboards of who has the best love going um
i don't know why who's currently winning griffin oh man mica and jay molson's i have another
message this one's for michael g and it's from julia who says that's right i just dropped a cool
hunna to get these sweet boys to tell you how much your friendship means to me happy approximate
birthday and thanks for nearly three years of friendship and roommatehood love you and great job
and as for as close to june 24th as possible we're fucking crushing it yeah this is really good now
three years griffin where does that put michael and julia you know i've got a different one for
roommates and three years of you know not pushing a roommate down the stairs is like really good
actually you're really really far ahead of the curb so did i say curb boy yeah but i love you
also uh good news the uh traditional third year is
leather so you could have some fun there oh all right get to if you get to the second one though
cotton so we kind of missed it a little bit yeah well i'm sure they got each other
here they huge vape rigs yeah yeah hey guys this is adam conover you may know me from my true tv
show adam ruins everything well guess what now we're doing a podcast version right here on
maximum fun what we do is we take all the interesting fascinating experts that we talked
to for just a couple minutes on the show and we sit with them for an entire podcast really going
deep and getting into the fascinating details of their work find adam ruins everything wherever
you get your podcasts or at maximum fun.org how about yahoo yeah that would go down real smooth
right now this one was sent in by ryan p fahmy thank you ryan it's yahoo answers user no name
that is their name i don't know why um should i invent a contraption that only the very smart
sperm cells are able to make it through will this make future generations smarter i am a scientist
i am a scientist i therefore want to invent some sort of maze that sperm cells have to move through
the problem with this maze is that only the most intelligent sperm cells will be able to make it
through this maze therefore since only the most intelligent sperm cells will make it through the
maze the egg will only be fertilized by the most intelligent sperm and an egg fertilized by an
intelligent sperm cell will make a super intelligent baby again just to go back to
the first sentence here i am a scientist this is some um i mean light eugenics it's
it's yeah it's a mild soft um here's what let me hit you with this open up sunday paper laugh at
foxtrot done i'm i'm glad i'm done with this sunday paper because it will not be usable after
this next part find the the maze or if your local paper does not have a maze junior jumble
or maybe even the sudoku blast one out on it see who wins take that one and then do a pregnancy
with it so i'm a scientist and i i'll tell you the the issue is that i came on the junior jumble
solved it right there and the one that i saw sort of scribbling out the answers scooped him up with
a you know tool science tool and did a pregnancy with it and uh einstein jr came out so my problem
with this is that there's a lot of different kinds of intelligence yeah and i didn't get fluid liquid
and what you're solving for is a very particular type of um a very particular type of intelligence
and i'm not necessarily sure i'm ready for a world populated by basically just will shorts just like
a sort of huge gaggle of will shortes just sort of running buck wild across yeah where's our like
street smart sperm you know what i mean like they can't make it through a maze but they could tell
you how to get like how to get to the store the quickest way or like well let me tell you this is
how it works this is where you're going to get like the freshest you know vegetables at the market
or like uh you need to make friends with the bus drivers and that's how like where's that
kind of intelligence they kind of tell us that they don't teach at sperm school you know yes
um the kind you learn living on the streets of goo york oh man
we've talked a lot about new york which one they're both gonna stick right i mean they're
both sort of well something's gonna stick oh god thanks i just want a sperm that's gonna be able to
like explain twin peaks that return to me just like tell like oh i've never thought of it that
way you're intelligent in a very specific way so in order to come up with that joke i just said i
was trying to think of like a movie i could say there instead so i googled smart movies and just
like going down um the google search history that just popped up in my bar smart movies apple juice
diarrhea dave thomas problematic dave hester's son these are all very very good i am on the fbi
watch list for some something uh here is another question um whenever i'm part of a group photo
inevitably someone says okay now let's do a silly one i never know what to do for these and usually
just didn't up making a face it looks like i'm in pain any help for what could be my thing that's
from sans silly in san francisco and if you're looking to measure sibilance in your broadcasting
equipment that's a pretty good one to go for um i like about this i like uh just like a context
list silly like no matter where this silly will always play you know what i mean i try to just
sort of register my disappointment in the request in the photo itself and then like if everybody
else is like making a fart face or a funny you know like either yelling or doing a like a you
know a fucking jack jack nicholson like you know uh but you just you see my face in the background
i'm like fuck off with it like it's kind of funny it's like a silly you know i'll tell you a good
i'll tell you good go to turn around goku well that also works but turn around just turn your
back on the camera that's so silly because the camera's supposed to your face yeah and you put
your glasses on the back of your head and unbutton the your butt flaps so your butt's hanging out like
a little kid and turn your shirt around so the ties on on your back and also turn your pants
wait no then then it does just look like you're facing forward and maybe it won't play put eyes
and a nose on the back of your head oh wait it's gotten away well get out of the blow up sexual
doll and blow it up right there you have it ready help wait make them wait don't let him take the
photo while you're blowing it up it's not going to play you need the fully blown up sexual doll
that you have with you pull it out of your backpack and do it right there so good dude
are you kidding if i saw that fuck maybe you take a picture of them taking a picture of you
oh you have your own camera yeah push it like just start pushing everyone around you really hard
don't hurt them but just push them all over push them here's one that you all see a lot just give
them like a was that was that was great because they'll be so excited to see that that's and
somebody looks at that photo they're like when was this taken and you'll have to convince them
that like no it was not during the wasab craze of that particular super bowl it was afterwards
ironic why don't you want to hinge your jaw and put the head of the person standing in front of
you completely in your mouth like a big snake or something i love that that's really funny when you
do that vogue vogue is good voguing is good maybe put on a really convincing mask so it's like
suddenly what's that oh tom cruise was there what's he doing there but he wasn't so you're
so you're thinking that you maybe are getting ready to leave for an event and you'll just sort
of put into your back pocket a mask of tom cruise that you'll like just sort of carry with you
throughout the day for this payoff you make an accent point justin what you're gonna need to do
and i i will consider this part an homage to mr cruise himself you're going to already want to
have the tom cruise mask on and then put a mask of yourself over it oh remove your mask to reveal
tom cruise mask then it's good like mission impossible jokes exactly what about ellen ellen
what about ellen um and bradley whitford brad bradley cooper do you remember at the oscars when
they took that picture and like everybody was really deeply into it yeah for sure could you
do something could you do something like that that's what that's taking a picture though
griffin like you're you're already doing something like that by taking the picture i was just trying
to take a good picture like good funny pictures it's a it's a hard needle of thread and they did
a good job can you wear a child's uh two-piece bathing suit and then right when the picture's
about to be taken you get a dog to kind of funny cute come up and like pull the bottom of your
britches down i like that sort of like the exposed butt's gonna get you there like no matter what
there's really no if your first ingredient is exposed but there's really no recipe but not
mooning not mooning because that's gross and awful but like if a dog comes and shows your
butt a little bit then here's my worry here's my worry about exposed butt guys oh yeah first
time it's pretty funny the second third fourth fifth like okay but then do you think it comes
back around on like the 12th time like he's doing but again yeah what if you just i don't know man
smiled if you just have a nice smile what if you oh this is fucking great this is great
just do like a fucking like sexy smile and then everybody else around you is like
and you're in the background just like what's up but not in like the budweiser way but like
just that you're saying it in a cool way then everybody's gonna look at this picture and be
like look at all these jagoffs wait a minute who's that in the background who is this they
they look like they just drank a bunch of apple juice so they're ready to go to my home my home
to my hometown and here's here's the here's the power move if anyone sees that photo and says to
you like that's weird everybody's doing a silly one why didn't you do a silly one you say here's
the weird thing the photographer didn't say yeah that we were gonna do a silly one everyone else
are just that's so good so they photographer actually said make it do a sexy one and that's
why i look so sexy everybody else you see in this picture and it's everybody that is at this party
that i they look really pissed off because i'm saying this really loudly so they can they're a
bunch of fucking clowns when it comes to sexuality so what i'm saying is that i'm a mature grown-up
who is in full control of their own sexuality yeah and and that could be yours that's what i've got
on on doc every time you go to a party that these people host you bring that picture with you your
new person comes apart hi what's up i'm david let me show you this picture before you sort of start
making judgments about people here at the house um that is me in the back yeah it's different
than everyone else i know we were asked by the photographer to confront and expose our own
sexuality and this is what these i mean forgive me clowns brought to the table vis-a-vis their
their own human beautiful human sexuality do you like to get out of here would you like to get out
of this den of clowns do you want to get out of here do you want to hook up with uh let's see
there's two different groups of people doing charlie's angels so that's their sex so maybe
we should just a go because it's as good as it gets jack nicholson do you guys think when they
do a group shot at an event for clowns and they're like do a silly one i bet it fucking pops off
right i bet it's like so silly back when clowns were legal because barnum and bailey shut down
and by the way everybody just a heads up about that barnum bailey shut down so be on the lookout
for clowns and jugglers just like roaming the streets like wild animals specifically jugglers
you have to look out for but um i i would be careful about that i was driving the grocery
store with my kids and i looked to my left and there's a motorcycle on a big steel ball
it's not safe that's not safe get that off the road big steel ball could roll over my car crush
like indiana jones here's the good here's the good news you're gonna see jugglers and you're
gonna be terrified because they have the projectiles right there in their hands and it's
very very scary but the truth is if they were to use one of those projectiles they then lose all
their power and die like exactly don't be afraid of them yeah it's they're they're a lot more
threatening uh looking than they actually are but don't get too close because if threatened
they will sacrifice their juggling career to fend you off so appreciate it at a distance
um the danger the majestic danger of the juggler well folks that's got to do it for us here on my
brother my brother and me uh we hope you've enjoyed yourselves happy uh father's day to all
the people filling that role or i think any parent parental role it's a tough gig and uh
congratulations to all of you um to anybody who's filled the role taking care of anybody really i
would say like if you've helped all our caregivers yeah if you've helped or even just neutral even
if you didn't help but you didn't stop someone else from taking care of somebody else and plants
and plants and plants uh uh grave keepers the crypt keeper thank you for your dedication and
your service mm-hmm um crypt keeper also a great uh daddy real great daddy oh yeah much love to
oh much love to the keeper and he's uh i bet he's married to a great mummy
oh i see so um his his spooky stories to get you so scared you'll be crying for your mummy
hey um i'm gonna be uh doing saw bones sunday july 16th uh at the philadelphia podcast festival
uh that shows at 2 p.m that day it's all ages uh tickets are like 22 to 24 bucks i think um
but if you go to bit.ly forward slash saw bones philly um it's gonna be at the trucadero theater
uh um and it's gonna be really fun and sidney and i are gonna do a fun show and i think the
chucks will be there and we're really looking forward to it so if you can come out go to bit.ly
forward slash saw bones philly and come say hi to me and watch our show and say hi to i mean
sydney as well say hi to everybody really uh and uh we hope you'll come out also flophouse is doing
a show at that same festival like i think directly after us at the same theater so um uh it's gonna be
a lot of fun you should take us through their show too and come on out and see us
um and shortly after that a few days after that we will then be doing our sandy jugger comic con
show so go ahead and start sending in your questions now and make sure to put it you know
in the subject line of sdcc live um and we'll see you there uh i want to thank john rogerick
and long winters for the use of our theme song into departure off the album putting the days to
bed um it is it's a really good song it's a really good album and please go please go get it please
just go get it thank you um we also want to say you know you can follow us on twitter imbm and
all of us individually or whatever and then you can go to mcroyshows.com where are listed all our
other projects as well as our twitter accounts facebook groups uh p.o box addresses that kind
of stuff mcroyshows.com uh and thanks to maximum fun for having us go to maximum fun.org check out
all the great shows um that's it that's it it's finally on who was sending by level 9000 yadru
drew drew davenport thank you drew it's yadru answers user juan colt says what gun can you
picture ash with from pokemon oh my name is justin mcroy i'm travis mcroy i'm griffin mcroy
it's been my brother my brother may kiss your dad's square on the lips
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported hello internet i'm your
husband host travis mcroy and i'm your wife host teresa mcroy and together we present shmanners
it's extraordinary etiquette for ordinary occasions we explain the historical significance of everyday
etiquette topics then answer your questions relating to modern life so join us weekly on
maximum fun.org or wherever podcasts are found no rsvp required check out shmanners manner shmanners
get it