The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Welcome to the Solstice! I knew it! That's what I was gonna do!
It's my brother, my brother, and we special summer solstice episode.
As we dance amongst the fairy rings. The sky hangs high with the brightness of a
luna as the sun beams down on us from its highest position.
Lightning bolt, lightning bolt, lightning bolt, lightning bolt.
Let's all start fucking. My, there's only three of us here.
It's hugely creepy. I'm the oldest traveler, Justin McElroy.
I'm the middle-est and naked-est to Travis McElroy. I'm free!
I emerged from the mist one. I emerged from the mist two.
I emerged from the mist three. Hi, my name is Griffin McElroy.
I'm a level 14 troll berserker. And I, sorry, I hate to.
One of you guys buffed me while I was emerging from the mist,
which is LARP rules like 101. You gotta wait for me to be summoned
before we can begin our encounter. I actually have an enchanted mirror of
Conchlin Crong and it helps me to see you from the mist.
Have you had those new, those Fritos Conchlin Crong?
They're so good. They're buffalo blasted.
I did just watch Monster Camp again, so I am like coming hot and fresh
off the like, that glow that you get after you watch Monster Camp.
People watch Monster Camp. I think you have to like rent it on Amazon Instant
Video or something like that. It's an important movie and it's one of
those movies that you watch it and you're like,
this is a crazy world I know nothing about and I never will. Look at these,
look at all these people. And then also you feel like,
could I maybe like uh, could I maybe dip in?
That is the great dark secret of Monster Camp is that you
watch it. You were the monster the whole time. You were the monster the whole time.
You will watch this movie with your significant other
and your your wife, husband, boyfriend, girlfriend will be watching it and
laughing and you'll be laughing. Inside you there's another you that's not
laughing. Not laughing at all. There's another you that says maybe I
could dip in. It's weeping with a fantastic longing.
I want our listeners to know that I felt like that
goof was general enough that I can't imagine we were making fun of any
specific group. No, I think we were mostly making fun of ourselves.
Yeah, I felt that way too. Because of our distinct lack of knowledge of what the
Solstice is, what it does. Don't you take this as an opportunity to
educate it either, dear listeners. I'm onto your game. You can educate me.
I like learning stuff. I'm not afraid to learn and expand and grow as a person.
I'm done with that. I feel like I have to with a with a child so close I feel
like I have to cauterize myself as a human. I have to like
you can't grow anymore. I don't want to grow anymore because that would be
confusing for them. So I basically just have to cap it off
here. Well and then it's all like bigotry and
ignorance and just waiting.
I guess. Well and then you start to pass on your memories to the child
as like what it's like to sled and what the color red looks like.
Right. And and how cinnabons taste. And where the baby hole in the wall is where
you put the bad babies. Mm-hmm. That's dark book. Is it dark book?
Dark book. I'm glad they want a new berry then. Yeah did it win a new berry?
I believe it won a new berry. Can we get to the comedy already? I'm dying
inside and outside. I have noticed that the way I shake
hands with people may be a little off. I have a firm grip
but I tend to counter the other person's pumps
with trying not to pump at all. Instead I flex my shoulder and arm
so while the person is trying to move their arm up and down my arm stays
completely still. Yeah pump that shit. Just try and pump that shit idiot. Pump it.
I imagine the other person encounters some unexpected resistance to an
otherwise routine bump or two. Brothers how am I supposed to be doing
this? You know how you're supposed to be doing
this? That's from wrestling in Winchester.
Now listen my brother my brother me listeners. Before you start laughing too
hard I've shaken a lot of your hands. You're
a wonderful people. Kind. Oh I love your spirit. So many of
you came up to the LA show. We met so many
so many beautiful hearts. Sometimes you're bad at handshakes. I've shaken a lot of
your hands. Some of you could pick up a tip or two.
That's all I'm saying. I always just assume that it's like
and not because I've done this before as well like if you're standing on a line
for something or you're waiting and you know that handshake's coming
like if somebody just encountered you at random was like hey and you shook their
hand you would nail it you know 100 percent
but then when you have time to think about it yeah I'm about to shake this
hand it's up and down right no wait hold on be proactive about it
wait if you're if you're waiting in line to like after one of our live shows you
want to shake our hand and like that's super cool um go ahead
and like get your hand ready do do a little bit of pre-pro on that
hand to make it perfect for us maybe breathe into it a little bit to
get it to the ideal temperature for me that's 96.5 a little bit cooler
than normal um I like a definitely not warmer
definitely not wet definitely dry that hair right off
I'm not sure which um which handshake I find more upsetting like
on the one hand you got the one that feels like their arm
was like somebody filled up a jello mold that's shaped like an arm
and then just kind of attached it to a person as if I wouldn't notice
I don't like that handshake but I think what I find even more upsetting
is like the super firm like they gotta like dog
like don't try oh I like that one don't try that fucking pickup artist bullshit
with me I just shake my hand I can win that one
so I like that yeah Travis is Travis has like extra knuckles
inside of his hand his hand is like a I don't know it's
bristling with knuckles on the inside the one I the the handshake I
dislike the most is that one where you go over the handshake and their hand
closes like a second too soon like some kind of awful claw game
oh yeah just they grab like your fingers instead of like your palm
yeah and then they get embarrassed and try and back out and it's like don't
back out just like fix it just fix it just back out now
this is what I'm gonna remember you by finger grabber handshake
is like making love there's no standard for it you have to
and you can get the presence from energy yeah
you have to see where they're going with it you can get crabs from it
you get all kinds of stuff this person is playing a dangerous fucking game
because if you ever meet your counterpart in this world
and you guys go in to shake hands and then both of you just grab hands
and then stand perfectly still you are holding hands at that point
that is cease to be a handshake you are holding hands if that's your boss
that's a whole ordeal we got to call HR into the room HR please witness this
this is just a shitty handshake we're not holding hands in the office
on office hours okay but here's is I can I get this a little you don't pump
you're not a pumper no but I I there's something to me that's
always seemed so calculated and forced about the like
handshake pump pump pump done there's something about like just a grab
and kind of a like a almost like just a flex is all the pump you get where it's
just like grab and like you're just kind of flexing
your arm and then you break off and that you go
you go into the you don't go up and down you go like in
and you hit yeah you're walking like Voltron it's kind of just like a yeah
put her that like a putter there yeah yeah yeah yeah
which I kind of dig that way more because it's much more of just like an
acknowledgement of like now our hands are together and now
our hands are apart and there was no kind of extraneous motion in there I
kind of dig that maybe but that said if the other person
starts to pump you don't just like stare me and go
don't leave them standing alone on pump island
you've got to fucking send them a raft uh I want to ask one other quick favor
since I know that this only applies to like people who do meet and greets after
their live podcasts so this won't be widely useful uh but it
I'm using our show as like a megaphone for
my own wants and desires when you're at a thing
and someone says hi I'm Justin McElroy and and you say yes I know
that's incorrect
wrong you wanged it you wanged it because I
I know you know we're playing a game here you and I
we're going to meet each other it's an introduction I want to know you as a
human you may not believe that but I do I want
to know each and every one of you I wish I had the time after a live show to
have a nice 20 to 22 minute chat with each of you
about uh uh just your life and and learning and living and I want to get to
know you so please say your goddamn name just
say give me your name please give me something to work with
and I cannot stress enough we love all of you please don't ever stop shaking
your hand and talking to us and being yeah we don't get because we need you
very much we need you can I say one thing that uh our our
listeners did fucking nail what uh and are consistently very good
about I was at the uh LA live show
and after you do like a live podcast or whatever
or a panel maybe or and you know or even like a wedding thing that you know
that you're gonna like shake a lot of hands afterwards
uh uh so I was in that mode right like I know I'm about to go shake everybody's
hand I had to pee super bad the show had just
ended there were and I was like I gotta hit the
bathroom I walk into the bathroom there's four people who I know were just
in the podcast watching my podcast show I peed I washed my hands I left not a
word was uttered to me nice like I was not there and I was like in my head
thinking you sons of bitches are crushing this
right now let me get out this door and I'm gonna praise you
heartily because you are playing this so well and I'm I'm so happy
what were they gonna do hey like hey I hate to interrupt you I just want to
let you know it was a great job thank you hey my good good hey my good good
people wait what are you gonna do you got your dick
betwixt your fingers just wanna let you know you also had my heart in your hand
I use all five what the hell like a crow's beak
well now I've got to think about it hold on now you now I have to think about it
and I'm mad at you for making me do that y'all want to yahoo
hit yeah this yahoo is sent in by Drew Davenport
emerald member fucking diamond member forever friend
guys if you weren't at the LA live show you missed Drew Davenport
like in all his glory us fucking ascending the throne
here's some fun facts about Drew Davenport he is
13 feet tall uh he is as wide as a bull he's a mountain of a man
and a jovial one to boot and he no shit has a natural glow about him that's
blind he's got a beard you could hide a fist in
he's got a lot of stuff a lot of great ass heads thank you Drew for all the
good times so that's why yahoo and the bad times
yeah thanks for being there just thanks for he's a fair weather friend
uh is asked by yahoo answers user derp who asks
becoming Barney in school wear what so I have the perfect neat slim fit
blazer trousers shoes tie belt for school
I have just recently been addicted to how I met your mother why the finale why
and Barney diversion and Barney is my idol
I was just wondering I'm in high secondary school
but I am known for being the suit guy but I feel like I lose this in school
how should I dress act and talk to become like Barney or in
other words become legend wait for it fuck you let's do this
question all right derp Barney is a fictional character fictional
character I want to be Robinson Caruso did I say Caruso that's not his name
he's a he's a caricature of a person uh in real life no one would like that
no one would no one even likes him on the fucking show
it's he's a punchline that's that's the thing is he's a goob
he's not he's not a real person you already fucked up if you're in high
school and you're the suit guy the suit guy is not a thing you want
to be in high now that said if you're in high school and you wear a suit good for
you I don't think anyone should ever be
identified as the blank guy no not good for you Travis you said a
bad thing don't wear no I don't want to judge listen if somebody
wants to wear a suit if someone wants to wear
a spider-man costume if somebody just wants to like roll out the school
incorrect no no I'm done with the idea that people in
high school should be making choices about their
identity and everybody should just passively be okay with it listen
you're still in your formative years okay I there's still a chance for me to
help you you wear a suit to weddings and funerals
stop it stop doing this you can wear a nice
a nice pair of slacks um and a a polo or a button down
if you want to elevate your fucking like jinko style
I get it I get it go for it but there's what if I want to wear
tearaway pants and a button-up dress shirt you mean like you
you mean like you did every goddamn day just
just as an example can I can I let me ask you a question real quick because
you did that was not a joke you wore
tearaway pants basically basically around the clock
were you getting so much trim that you I did not first of all needed to have
that first of all maybe once a week and it is
because I was in fucking show choir on pussy day
you mean they were comfy dance pants gotta be at the ready
Minutemen Minutemen assemble I mean my balls get out of here I like I like that
Travis's answer about uh uh meeting them for show choir was
actually an implicit answer to Griffin's question about how much
trim because that zero no no I don't know
I was in show because my girlfriend was in show choir
and you put on that sequin vest and you saying we built this city
and just the city was the year before me Griffin my year was things
got damp um we did more of like a Billy Joel
uh kind of style like oh it just got 10 times better in the erotic
actually I'm gonna I'm gonna hope against hope
that you were doing that because it was in that the the few years that uh
Billy Joel was married to one of uh Huntington's native daughters
and you were hoping that maybe he would come by see
Justin I live my life every second hoping Billy Joel comes by
so here's here's just his body not like him driving into your office window god
no here's a fun side story okay Billy Joel
marries have to have told this story before no I don't well
no I don't think so okay so Billy Joel married
Katie Lee who is somebody that um I knew a little bit we did some shows together
uh back in back in the day in the in the outdoor theater
so he married Katie Lee who then goes on to she hosts the first
season of Top Chef and she's done some other cookie shows
whatever that was after this so Billy Joel marries Katie Lee
and the the interesting thing about this is that it starts this like
weird it's starting it starts this weird sort of like
pseudo paranoia in Huntington that at any given moment Billy Joel could show up
to something and it's more of like an expectant thing
like a like a child whose parent has abandoned them
that every time they're at like the science fair or something they have that
like back of their head fantasy that maybe
they heard about it and their erstwhile father will show up
it was sort of like that with Billy Joel for a while anytime like a large house
sold in Huntington the room room mill would fly and it was
purchased by uh Dr. William Joel honorary uh and
and and it was his that was his home that there was gonna live there was a
bar on a home here that bar on 4th street that used to be
club echo that it peaked at club echo but it would like rotate every maybe
year and a half to become a different bar in the height of that fever it became
cno piano bar and i think it fucking became that
like expecting that maybe the jolster would cruise on through
a piano bar hey why i just happen to know a piano man
uh-huh billy just keep driving billy just well just once
no we're going to chickadees stop it could it hurt we're going to
we're going to stumblers to still stumbling we can't stop and see you know
piano bar we left your tab open before we went to see a movie at the camelot and
we said we'd be back and now we have to go back a lot of really great
lot of really great references another question yeah uh years ago my two best
friends who were dating had a wickedly ugly breakup which
resulted in me having to choose sides i sided with my homeboy and broke contact
completely with the other it's been six years and emotions have
subsided so i decided to bury the proverbial hatchet and just make peace
now she's inviting me to hang out as if nothing happened
when i don't even really know this person anymore
should i just accept that i open this pandora's box and jump back into things
or should i go with my gut and tread carefully that's from critically
confused in cranberry oh i feel
i feel some real advice coming on this it's been a while
uh-oh i know it's just like this is a thing that everybody i think has
to deal with it's like a combined thing of having to choose sides when your
friends break up is already pretty awful and it's unfair and it's
something you shouldn't have to do but we all have to do it at some point
um it is that combined with the like latent awkwardness of i haven't seen
this person in years do we like
making like the catch-up call to somebody that like you used to be really
good friends with and then you haven't talked to
uh is always like in your brain before you do it like the most going to be the
most fucking uncomfortable thing ever because you have to ask them like
what are you what are you well let me counter that though because i think that
it's my i think the ideal way to do it is you
kind of fake it till you make it kind of thing
no well hear me out where you jump in like
you know you just spoke the day before and then things kind of shake out where
it's like okay great i'm noticing that this is
different and this is different they like this now
instead of like let's sit down and have a 30 minute intensive conversation about
what's different in our lives no i think that's what you gotta do and
i think that's worth it because you can't just be like
you sit down hey hey it's good to see you you too should have done this a
while ago yeah sure so how's work like now i've been in grad
school for three years you fucked that one up next how's jimmy
jimmy's jimmy's astronaut now jimmy's in space i i don't see jimmy anymore he's
with the space men now he's a space jesus now how's your dog
dog died next keep it up do you wanna i i hear the
good are you saying that that's the ideal like that's what you have to do
no i'm saying that's what you get when you fake it when you until you make it
that's your strategy i sit down and i say let's just like
fucking hash it out you play mario kart 8 and like you don't talk about shit you
don't know the answer and then they leave and it's like oh fuck i forgot to
ask anything about you because i don't know
anything about you i guess our whole relationship we have to be playing
mario kart 8 whenever you come over now shit that's kind of weird to me
in this question uh i don't you said it's been six years and emotions
subsided so you decided to bury the proverbial hatchet make peace
what where does your homeboy figure into this what is his
like did you ask his blessing before burying this this hat i don't think you
need to six years is a long fucking time six
years is a really long time how bad were these emotions at
six years yeah i mean it could not be it couldn't be that it could just be like
you stopped hanging out with this person and when you do that like they left your
mind's eye and you didn't like think to do this i'm
saying it's always worth it to like to try and
reconnect with a person like it's always so great because then you have like
one of your old friends is back it's always like the best thing
ever it's just like broaching that subject is always really rough i think
you have to be like really open about it like
hey we lost touch and that sucked let's just like
just run through it let's this hangout is going to be us like fucking
getting through the past six years and then the next time we hang out it can be
just like what did you do this you will honestly you will be surprised how
quickly you can wrap up the important things in six years it's easy and like
they're doing it they want to do it too i'm with you guys on this they don't
know what you've been up to like they're in the same boat like because
in any in any relationship communication is key right like that's the thing
so i changed my mind how because here's the thing if you really are going to
re-establish a a true friendship with this person you
were best friends before this all shook out
and now you're looking to like rebuild that i think it's perfectly justified
would be like hey i feel like you know we really grew apart in
that six years and we lost contact so what's up but you know let's
let's catch up i would find it so flattering i would find it so flattering
that like you want to put in the effort to like
the like this relationship meant something to us at some point like it
really means a lot to me that you want to like work to to get us back
to where we were like i don't know man i think it's i think
it's super it's super nice and it's something like i'm
i'm dishing it out but like it's something i struggle with i've been going
to a lot of weddings this year and like reconnecting with like my literally my
oldest dearest friends that i'm just like such a
shithead about you know calling once a month or so
um i i think the more that you do it i think i feel like that's a big part of
becoming an adult is like realizing that everybody that you
were friends with in school coming up have also become
adults and it's so fucking cool to like talk to
them and see like how you guys have how you guys
have developed things broke bad but most of the time
they're not gonna get weird the nature problem with these
conversations this is why it's such a like this is why a lot of times in my
life i will avoid these conversations because
i'm so afraid of saying to the person like
so how is this person that i sort of kind of remember from your family
and they're dead and like that's i can't even process that
like this is not a goof like i i'm i worry enough about that that
that i will actually avoid conversations like this because i i i am so paranoid
about i i think it's honestly just like looking
stupid because i don't think people would be like upset
angry at you like i i'm just worried about looking
dumb in front of a person and saying like the stupidest thing
but geez isn't that like a litmus test where if the person's like
uh they're dead and you're like okay so's this friendship
like where that person's gonna judge you for not knowing this thing because you
haven't spoken anxiety isn't really rooted in
like social anxiety especially isn't really rooted in
the realities of the situation because almost with all of these like the worst
like people are usually very sort of like generous and kind about
conversation that's the thing you have to like
concretely remind yourself of but but you know
it's not really rooted in the realities of how they're going to react it's like
yeah it's just that's just the paranoia start start general
like i i start with like so what do you like what are you doing now like where
do you live that's a good one like where do you live
and what do you do there is a good way to like start out and then
like you get your feet wet from there don't start with who in your family
died this year like that and don't and try to say general i think don't ask
like are you still really into deep blue
something because i seem to remember you being very into that band
sure and what if their answer is yes i'm a groupie for them
hi they let me in the band i'm in the band i hand job to all all of them
yes could you just throw out like how's your family and then
let them fill in the blanks as they feel comfortable with that's like as
opposed to like well as opposed to like how's your dad
doing how's your brother who had all those
risky tendencies keep it keep it real keep it real real general i think and
and a lot of people in your life that's gonna like
whatever they tell you is probably going to be a pretty good indication of who
they are and then you can move on from there but it's it's
it's hard and it gets harder the longer you go without
talking but man like i never get off a phone call
with one of my friends that i haven't talked to in a few months without feeling
like fucking awesome about it yeah um
you're right griff i need to just get over and just do that more just because
it really feels kind of like finding a time capsule we were like oh yeah
there's all this awesome stuff i forgot about
yeah and you think i i think this is one of the problems with like
i've really turned a corner on twitter and facebook i kind of think they're the
fucking worst now um and i think it's because like you
follow your friends on there and you see pictures of like the food that they
eat in the vacations that they take and you think like
man i really know what this guy's up to now
but you fucking don't like you gotta call them and you need to like actually have
a human conversation with them and then you will and then you'll know
you trick it social media is like a way of tricking yourself into thinking you're
staying in really good touch with their friends
but really you're just like a creepy voyeur of their the
meals that they eat well i but i will say this i think the one thing that
facebook really does well for me is even if it's not
deep it at least keeps in my mind's eye like hey you haven't talked to jordan in
a while and it's like oh yeah you know what you're
right i haven't i don't know it's like you can if you see
someone coming up that you know they haven't talked in a
long time you can sort of hide in their periphery
as you check their facebook and there is also that
get get a few sort of ground things grounders
i call them yeah a few easy ones you can ask about because yeah then you always
have the hey i saw on facebook that you just got a new puppy
how's that going and then you've got weird things
i don't know now i say that i would say no don't say that out loud no that
seems like hey i know we haven't talked in six years but i
looked at oh i still watch but isn't that completely socially
accepted at this point that people look at your facebook all like
hey the reason i follow you on facebook is so i know this shit it's not like
but it's not like you're nsa hacking them like no
i prismed you and it looks like you're really happy with that new man
i guess it might be naive of me to say this but i would like to think that if
you were close with this person they they might be feeling the same
thing and saying like hey i don't want this to be awkward but
it's been so long since we talked let's just like get down to it i i mean
i would like to think that would be the best way to approach it i know
that's completely different from how i started
yeah we changed we changed minds together just yeah but it's like you know
what just like be real and if they were really your friend and
if that's really a connection you want to rebuild
then rebuild it and sometimes that takes work and sometimes that work
is this is scary it's going on too long i love you
i got it it's taking forever it's just that i miss you get it i feel like we
never talk we get it we just never talk and i miss you
get it we get it we get it whatever you have to we get it
okay i get your whole thing i get it you're just wrong
we we just did like 30 minutes on that question we were wrong the whole time
you didn't say anything i just got i got bored enough that all i
just did i just think you feel like you're wrong
i feel like no right answer should take that long to explain
i feel like the easier the the simpler answer is usually the right one isn't
that what ockham's razor is yeah i think ockham's razor is from harrys.com
check out harrys.com for all your shaving needs
bitch we're not doing they didn't pay for that edit that out bleep that
no i'm just using a harry's razor right now so i thought about it can we talk
they're not bad they're pretty good can we talk about the companies that did
give us money to talk about the product
problem with doing ads for major companies
is that you get all this money and you don't have anywhere to put it
it is such an issue i deal with it every day i deal with it every day we insist
all of our uh payments come in quarters yeah so have you seen hoarders it's kind
of like that have you seen a show of hoarders have you
seen quarter hoarders what what's the show called quarter hoarders
you're saying quota quota hoda it's called hodor hoarders
i got all these piles of hodors what do i do with them
well you can put them in simple.com you can go to simple.com and put your giant men
deposit all your giant men at simple.com the way banking should be
they're rebuilding banking from the ground up if you don't
that you can spend without stress if you don't know if you have enough hodors
in the bank you can spend them simple simple is the only other word that hodor
knows that's how good a product it is that's
how good it is yeah save automatically you have a goal i want
to have a thousand hodors by the end of this year
simple will tell you how many hodors you need to save it'll do it
for you it'll put it aside for you um that's good because i these hodors are
just burning a hole in my pocket you can actually deposit hodors from
your phone now here's the way that works you take a picture of it
and then you and then they scan it and they say okay that one counts and then
you burn it yeah you burn that in your account he's
gonna be scared of the of the fire and the technology the
whole process is not going to be great for the hodor but you've got to
digitize them you got to uh it's just like tron uh it's
they're instant free transfers between your different simple accounts
for when you forget to pay your roommates for that cheetos bag
i don't know i think i mean bag of cheetos it says bag of cheetos
okay so in our copy it says that cheetos bag i'm assuming we're talking about a
bag of cheetos they're not selling collectible cheeto
wrappers i've got a weird like packaging economy you
and your roommate was this copy that simple sent us or is
this travis's own input travis
no this is the copy this is the copy they sent us
when you have to pay your roommate for that cheetos bag what is there
okay the banking solution they have come up with is arguably the greatest banking
solution on earth oh they've solved banking they
fixed banking but it sounds like their whole situation
maybe their home life is not so great i mean it also says
pay your bills fast before your hot pocket is done microwaving
they uh yeah and they've also imagined a sort of
odd post-apocalyptic bubble future that's only in your apartment where
cheetos bags are currency right that'll be uh two cheetos bag and
three pop tops sorry man that's how we do it in the
wasteland what are you talking about the wasteland
this is barbersville now i call that's why i call my apartment it's the
wasteland it's a post things are very good here
it's my roommate and i haven't talked in six years can i cut you a rent check for
my part of the rent uh your money's no good here your
american currency you can go to the bank by which i mean
the kroger's where you can exchange your american
currency for cheetos bags thank you very much
uh don't bring the cheetos around here though the actual cheetos i'm highly
allergic to uh simple is a real bank it's fdic
insured uh and you can go to simple.com slash my
brother to skip the wait list uh otherwise you have to wait to get in
but that's that's that's not gonna happen you're gonna go to simple.com
slash my brother and uh simple that's the way banking should be
listen we joke but go check it out it really is like an amazing shit
it really is it's an amazing it's an amazing shit
you know what you know what i don't need
um uh advertiser dollars apparently uh guys this i'm this is not a joke i'm
very hungry um and i would like did you eat that
bagel yet no i'm looking forward to that bagel
it's a uh it's a what is it reclaimed wheat
or reclaimed it's a reclaimed grains bagel
can i tell you the problem with that griffin it's gonna give you a fat ass
it is it goes straight to your ass my traitor joe's
reclaimed grain bagel it's gonna go straight to your ass
you know i bought that thinking it was gonna be real tasty what did they
reclaim those grains from from an old school
from an old old shutdown school uh-huh ah fuck we left so many cranes
behind in our old school you can make a living just like
demolishing buildings and returning those getting all the grains out of them
yeah they give you a dollar per pound of grain that's a good good deal
or you could just fucking go to naturebox.com
so you can get in shape get blasted get tiny for the beach
your enemy is the vending machine that's all pre-packing you gotta kill the
vending machine you have to destroy the vending machine to get strong
uh it it's easy naturebox makes eating better easy they're gonna send you great
tasting snacks right to your door uh you know what i i've been eating a
lot of french toast granola lately that's a very good you know
so good i it slipped my mind and i forgot to like
fill out my order so they just sent me like five surprise snacks
and they're the fucking best um got some sea salt pop pops how are those pop pops
they are so fucking good it's like a mixture of kind of like uh
the the like toasted kernels and like slightly popped
popcorn the flavor is like really subtle but still good
we got some cheddar onion um cheddar onion uh sunflower seeds
um oh this uh peanut butter nom noms okay so they're just like making they're
like making like fudge fudge fudge is yes but the
peanut butter nom noms are these really soft kind of cookies
oh they're incredible they're really really great um
they're all healthy they don't sound healthy you talk about i don't know
pop pops doesn't doesn't sound healthy it is i promise there's no trans fats
no fructose get all that fructose out of there
um no you'll even find sacks that are gluten conscious and uh do not contain
gmo no gmos if that kind of thing is important to
you it should be you're poisoning your body now
well it is if it's important to you it's on there you look up in the sky and you
see all the kim trails gmos are just kim trails that you eat
okay that's fine i just think it's anti-science to begin
oh come on that's just me no i personally but
i don't care one way or the other because i don't care about things because
i'm dead inside you should care about kim trails absolutely
you should care about who is kim trails
try nature box dot now 50 off your first box
by going to nature box dot com forward slash my brother that's a
pretty big savings if you want to try this it's like half it's like
almost half and there's different sizes of boxes too with like different amounts
in them so like if you were you know if you're one
person if you're a family it goes both ways and those things last
man like i was really worried that uh like teresa and i we like snacks i was
afraid we'd burn through them it pretty much balances out so that
like once a month you get the box and then
you're just about ready for a new one when the new one arrives and they stay
fresh for a while so yeah yeah yeah i've been i've been eating that
french fry for a while anyway nature box dot com slash my brother go
um i got a message for jennifer spies you think it's spies
yeah not speeds i'm gonna go with the spies
it's way better right jennifer spies uh from michael
feel can we just get some names whatever happened to like johnson
hi my name is jeff johnson that's easy my name is jack johnson my name is jack
johnson i'm public health um here's a message it's for jennifer
happy birthday jennifer this is what the money i got from
drilling screws out of asbestos filled ceiling tiles went towards so i hope
it's worth it wow wow probably not sorry about your
lungs i love michael way to just be like hey this is what i did for you i love
you and i hope this shows up in an episode
at least within a month of your birthday on june 13th this is
pretty close yeah about a week and a half afterwards um
happy birthday jennifer happy new lung day michael because
sorry about your mess so sorry about your whole thing
sorry about your miso sorry about your miso soup
sorry about all that stuff uh i took a quick look to see if i could
find jennifer on twitter i don't think this is her their uh
username is at jen equals drink and drink is in all caps
and her last tweet was from june 8th and she says
if we can't say and the n word is here okay you can't say yeehaw lmao
hashtag passion hashtag crystal keg wow it's a pretty good tweet i don't
think that's our jennifer that doesn't sound like our jennifer
does it no that's not the jennifer i know she would never use that kind
oh this jennifer also asked where can i buy use sex toys and she should know
if she listens to our program where she can do that i don't think that extreme
restraint yeah they don't have like an exchange program they don't have
they can't give you store credit for your
salty dildo no it is not a one in one out kind of thing
although they do have a product called the one in one out right
um uh so happy birthday happy birthday jennifer please don't be this terrible
person we just found but you aren't i know you aren't
no you're not and don't go tweet at that person please
yeah everybody don't tweet at that person they've got enough going on
they have a lot of terrible stuff this next message is for hannah and it's from
becca aka bex and bex says to my big sis hannah
it's been an amazing 20 forward for you congrats on your phd
your new job and your impending nuptials you're the best sister in the world
even if you did used to call me chubby laboo
i'm sad you're moving away but i can't wait to visit you in austin where i fully
expect you to become bfs with griffin keep killing it and that's from chubby
laboo i already have chubby laboo says i have like one bff already and like
i it's very serious to me you know i'm not i don't i'm not like a run around
sue i have the one bff and i you know i keep
is your bff rachel oh yeah yeah yeah you hesitated no yeah
of course my wife my wife you guys remember where at
my wife no but austin's great you're gonna really like it
uh i'm too shy to talk to um so that's uh from bex to hannah
and then we had one uh to jennifer from michael um thank you
guys uh for both telling everyone that you love
them and supporting the show if you'd like to get a message
on the money zone then go to maximumfund.org forward slash
jumbotron and you could do you know birthday message or happy
anniversary you could also if you have a business and you would like to help us
make people go to your business then go to maximumfund.org forward slash
jumbotron that's what that is y'all want to yahoo
probably not make fun of your copy no we might no we only make fun of like big
business copy like independent alternative we're
alternative we're all you know what here here is a fucking fact
for you dear listeners that will shock you and there has never been
an advertiser that has pulled their advertising from
our show nope uh and i think we keep pushing it just to
like we keep walking the line because i think we kind of deep down want that
eventually like we want that to happen we're trying
to be controversial like we really are i don't think they
listen that's what that or it's some kind of
like weird shaming thing where they're like we do deserve
advertising as uh masochism apparently sure hey ross
hey carrie hey it's me your co-host oh yeah we have a show don't we have a
show oh no ross and carrie it's about
undercover investigations of fringe groups
yeah like the toni olamo ministries cult yep that's led by a pedophile
he's in jail he's in jail also we became mormons we became raelians
which is a ufo group that's right we joined the ordo templi
orientis yes the 911 truthers we got cupped we got
acupunctured we got rakey we've pretty much anything that you've
heard of and been like that doesn't sound quite right we've done
that so you don't have to do it so if you want to hear about this and
you should then go to maximum fun dot org
uh this yahoo was sent in by tanner thank you tanner it's by yahoo answers
user naomi who asks i got baptized then smoked
weed a day later and this happened i got baptized on
wednesday then smoked some weed well reggie
is that like a brand of nickname is that like a strain
hold on i'll hook it up you guys go on i'm on that reginald
on thursday on that val johnson i'm on that reginald val johnson
on thursday i've smoked okay fuck this question no punctuation i got
baptized on wednesday then i smoked that sweet dank reginald val johnson on
thursday i've smoked before so it wasn't new to
me and then it says in d
which is like maybe a typo maybe they meant to say in bd like no big deal
so at first i was feeling good just chilling
then like 40 minutes later i got in the car and was going to drive home but
everything went right then black and then another in d
i couldn't see i drove over a curve curb and got really dizzy and threw up
after that i was a little high and felt pretty much sober
but that had never happened to me before i've smoked
way more than that before and not long ago from that day
so i don't know what happened any clues
just to clarify reggie is like regular like street grade
weed
that's uh that sucks because reginald val johnson
is far from a regular street grade actor no he is definitely top quality he is
that is dank kush prime kush is this person's theory that had
they not been baptized this wouldn't have happened but because they were
baptized jesus looked down and said like oh
smoking weed a can't do that you got smoked them you
gotten sanctified waters and that will blend
with that good good reginald cannabis inside your body
that dank dank kush and it's going to create a chemical reaction in your body
that is going to be a fucking like visceral experience
oh so it's like it's a cross like bong water and holy water together
gonna fuck you up not like jesus was like no more weed for you
no i mean there's a purely scientific reason for it sanctified water
plus val johnson tight tight smoke in your lungs i feel like enough
time passes between the introduction of the fact that this person got
baptized and the end of the question that it almost takes on sort of a a
checkoff's gun uh uh veneer so that you don't you
aren't actively thinking about it and maybe that's the twist
it's like you're it gives you long enough to sort of forget about it and
then so when it pops back up you're like oh that makes perfect sense so maybe
this question i sort of literally did not remember
the baptism part and when people circle back around on it oh
actually now that you mentioned that baptism i've forgotten i call that i
call that trope burke's law because that was every episode of burke's
law well they fucking show you they give you
all the clues that you need to solve the mystery
it's right there at the beginning especially if you're 75
if you're 75 years old you're gonna figure it out it is slylock fox level
difficulty um we can agree that this person had
an embolism right or i don't think that that is what happened
i think that i am a huge advocate for not a huge
advocate i don't actually for smoking weed and driving
i support no i support no i no no i support the legalization of marijuana
pretty broadly these are helpful reminders i think
i think is a is a helpful reminder that not just the smart people get to
purchase legal weed there are going to be some people that
get baptized and then get super reggie high the next day and then
think you know what i'm going to motor on over
to a destination of my choice in a car a heavy one too a real heavy the heaviest
car i can find i'm just gonna get get to driving in the
heaviest car i can find i'm a little high but i'm mostly over puke
should i take the smart car nah i'll go with the homer
is it possible that the original val johnson was was laced with a little
urkel
i'm on that urk i'm on that jaleel i mean just like a
five percent urk mix you know what i mean just enough you're like yeah i feel
fine but then you introduce like a bunch of
moving objects in your rear view mirror and suddenly blackout puke puke puke
you said you were selling the reggie this is this is fucking richie
this is bullshit i paid top dollar richie was a character on that show
little yeah he was the little kid he was the littlest richie
um guys is it cool to like when he got baptized did he not be like
as part of this ritual i promise to you jesus that i'm not gonna
do as much weed smoking i'm gonna give you like a 24 hour
window of just like blissing out on these holy waters i don't think jesus
gives two shits either way i guess not but this guy obviously
thinks that there's a connection there because he has smoked this reggie on
the reg on the reg so like reggie on the reg this has never
happened to him before and he seems like the kind of person
that smokes a lot of weed he seemed like an informed scientist
he's taken notes and a complex journey which is what makes me think that this
reaction transcends science i don't know guys i think there
might be a little uh i think i think you might have gotten
touched by angel this week on divine intervention
maybe i've watched that show by the way makes you think
have you listened to the bim bam yeah that podcast makes me think
and that's why i like it i wonder if this person got to the end of writing
this question and thought what am i doing
what what am i doing here i i don't think there's even a question
what am i doing i think we're just a weird story i'm telling
i feel like i'm telling a weird story i don't know what the response would be
or who could respond to and i have to get ready for work as vice president of
the united states of america
i got another question for you guys i'm getting married next may
while planning the celebration has been a breeze my fianc
and i have hit on one point of conflict whether to have a wedding cake
or go non-traditional to have a wedding pie
if i can get you brothers on my side maybe my big day will have that extra
berry filling to put it over the top that's from fearfully frosted in
philadelphia now you can't see this at home
but uh the f from fearfully frosted has been translated
to replace the ph in philadelphia oh that's fine
can i tell you something choose i love the way that you say the word fianc you
sound like john malkovich's character in rounders
when you say like trying to say fancy yeah
fancy um um chick chick chick let's all
simultaneously do our teddy kgb impressions
chick you give some money money that was my favorite i we're a cake
family damn it um this this used to be like the big
point for i feel like we had again have to have talked about this on the show
like uh we used to have like brutal fights
about whether cake or pie was better um
i feel like i feel like wedding traditions in our generation have been
all but phased out yeah at this point don't you think i
think that the idea of doing something because it's traditional
is the wrong reason to do anything if you're saying
i want pie and my fianc wants cake that's a much different discussion then
we both want to have pie but he's worried about breaking i actually feel
like the commerce the conversation about whether or
not to have cake or pie at x event is more important than the
conversation as to whether or not it's important at a wedding just the
general question is the is the thing you need to be worried
about whether cake or pie is more delicious
right and we can't get into this we could let me throw this out
both yeah what have a groom's a groom's pie
yeah you know at our wedding we did uh like cheesecake bites
because we love cheesecake and that was the way we went with it and then
and it was kind of that well but not what i would have guessed well here's the
point of the story is that we were worried about it going in
like oh is this weird because we're not going to
have like you know the traditional like three-tiered cake or whatever
and then it was one of the things that people talked about most of like
i love that that was so cute and so you guys and blah blah blah it's functional
too and i have to worry about like fucking like waiting
my turn to get like a person who didn't want to be there to like
cut me off a big old chunk is the chunk too big i can't eat all this but i have
to also feel guilty is it too small and i have to go wait and fucking
line again and yeah we just set out like cake
plates on each table with cheesecake on them it was
it was pretty brilliant if i say so myself but if you guys want to do pie do
pie if you want to do cake and pie do cake
and pie if you want to do a pie cake shut up that's not a fucking thing
if you want to do ice cream cake if you want ice cream cake at your wedding
fuck it that sounds awesome go to dq throw them on the table go to fucking dq
and get some blizzards and then wedding blizzards if you want
wedding chicken strip baskets go for it this they got that texas toast
i as part of my vows will now feed you a dilly bar
i gotta say travel i drove your uh your cheesecakes to the event that
was my contribution is i went and picked up your cheesecakes
and i don't know that i've ever been so excited as when i
had four cheesecakes stacked up on a passenger seat knew that i was going to
be able to hit those home i never ever get that excited about cake
nope ever no they were good too we got that was our special like you
know the the wedding party table we got cakes from cheesecake factory
i will say i will say that kicking it at cheesecake factory
on sunday morning uh the day of the morning of my brother's wedding which
was kind of a weird experience for me i was the most dressed up anyone's ever
been inside a cheesecake factory ever um felt a little bit out of place a little
bit fish out of water was that before or after i made you drive
back to my house to get my special Travis made us get
his special wedding night underwear and i had to look at them
i had to get them i had to get them from the underwear spot
where he kept all of the things and i had to get it
and i touched them to yeah they acknowledged that they i had to
i had to okay here's the order i learned about them
i said that's terrible then i learned that i would have to retrieve touch
no feel believe hold grasp acknowledge become
embrace absorb and now you guys are doing that at home
they were silky as fuck no they were silky and they were black
and they were kind of black just a little bit sheer just a little
bit sheer so i just just like i'm a little bit dead now i acknowledged that
they existed i had to touch them my balls went into thought about
Travis thought about Travis's balls how they would feel
inside of them had to acknowledge the moment where Travis
decided to get special wedding underwear then go to a store possibly with his
bride to be had to think had to learn a lot about
traps more of an impulse buy it was a lot more of an impulse buy where i
looked and i said you know that's gonna feel real good i had to learn a lot
about Teresa that i didn't know and the things that she prefers
there around there terrific best wedding ever here let me rewrite
all of my best man speech because i have new fucking subjects that i
need to address i'm gonna oh wait i'm gonna go pop up
music behind the behind the music for a minute don't say pop up
pop up video behind the music i bought the wedding underpants
not for a sexy bent but because i knew the silky smooth material
would prevent any chafing day of which i didn't want to deal with as i'm walking
down the aisle i need to call on you Travis uh
the the decision to buy special sexy wedding underwear may have been an
impulse buy the the decision to send your brother
to go get your special wedding and it was malicious
it was a combination of because i knew that if i didn't
i would think about it all day because that's the way my brain works like oh
well i might rather i think about it all day and then to
all life it was funny to me to make griffin yeah it sure was i guess
your keeps in here man you said whoever you want to go get your special wedding
underwear let's finish the show i have to go
purge uh thank you so much for listening to my brother my brother and me
uh we hope you've been having a good time uh uh listening to it
uh just like when we were making it we had a good time
uh uh thank you to people tweeting about our show like ryan lynch
uh patrick doan uh frida zinc sam tepper matt
wade rocket blue delinquente i think whoa uh many others beautiful
uh thanks everybody good luck to our friend daniel corsetto who's setting off
across this great land of ours hopefully she'll take our podcast along
the letter entertainer i i want to thank a few people
that sent us uh some stuff to our p.o box it's p.o box
5400 west virginia 25706 uh courtney salazar sent us some uh some
snack bars and i've been enjoying those my wife had one for breakfast just this
morning are they good tell me about them they're
good they're good they're kind uh it's like the cranberry almond
nut type things uh thank you for the beautiful postcard to boy it in the
beltway sent us a lovely note about uh
how much our show has meant to her another one from renee along those same
lines so thank you so much renee that was lovely we got a
uh uh and she graduated so congratulations from the university of
baltimore congratulations renee sorry we couldn't be there for
your special day i got a beautiful postcard
from adam and shelly it is a little boy peeing
okay from from the neva ones i believe is that what they're into over there and
then uh thank you to uh i believe this is
jeffrey for a uh postcard of uh from hawaii
that just has a uh uh some sort of uh island woman in a thong
in front of a waterfall and it says paradise on it awesome
you definitely know the way to our heart and uh thank you to terry and andy
for copy of their book the complete monster exchange program they thought
we would uh get a kick out of it so they sent it along so thank you so much for
that thank you a lovely gift travis you and buttercup
also got uh a gift oh yeah downstairs though i'll get it
for you next time you come in so thank you
to whoever sent that along um that's mysterious thank you to everybody who
came out to the other live show it was amazing
um uh and sorry for the audio quality of the the new
york live shows we had to kind of throw it together last minute um
we try to fix it up as much as we can uh there's james gowdy complained about
that and then i was i was joking around with him and now he
like i think he's legitimately mad i tried to
we're so sorry please if you're listening he's not listening he's done
he's not listening he's done listening because i pissed him off i didn't mean to
so i'm sorry to him um but yeah well we're still gonna parse those
or i said that last week and it didn't make sense we're spreading them out a
little bit um i i'll be out of town july 4th
weekend we're doing our like fucking show
planning on the air now um so maybe we can drop one then and then
justin's gonna have a baby in like god like a month and a half
so i imagine we'll need one for that you get and we're we're in
talks and planning to do more live shows so yes we weren't able to make it out to
the ala one we're doing so many more where do you
live 2014 2015 where do you live in the country
we're gonna be there probably we will come to there we will come to that
um we will take your money we will um spend it probably on reggie yeah
so tight um but seriously thanks everybody for coming out it
it was a very very wonderful evening thanks also to john roderick and the
long winters for the use of our theme song it's a departure off the album
putting the days to bed our boat party tickets still on sale i
feel like they're like in the final stages it's like final stages but you
can actually get uh you can get them uh
for cheaper uh you use the coupon code
middle list no no coupon code last minute sexabunga 50 bucks off it's till
wednesday you go to boatparty.biz you are not
gonna want to miss this it's i really really want to get if i if i had more
vacation time i would be there in a fucking heartbeat if i wasn't taking my
honeymoon this year i would definitely definitely definitely
be going it seems amazing and we want to say thanks to nature box
um for god continuing to be an amazing supporter of the show if you haven't
gone to check it out what the fuck are you waiting for go to
naturebox.com slash my brother and you'll get 50 off your first order
go now also thanks to simple um who's rebuilding banking from the ground up
and basically has just revolutionized bank they've solved banking they fixed
it um they put people before policies and it's
really just an amazing idea um and there's a huge wait list that you
can skip if you go to simple.com slash my brother
um so go check out naturebox and go check out simple.com
um also if you haven't taken the chance to listen to
all the other amazing max fun shows um then then you need to do that because
i love them they're very good i listen to them all the time
i spent the last three days listening to episodes of the goose down
uh oh no ross and carrie wham bam pow lady to lady
uh one bad mother jordan jesse go bullseye
all right throwing shade sure uh stop podcasting yourself
i feel like i'm missing some oh and saw bones
which if you like the dulcet tones of justin mcroy
or even if you don't don't worry sydney's there and she'll she'll make it all
worthwhile yeah um but check out these amazing shows just
go to maximum fun.org and all of them there oh judge john hodgeman i knew i
was missing one well you forgot a lot anyway ah damn it but there's tons go
check out maximum fun.org you're gonna find something you love um okay
we are done uh this is the end of this final yahoo is sent in by justin long
thank you justin long it's by yahoo answers user addison may
who asks memory foams do they record dreams
i'm just mcroy i'm jealous mcroy my brother my brother me kiss your dad
scram ellipse
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported have you made
vacation plans yet the second annual atlantic ocean comedy
and music festival is ready to set sail this summer
and we want to see you on board imagine amazing comedians stellar music and
beautiful caribbean views it all takes place july 25th through
28th en route to nassau the bahamas and frankly
we've impressed even ourselves with this lineup of bullseye favorites
you've got moshe kasher i was in an airport recently you ever you ever see
somebody and you're just like oh so you're what's
wrong with everything in the world kyle canane anybody else in here
gets so drunk last month you had to call a cab just take you to wendy's
w kamau bell so complicated my feelings
morgan murphy i don't know if you guys know what a facelift is it's
when they take your face skin and they uh peel it away from your face and in
that little space there that's where they find your self-esteem
and besides them greg barrett chris fairbanks karen kulgarov natasha
lugero guy brannum tony coming and carol cole plus an
awesome music lineup hosted by john rodrick of the long winters
and featuring our pal gene gray come on what else are you going to be doing
don't miss the funniest weekend of your life get your tickets right now
go to boat party dot biz yeah that's right
boat party dot biz the atlantic ocean comedy and music festival
comedy music shuffleboard