The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
Here come the McElroys, we've got jokes and bits.
We're gonna give advice and do funny skits, laughter it is in store.
Come inside and see, it's time to start.
It's my brother, my brother and me.
Hey everybody, welcome to my brother, my brother, mean advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middlest brother, the old spotty dog, Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
It kind of fucked me up that you said hey and not hello, which is...
Yeah, I've never said hey, it felt casual.
It felt like we were on Twitch or something more casual than...
Like a TGI Friday.
Hey guys.
Yeah, hey guys.
Don't forget to like and subscribe.
Yeah.
I've been working on some songs during quarantine, and I finished one up just recently.
All right.
And I wanted to see what you guys thought.
Now, what kind of songs are you talking about?
Like what genre?
What kind of song is it?
It's just one song.
But you said plural.
I mean, you said plural.
Does it play an instrument?
No, there's no instruments on it.
It's acapella.
Okay.
Can I sing it?
And please don't interrupt me or anything while I'm singing it, okay?
And it's just a song.
How will we know when the song's over and we can start talking?
There's like one whole rest.
So if it goes longer than a whole rest.
Okay.
Here's the song.
And your brothers will never know that you're eating chili while you record.
No, that's a secret you'll take to your grave.
Now your brothers will never know all the beef and beans you're shoving in your gourd.
They'd prefer it if you would just behave.
It is Thursday at 2.41 p.m. and this is happening in real life on the cilantro sprinkled across the bowl that was chopped up recently by your wife.
Okay.
What do you guys think so far?
That's verse one.
Now.
Oh, it's not.
There's more to it than that?
That's just the beginning.
I wanted to stop for notes.
Now, let me say this.
Uh-huh.
It's 2.41 p.m. now.
Yeah.
It's 2.42 according to the clock at this point.
Well, that's not my point, Justin.
I think what you were hoping or maybe anticipating here was that we would be upset that you're eating chili during recording.
I'm upset that you're eating lunch at almost 3 p.m.
Okay.
Well, it is just a...
I feel like I clarified at the beginning is just a song.
It's a song, Travis.
It's just a song.
Well...
It's like the...
It's like confessional standup.
It doesn't always...
It's not describing what's happening right now.
It could be a recording that he did, you know, a couple months back at 2.41 p.m. now, 2.42 p.m. on Thursday.
Yeah, but there were a lot of specifics in there, Griffin.
And at one point, I believe he said, this is happening right now.
Right.
But that's in the...
That was...
Did you hear that that was part of the song?
Yeah.
We've done this 560 episodes.
We've done it 560 times.
Like, odds are we have recorded on a Thursday at 2.41, now 2.42 p.m.
Can I just...
Can I just continue?
Yeah, sorry.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
And the spoon is literally in my hand.
Me, Justin McElroy, the person singing this song.
And it's not just a song.
It's a story about me eating chili while I record the show.
My brother, my brother and me, this episode right now.
Now that's...
Okay, Griffin, you have to admit that that seems suspicious, right?
It could have described any episode.
He said this episode right now.
It's when he's singing it.
It's just a song.
No, you said in there that it's not just a song, Justin.
No.
Okay, but that was in the song.
Who are you going to believe, Travis?
Our brother or the song?
I believe our brother.
No.
Okay.
This song, he says in the song...
It's just a song.
It's not just a song.
You said in the song that it's not just a song.
But I said in the song, if the song is just a song, you can't pick and choose what different parts you're going to listen to.
You know what?
You're right.
I can't decide you believe the part where I say it's not just a song.
No, Justin, I believe all of it.
This is the thing.
I believe all of it from start to finish that you currently have a spoon in your hand that you're eating chili that your wife puts cilantro on that you're eating it right now as we record this episode.
Travis.
You're killing me, dude.
It's just a song.
And I would sign an affidavit with my legal name in front of a notary.
Say hi to eating chili.
But it will not come to that because my brothers will believe me when I say that this is just a song, even though it's not now.
Oh, I was ready to buy in until that very last...
Ooh, that very last kickflip there.
What was different?
Did you not like it different?
What part was different?
Is it because it didn't rhyme?
No.
I was struggling with that.
No, I'm fine with free verse.
It's more that right there at the end you said it's not a song again.
Yeah.
Still not Jermaine, though.
But it's very clearly not a song.
Like if OJ Simpson put out a song like, I definitely did it, people would get suspicious.
He realized that, right?
Yeah.
Hmm.
That's...
I mean, he did put out a book that was kind of like that.
Yeah.
And he wasn't like, it was just a book.
Hey guys, it's just a book.
Weird co-winky dink.
I ate leftover chili for lunch.
What does that have to do with me?
Right before...
Well, because that was the nature of the song.
I'm not saying that that's what you did.
Oh, thank you.
Okay.
But I washed it down with a probiotic soda that Rachel brought into our house.
For some reason, it was a chunky soda.
And so my body's going to make something new.
What are you guys doing to yourself?
I had a fruit smoothie for breakfast and then I had a nice salad.
What's wrong with you two?
I had some turkey and celery and hummus.
And then chili.
Yeah, I actually had a quinoa bowl trap from Panera Bread,
so I don't know what you're talking about.
That thing I just said about the probiotic soda and the chili was a poem.
No, it wasn't a poem.
It was Robert Frost's poem about chili.
Oh, I actually remember that now that I know how you say it.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Excuse me?
My body dead ass feels quite bad.
I'm actually weirdly pretty hungry because I meant to eat lunch before.
Yeah.
I meant to eat lunch before we started recording and now I'm going to be hungry for the whole show.
Sure.
I did recently do, not that I'm saying what you said is true, Justin,
but I did recently do a livestream game in which 30 seconds before it began,
my wife lovingly brought me a plate with two big pieces of pizza on it.
Oh, God, Justin.
And then I had to eat it on the stream by ducking down below camera level,
taking a couple bites, chewing and eating, then raising back up.
Now, Justin, do you want to make any more horrific meat slapping sounds?
Guys, hold on one second.
Sydney's coming in.
No.
Yeah, no, it was delicious.
Thank you.
Yeah, the cilantro really, really helped.
Okay.
Now, Justin.
Probably just cut that.
That was a skit.
Now, Justin.
What's up?
You just said.
Tell him, Justin, it was a skit.
She said, yes.
I said what?
You said the cilantro was good and that was something.
She suggested the line about cilantro.
Yeah.
They're a comedy writing team and they're doing some sketches.
We're basically a comedy writing team?
Yeah.
You get it, Justin?
I'm not going to rest until I crack this.
Yeah.
You can try it.
Whatever.
You can't run from me, Justin.
I will hunt you down like a dog and I'll prove you ate that chili during this recording.
I don't think you ever will.
Justin, I got a whole board set up on my wall already.
I got strings running the things.
The only...
Now, listen, I'm looking at your board via Skype.
No, that was just a poem.
I don't have a board, Justin.
It was just a poem.
It wasn't a real board, Justin.
Even if you did have a board, the only thing you could pin up there is that Justin repeatedly
stated that he ate chili during the recording.
Right.
That's a bad board.
Can we do a...
Oh, I'm sorry.
This has been a bit the whole time, Justin.
I knew it was real and just a song at the same time.
I don't even care.
It was just a bit.
Yeah.
What about a question?
You know what I deserve for that?
What?
A Bitcoin.
Oh, I get it.
Boy, I wish we got a coin for every bit we did.
I think it'd go a little something like this.
Did I invent the term Bitcoin?
You did.
Bit?
Just now.
Did I coin Bitcoin bit?
It's just you're taking so long to get...
It's taking a really long time.
You get mad at me for interrupting you, but everyone knew where you were going 30 seconds
before you said coin a Bitcoin Bitcoin coin.
Anticipation.
Okay.
Now this first question is not one we normally do, but it was such...
It tickled my brain.
Are you going to read it?
I love it.
You do it.
You should read it, but it's a good setup.
Who is the best farmer in the world?
You know how there's the best soccer player or basketball list in the world?
Who's the best farmer?
Who has the most farmer stats?
And that's from Gmail.
And what I love about this question, and what it makes you think is, this is not saying
are there good farmers and bad farmers?
Because yes, of course it's true.
But is there a best farmer?
Huh.
Do you know how you know who the best farmer is?
How?
He's outstanding in his field.
Okay.
Huh.
I didn't do this question just to set that up, but it popped in my head.
All right.
I liked it.
I would say whichever farm has the most crows.
Oh, you think?
The crows have spoken.
This farm is the best one.
It's got the best corn or grapes or whatever crows like to eat.
Probably corn.
I think it's corn.
I mean, it's Mr. Monsanto.
Yeah, I love that.
In his many farms.
What I like about this question, too, is it has a deeper implication that every job,
there is a best at it, right?
Sure.
Like that there is out there somewhere the world's best sanitation worker that can like
pick up a garbage can and kind of do this scoop move that launches the bags 30 yards
into the truck without having to walk over there, right?
That everyone's like, oh, they're the best, right?
Like that has to exist.
There is a ticket taker somewhere that rips it right in the middle every time.
You know what I mean?
Right.
There has to be a best.
Someone has to be the best at it.
Yeah.
And I feel like that's a dream that we all chase is being the best in whatever field
we're enthusiastic about.
I feel like for a sanitation worker, it would be the robot arm that lifts up the can and
dumps it in and doesn't lose like a pizza box over the side or something like that.
Like maybe they were in the military.
They did one of those bomb exploding robots, and so they got good garbage arm training
for that.
And now I'm writing a fucking Tom Clancy novel in our podcast.
I do apologize for that.
Is there something that you guys think you're the best at?
In the world?
Yeah.
Like when everybody looks at the leaderboard right there at the top, you got most saying
the name of Justin McElroy or Griffin McElroy.
Hmm.
No.
Wow.
That's a deep dark.
No.
Nothing.
I'm the best at not remembering to get a napkin or paper towel when I get my food at a restaurant.
Oh, yeah.
No, I've said that.
I said that about you before.
Griffin, every time.
I come back to the table with our food, and you guys are like, where's the napkins?
And I'm like, I did not get those.
And then you always say to me, you're the best at that.
You're the best at that.
It's so consistent.
You're the best at not getting those.
That's probably up there for me.
Mm-hmm.
Not the worst.
I mean, there's less thing I'm not the worst at.
You don't think there's anything you're not the worst at?
Because I would say, I'm not saying that about you.
I think it's way easier to be the worst at something.
Oh, sure.
You know?
No, because you get to a base level where just lack of any experience is a great leveler.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
You could say worst stock trader, and you're going to hit a point of the population where
like, don't know, never looked into it, do not know about it, don't know what it is.
And that's like a wide swath.
You couldn't be the worst just because of your ignorance.
Yeah.
There couldn't be one worst.
I actually have bad news about this best farmer question.
What's that?
Well, I was thinking about it and how it's like all family farms, and it's like all huge
family farms over, and it's all just these big corpo farms.
Oh, yeah.
And then I started looking into it a little more, and here's what they don't want you
to know, guys.
What's that?
There are no more farmers.
Oh.
Yeah.
We actually don't have farmers anymore in America.
A lot of it comes from China, and a lot of it comes from robotically run food farms that
are, but there's no farmers anymore.
If you're listening to this and you think that you're a farmer, someone's running the
long grift on you because we don't have them anymore.
Now, what about farmers only, Justin?
That's why that crashed in the.com bubble of pets.com, farmersonly.com.
I lost my fucking shirt when farmers only went under.
Luckily, I had Christian Mingle there to kind of keep me afloat.
Oh, I'm more of a plenty of fish guy, but yeah.
Hey, can I do a Yahoo?
Yeah, I'd like that grift.
Thank you.
This one was sent in by Amy.
Thanks, Amy.
It's Yahoo Answers user Ray who asks, how do you become the guy who controls the family
dinner table?
Oh.
Like in the show Boardwalk Empire, Nucky Thompson?
Is that-
That can't be it.
I don't know if that's a typo.
I'm Nucky.
It was Nucky.
Welcome to-
That can't be it.
Time for me to-
I'm assuming this is on some sort of like Boardwalk Empire-centric sub-Yahoo because
that is the only place that that program would be summoned up for polite discussion.
Without even knowing the rest of the question, Tony Soprano should be the reference, right?
Not Nucky Thompson.
It's Nucky Thompson.
I'm Nucky.
Thanks for enjoying the meatloaf today.
Nucky, can I ask a question?
No.
You can't.
In the show Boardwalk Empire, Nucky Thompson is always the guy with the cool stories and
stuff to say at big family parties.
I'd love to be like that.
How do you become the guy who controls the family dinner table?
Now, hold on though, because the question isn't about the person at the head of table
who everyone looks to.
It's not a locational, it's not based on orientation.
I mean, that's got to contribute to it somewhat, right?
Well, if you want to be the story person though, you want to be in the middle of the table.
Because you want to just look slightly to your left and right to be able to see everybody.
Yeah, I love that.
Also, big hands, bigger the better.
You think big hands helps you because everyone is kind of quietly, subconsciously threatened
by you?
Or why the big hands?
Oh, no, sorry.
I meant big hand movements, not just like large hands.
Oh, he gesticulates.
Okay, I thought you were saying large physical hands, and then I was like, maybe that's why
they call him Nucky Thompson, because his knuckles are so ginormous.
Large hands does contribute well to large hand movements though, because you have to
do a lot less work to just like, now you've moved seven inches.
Because the hands are so big, it doesn't take much.
Does being the source of the food help you sort of seize the day here?
Like if they're eating you?
No, well, that would certainly be a topic of like a real starter, you know what I mean?
Oh, if they're like serving sushi off of you, you mean?
Oh, no, I thought you were saying like, we're eating Nucky's forearm today, and you would
kind of have to talk to Nucky about that.
Well, kind of both of those things, right?
Kind of both.
Because if you're eating sushi and you're just way too hungry and you get into it, you're
like, oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you say something?
If you let the sushi eat off a person's body, what's the etiquette for going for the pieces
on the privacy area?
That has to be less.
You can't eat them first.
Yeah, 100%.
Nipples, I think that that's a straight, I feel like when you pick up a little hamachi
off the nipple and then you find out the nipple's under there, you can plead ignorance a bit
and just be like, I didn't think the nipple would be fair.
I would put it back, by the way.
If I did that, I would just put the sushi back.
No, if somebody saw you pick it up and put it back, the party would be over.
You would be uninvited from all future nude sushi parties.
I would let people eat sushi off my body if I was fully clothed.
If I was wearing a suit, I'd put sushi on my sushi suit.
I feel like it's just whoever is the most proactive, whoever sort of starts the conversations
and guides it.
It's less about power and strength and being naked and having sushi on your body.
You don't have to wrestle that away from anybody.
I'll tell you who's good at dominating conversations, it's Justin.
I'm going to show you guys, Justin's going to do a little practical example here for you.
Griffin and I will have a conversation and Justin's going to come in and nucky all over it.
You ready?
Travis, did you watch the Blues game last night?
I did.
Those coyotes are really giving them the run around, huh?
Yeah, but they did some great scoring and shooting, and I like the way that one of them iced another one.
Yeah, I mean, Bennington's doing his best out there, but unless that defense solidifies,
they're not going to be able to keep it out of their zone, you know?
Yeah, and I was amazed at how many triple dekes they got away with, you know what I mean?
Yeah, those are the new hockey rules because of COVID regulations.
There's the slap shot.
It looks like Justin's trying to say something.
Justin, are you trying to say something?
Oh, so you finally ran out of steam.
See, this is the secret.
You hang back and you let everybody else burn out.
So anyways, yeah, the Blues game was great.
And then you stand up and you take control of the table.
You've had your shot.
All the sushi fell off.
We all heard how that worked out.
Don't stand up.
Don't you talk over me.
Don't you talk over – I smashed a bottle on your head.
Roll dexterity saving throw.
I got a 17 plus 3, a 20.
You effortlessly duck out of the way.
I attack Nucky.
Oh, hell yeah.
Get him.
Fuck him up.
That's a 15 plus 2, a 17.
Does that beat your AC?
Did you use pure silver?
Yes, of course.
I'm not a noob.
Yes, I am defeated.
Okay.
That's one way to do it.
I guess I haven't watched enough Boardwalk Empire to be really useful here.
No, that's basically how it goes.
I guess.
There was a lot of D&D influence on that show.
There was also – it felt like a little Peaky Blinders in there, Justin.
Was there just a little Peaky Blinders?
I've watched even less.
Are those two different shows?
It's like Boardwalk Empire and then Boardwalk Empire colon Peaky Blinders.
Okay, I see.
I got another way to control the dinner table, the family dinner table.
So why don't you two start?
I'm talking about something.
Hey, Justin, did you see that new episode of Boardwalk Empire?
No, that hasn't been on for a really long time.
No, they just started making more of them.
I don't think that that's actually accurate.
Yeah, Tom Welling's in it.
Hey, get this.
When I was recording my other member –
Sorry, guys.
I got a phone call.
Yeah.
No, it's me.
Yeah, I can talk.
Yeah, we're having dinner.
Can you – sorry.
Sorry, one second.
Can you guys please just give me – can you please just give me a – this is really important.
Can you please just give me a second?
Okay, we'll just talk quietly.
No, no, no.
Just don't talk.
Thank you.
I'm back.
Thankfully, we know sign language.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
When I was recording my brother, my brother and me earlier this week, I was eating chili
during –
I fucking knew it.
What?
Yeah.
Well, this is just in the context of a bit.
We'll tell them when 2024 runs around.
Yeah, same thing.
Same thing.
We'll talk about a run then.
Yeah.
No, no.
I'm killing Murphy.
Okay.
Give my love to Dennis Kucinich.
All right.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Bye.
That was my – that's another phone call.
Sorry, guys.
You're blowing up again, huh?
Your real phone calls.
That was when I'm a kid.
I'm going to be Dennis Kucinich's campaign manager in 2024.
Oh, nice.
Now, do I know who that is, or is it just a name that I pulled from the void that is
my mom?
Is it deeply problematic?
Is he?
I don't know.
I literally don't know.
Is he alive?
I don't know.
Can I show one more way to kind of dominate?
Yeah.
I would love that.
This has been so good so far.
Okay.
You two have the conversation.
Hey, thanks for having my back on the chili thing earlier.
Yeah.
It was my pleasure.
I would do anything.
Ahem.
I will be turning in the coupon that you two gave me for my birthday for one half hour
of uninterrupted monologue by me, and I will now be completely recapping the plot of the
Brendan Fraser movie, Blast from the Past.
Yeah.
You see, it all began when Christopher Walken's character feared that there was going to be
a nuclear attack, so he built a bunker in his basement.
That bunker, it looked a lot like a house except underground, and there was raised-
Why is he talking like this?
A young Brendan Fraser, and then he became old, and he was sent out to the surface-
Like, we just used our regular voices, but Travis is doing his weird-
Where he befriended Alicia Silverstone.
British affectation.
And I believe Dave Foley.
It's funny.
I think if he knew the plot well enough, he'd go faster, right?
Yeah.
And then it turned out that because Brendan Fraser had been raised with 1950s and 60s
ideals, everyone loved him, a thing which is demonstrably untrue in today's society.
Let's do the money zone, maybe, while he continues to recap.
I'd love that.
Hey, thanks.
We all shop online for stuff, shoes, for instance.
What else?
Sandals.
Can you give me six more?
Boots, Crocs, galoshes, and shoes, and sneakers.
Yeah, put six.
So you see that promo code field at checkout, and you're like, is there a way I could save
money and not spend as much money?
And the answer is honey, which rhymes with money, which is the mnemonic device I use
for it.
It's a free browser extension, and whenever you buy something that has one of those little
coupon code fields, it scans the internet.
It releases its little burr, its little sparrows.
Or bees.
It's little bees into the-
You're not a fucking asshole.
It releases its bees out into the internet and into everybody's phones, looking for coupon
codes.
Who's got the coupon codes?
And then the bees come back, and then honey tells you, and it's like, here's $33.
So that's amazing.
It's literally, everybody should be doing it.
It's free.
It sells in just a few seconds, and you can get honey for free at joinhoney.com slash
brother.
That's joinhoney.com slash brother.
Have you guys ever eaten food for sustenance?
No, let me do this ad.
Okay.
How good is Sun Basket?
Very good.
Sun Basket is a meal delivery service that has a wild variety of options for you to get
into.
No matter how you're eating or what you like to eat, I truly believe that they are going
to have a meal to suit your needs, and more importantly, your desires.
Getting a meal on the table quickly doesn't mean you have to sacrifice nutrition or quality.
With Sun Basket, you can actually have it all every single day.
So they have the meal kit stuff, and there's a huge variety of those.
What I love that I've just recently gotten into, they have these fresh and ready meals.
They're $8.99, and they come, and you basically heat them up, and it's like a gourmet meal
that you're just instantly enjoying.
They have a chili that I just tried today, actually, earlier today, and it was so delicious
earlier today and very recently, but earlier in this day we were in, and it was so delicious
that I couldn't stop eating it no matter what.
I would do anything, anything, to keep eating it no matter what the cost or the podcast,
whatever was going on in my life.
Even if it meant losing a relationship with one of your brothers.
I don't remember exactly, Tri, but it was a very strong desire to keep eating the chili.
I do remember that.
Right now, Sun Basket is offering $35 off your order when you go right now to sunbasket.com
slash my brother and enter promo code mybrother at checkout.
That's sunbasket.com slash mybrother and enter promo code mybrother at checkout for $35 off
your order.
Sunbasket.com slash mybrother and enter promo code mybrother.
And I'll go ahead and read the tagline here, Sun Basket, let our chili take its dark hold
on you.
Huh?
I'm Judge John Hodgman.
And I'm Bailiff Jesse Thorne.
Ten years ago, I came on Jordan Jesse Go and judged my first dispute.
Is chili a soup?
It's a stew, obviously.
The judge has dispensed a decade of justice.
He's the one person wise enough to answer the really important questions like, should
you hire a mime to perform at your own funeral?
After they cry, I want them to laugh.
Do you really need a tank full of jellyfish in your den?
They smell like living creatures decaying.
Only if they are decaying.
Yeah, which they will be.
Real people, real justice, real comedy.
Winner of the Webby Award for best comedy podcast.
The Judge John Hodgman podcast every Wednesday on Maximumfun.org.
How about another question?
We're gonna help somebody else.
Okay.
We're doing better.
Do that.
I've been a huge Tom Hanks fan for years and currently have a steady girlfriend.
Recently we've been watching movies and I recommended the 2000 Tom Hanks classic Castaway.
But when I brought up the film, she refused.
She said she thought Tom Hanks was overrated and had no desire to watch the film, claiming
it's too long and probably sad.
Yes and yes.
How do I convince her to watch this Thomas classic?
Which I'm sure she would thank me later for getting her to watch.
I'm stranded in Stratton, PA.
There's different categories of films of this type, I feel like, where there's films that
are culturally important.
And then there are films that are like, if you want to know what the whole hand on a
volleyball thing is, you got to watch Castaway.
You have to do your due diligence and spend two hours watching Tom Hanks cut his teeth
out with roller, with ice skates.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
And that's the price that you pay.
Now I have a lot of films like this.
Whenever people quote Casablanca, I nod my head along.
Oh yes, yes, yes.
A classic gray film.
I do not know.
I have not seen this film.
And so there are parts that it could patch up some of my lack of cultural knowledge there,
but I've decided that my time is better spent elsewhere.
And that's what your girlfriend has done.
And you know, that's what the internet's for.
You Google what's up with the volleyball hand.
Now I know I don't have to watch the film.
You know, you make a good point, Gervin.
We've entered a new period in time, this 2021, Big Dog Ren.
And perhaps now's the time when someone's like, you haven't seen Casablanca.
You have to watch it.
And you just go, no, I don't.
Do you know how many other things there are within my reach at any given time that I could
choose to do?
Yeah, it's liberating in a way.
I will never watch a Criterion Collection film.
And that's a huge weight off, being able to say that out loud in such a public place.
But there it is.
It's out there now.
It's wild to me that that movie exists, isn't it?
That seems like Hollywood was like, people seem to really like Tom Hanks.
We should just do, just maybe just have him.
A one-hander.
Oh yeah, like a movie where he's having a good time and living his best life.
Bad time.
We destroy Tom Hanks for all of America to enjoy.
I want to hurt Tom Hanks.
And I'm a movie executive, and this is my pitch.
I want to hurt Tom Hanks and see what happens.
I'm going to hurt Tom Hanks for two hours and 24 minutes.
Did you guys see the money pit?
Every time that Tom Hanks falls in a hole or gets electrocuted or, you know, wastes
money on this bad house, that was good for me.
And I would like a film that is just about that, about Tom Hanks being hurt over and
over again.
There was a period of time that I think, here's my theory.
There's a period of time where everyone really enjoyed watching Tom Hanks get hurt.
Like the burbs and money pit.
And then I think the natural culmination of that period was cast away.
And I think after that everyone went, I don't like this anymore.
I feel bad now that we've done this to Tom Hanks.
Can he enter the period of time where the worst thing that happens to him is he's trapped
in an airport terminal?
Thank you, please.
The worst thing that happens to him is he has to go back to community college, I think.
I never saw that one.
How long has it been since you guys watched Cast Away, the film Cast Away?
Well, when did it come out?
2000?
So I would say about 21 years.
Yeah.
Yeah, I would estimate it's around there.
Quick spoilies, just because I feel like we're kind of missing it.
Just for just a minute.
On Cast Away, he does get off the island.
Do you guys remember that when he got off the island, his girlfriend married and had
a kid and they had a funeral for him before?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Justin.
What a picture that is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What a picture.
Do you think Bobby Zemeckis is like, my dream is to hang out on an island with Tom Hanks
and just me and my friend Tom, and we're just getting buckwild on it and loving it.
And that's what my dream is.
Can everyone do that?
Can we also remember that the big positive ending though is, don't worry, he still has
that one package to deliver.
So everything's not all bad for old Tommy Hanks.
Can everyone real quick do their best impression of Tom Hanks' character in the Polar Express?
I haven't seen it.
Just saying like, where's your ticket?
Now he has to say, I haven't seen it, but I'm going to do my best, okay?
But where's your ticket?
I'm Thomas Hanks.
It's not all bad.
It's more like, my ticket, please.
My ticket.
I need to see your ticket.
See, yeah, see?
All right, I'll try.
I need to see, I need to see your ticket.
Tom Hanks is a hard impression to do, huh?
Yeah, he just sounds like everybody.
Tom Hanks is the default.
All other impressions are in relation to how Tom Hanks sounds.
Do Woody.
Okay.
There's a snake in my boot.
No, not that line.
Do another line from Toy Story that Woody says.
You are a toy!
Whoa.
Hey, Trav?
That was actually Trav.
That was really fucking good.
He saw the podcast.
Hey, Rachel, can we get it again?
You are a toy!
It was really good, Travis.
It's good.
It's actually pretty good, Trav.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You've been hiding your line under a bush.
No, I'm never going to try it again.
Yeah, you can't.
That was right off the hip.
Can't hit that target again.
Nobody ever asks Travis to do it again.
He'll buckle.
He'll do a really shit job the next time because we got that magic moment on tape.
I'm so happy.
In that moment, I was Tom Hanks, you guys.
I saw his face overlap my face for a moment.
Can I do a Yahoo?
Yeah, please.
I just want to send in by Graham Roebuck.
Thanks, Graham.
He's an anonymous Yahoo Answers user who I'm going to call Dan and asks, is there a special
taste bud for chicken wings?
I like to position the foods in my mouth to taste them according to the taste bud that
tastes best for that food.
Is there one for hot wings?
I've recently learned that the taste bud map of your tongue is apocryphal, and this was
heartbreaking to me.
Really?
I thought it was a thing.
No, they're all mixed in with each other, except for the chicken wing taste bud, which
is that dangly thing in the back of your throat.
Oh, that's the chicken wing taste bud is the dangly thing that dangles down?
So if you want to get the most out of your chicken wings, you got to shove it back there
and rub it against that dangly thing.
I always thought that was a sort of, I always called it the throdom because it was like
a-
The throdom is unpleasant.
No, but you know in WAP when she says, I want to gag on a joke, I want it to touch that
dangly thing in the back of my throat.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
That's what it means.
Because she couldn't say my chicken wing taste bud.
My one big one.
Yeah.
No.
But that's why if you just hold the chicken wing on the tip of your tongue, nothing.
You can't even, it's like there's nothing there.
Yeah.
That's interesting, Trump.
As it slides whole down your gullet, you get all the flavor profile there.
Maybe cry a little bit out of joy.
Do you guys, I don't want to do it all, but do you guys know what the, do you guys know
what the radio edit of WAP is?
No.
The radio edit of WAP, and I just want to take a quick poll.
The radio edit of WAP is not wet ass pussy.
It is in fact wet.
It's wet and gushy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
No, it's worse.
Hey, it's worse, right?
Like the radio edit is worse on that one.
Yeah.
It falls into a category that another one there is, there is a song by the Ying Yang
Twins, and the real line is, we all like to see ass and titties.
And then the radio edit is, we all like to see tiggle biddies, which I would argue is
far more offensive.
Yeah.
Yeah, hugely challenging.
A hugely challenging thing.
Yeah.
Till the sweat drops down the walls.
Okay, we got wet and gushy.
Although wet and gushy is good because then it lets her rhyme the next line where she's
like, have you seen my tushy?
Which is in the original song, and it's sort of a slant rhyme with the-
Release the tapes about gushy.
Yeah.
There's not a special taste bud for chicken wings.
I wish that there was though.
I wish we could hack our tongues.
The right chicken wing engages all the buds, you know?
The right chicken wing has invites over his friend Spicy, but he makes him stand outside
and then he brings Sweet in, but then sends him out.
And then Sour is on Zoom nearby, and Bitter is occasionally welcomed.
It's Bitter's house.
But not all at once, Justin.
You're making it sound like it's stages, like a Neapolitan chicken wing.
That's how you feel really savoring it.
You're getting the heat, and then you're getting a bit of Sour.
Oh my.
Do you know how, Trav, when Justin eats chicken wings?
He first dabs it on the tip of his tongue, which he has stuck way, way out of his mouth.
And then he just kind of rubs it in a clockwise circle around his tongue and lips.
He also will swirl the chicken wing around and then sniff it deeply.
Yeah.
He says that-
Which I've always found troubling.
Yeah.
He says it helps him hit the flavor spot, and I don't, I don't.
And he'll kind of like half moan, like, look at the legs.
Yeah.
You have to see its fingers.
He doesn't actually chew and eat it, which is weird.
He sets it right back down.
Yeah.
Spits it right there in the bucket.
All naked wings that you ever eat in your entire life have been pre-lit by me.
That's true.
That's weird, but it's true.
And if they're a little bit crispy and naked, they've just been sitting out a long time.
Yep.
They've dried.
Just dried in the sun.
Yeah.
I've been eating a lot of chick wings lately.
Oh, tell me more.
No.
Okay.
Yeah.
You know what?
Here, I have this for you.
I have this for you.
I want to munch.
Squad.
What I was trying to capture there was like the soul of winter that didn't have a holiday
feel.
Oh, see, I was thinking it was feeling very, very Georgian.
Okay.
Very, uh.
Sure.
Yeah.
Very Georgian.
This is-
Point Petersburg, Chekhov, Three Sixers, Uncle Vanya.
We've never had you sort of just lay a munch squad at our feet, which is what it feels
like you've done.
I brought this to you.
I usually interrupt, right?
Yeah.
But I feel like as you get older, you don't always want to be saddled with the bad boys
podcasting.
Yeah, sure.
And I mean-
You know.
Especially as this segment moves into its denouement.
Right.
It's final.
Okay.
Right.
That's out.
So the other thing is like this one is, it's like, okay.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
And I don't want you guys to be like-
It's good of you to know that about yourself, Justin.
Why did you interrupt it?
You know?
Sure.
Like why did you interrupt us for one that's okay?
Panera bread.
Do you, you guys heard this?
Yes.
I believe that it translates to bread bread, if I'm not mistaken.
Panera bread did a, um, God, it's really weird.
You know how they have bread bowls?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
So they've made an ice and toasty bread bowl glove.
Wait.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
So what the thing is with this is that it is a hand warmer.
That's also a cup holder.
So you can drink iced coffee, even when it's cold.
And also it looks like a bread bowl.
Now, okay.
Until you got to that last part, it's just a glove, but then, huh.
That's it.
It's not made out of bread.
Is it?
Uh, no.
That's the other thing about it.
Fucking cowards.
It's not made out of bread, right?
So like, why did you?
Why did you do it?
Panera bread.
You could have had, oh my God.
Think of how much money they could have saved on soup.
If they had started selling warmed, like right there, fresh from the oven bread gloves that
you would go into a Panera bread, jam a couple of these on your fists and they'd be like,
okay, that'll be 14.99.
And you're like, I can't pay that.
Look at my hands.
How am I, how on earth am I supposed to pay that?
That could have been so nice and fun.
I sent you an image in Slack so you can look at it.
It looks so wild.
It looks like your hand is like a Lego person's hand made out of bread.
What it looks like to me is like, there's some kind of bad guy in Doctor Who where it's
like actual living dough that's trying to look like people.
Okay.
Yeah.
I love that.
And that's like how you can identify like, look at their hands, Doctor.
There's nothing about it where, you know how sometimes you put your iced coffee into your
bread bowl?
It's like, you just combine things you had around.
You know what I mean?
Your iconography is getting fucking sloppy.
Yeah.
Like if somebody saw that, even if they thought, is that a real bread bowl?
Their next thought would be, and are you using it to hold an iced coffee?
What?
Are you okay?
I feel like those realizations would come the other way, Trav, where it would be like,
why on God's green earth and Christ's earth do you have an iced coffee tucked into a bread
bowl?
And also, is that your hand in there?
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
They did a, oh God, it makes me so angry.
So they did this.
Right?
Yeah.
They made 450 of them.
That's it.
Fucking thanks.
Like just have some fucking, some strength of your convictions.
Right.
You know, like if you believe people want it, you nasty pervert, then do it.
Yeah.
Right?
Then just do it.
You know what?
Nothing can stop me from going into Panera Bread and ordering a empty, a bread bowl straight
up and cramming my little, and cramming my little paw in there, is there?
There ain't no log in it.
There's nobody who's going to say anything to me.
No, they wouldn't take it back from you.
No, I paid for it.
You know?
And you'll pay for it.
In the release where they were talking about it, they said, they cited a statistic that
78% of Americans told them, Panera, that they continue to drink iced coffee even in cold
weather.
Yeah.
Okay.
Then you're fixing a fucking solved problem.
Yeah, we already got this.
We've got it.
We're just doing it and going for it.
78% said they still drink iced coffee, and 100% said they want to stick their little
paws into one of our bread bowls.
I think anybody, when given that opportunity, would leap at it.
Would jump to, hey, I got a hot bread here, you want to jam your hand in there?
Are you going to eat that bread?
It seems like a waste of food.
No, I'm not.
This isn't, if you don't do it, I'm going to let somebody else do it.
Oh, okay.
Everybody would jam their hand in there.
Everybody, everybody, everybody.
Now if the glove was fresh bread bowl sent in, forget about it.
We're done.
I'm taking that all day every day.
Yeah.
I wanted to thank Liam for this one, actually, so thank you, Liam.
Real quick, I did go ahead and go on over to icedandtoasty.com, which is weird that
we didn't own that, but I did go to icedandtoasty.com, and there's just a big picture of the bowl,
and then it says, sorry, we're all out.
Oh, man.
But then under it, there's a link that says, what does this mean?
Oh.
So I go to icedandtoasty.com, and it says, sorry, in huge letters, we're all out.
What's that even mean?
What does this mean?
What do you even mean, sorry, you're all out?
If you click, what does this mean, it then gives a really wordy explanation that breaks
down to, we don't have any more.
We don't have any more of them.
I clicked it.
Here's what it says.
This is from Zach.
Well, it's probably Zach, isn't it?
Well, Zach, and then he's doing the rock horn emoji.
Yeah.
You may receive this message if all of the products in your area have been claimed or
you're participating after the promotional period has ended.
So in other words, they're all out.
They don't have any.
Well, and then down at the bottom, it then says, 11 out of 23 found this helpful, which
means that there were 12 people who were like, I'm still confused.
I don't get it.
Get it.
How does this help me get a bread bowl glove?
Explain again, Zach, but slower.
Anyway, you can't get it.
I don't know why I wasted your time.
It's a dumb idea.
When Liam sent it, Liam said it's an edible Panera bread cup holder.
That's not right.
Well, it's also right in the sense that like, why the fuck else are they doing it?
If they made an edible cup holder, that's like we baked in a slot for your hand because
we're absolutely out of a solitary fuck to give that I'm into it.
If you want to let me like hold an iced coffee and then finish it, then eat the thing out
my hand because it doesn't have a purpose anymore.
That's biodegradable.
That's 2021.
You know what I mean?
That's new tech.
I think we've talked about it on this show before, but edible doesn't mean digestible.
Liam's not wrong.
Yeah.
You could eat that glove if you tried hard enough.
I'm just saying if they wanted to rebrand as Panera's boutique and they only sold bread
clothes, I think that would be a killer Swaperoni.
Oh yeah.
What else do you guys want to do?
I mean, we do the questions.
We only did two, I guess.
Two?
Yeah.
Two.
Okay.
That's not bad, but I will do another one if you want or Yahoo.
I think the second question is powerful and we should read that.
My employer offers a small stipend for purchase of clothing with the company's logo.
Most of it is pretty bland, polo shirts, light jackets, caps, et cetera.
This year though, they're offering jeans with the company logo embroidered across the ass.
What occasions are appropriate for business casual juicy jeans?
How should I complete the outfit to really impress our clients?
Dress to impress in DC.
An unbuttoned, white, thin fabric shirt and there's a fan close by.
Also, you could do a popped collar jean jacket of the same denim material and make sure you
always have your back turned to them and you're looking over a shoulder.
And make sure you tuck that jacket into the pants just to really complete the look.
That's good, Trav.
If you can find denim shoes, I don't know if that's anything, but anything that draws
attention back to the ass is what you want.
Let me call John Mellencamp and ask to borrow one of his many pairs of denim shoes.
Hold on.
Okay.
I'll get them on the horn.
This is not a skit I'm going to do because I don't really know anything about John Mellencamp,
but-
I feel like a great use of this would be if you're doing a presentation and you're like
to a new client and then it's like you use it as the punchline of the presentation because
it makes it look like you went the extra mile.
You know what I mean?
It's like, and one thing I can say about Fidelity Capital Management, we won't be bringing up
the rear.
That's really good.
And you show up your ass and it's like, this company gets it.
That's it.
Yeah.
And then they'll be like, why do your jeans look so dirty and smell so bad?
And you're like, I do not take these off because I love the company.
You heard the part where I talked about loving the company, right?
So like, why would I take off my Fidelity pants?
You could do another pair of jeans over those jeans.
And then when someone's like, I can't believe you wore jeans to work.
You're like, yeah, sorry.
I forgot.
It's a little too casual.
And then you tear those pants away and underneath you have your business, Juicy Jeans.
And everyone's like, that's what I talk about, bro.
And you all high five a bunch and then maybe play some volleyball out in the lawn, I assume.
In your jeans.
Just some jeans volleyball like you do.
Just some jeans volleyball.
Regular jeans volleyball.
The chafing is part of the fun.
Yeah.
It's an endurance sport, jeans volleyball.
Why do they make these?
What do you mean?
Why do they-
It's really kind of weird, isn't it?
It's kind of weird that they would think you would want to put the company's logo right
on your ass.
Yeah.
No, it's not a good place for that.
I guess it depends on what the company is.
Is there a company where, other than Juicy, do you work at Juicy corporate headquarters?
What about endoscopy cameras?
Like if you were like, is that the right one?
Colonoscopy.
That's what I meant.
Like if you were a company that produced enemas, colonoscopy, or just like a billboard company,
and then it has it there and it's like, you looked, didn't you?
And this is what you're trying to sell now is, hi, my name is Travis McElroy, and for
$100 a month, you can buy ad space on my ass.
That's it.
Oh, it's for sale.
Does jeans but advertising work?
Just did.
Because you looked.
I made you look.
You looked at my height.
You looked at my hiner, didn't you?
Yeah.
Are you looking for a house with a great backyard?
And then it has like the listing for, you know, some real estate agents in there, right?
Yeah.
But it's on my ass because I have a great backyard.
Yep.
Next Buc-ee's, exit 23A and 15 miles.
But it says it-
Follow me to-
Right.
Follow me to Buc-ee's, and it says it right there.
It's got basically MapQuest directions to Buc-ee's on my dumper.
Yeah.
Yep, yep, yep.
Now, this started as a joke, but now I'm starting to think I could maybe sell some ad space
on my butt.
I think anybody could.
Okay, I want to give you guys a challenge.
Okay, okay.
Are you guys ready for this?
Yeah.
This is a thought experiment for thought leaders like ourselves.
Okay.
If we had to put up a piece of McElroy Family merchandise where it was jeans but the logo
was on the ass, what would you guys do?
We have to do it.
What, would we advertise on the back?
Or what would that-
What would it be?
Just, yeah, describe the product, I guess.
I'd probably put an ad for pets.com on there, but I think it's because you mentioned the
.com bubble earlier.
Yeah, yeah.
And now it's kind of all I can think about.
And my brain went there, too.
My brain was-
So that would be a piece of McElroy Family merch that we would sell that would be the
pets.com logo?
Yes.
Yeah, something like that.
Okay, so you've already, hearing it back, parroted back at you to try to cease the cracks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a truth campaign, but not their anti-vaping thing they're on now, but like old truth back
in like 2001 where it's like, check out this person and the machine they use to talk.
But we've put that on their butt of merch pants.
I think I would advertise the pants on the pants so that when people look at the pants,
they're like, well, now I want to get those pants, but I don't know where to get them.
It's like, well, the information's right there.
Yeah.
You can get ad pants right there.
I like that.
Or it's like the pants are an ad for your ass branding company, ass branding limited,
let's call it.
And the logo is a pair of jeans that have the ass branding limited wordmark on them,
which happens to be shaped like a pair of jeans, so it's just infinite into your butt.
Jeans all the way down, baby.
Jeans all the way down.
You need a kit, but the good news is if you go too deep, Joseph Gordon-Levitt will kick
your chair into the bathtub, kick you right back up, right out the jeans.
Joseph Gordon-Levitt, that chair kicked into the tub, kicked me right out my jeans.
Kicked me out my jeans, JGL.
Thanks for saving me from my jeans.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, where's my top?
I need my shirt that I wore with the jeans, JGL, damn.
Are you wearing those jeans?
Were you wearing those jeans when I went in?
Are we still in it?
Oh no.
Kick it.
My wife is trapped in some jeans.
Kick me again, JGL, damn.
I'm in my wife's childhood jeans.
My wife created jeans for us to live in together, but it was between our two jeans.
Oh no.
Let me spin my magic top.
All right, damn it, I left it in my jeans one layer up.
Fuck.
Hey, Tom Hardy, bring my jeans now when you come.
Or at least my magic top.
It's in the pocket of my jeans in your jeans layer.
Hey, I just want to tell you, guy, you're super old now.
Your jeans still look great.
Still wear the hell out of them jeans.
I believe you mean Ken Watanabe.
You said the name.
Extremely old man.
Yes, yes, yes, Ken Watanabe.
Elliot Page.
Way to spoil.
Yeah, way to spoil everything.
Elliot Page, I need you to craft some jeans for me with your... No, the jeans were paying
attention to themselves.
The jeans are aware we're in them.
I'm a jeans architect.
You're a tailor?
No.
I've said that many times.
Michael Caine, young and old Michael Caine, all this must be a dream.
We're all three in jeans and kissing.
Sydney made fun of me today for falling over in the snow, and I said, why do we fall, Master
Bruce?
It's to get back up again.
And my voice started sounding like Bane, and I accidentally, and I did Michael Bane.
Michael Bane.
It sounds like a Michael Caine and a Bane impression mixed together.
Mr. Wayne?
Mr. Wayne.
Come in the shorts to a store, Bob.
It sounds like he's drowning now.
Henry loves Batman, and one time I had him say, where's Falcone, as deep-voiced Batman,
and now he says it anytime he plays Batman, and I feel like I've ruined him.
I feel like nothing will satisfy him now.
Where is Falcone?
Yeah, he asked, and he's like, who is Falcone and why does Batman want him?
And I have to tell him it's because he didn't pay attention in virtual school.
You think that's bad?
My daughter said ba-ba-booey to me this week.
Oh, that's so bad.
That hurts.
Thanks for listening.
Thanks for listening to our podcast.
We're three great dads, and we're happy to have you here.
We hope you're hanging in there as much as can be expected.
If you want to buy some merchandise, we don't have any jeans on offer currently, but if
you go to McElroy Merch, you'll find some other stuff.
There's a cute little boy car pin by Zachary Sterling, our candle lights special, you can
now get that.
We got a Taste of Luxury stemless wine glass and a t-shirt designed by Kevin Budnick.
If you want to watch that, by the way, search Taste of Luxury on YouTube and watch it.
I'd really appreciate it.
It's real funny.
I'm so proud of it.
I'm so proud of watching things.
We got an Adventure Zone Live virtual show this week, February 19th at 9pm Eastern Time.
It's virtual and interactive.
That means there will come moments when we'll need your help deciding what the players do.
We're going to be playing Honey Heist with special guest Erica Ishii.
Tickets are just $10.
You can get them at live.themacroy.family.
It's going to be a blast and a half, folks.
Hey, pre-order Crystal Kingdom.
The third?
Fourth?
Fourth.
Jesus.
We've written a lot of books.
There's a lot of novel in the Adventure Zone balance series.
It's real good.
Go to theadventurezonecomic.com.
Book comes out July 13th, 2021, but don't wait.
Y'all want a final Yahoo?
Yes, please.
Absolutely.
This final Yahoo was sent in by the wizard Ben Cant.
Thank you, Ben.
It is Yahoo Answers user T who asks, how comes bad guys in movies don't eat an apple with
a pocket knife no more?
Yes.
Thank you.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been my brother, my brother, me, Kiss Your Dad.
School.
Air on the lips.
Okay.
That was the show.
Hope you had some fun.
Talked for an hour and now our job is done.
Go back into the world.
Face the day ahead.
Please don't tell our grandparents all the cuss words we said.
Maximumfun.org.
Comedy and culture.
Artists owned.
Audience supported.
Hey, it's Jesse.
Hi, Chris.
It's Jesse calling from Maximum Fun.
Hey, Jesse.
I heard that you got into a car accident.
Yeah, I was listening to stop podcasting yourself and I just laughed so hard that I slammed
into a construction barrier.
You remember what it was that was so funny?
I will never forget.
I'm sure.
They started talking about Vegas and the, you know, if it happens here, it stays here
and that's Logan.
And then Graham was talking about, oh, you know, wasn't there some other slogan for another
commercial?
I was like a commercial for food and it said like, whatever's in there stays in there.
I can't remember what it was, clams or something, just so ridiculous.
And man, I got lightheaded.
I was laughing so hard.
Next thing I know, they are, they are just brilliantly funny.
So I talked to Dave and Graham from stop podcasting yourself.
We would like to pay your car repair bill.
Is that okay?
That, I mean, that would be super nice, Jesse.
I really thank you.
I appreciate that.