You're not fucking Bono, sit down in the chair.
That's how Bono starts his shows is he runs up and high fives you.
I know one thing about Bono.
I assume Bono doesn't get winded.
Randy Kraut.
Hi everybody.
Hey guys.
I loaded up my computer to get the Yahoo's ready, get the Yahoo oven preheated to 350.
Travis, you want to tell me what popped up as soon as I typed in my password?
That would be Reba McEntire's fancy.
That's right.
It's on Spotify premium.
He knows what you need, he's making the best use of it too.
I just got super nervous all of a sudden.
Are you guys going to be cool or are you going to be dicks?
Are you guys cool?
I don't know which one that was.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Welcome to my brother, my brother, me and advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm the sweet baby brother.
Oh shit.
And we're done.
Thanks for listening everybody.
I'm the sweet baby brother, Griffin.
That'd be a tight stinger.
Every time he said dope shit, it'd be like, that was our outro music.
We'll do a show first and then we'll just try it again.
We'll come back around.
Don't worry.
Keep the finger on the button though, because you don't know.
Because if it starts to go bad, we are dipping.
We will fucking eject.
Let that be a warning to you.
Hello, Los Angeles.
Hi, Los Angeles.
Sorry we haven't, we haven't been to you in a while.
I guess we haven't been to Los Angeles proper like ever.
We've performed a couple of times at Lake Arrowhead, which is LA adjacent, I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like five hours away, so not like super adjacent.
Depending on fog.
People here hate Lake Arrowhead?
Who is booing?
It's like the best.
Boo!
Beautiful artificial lakes on the top of mountains.
No, thank you.
It's perfect.
Just like I imagined heaven to be.
They give you free, lots of bacon, there's always bacon up there.
Is anybody else here living in mortal terror of the fact that the Los Angeles Kings just
won the Stanley Cup and, oh, sorry, spoilers, I guess.
Were you waiting?
No.
No, I mean, it's not going to be a spoiler.
You're going to cross the threshold of this building and it's going to be a nuclear wasteland
outside.
You're like, oh, I guess we won.
Sweet.
Except my, you know, my entire neighborhood's destroyed, but everything else is totally
sweet.
I'm not worried as much about hockey fans writing.
They seem like a polite, kind of chilled out people to me.
They're just so happy people are paying attention.
I need my gummy berry juice.
So, between the World Cup happening and the LA Kings winning, somewhere there is a man
with very specific sports taste who's very happy tonight, who really feels like the superstar.
Like, finally.
You know what?
This feels like the start of something.
I think we're finally going to get the attention we deserve.
So this is, raise your hand, is there anybody here for the first time who's never listened
to our program?
Never heard the show before.
That's awesome.
Cool.
Fantastic.
Well, welcome to you.
You're wearing a My Brother, My Brother, Me T-shirt.
How did that happen?
I'm fucking into that.
What the fuck is your story?
Poser.
We're going to get him up here later and I want to learn some things about that man.
I want to unfold his story.
I did it when I saw live for the first time, so don't feel bad.
I got to see that live.
I wish I had seen live.
That was bullshit.
You know what I was going to say?
I was going to say an actual concert I've been to, which is Dave Matthews' band, but
you know I was into that.
No lie.
So this is a device show where we take your questions, your queries, and turn them Aquame-like
into wisdom.
We might have some questions from the audience here, so if you want to try to cook something
up in your head that is real and a problem we can fix for you.
And not a bummer.
Not a bummer.
Not a bummer, so help me God.
We are nice people.
Talk to us about, we'll answer your bummer questions off the air, I guess, fun party.
But not on the show.
And no, like, tell them how many jokes about poop and stuff.
No poop jokes.
Those are for us.
Those are for us only.
Not for you.
Those are for adults only.
Those are for comedy adults only, and they need to be handled carefully with precision.
So you're not ready for that.
Trust us.
Travis, how about a question?
Okay, great.
These were also asked by people here, correct?
Yeah.
I believe so.
Let's see.
Oh, I won't read the person because it's the tag line.
I have a lot of vivid weird dreams that more often than not contain people in my day-to-day
life.
Naked, and they're like on top of me and cool stuff.
It's implied, right?
Okay.
In my day-to-day life, doing something I think is worth mentioning to them.
My question is this.
Is it socially acceptable to tell people that I've dreamt about them, or say you were in
my dream last night, or will I be giving everyone I know the willies by doing this?
And that's from I've even done it to Justin.
Woof.
Hachi-machi.
You know, we try to keep-
Do you want to raise your hand if you're here and you did this?
We try to keep-
You did this terrible, terrible thing?
I don't see a hand.
Somewhere in the void.
Can you howl?
No, no, no.
It's better this way.
No, don't do that.
It's better.
Could you come down and explain your dream about Justin in graphic detail?
It's way better for the podcast that I have to do than if I don't know what you look like
and I know you're just out there waiting.
That's super cool for my stress levels.
I appreciate it.
That way, I can look at every face and wonder, is it them?
And then look at some other faces and think, well, maybe it's them.
Very flattering.
All right.
If there's no level of innocuousness of the subject matter of your dream, it could just
be like, me, you, and Alf eating a hot dog.
And then I would immediately think, and then we had a crazy Alf three-way and it was totally
awesome.
That was the part of the dream that you didn't tell me about, but I know that you dreamt
about fucking me and Alf at the same time.
Yeah.
Because here's the problem.
As soon as you broached the subject, you were in my dream last night.
Right.
The person hears fucking me.
We had a wobbly age with Alf and it was totally great.
It was a lowercase H. Having sex with Alf.
Two in the snout and one's left out.
Yikes.
Sex with Alf.
I want you guys to know there's a joke about eating Alf.
Two in the snout and no time to pout.
Have some sex with Alf.
That's a new teen trend.
It's called Shumwaying.
Yikes.
No, fucking of course not.
Under no circumstances, no.
There's a reason that dreams only happen in your head and it's because it's for you.
Well, unless you're Travis.
Travis, you tell a lot.
I love you.
You're my brother.
My dreams are fucking awesome.
Yeah.
Totally.
No, yeah, totally.
Sure.
I remember a lot of them just because of the great stories that go on in there and that
beautiful head of yours, all the great dream stories.
If any of you want to hear my dreams later, just let me know.
How about a Yahoo answer?
That's it?
Did we fucking answer that?
That's fucking it.
Hey, Cooper, keep your shit to yourself.
I mean, it's not acceptable.
I know it's not creepy.
I know you're not dreaming about having sex with him, but that's what people are going
to think.
It implies intimacy.
No question.
No, it's inappropriate.
Don't ever do it.
Ever.
Just stop dreaming.
Stop dreaming.
Let your dreams die.
I'm 33.
It ain't hard, gang.
Come on.
This Yahoo was sent in by Drew Davenport, who is here tonight.
Drew Davenport.
Come on.
Get the fuck up here.
Drew Davenport, stand up and come to the stage.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Fucking keep it going.
I want five uninterrupted minutes of applause.
Come here.
Get the fuck over here.
Ladies and gentlemen, Drew Davenport, an emerald level Yahoo answer shaman, finally.
Yes.
This is what it sounds like when doves cry.
Drew, thank you so much for saving our program time and time again.
He's a lot taller than I thought he was going to be.
Man, if I was as tall as you, Drew, I would have no time for looking for answers.
I'd be too busy beating ass.
Everybody, give it up for Drew fucking Davenport.
You're all unnoticed.
Wind beneath my wings.
Drew Davenport.
If it weren't for Drew Davenport, the pre-show would have been over.
You're all unnoticed.
If it weren't for Drew Davenport, the production time that I would put into this show would
be like 20 minutes more a week, but that's a lot.
That's a lot for me.
Thank you.
If you're listening at home, he was eight feet tall.
Eight feet if he was an inch.
As broad as a bull.
There's a service called Yahoo Answers and we dig into it.
For you three new people.
No, I'm going to keep talking to them.
I want to win them over.
Your business I have.
I want to win the new business.
We try to answer them to the best of our abilities.
When I say we find them, I mean Drew Davenport.
Almost exclusively.
Almost exclusively Drew Davenport finds them.
Thank you, Drew Davenport.
This Yahoo Answer was asked by a suspended account.
Why were they suspended, you asked?
How could I make wee bowling sexy?
So my girlfriend and I have a habit of trying to make simple everyday things into something
remotely sexy.
So they're not trying super hard.
No, yeah.
Our bar is low.
You're making that grilled cheese, why don't you get a bowl out?
Sure.
My chatbook's looking mighty balanced.
Does anyone have any clue how we can make something like wee bowling sexy?
Also I do realize this is a ridiculous question.
They should just fucking have some sort of script on Yahoo Answers that immediately puts
that at the bottom of everybody's question.
That's about putting Doritos in your butt, like yeah, it's pretty ridiculous.
What about this?
I got an answer.
What if you play wee bowling with your balls out?
Don't fucking salt my game, Travis.
You play wee bowling, and while you're playing it.
Put the kids to bed.
Put the kids right in the sleepy town.
You play wee bowling.
Here comes the sex.
Quiet, quiet.
While you're playing it.
What are you doing?
You have a sex.
That is going to throw off your handicapped.
Yeah.
No question about it.
Too hot for TV.
Sorry.
Keep that.
A bowling handicap?
It's a thing.
I guess.
Like bumpers?
You're bumping something.
Yeah.
Genitals.
Like your genitals.
Yeah.
Genitals.
That's what we're doing in New York.
Talking about your genitals.
Yeah.
You're bumping your genitals.
Ah.
I saw some rocket loot being tossed around.
That would probably be integral.
Well, I mean.
You got to be careful.
Because you'll throw it right out of your hand.
Yeah.
You'll smash that TV to fucking bits.
There's nothing sexy about breaking your television.
That'll kill the mood.
When you're doing that, though, do you use protection?
By which I mean use the Wiimote wrist strap.
On your wiener?
No.
On your fucking wrist, Travis.
On your fucking degenerate?
No.
Listen.
I said degenerate.
But I'm not here to pass judgment.
No.
Listen.
If you like them twerked, you like them squeezed, you like them worked, whatever.
It pleases.
You like them Wiimoted, I guess.
You like them.
Okay.
I guess.
I'm trying to be really accepting.
It's my new thing for 2014.
Sorry.
2013.
No.
Sorry.
2014?
20-forward.
There we go.
Yeah.
That was a test to find the true fans.
That's a motto we've really subscribed to.
Yeah.
Well, we did some live shows this year.
We've been doing good about that.
I guess that's true.
Can I give you a sneak preview?
Because I'll forget about it.
Sure.
And what I was thinking for next year.
Yeah.
20-spliff-teen.
Sure.
He's so bad.
What won't he say?
Like drugs?
Oh.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
How about a regular non-Yahoo?
Okay.
Great.
That also comes from hopefully someone in the audience.
Can we call these Google questions?
That might be fun.
I mean, they're all Gmail.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
No.
Let's talk more about web platforms.
All right.
Spliff-teen.
Yeah.
Got it.
Read the question.
Come on.
How do I prepare myself to be robbed?
Terrific.
We should all actually be thinking about this legitimately.
I have many examples of this, but one time my cousin jumped out of the bushes and saw
me and scared me.
My knees locked and I fell over like a fainting goat.
It was very embarrassing.
What if this happens when an assailant tries to jump me with a knife?
I want to stay on my ground and at least seem threatening.
How do I get tougher and less scared of people jumping out and surprising me?
And that's from neither fight nor flight in the fourth round.
Did you actually fucking manage to get in the fourth row?
Nailed it.
God damn.
That's dedication right there.
That's a called shot.
Sorry.
What's your name?
JP.
No you're fine.
See how you're fine.
I don't think it's as bad as you thought it was going to be.
Hey everybody, if you see JP later after the show, just give him a little spook.
That's it.
We got to toughen you up.
We're going to toughen you up.
This is immersion therapy, JP.
We got to rock the gauntlet.
That's how Daredevil got started.
People just kept spooking him and spooking him and spooking him.
And then he went blind.
He did go blind.
He went blind from the spooks.
Not from...
No, it was like ass spooking him.
Oh God, I spooked you too hard.
I spooked you too hard.
You're eyeballing.
I'll be your friend forever.
My name's Foggy Nelson, backstory, origin, one guy, thank you, sir.
In Daredevil's...
I would throw this out, JP.
A knife.
What?
Whoa.
Look out.
Also, I'm going to fucking break you of saying let me throw this out.
Okay.
It's the last thing I do.
Holy shit.
Thank you.
I can't believe...
Can we like come up with some sort of audience response?
Like some sort of like great chorus?
Does anyone have a can full of pennies you can shake at me when I do it?
No, no can.
I was taught by my parents, and I assume my brothers were too, that when accosted-
Make yourself small.
By a potential robber, you seem as non-threatening as possible.
Sure.
You say, yes, of course, sir.
Yes.
Here you go.
Or madam, let's not be sexist.
Yeah.
Sir or madam, who is robbing me at this moment, here are all my belongings.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, please take them.
And congratulations.
This is some great stuff.
I hope you enjoy them more than I do.
You have bested me.
Listen, I'll be a good sport in this regard.
You have won this encounter.
And let me also congratulate you on your choice of targets.
You have couldn't have-
You have done very well.
And then you lay on your back and pee all over yourself to show submission.
Out of curiosity, what could I do better in the future to prevent myself from being such
an obvious target robber?
I'm just going to slide this comment card across the table.
If you could fill that out before you leave, I appreciate it.
Have you experienced better?
Was I not robbable, robbable, or very robbable?
JP, you've got to get diesel.
There's the only one kind of person that's not afraid of other people.
Drew Davenport.
Okay, there's two.
And the Lou Ferrigno's of the world.
These super diesel folks.
I would fold those two categories sort of in together.
Yeah.
He is Ferrigno in scale.
You're Drew Ferrigno's.
Drew Ferrigno.
If you get Drew Ferrigno diesel, and then no one will mess with you.
Except for Lou Ferrigno, and then it's just a battle of titans between the two of you.
We actually should, like, if you could not mess up the curve, because we need as many
people sort of like looking like obvious targets for robbery as possible.
Yeah, yeah.
It helps us to blend in.
I try to look so tough.
I've only been robbed once, and you could do the tactic which I employed, which worked
out like super well for me, which is to lie about the things that you have.
It's a risky gambit, I will be honest.
This is not a goof.
Griffin was working at GameStop when he was younger.
Guy comes in and says, give me all the PS3s you have, points a gun at Griffin.
And me, Mr. Brand loyal to GameStop.
Icy veins, no fucking skin in the game whatsoever says, we don't have any.
Also, so you know, the only thing protecting this ruse was a door behind Griffin.
Which in which, behind which was a giant pyramid of PlayStation 3s.
Right.
Oh, those PS3s.
Another fun part of that story is I didn't, I wasn't allowed to open the register without
making a sale because GameStop had never taught me how.
So they said, open the register.
And I said, let me get my manager and expose her to this robbery.
Let me pass along this cool Sunday I'm having and share it with a friend.
Come have a portion of my cool Sunday, manager.
You know what this encounter needs?
Witnesses.
Yes.
How about another Yahoo?
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
Man, I'm glad I'm not dead.
Me too, in a way.
Yeah.
We never would have been able to do this show.
We would have.
It just would have been missing something.
Yeah.
This Yahoo was sent in by Nat Steinsultz.
Maybe here?
I don't know.
There's a lot of people who live in Los Angeles.
No, I guess not.
Thank you, Nat, by Yahoo Answers.
Thank you, Nat, by Yahoo Answers user Romario, who asks, my manager is a female, and she
pees so loud, how do I tell her that's annoying?
How could that?
How often does that come up?
How thin are those walls?
How close are you?
Why don't you dismiss yourself from the region?
Do you work in a food cart?
Maybe that's what's going on.
You can't get out.
Maybe he's a bathroom attendant.
Okay, so wait.
Just to be clear, he-
Whoa.
The fiction was so bad that it gave Justin a-
He's a bathroom attendant who has a boss that comes by just to see how the attending-
Justin, check up.
Let me test and see what you did.
Let me ruin your work, Robbie.
Fuck you.
Clean up on me, Robbie.
Listen to how loud-
Listen to how hard I can push this out.
How bad could this possibly be?
Sploosh.
I mean, bad enough that he says annoying, not like gross or like it makes you go, it's
annoying.
There she goes.
God damn it.
Fuck.
Again?
Maybe the manager has-
Jesus.
Maybe the manager has some sort of cool pee kegels, and she can pee out, listen, stick
with it.
Now we're going somewhere.
She can pee out the rhythm to Gangnam Style and it's like, Gangnam Style.
Gangnam Style, really?
It's 2014.
Kegel another song.
I know it's not a jukebox, but you got to teach that thing another song.
She doesn't know where to find another one of those player piano spools.
Travis liked it.
I don't know.
I love that joke.
That was a good joke.
I don't know why you guys, Travis likes it.
That's all I care about.
I was confused about the physiology, I guess.
I don't understand why you would stay close by.
Just you know what's going to happen.
Maybe it's like looking at a car accident, like he doesn't want to.
There are a lot of variables.
I've got a timer.
See how fast you can get done today.
A lot of variables apply.
Ooh, shaved off three seconds.
Sure.
We're talking about distance to the turret light.
We're talking about thickness of the walls of the turret light zone.
And we're talking, to be fair, to give this guy the benefit of the doubt, the general loudness
of this manager's team.
Like decibel level.
Like wow.
Like synths around, like holy shit.
I feel like all you have to do, and it would take a bolder man than me, but when she comes
out, be like, hey.
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm worried about you.
This could be the start of the worst moonlighting style will they won't they I've ever heard.
We've been dancing around this for a while.
You pee real loud.
You pee super loud.
So loud.
Like really loud and really short.
Like it just like, just like it falls out of you.
It sounds like somebody overturning a bucket and I'm worried about you.
And then you come out real wobbly legs.
Yeah.
And you're frowning, but kind of laughing.
And here's the other thing about it.
I hate it.
I hate it so much.
I hate when it happens in the bucket and I'm like, darling, I hate it, darling.
You're the worst manager, but this is the best job.
And frankly, I can't fall asleep without that noise anymore.
So I guess, I guess, I guess what I'm saying to answer your question, Reverend, I do.
How about a, how about a regular, how about a normie?
You all right?
I can read it.
I'll read it.
I just pictured her peeing on the altar.
Goof, goof so hard I broke Travis.
Oh Jesus.
Dear brothers, ice cream trucks never pass where I live, ever.
So sorry.
This is a problem.
All right.
Ice truck, ice cream trucks never pass where I live, ever.
Okay, I heard one outside and I booked it out the door.
He was driving away from me, but I finally caught up with him.
Well done.
Good work.
Those things, those things don't drive especially fast, if I remember correctly, but still kudos
to you, I suppose.
Faster than human land speed.
I guess.
You earned your dilly bar.
When I bought my, how old am I?
When I bought my ice cream, the ice cream guy just gave me this incredulous face and
seemed to be annoyed that a 20-ish year old would be so excited about it.
You know your age, right, I'm guessing?
Yeah, but like the ice cream- I was left on a doorstep.
It's good storytelling.
He's not forcing omnipotence and omniscience onto the ice cream truck driver.
Would be so excited about an ice cream truck.
Am I too old to be excited about ice cream trucks or was the ice cream guy just a downer?
And that's from vexed in Ventura question for you audience.
Vexed in Ventura, are you here?
Hey, welcome.
Hey.
If you're an ice cream driver and it's 2014 and you're in LA, how good is business that
you can fucking get judgy on people?
I don't know.
It feels like you should go, do you want anything else?
Yeah.
Please?
Let's do a quick audience poll.
Also, can you think of anything else cold that I could sell?
Because I'm dying here.
Time's fucking broke out.
Let's do a quick poll of the audience.
This is interesting.
In the last, let's say, three months, has anybody seen an ice cream truck that was stationary
and selling its product to anybody?
Just a quick show of hands, stationary.
Okay, more than I thought.
Better question.
No, I'll be the first to admit that I fucked up with my judgment.
I haven't seen a stationary ice cream.
Every time it's just like slowly crawling at five miles an hour, it's like, anybody?
And I'm not talking, by the way, I want to clarify, I'm not talking about a food truck.
No, no, no.
You know what I'm talking about.
Ice cream.
I'm not talking about our keys and all like, it's got avocados in it.
That's what you sound like, food truck drivers, I guess.
I don't know what the ice cream truck environment is here, but I know what it's like in Cincinnati.
When you see said ice cream trucks, is the paint peeling and the pictures faded and it
looks like they just killed kids?
Sometimes they've got Pikachu on it and it's like, hey guys, let me just call Nintendo
real quick.
Yeah, you didn't like go through the right fucking channels to get fucking Pikachu to
sell your iced wares?
I would, I would feel uncomfortable and only because I would be so worried that I would
come up from vector A and sort of like in my periphery out of nowhere would be a kid
on vector B and we would arrive at the same time.
And you would force the issue like, I was here first.
You know, I was here first.
Hold on.
We got, sorry gents, we got one push pop left.
Looks like you're going to have to wrestle for it.
Sweet.
You're really little and I'm really big.
You just want to give it to me?
I would grab their head and just push it below the window so the guy couldn't see them until
I was done purchasing my novelties.
Have you guys noticed that the only people on fucking earth that call them novelties
at the grocery store, they used to confuse the hell out of me when I was a kid.
What's a novel?
It's ice cream shit.
We all know what you're talking about.
You don't have to get fucking fancy, Kroger.
You sell big K. Don't fuck with me.
Do you want another Yahoo?
No, I'll buy these.
Do you want another Yahoo question?
A little Yahoo.
Yahoo Knights mystery.
I actually just had something pop up in my head that I wanted to, no, no, no, no, no.
So we were, we were supposed to have some merch and it didn't come.
And so I wrote a little apology and an explanation as to why the merch wasn't here and I would
like to read it for you now.
Sorry that there is no merch tonight.
Here's what happened.
We ordered a slushy amount of the jankiest stuff, posters, tote bags, banana hammocks,
boners, frosted nuts, everything.
But the shipment was delayed by a flock of slurping sponges.
Those driving butts got in front of the bodacious penis hat filled with our merch.
Merch that was supposed to go to you, our moist puppies.
But from the bottom of our nipples, we apologize, love the pickled McElroy brothers.
Thank you.
You know, the funny, the funny thing about listening to that, A, nothing, B, do you notice
how no one was really like, there was sort of an initial like, this is going to be so
great.
And then like, fucking nothing from you.
Remember how you didn't laugh at all for the past 45 seconds?
It's not funny.
I will be signing copies of this later.
The one he has and the one I have.
And others he can scribble out for you.
I did a fun gag where like I like saying my beer like, oh, this makes you so mad, I'm
gonna say my beer.
I don't know how many beer left when we just started.
Ahem.
Give me some of your angry orchard, Justin.
Okay, sure.
Give me half a pour, maybe.
Yeah, I'll give you half.
Thank you.
How about Yahoo?
Listen, I can't go on.
This Yahoo was sent in by Josh Williams.
Josh, are you here?
If anybody wants to bring us another beer, you're welcome.
No, don't.
I don't want to do that.
No, but one at a time.
Please.
No, I'm just kidding.
Don't do that.
Thank you, Josh.
It's by Yahoo Answers user supertifster who asks, I need extremely dirty truth or dares.
Every time I pick a Yahoo or rather Josh Williams or Drew Davenport sends a Yahoo to me, I always
hope, like, is this going to be in the next Warrior Cats?
I think this one might.
We can never think of any help.
That's fine.
Kind of basic.
Not a lot there.
Listen, we could do a few.
I'm not as interested in that as I am about what the helpful folks on Yahoo Answers...
Oh, that's funny that you say that because Yahoo Answers user bigwavegirl2006 has a few
helpful suggestions.
It's worth pointing out, this user is definitely, definitely suspended, holy shit, to like the
ninth level of Yahoo hell.
I'm not making this up.
This is the actual order in which these were sent in.
Number one, truth questions.
Number one, ask a girl if she were a guy which girl in the room she would date.
Do the same to a guy.
Okay?
All right.
Sure.
Number two, do you swallow or spit?
That's for girls.
For boys.
What's the fastest you have C-U-M?
What the fuck?
This game escalated.
Who would you date in the room to?
How fast do you cum, Jake?
No, not just how fast.
What's the fastest?
Not the average.
I don't want to mean...
I don't want a median of cum times.
I want to know the peak of the curve.
What do you clock out at?
I want to know your curve breaking cum times.
That's what I need.
I want to know what's breaking the bell curve of your ejaculate.
And then way over here off the line, 30 seconds.
Interesting.
Is this an outlier?
I don't know, Malcolm.
Is it?
How fast do you cum?
How about number 17?
Have you ever skinny-dipped?
Okay, good.
Number 25, which guy playing do you think has the longest penis?
Those are actually kind of connected, like, well, let me find out.
Let's do 17.
25 will be answered very quickly.
Number four, which girl do you think would give the best PJ?
Cool big wave girl, cool.
Which girl do you think would give the best PJ?
Seems so like...
I'm going to go with Susan.
She's just a hard worker.
Seems like she'd really commit.
She'd give it her all.
I worked with her on a science project last year and she did not give up until it was
done.
I'm going to go with Susan.
Ladies, can I just...
Sorry, Lydia.
Ladies, can I just ask everybody sitting in the circle to just yodel for me?
Okay.
Interesting.
Some surprises here.
I'm going to have to go to the leaderboard.
This is a great one.
Let's go to the leaderboard, Moe.
Who gets a piece of that radical rock?
Okay, guts.
Let's talk about guts.
How about number 11?
Who has the biggest ball you've ever seen?
Left or right does not matter.
There's a lot of nuance to number 11 because they add funny since it can be told literally,
but someone will take it sexually.
I could be talking about a medicine ball.
No, you couldn't.
Not enough a jillion years could you be doing that, but God, how badly do you want to play
through the day with that guy or is that, wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Do you need genitals or medicine ball?
Point of order.
Just want to clarify.
Super quick point of order.
Because what if somebody in this circle had one ascended ball and one crazy huge descended
ball, like wow, like wowzers, like wow, like an egg yolk in there, like wow, like crazy.
An egg yolk?
Yeah, because it would be like, you know, you look at an egg yolk and it's just like
one thing sort of suspended it in another thing.
I tried to think of something more organic.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
That's the good stuff right there.
What's your name?
Because this is like the fourth drink that you've bought for us.
Here we go.
Here it comes.
I'm Jenny and that's John.
Jenny and John.
Famous forever.
They saved the jokes.
Get the groove juice flowing.
What is harder than watching a guy slam a cider?
Nothing.
I would crush this on my head, but it's tall.
You know what would happen then.
I'd get lacerations.
You want to jump to dares?
Number 17.
Play one round in your underwear.
Cool.
Number 23.
Stick your finger in your ass and then lick it.
What in the?
Big wave girl, go fuck yourself.
I would like to go back to truth.
I regret asking.
Stick your finger in your ass and then call your mom and apologize, you terrible person.
We didn't even invite you, Debra.
That seems like how to end a truth or dare game.
I dare you to put your finger in your butt.
God damn it, Steve.
Are you going to do it?
No, that was me leaving, but now I feel on the spot.
They pay like $25.
How much would you pay to watch a grown man?
How much would you pay to not?
Wait, don't.
Don't answer that.
We're going to hold you, motherfuckers, hostage.
How much would you pay to not let my brother lick his butt?
Guys I'm- Save me for myself.
He's a broken man.
I'm going to credit where credit is due.
These are fucking extremely dirty.
Number 21, masturbate into a shot glass.
Real thing!
Someone said on Yahoo!
Yahoo!
Masturbate into a shot glass for me.
I don't know much, Griffin, but is there not a second half of that dare?
Number three- Why would you?
Okay.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Back out.
My issue with the question answer is not that they did not generate some extremely dirty
truth or dares.
It's a question of editing.
Once you've created these masterpieces of dirty truth or dare, how do you leave something
like Who Would You Like to Kiss?
The problem with the great, what separates a good super dirty truth or dare creator from
a great super dirty truth or dare creator is being able to separate your wheat from
your chaff.
I dare you to separate your wheat from your chaff and then lick it and let us watch.
No others?
I mean, there's fucking 60 of them and they keep jumping back and forth to like, kiss
whoever you want in the room to number 30.
This one's a partner dare.
Have a blow job race.
Fuck.
I'm picking the guy who I think is going to come fastest.
Get over here in 30 seconds, Jake.
This is a different game.
This is truth or dare or eyes wide shut.
We love it.
We love Ellie.
It's true.
Oh my God.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh no.
The mutation started much earlier than we expected.
Hey, hey everyone.
Justin, welcome back to the podcast.
This is the first time I've done anything sort of that even resembles work or not work.
What is it contributing to society in other ways than like forming the next great generation
of humanity?
What generation is your baby in?
Is it like, are we up to like omega?
32 bit.
Epsilon?
Okay.
Your baby, your baby do it and then don't is what you're saying.
That's basically what I'm saying.
You are not ready is what I'm saying.
Listen, just because we, uh, I'm not here doesn't mean I don't need money.
I have a mouth to feed and uh, you know what I'm going to be feeding my baby, but that's
right.
Nature box.
She is not ready for, I'm just saying to the nature box offers a delicious catalog of delicious
healthy food stuffs.
She's probably not ready to chew down on some dark cocoa almonds.
I think you're not ready cause I am.
I have teeth.
I have human adult teeth.
Oh, but you don't like a lot of sugar and you don't like trans fats and you don't like
high fructose corn syrup.
That's all true.
Okay.
Then you're ready for nature box.
They've got delicious snacks, uh, that you go on, you pick the ones that look good to
you.
They have, I mean an insane amount of, of different varietals, varietals of snacks.
Are any of them pre-chewed?
Like don't get me wrong.
Peanut butter nom noms, delicious baked sweet potato fries, fuck yes, but your baby's not
going to be able to enjoy these in the way that they're meant to be enjoyed for another
like three years or so.
Okay.
I'm going to hit you with a few that they have.
And you can tell me if it's appropriate for the baby.
Okay.
Uh, baked sweet potato fries.
No.
Um, yogurt covered pretzels.
Oh, actually that one.
Yeah.
Okay.
That one's okay.
Babies, babies love pretzels.
Breast milk guzzlers.
That sounds, actually that sounds all right.
That one would be okay.
Can I order those, can I order those or am I going to be put on some sort of watch list?
Uh, if you go to naturebox.com, you can get 50% off of your first month's box.
You go to naturebox.com slash my brother.
That is the key thing.
You can't get that original address.
You go to naturebox.com slash my brother, all one word, and you can get 50% off your
first month's box.
Try them.
A ton of our listeners have, and they've really, really liked them.
They very much enjoyed them.
We get emails all the time like, I'm full and healthy.
I'm full and healthy, brothers.
Thank you.
Um, once you have managed to get your body-
It's me, the mole man, your favorite listener.
I'm Adam Sandler, the mole man.
I live under the ground.
I'm the Adam Sandler of the mole man.
Man, you've just been, it's like falling off a log, isn't it, Juice?
Comedy is easy.
Parenthood is hard.
That's my new book.
Me and Irma Baumbacher co-writing it.
That's coming out.
Dave Barry, Justin McElroy presents, comedy is easy, parenthood is hard, and on the front
it's me in a smoking jacket and he's behind me juggling a baby.
We are changing our schedule now.
We are only going to record one episode every nine and a half months.
You're going to keep having babies, and then we're going to fucking get you on here for
that prime material, that prime time.
Here's a joke I wrote about fatherhood last night.
Okay.
I don't know why everybody's in such a hurry to teach their kids to talk, because it makes
it so much harder to frame them for farting.
That's pretty good.
Thanks.
I'll be honest, that's about exactly what I expected.
Perfect.
Okay.
Well, that's about where I am in my life right now.
I guess if you want jokes maybe better than that, you can probably find them on Hulu,
Hulu Plus to be specific.
It's like the Hulu reviews on your computer, only you can do it anywhere, anytime at your
whim whenever you don't shackle yourself to your MacBook.
You can get on your Roku, your Apple TV, your sex box, whatever you want, and just watch
Hulu on the go.
They got current season episodes of your favorite shows like Modern Family.
They got Daily Show with Jon Stewart.
They have every episode of shows like South Park, which is only available on Hulu Plus.
You can do it how you like.
Oh, fuck.
Justin.
Griffin.
I have the best news ever.
Tell me.
And it's germane to Hulu Plus, because that is where I enjoy it.
Okay, tell me about this entertainment you're enjoying.
You know how the house has seemed very empty lately?
The house has seemed hollow?
That's what everybody's saying.
People are always saying the house seems very hollow, and I think it's just because for
a few months now, there haven't been any boys in the house.
Boys in the house.
It is right back where it needs to be.
Cycle 21.
Boys are back in the house for America's Next Top Model.
Fucking Cory, so tight, he is now a judge, well not a judge, but he's like a host.
He was this super sweet dude who in the first episode, they were like, boys on one side,
girls on the other side.
Boys pick a girl and walk down the stairs.
And he walked towards the girls, and he's like, no, this will not do.
And he turned around, and he got himself a boy.
And they walked down the stairs.
And you're telling me he's back?
He's back, and he's a fucking judge, he's not a judge, he's a host.
So he'll talk to them and be like, aw man, I've been there, you guys look fucking amazing.
He's like super sweet, super supportive.
Anyway, boys are back in the house, Cycle 21, check it out, Hulu Plus.
It's only $7.99 a month.
That's a great deal.
It is a good deal, but the better deal is we can get you two weeks free.
Two week free trial, it's longer than the usual one week free trial.
We're gonna give you that extra week, just go to HuluPlus.com slash my brother, and you'll
get that two week free trial, and it's good for us, because they know that we sent you,
and they will continue to support my brother, my brother, and me.
So it's a...
And my infant daughter.
And Justin's infant daughter, and my infant niece.
Same person.
Same person, it's the same one.
I wanna give a very happy message to Yohan.
It comes from Candace, Chris, Noah, Rachel, and Olivia.
They say, hey Yohan, congratulations on finally being legal.
We're so proud of you for everything you do in terms of hard work and training, as well
as being a stellar guy in general.
This fucking sounds like code.
This sounds like they're hinting around some secret government skunk works, black ops shit.
Are they activating Yohan's wet works protocol?
We honestly couldn't ask for a better friend, and that's in quotation marks, and italics,
and underlined, and bolded.
And there's a bunch of upside down triangles in it.
So we hope that a special shout- Is that Illuminati?
It's maybe the Illuminati.
We hope that a special shout-out from the Brothers Mackerel will make your day.
Happy 18th birthday.
We love you.
Has anyone ever made a porn called Illuminati, like the word naughty, and it's like a bunch
of people in robes, and maybe some of them are lizards, and then they fuck?
I would watch the hell out of that.
Yeah, of course you would.
From an academic kind of perspective?
Yeah, and also you're a stonemason.
Happy birthday, Yohan.
We're very proud of you.
We're so proud.
You're living so right.
Got another birthday for Emily Brunston.
You have a birthday for her?
I have a birthday for her, to offer her.
Please accept this birthday, Emily Brunston.
It's from Avital and Julien.
Avital, maybe Avital, it's a lovely name.
I'm sure.
However you interpret it- However you say it, you can't mess that one
up.
Avital.
You can't fuck that name up.
Any way you say it, it's beautiful.
Happy birthday, Dumbleton's dog, sending this message is cheaper than buying people off
to ensure that Mad Men ends in a full-blown orgy like you richly deserve.
Instead of measuring the next year in love, which is weak and filthy, may you measure it
in delicious dips, corgis, and days at the office without a visit from ProBot, the probing
robot.
And I think there was a series of- I would assume in-jokes there?
I think they're not- No, ProBot's a thing.
ProBot's a thing?
Yeah, you said- Is that a-
There's a robot that just like gets in there and like makes sure everything's okay.
What about corgis?
Those are fake.
Those are fake, okay.
I knew that there was something messed up in there.
Happy birthday, Emily.
We hope it's a great one.
Yeah, we're very, very happy for you.
It sounds like you have a pretty sick life.
Sick in a good way.
Should we do some like housekeeping?
Thank you all for- We got so much amazing feedback for the Adventure Zone, the D&D episode
we did last week.
We're gonna figure out a way to continue doing those.
Not I think- I mean, based on what we talked about, not on the Mabim Bam feed, as it were.
You think this is all safe to talk about?
Yeah, I think so.
This is our plans as they stand right now.
Not a Mabim Bam thing, but maybe a separate thing?
Maybe.
Maybe?
People seem to like it.
We're figuring it out.
So, yeah, thank you all for the feedback.
There's actually in the Facebook group, which I don't know if you've been on there recently,
has been like popping off.
Go check it out.
We're usually pretty quick about letting people in.
It's a closed group, so haters can't just hop in.
Sometimes spammers- Spammers do.
They trick me.
They trick us to get in and kick them out, though.
But yeah, there's actually a lot of really good feedback on what we could do better.
Some good ideas for what a D&D podcast could be.
So thank you all very, very, very much for that.
Hope you're enjoying the LA live show.
It was a hoot.
We're figuring out our plans for next year.
We're going to do- Spoiler alert.
We're going to do a shit ton of live shows in 2015.
Basically all over this beautiful nation of ours.
So look forward to that.
Do you think we'll be back?
We'll probably be back next week, right?
I would imagine.
Yeah.
My baby can't hold my attention for that long.
That's true.
Especially with all these fucking dad jokes.
I am cooking up for you.
Yeah.
I am in heat right now.
I am in bad joke heat.
We can't waste a second of this.
All right.
Well, we're going to get back to the show, but thank you all for being so wonderful.
And yeah, more episodes, more regular stuff next week.
God bless.
Hashtag bless.
Hey, Griffin, you could tilt your mic down a little bit.
Yeah, I'm really having to get up on it.
Just like angle it.
There we go.
Oh, if only.
Here we go.
What?
Who's laughing?
Oh, like a dick thing?
Oh, like a dick thing, guys.
It was a dick thing.
Great.
No, it was actually very good.
Well done.
How about another question?
When did we start?
Hey, let's take a question from the audience.
Yeah, what time did we start?
Should we?
Who's got like a great question?
Well, hold on.
You got to be quicker on the draw.
Drew Davenport, do you have a question?
Yeah.
Sorry, fuck everybody else.
Drew Davenport, get back up here.
All right.
Griffin has a glass.
He doesn't get to keep the can, too.
Come on now.
I need a...
We got to conserve our rations.
We're in a riot situation.
Hey, everybody.
It's Drew Davenport.
Woo.
Yeah, there you go.
Angle it up, you giant man.
Yeah.
And turn it a little bit so you can face it.
Look at us now.
Now make eye contact with Griffin.
Look at me now.
Me only.
Go ahead.
Drew, it's just me and you.
Open your heart and let us climb inside, Drew.
This is from a conversation I had on the way here with my girlfriend.
Terrific.
Is it okay to put groceries in a truck bed and drive home?
Oh, no.
It's not.
No.
It depends.
Wait.
What groceries?
Yeah.
If it's a Lean Cuisine, a Lean Cuisine is a little self-preserved little pocket of amazing
food.
If you put a head of lettuce in there, it's going to be gone by the time you get home.
Just the microbes in the air will just dissolve it.
Yeah.
And rinse food, sack of potatoes.
Sack of potatoes, that's okay.
The flowery foods and artichoke.
Paper towel roll.
No, no, no.
Your towel roll is done.
Except flowery foods, except flour because if that bursts back there, that's your week.
That's your whole week at that point.
That's your week.
You are no longer driving.
You are making a rue.
Do you own a truck?
She owns a truck.
She owns a truck?
It's her truck.
Don't.
Well, don't.
I think she gets to call the shots here, Drew.
Drew, wait.
Are you pro or against?
Oh, I'm pro.
You want to put your food out in... Hold on, just so I'm clear, if I took all the food
that you have in your house and I somehow held it in my giant arms, and then I ran down
the street at 55 miles an hour for, I don't know, 45 minutes, and then I came back to
your house and I said, eat all this now, you would be like, yum, yum, give me some.
Can we... Wait, hold on.
One more again.
Can we jump back to 30 seconds ago when we loved Drew?
I love Drew and I want to keep him food safe and food smart.
Everything in there's got E. coli, it's got bird flu, it's got bird shit on it.
It's probably got birds.
It's got live birds in there.
You got a bad case of birds.
You got birds.
Plastic bags, you tie up.
That's not... Yeah, Drew, that was our problem the whole time, Drew.
You really uncorked it.
Did you see that virus... What we thought of bags.
That virus movie where Gwyneth Paltrow got fucking wrecked in the first 15 minutes, and
they were like, guys, don't worry, just get some plastic grocery bags and just wrap that
around your shit for 15 minutes, and the movie was a half hour long because that fixed it.
That did it.
That was how that movie ended.
Super quick, don't even think about it.
Tell me the dirtiest thing you've ever put in your truck bed, go.
I don't have a truck.
Okay, the dirtiest thing that your girlfriend's ever put in her truck bed.
Help him.
Dearest.
A carcass?
An animal carcass?
I just assumed.
You a big deer hunter?
I'm stigmatizing.
Oh, God.
What?
That's everything you... Okay.
Worse than dead deer.
When was this?
Give me a rough timeline.
Okay, so for six months, you've been eating couch Craigslist food.
You've been eating the ass of the person you bought the couch from on Craigslist.
Is that okay?
Imagine the dirtiest person you could think of.
This salad is crazy.
It tastes... It's not... Do I detect a hint of Craigslist ass?
It's not good, but it's not bad.
It was cheap.
Imagine the dirtiest stranger you ever met reached underneath their couch and retrieved
a Hot Pocket.
Yeah.
They then handed that Hot Pocket to you and said, here, stupid.
Eat this.
Eat these Craigslist croutons.
Yeah, absolutely.
This is great.
I'm so excited about eating this that you've retrieved from me.
That's been six months for you.
That's six months.
I fucking hugged you earlier.
That was a bond of trust.
I hugged you, trusting that you didn't have Craigslist mouth.
That's where we are.
These are all hypotheticals.
Yeah.
Oh, well, then it's totally... Oh, well, then I guess we're fine.
I guess we're cool.
Don't worry.
Good job, Drew.
Everybody, Drew Davenport.
Drew Davenport, fucking savior of the podcast.
Where did that full anger go?
Regular question.
Here we go.
Pop it back.
I got a real-ass question.
Corinne, are you here?
Corinne?
Can we keep the chatter down in the audience, maybe, for this?
It's our show, not yours.
We're trying to do a show up here.
Corinne?
Okay.
All right.
Okay, she's here.
Raise your hand, Corinne.
Corinne says, you don't have to come down.
You don't have to come down.
Yeah, she's coming.
That's fine.
No, okay.
You're halfway.
No, no, come on out, Corinne.
Come on down.
Stand in the aisle for the whole time.
No, Corinne.
No, come here.
Come up to the microphone.
I'm fucking with you.
Corinne, this is one of those questions that you did not give us nearly enough details.
Okay, Travis, go.
Well-
Corinne writes.
This is perfect because she's like five feet away.
Yeah.
Just move your mouth up and down, Corinne.
Let's try this.
This will be great.
I teach in an art school and I hate all my students.
Let's not say, hey, let's make a pact not to say Corinne's last name.
Yay.
I hate my students.
Super best, Corinne.
I have to say, Corinne's in a bad situation because if you want to not curry favor with
me, here's the number one thing you do.
You give me art and then you ask me what I think of it.
You know the only art I like?
Wayne's World, the movie.
I haven't liked-
And Wayne's World, the movie-related art.
If you want to give me a framed cell from the original cut of Wayne's World, I'd be
into that.
Can you give us an age window to imagineer with?
I teach at a private college.
Like adult?
Yes.
Not like six-year-olds at which point you go, yeah, this is great, there you do that.
Yeah, it's totally hateful.
Like adults, you can go, no, shit.
Can we get some detail on what it is?
Is it a-
Nude class?
No, come on.
Actually, I do.
I do teach life drawing.
That's one of the classes I teach.
Is that kind of why you hate them?
Because there's obviously some dudes getting there with some future jerk material.
Do they woo?
Like they're on the fucking set of Saved by the Bell?
I don't think-
Like, yahoo!
I'm pretty sure if you yahoo, you are asked to leave.
Corinne's feelings on you as a person have no-
There's not a three strike policy.
No, I'm pretty sure.
Steve, and you've won sports.
Neat bush!
Keep it down.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I need this.
I just get so excited when I see-
I get excited when I see a neat bush.
Are we close?
I'll be honest.
We have many conversations in the beginning of class where I have to tell them, like,
you know, if there is an erection or a fart or-
I'm sorry.
No, I just did the thing that you hate probably.
And then, yahoo.
Because, you know what I love?
Is that you said erection, which is like such a proper way, or a fart, and that made me
so happy.
Corinne, if you can make farts not funny, I'm going to name you the president of magic.
I will follow you around like fucking-
And be fishers of men.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
I will win people to your cause, because you are a wizard.
I tell them that farts are funny, and that's okay.
If you need to laugh, like, just leave the room and laugh, and then come back in.
Have you ever had any smart ass students that tried to-
Tried to paint the fart, like, onomatopoetically?
Braap.
Yeah.
You've done really great work on the chest muscles here, Brett.
You've done- you're really coming along as a student.
You did make it say fart with five R's in, like-
But the shading is spectacular.
And the font was, like, a stinky green cloud, and that was- I'm not going to lie, like,
it was a good stinky green cloud.
It's just the subject matter of it was troubling Brett.
Stop.
This is my kryptonite.
You're killing me.
I mean, the most troublesome poses are when the model decides to do, like, Captain Morgan.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, right.
Like a look-a-matang.
Yeah.
Or a-
Well, it's actually typically women that take that pose.
Men like to do, like, the drop down, let everything hang.
The touchdown dance.
Yeah.
I'd like to do the cover-em-ups.
Is that a pose that's-
I like to do the stay in the hallway and refuse to come in the room.
I'm scared.
I changed my mind.
Is that a pose that's alright?
I do the-
You can keep your $25.
I do the why can't they just paint my jeans while I'm wearing them also.
Why don't students need to get good at painting jeans?
I do the aren't jeans art two.
I've seen a lot of dong paintings, I haven't seen a lot of good jeans paintings.
I don't think Van Gogh had a jeans phase.
Let's tackle that subject next.
Let's cross boundaries together with these dungarees.
It's very avant-garde, yeah.
Yeah.
It's very avant-garde.
So is that-
Okay, we've been talking about dicks for, like, 30 minutes now.
What is it that you actually don't, aren't so crazy about?
Is it really dongs and erections and parts of it?
There's just a lot of, you know, people don't want to be enthusiastic about things, and
that makes you hate your students as a teacher.
And I think that crosses all subject matter.
Real quick, they're paying to be there, right?
Yeah.
They're paying a lot of money to be there.
Yeah, that's gotta be fresh.
Good work, everyone.
Yeah, great job.
Way to go, higher education.
I could see how that would be frustrating.
I would say, though, Crim, it might be a case of them just not want...
I would be so terrified to just do it wrong or have people think that I looked at the
naked person wrong.
Yeah.
Or looked at them too hard.
Or too hard.
I would be constantly averting my eyes.
You would probably get a very disengaged vibe from me, I would think.
Yeah.
If I was in your class and you brought in a naked man that I would draw him, I would
make it fleshy and smooth like a Ken doll down there, because I wouldn't know...
That's a thing.
You call that the Ken doll.
Yeah.
I would know if I was supposed to draw a dick, and if I did, then you'd be like, Crim, I'm
very disappointed in you.
Especially if it's just kind of a stick figure man, but a very precise, detailed dick.
So maybe it's not that your students are...
Really dead on.
Right.
Maybe it's not that your students...
I could pick that out of a lineup.
Sure.
Dead eye dick.
Maybe it's less of a case that your students aren't...
Maybe your students aren't...
Hold on, let me figure out the sentence structure.
Okay, I think I've got it.
Maybe your students are enthusiastic, they're just scared that they're gonna paint a dick
and you'll be very disappointed in them.
So maybe you need to be very explicitly clear about what it is that they're supposed to
draw.
Like...
That I expect out of their penises.
Yeah, just say like, if you wanna go like, bathing suit area out, up and down, start
there.
If you want to really explore the space and do what feels comfortable to you, if you wanna
draw a dick, I'm not going to be disappointed in you.
Griffin, great job.
Some teaching tips.
Thanks.
That's the least we could do.
Give a big hand for Corinne.
Thank you, Corinne.
Thank you.
Got one of Yahoo Answers?
Yeah.
I'm into that.
This Yahoo Answer was sent in by Alan Black.
Thank you, Alan Black.
A very prolific contributor.
So this is by Yahoo Answers user, SlickNinja360, who asks...
Should be good.
Should be pretty good.
Would it be illegal to go into the middle of a forest and build a maze for you?
Yeah.
I guess, yeah.
I guess that's pretty good.
Upon entry, the entrance would close.
It would have spikes on the wall's tops to keep them from escaping.
I was also thinking of having booby traps and things like that.
Once they find the exit, they could leave.
I don't know about illegal, but logistically it seems like an issue.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're gonna have to have some fucking...
Is it a motorized gate or like a magical...
Yeah.
It grows over when they walk through.
It's gonna be a fucking pan's labyrinth magic moss.
I will say, if we can't fix gun laws, but we have been thorough enough to figure out
our forest maze laws, I might be very disappointed in our nation.
Yeah.
If you own the land, and this is troubling because I'm agreeing with the top Yahoo response
to this, but if you own the land, you can build a maze wherever the fuck you want.
I don't know that you can corral people into it.
That's where you run into...
You can leave a trail of peppermints.
There's no guarantee.
This is the beautiful thing about it, if you force people to do it, highly illegal.
Yeah.
If you offer people the opportunity to do it, highly profitable.
It's not like I just bought a house and I feel like I have total agency over it.
I do not think I can invite friends in and then lock the door and then swallow the key
and say, I will let you out as soon as you solve my puzzle of flesh.
And then I would show them my flesh puzzle.
Here's the funny thing about luring.
I would bet...
Is the flesh puzzle your genitals?
That's my balls here.
Okay.
It's your balls.
I would bet that 80 to 90% of the people in this room, if you stumbled upon what you were
guaranteed to be a solvable forest maze- That would lock you in and you would fucking
die if you couldn't solve it.
If, that's a big if Griffin.
How many of you would say?
All right.
Yeah.
I'll tackle this bitch.
This is everything I've ever trained for.
Yeah.
Everybody raise your hand.
If you stumbled upon a pan's labyrinth, you would not-
This is serious.
Okay.
There's a lot of people.
I'm raising my hand.
Okay.
You would risk your life.
All those years of playing Professor Layton games are finally going to pay off.
You're going to solve this shit.
Sherlock Holmes.
All right.
The Goblet of Fire.
Yeah.
The Goblet of Fire game.
It was so good.
Well, you play it in your head where you go, I would have gone left.
Yeah.
I would have slain the basilisk.
That's what you sound like.
That was in book one, dick.
Sorry.
Two.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Keep it to yourselves.
What would lure you into... Okay.
What would lure me into a forest maze?
Doing the opening of a fucking forest maze.
Right?
You got to.
What if it's risking your life, though?
I don't want... You know what?
The fourth verse of Tim McGraw's Live Like You Were Dying directly references, I went
into every forest maze I saw, I think.
I heard a pan flute beckoning me in, but there was gold doubloons at the end.
Bite traps weren't scared me wide.
Have you ever heard that song?
Have you ever heard the song?
I'm not great with melodies.
That's actually... I was singing the harmony.
I thought someone would join in.
What else we got?
Let's do another audience question.
Yeah.
How about another... Oh, fuck.
There's something about people being in the front row.
It's very intimidating.
Come on up.
You're on the front.
Yeah.
We'll do a front row.
Wait.
You raised your hand.
You can't say shit when we pick you.
Shit.
Me?
You walked into this forest maze.
You volunteered.
Now it's your time to get out.
What's your name?
I should volunteer.
My name is Linda.
Linda, no bummers.
No bummers.
Here we go.
Should I have another baby?
What?
For dinner?
Hey.
Come on.
How many are you... How many?
You popped into my head.
How many you up to?
I have two kids and they're nine and 14.
Boy or girl?
What?
Come on.
You're just gonna fucking chill?
Hey, everybody.
You don't know Linda's deal.
Leave some for the rest of us.
Linda, boy or girl?
14-year-old boy.
Trying to start a highlight team or something?
Come on.
And my new husband doesn't have any.
Have any.
See?
Come out.
Two people.
No boo.
That was you a second ago and now you have this new information.
You're like, this is a noodle scratcher.
Is your hubby a gung-ho about it?
No.
Does he have a gung-ho about it?
Does he want to have a kid?
He's very pleased to make me happy, but his love is
Sure.
Then you gotta do it.
Are you into it?
No, come on.
Stop it.
Are you into the idea?
I mean, that's ultimately like the only
It's scary, the only
I would love to have the support of a wonderful man
He's a bit nice, though.
You got the 14-year-old with the baby-sit.
That's true.
I mean
That's built-in.
That's nice.
Yeah, that's not a bad point.
Like, you don't get that.
Like you don't get that like Justin six me three Griffin like three months old. There wasn't like Justin you got this
Don't you're shoving a cold kid cuisine down his throat. Oh, he died a great work six-year-old
I guess you didn't first time my baby said I was 12 years old and I microwaved a pot
Because I was trying to make rice pudding from a recipe for book for kids
in my defense a recipe book for kids should have clarified the proper cookware
It's all say they'll know right? Yeah
No, it's
It already went to print
It's 1992. They'll know right?
I mean you do you want a pros and cons list like pros like
that this
Could be like this super successful kid this one. You might not have had the super successful kid
You might not have had the the Bill Gates yet. I don't know anything about your other two children
They might be very bright, but they are they are they are they here?
Okay, well it feels a little greedy
What if you're what if the reason once your ender?
Oh my god, what if the reason they've been so great so far is because you have exactly enough energy to raise two great kids
What if at this point you're dividing your labors and you're gonna get three our parents had two at one point and they were awesome
They were going
Everything was going so well
Hey, if it weren't for me the show we called my brother and me and we'd have some Nickelodeon would be very litigious in that regard
Yeah, you have to have me terrific Linda there is literally
Not a single piece of information. I need to answer this question that I would feel comfortable asking you
Literally cannot get any of the facts. I need to solve this problem for you and let and just to clarify
Once we answer this it is binary. Yeah
We are literally deciding the existence of a human being right now
Will you name that child after us? Oh shit by which I mean the brothers, okay?
the baby the baby the movie dot org dot org
hashtag
You put the hashtag at the end of the web address, right? That's how that wait
Do you want to do it?
Look at all three of us in the eyes six eyes six eyes all the stuff Linda. Do you want to do it?
No, fuck. Come on. I'm not gonna push it out of my body Linda
Yeah, I wish I could for you because I'd love to feel what it's like in the world. Anybody have a coin
Linda our level involvement with our child will put most deadbeat dads make them look like heroes
Like we are not going to be involved in the racing of this child. That's why I'm not tying myself to an answer on this show
Okay, well you ask I'm thinking of a number between one and two
Guess it
It was two that means you have to have the baby. Congratulations Linda. She's having a baby. I
I feel pretty weird about that one. I just created a human life. I am unto a god
Alright, what else we got guys? How long we've been going we've been going for three and a half hours feels that way
So do you wanna Yahoo? Yeah. Yeah
Come on
Show
Just created a human life what the fuck else do you want more fart jokes? We just created a person
You guys need to get your priorities straight this Yahoo was sent in by Charlene. Thank you char or Charlene
It was asked by Yahoo answers user Kayla who asks does this seem like a good PowerPoint to show my parents?
Convincing them to help me get a horse
I
Slide one horses are awesome. Click click. Hey, your joke is exactly what's in the bit
Title what I want most in life. Sure. Yeah
No, what everyone wants most in life really for being honest next slide content. Wait timeout. We talk about horses a lot
Sorry
Just here when everyone else does I don't think we talk about them more than like
Anyone should normal people like people normally talk about horses. They're pretty great
Pretty solid next slide contents asking them to stay silent during the presentation
Mom's dad's mom shit down fucking cell phone off. It's business. I worked on this for a half a fucking hour
You close Pinterest for us for like a second pause frozen
Amanda
close pictures
Next some photos of horses along with words all caps a horse
So just fucking laying down the foundation. That's good
The ground the equestrian groundwork in case you were not aware click click exhibit a exhibit a a horse
Or legs hoods. What if that's all it took? Oh, that's a horse. Okay. Oh shit. That's basically the cool
Yeah, you can have they have ever seen five thousand dollars and then five thousand dollars a year. Yeah totes. Totally. Yeah
Next telling them how I've changed and I'm responsible enough to take care of all I killed the last listen
I know I fucked up last year
Bad, I know I fucked up with dad's little dumpling last year
And then I know that I fucked up the year before that with dazzle dumpling jr. Wait
jr. Was predicated upon the fact that this horse was in fact going to die and also
Proceeded it's that it was a time-traveling feature horse
No one's a special horse listen, we had to act fast to buy that special special time-traveling horse
Forget already daddy's little Dublin
So much. It's a good name. I've changed though
And I can do it next supplies and costs. I've done my research
Check out this Excel spreadsheet. Does this get your blood pumping the next one's my favorite?
next
money saving tips and ideas
Mom dad you've been
listening
Diane do you need all those clothes? I need a horse real bad for the third time
We could cut our food budget click click in half that is
Next we're spending so much on oats our oats budget could know that's my mistake. That is not a typographical error
It's budget will drastically increase. I believe it may have been the bottleneck in the last two horse experiments
Come to think of it in retrospect
Upon further reflection our oats supply was was at issue
Next this little Dublin jr
Next explaining the benefits to owning a horse many pros and cons chart. I put together. I bet the cons list is pretty fair
there
cons too great
Too many main too smooth
Will eventually die in six months. Sorry dad. Sorry about this. Our yard is full
next
Showing one horse I really want and that would be perfect for me
then two others that would work great for me and I want so and
And they'll always know they were second and always horses have a sixth sense for that stuff
Next a last side note. Well, I guess they'd be their fifth sense because horses don't have thinking. Yeah
Or taste a some
Salt what do you want told great? No good choice just salt then
Fantastic. We're excellent selection Tom click. Yeah, perfect. You're just gonna lick a big block of salt. Fantastic
Do you want that over a potato? No, just the salts great thing. Thanks. I'm good here. Hmm. Just gonna give me running energy
terrific
Great work horse
Stupid next get a job get a job horse salt theme
What's your sodium like next a last side note and telling them I don't want to hear
Anything about this topic until next week so that they can talk about it with each other and then look at the PowerPoint and think
And whatnot, you know, yeah, what the fuck?
Do not rush to judgment mom and dad I'm gonna yeah, I think that's a fucking huge power
That's a shoe last slide. Click click stay silent after shut your fucking mouth
Keep your phone silent and also keep your fucking mouth shut not until next Tuesday
Yeah, we'll be horse to me click click for a week. Good night
You say that and we laugh at that that's gonna be just enough time for that sweet idea to firm it
Well, cuz what night one is like, can you believe she can you believe she did that shit for the third fucking time?
Like we would even do that. I think you were right. We should have another kid. This one's a bus. This one sucks
Then maybe three days later, it's like, you know what I'm thinking about it
We had some good times at that horse and then the next day it's like no
It died and then the other one died like super fast
What are we thinking right and then by the seventh day, that's when God rested. What were you talking about?
This seems foolproof to me
It's pretty solid if you have a foolproof plan for getting a horse and you've been sitting on for this long
I'm very upset with both of you
You gotta let me in on that stuff. Have another answer Travis question
Mm-hmm. How's the show go? Should we do one more from the audience? Yes. Yeah
Somebody far back cuz I want
Nobody back there has their hand up. That's fine. Anybody else? No, I see you. Yes
Yes, come on down far this back person we could see
Oh, no, we'll give J. Oh JP, I'm sorry
Hello, thanks
My name is Jeannie and my question is so I have a cat who pees terrific we all do
Hold the fucking phone one second
Yeah, it's great it's like a big long chair Jeannie was it was it Jeannie I
I would like to have a couch someday not a dream. You should announce in public. Yeah, I
Would like to have a kind of the perfect sitting platform
I'd like to solve this whole couch thing one day
Have you thought about finding a cheap couch that you can buy a wholesale that you can treat like a burner?
And you can have a burner couch that will last you for a month until the smell starts to overtake your your boot
Yeah buying a box your cat could be in yeah
Let's workshop this I want to hear the endgame of Griffin's plan where you have a couch
Designated for your cat to be in basically well
No, you would also do a little bit of sitting in it from time to time
Maybe a bit of lounging
Who gets stuck sitting in the bait cow?
What you know you have to take put a lot of tape down the middle say cat that have is your that's your
Be cool
When you watch orange is the new black. What do you even fucking do?
Do you stand up and look at the TV like you're saluting it?
That's what you're shaking your head. Yes. I stand up and look at the TV. What's your gym?
I should just lays down on the hardwood floor
Yeah, yoga ball. What's your sitting game like?
It's so wait. Oh my god. Okay, so your cat won't pee in a chair. It needs a lot of room to express itself
Is it like an inflatable plastic chair? I wish I had one. I
Considered it. Yeah, I said again like a plastic inflatable chair
Couch, this is such a nice furniture set. Yes from Spencer's gifts
It came with the plasma ball. It looks super great
It came with all the novelty greeting cards with bikini babes on
Jeannie how old is your cat?
Oh
Ornery pee cats. Yeah
Jeannie I got bad news who is real young. Yeah, that's a lot
13 I would have said stick it out take it out and then Travis. That's a bummer
So, I mean, I'm just saying you got like another 13 years of peace. Oh couch. Yeah
Maybe it's time for more permanent solution. Let the cat explore the world. Yeah, maybe that's an outdoor cat from now on
Cats cats can't talk and the only way they can ask for freedom is by peeing on your couch
Maybe that cat saying I think I can do this on my own. I
Caught a homer bound on Cinemax last week and that seems like something I could super get into
Please open the door or I'm going to keep peeing. What's your favorite thing? Cuz I guess it was couch
I
Read your journal about wanting a couch someday and I want out
You made me feel guilty cuz I have two couches
I have three couches in my house and you made me feel like I'm living some sort of life of extreme luxury that I don't
Does it not use the litter box what's going on with your cat's whole deal
Is she mad at you? Maybe she's mad that you don't have a couch. Get a dog cuz those never pee anyway. Yeah
That's isn't that why you haven't neutered
Yeah, yeah, that's exactly it. Do you want this water spot? Nah, I'm cool
I got neutered so I don't even need fluids in my whole body. No, so I miss folks super neutered. Yeah
I just get in there take it all just get in there with an ice cream scoop and really just like
Why is your cat crying oh she's not super super super neutered
It's basically eyes longs firm and that's about it. That's about all that's going on in there. She's very agile though
So that's I guess the best
I don't know what else to tell you buy a couch and just yeah
It's no I mean it is definitely your probably a couch in every room and you will have at least a while where she hasn't found
One yeah, she'll probably get into the jam of peeing on one and maybe you can put that in the bubble
Do you have any bubbles?
Can you put like I asked you a question whether or not you have bubbles
What about a tarp? Okay, you need you don't have a lot of things you yeah
Jeannie you have a lot of super achievable life goals, and I'm into that I
I think that's gonna bring you a lot of happiness
How are you feeling today Jenny like super fulfilled? I met like two of the biggies today. It's going good with one trip to Rite-Aid
Yeah, I got a Rite-Aid couch is great
Oh, yeah, I got a Rite-Aid couch is great
We should probably start moving
Thank you all so guys holy shit, thank you so so so so much
You guys are fucking amazing
We don't have anything to sell you we had an accident Travis's salad was not just a super fucking funny bit
We don't have we don't have anything cuz the post office fucked us again
But there are shirts. There's max fun shirts. There's max fun
Canteens out there. What are these what are these called now jeans? Is that an out? No, it's made out of no water
It's a fucking water bottle, whatever
We we do have some stuff and we'll be hanging out out there after the show to say hi and take oh bless you
You okay? Thank you all so much for coming out. Thank you very very much. Yeah, please be careful out there
I'm genuinely concerned that it's gonna be like rough fucking Mad Max
So so be careful. Don't let anybody steal your fuel
Sorry to interrupt past us but want to say thanks to nature box. We can order great tasting healthy snacks get in shape for the summer
well, I mean for the early fall and late summer with healthy treats like bbq kettle kernels and get
50% off your first order go to nature box comm slash my brother
Usually the way what happens at this point is we thank John Roderick
Thank you, John Roderick in the long winters for the use of our theme song and to departure off the album putting the days to bed
Fucking great. Great, dude. We got to chat with them last week. That was nice a super course
Thank you to the amazing Maximum Fun Network for thank you amazing Jordan Jesse
Jordan Jesse did a fucking great job another round of applause for Jordan Jesse go
For Janet Barney, thank you, Janet. Thank you. Everybody. You guys are so fucking great. You know what that final yahoo
Wait, how about a round of applause for yourselves? Oh, yeah
Hey, and how about another round of applause for true Davenport bringing the fucking heat? Yeah, we can we got Griffin hit me
This final yahoo answer was ended by anything about a true Davenport. Yeah
But yeah, it's in the arts and humanities section it's asked by Moniz who asked
Who was John Candy? What did he do? Why is he important?
My name is Justin McElroy. I'm Travis. I'm good for McElroy. This has been my brother my brother me kiss your dad
Skull wear on the lips
Now you can play the outro music this is a good point or not it's cool
Yeah
Maximum fun org comedy and culture artists owned listener supported
Hey feeling lonely, my name is Jesse Thorne. My name is Jordan Morris
Do you want to listen to a program where two good friends get intimate with amazing guests like Maria Bamford?
Rob Corddry and other comedy superstars Jordan Jesse go is here for you
Every week, we'll spill our guts for you and then make some jokes Jordan Jesse go free at maximum fun org