The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it
Also, this show isn't for kids which I mentioned only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening
What's up, you cool, baby?
It's better, it's better with you
It's better it's better with you
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother, my brother, and me, an advice show for the modern era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
Oh no. No, no, no, no, no. I'm Travis, the middle-est.
No, I like it.
I like the energy, except for the spin on the name.
Oh, nope.
Oh, that's good stuff.
It's something new, Travis. We're in the 600s now.
I was standing at the sexy sixes.
Oh, the sex hundreds.
The sex hundreds.
We're like 66 episodes away from another episode that we're going to have to skip.
There's no way.
We would get in so much trouble.
We would get in so much trouble with my dad for doing the devil's eyes.
I'm not going to summon El Diablo.
No, thank you.
We're already tempting fate enough playing Dungeons and Dragons to then mess with that black magic.
Oh my God.
This is like when my D&D character died all over again, just like that Chick track.
If you were to make a biopic of Gary Gygax, do you think you would put in a scene where he's looking at a piece of paper and it says Dungeons or Dragons?
And he's looking at it and he's like, well, hold on a second.
Then he just erases it.
And he showed it.
Should I make a game about Dungeons, question mark?
Dragons, question mark?
And then there was a character like Justin Timberlake in social.
Dungeons ain't cool.
You know what's cool?
Dungeons and Dragons.
But then the haters are like, how are you going to fit a dragon inside of a dungeon, Gary?
It's too small.
It's a small chamber, Gary.
What I'm saying is that I'm going to put the dungeon inside the dragon.
Well, I don't think that's it either, Gary.
And that's my vision for Elden Ring too.
The dungeon's inside the dragon.
Yeah, that's good stuff.
This is an advice show.
I'm standing. I wanted to bring standing energy to this episode.
Sometimes I dig deep, deep down and I stand up.
You summon everything within you.
I channel all my strength and I stand.
I used to do this for hours at Best Buy.
I should be able to do it for an hour while we record this podcast, right?
I'm at work.
I still have the same springy, dewy body that you had in your Best Buy days.
Yeah, that's true. I was fucking so sexy.
I was ripped.
That blue polo.
I was thinking about this this morning, speaking of dewy, sexy bodies.
What do you guys think you're the Ryan Reynolds of?
Because I saw Ryan Reynolds and clearly he's the Ryan Reynolds of movies, right?
Well, and selling cell phones.
Yeah, and owning soccer teams, I believe.
Did he need to sell the cell phones?
No, that's a passion. That's a passion project.
He just loves getting burners in the hands of miscreants.
The gym, the soccer team, the movies, that's his day job, right?
Selling cell phones, that's his passion.
One for him, one for me.
Yeah, he's the Ryan Reynolds of selling cell phones.
The Lord came to him in a dream and said,
Ryan, you must sell cell phones that when people drop them in the toilet, they go, eh, oh well.
I'll get another one.
That's fine.
What am I the Ryan Reynolds of?
Yeah.
I mean, is this about physical appearance?
No, no, no.
If you were saying, well, you know, like Ryan Reynolds from movies?
Well, I'm like the Ryan Reynolds of blank.
You know what I mean?
Can I say movies?
Ryan Reynolds of movies.
Well, I guess if he's going to take Ryan Reynolds of cell phones,
you could be the Ryan Reynolds of movies.
He shouldn't be allowed to take all that stuff.
You, as we realized this week, or as I realized this week,
you did perform in an Oscar-nominated film.
Right.
You're basically an Oscar-nominated film performer for your hidden cameo.
That's true.
It's not really hidden. I mean, I am in the credits of the film.
No, if you want to say hidden, Justin and I have a hidden cameo
where robots took our jobs.
Ironically, in the movie Mitchell's vs. the Machines,
robots took our jobs.
And you know I'm rooting for him in cancer.
You know I want Lenny to get that EGOT.
Obviously.
That would be so huge for him, because you know he's just like,
he's tortured until he gets that O.
But me, like, I could just have an awe.
You know what I mean?
If Mitchell's vs. the Machines wins the Oscar for best animated picture,
I think they do have to send me one,
because I did do a voice in it.
Who knows, that could have been the linchpin
keeping the whole thing together.
They should give out Oscars sized to the contribution.
So Griffin would get a little teeny tiny one,
because he had an off-screen cameo.
Like an earring.
Wow, okay.
I don't know why you had to tear me down for that.
Because we got cut because of robots.
Because robots took our jobs.
It's weird that robot didn't take my job though.
Did we tell that story?
We can probably tell that story now.
Let's preface it by saying,
there is no animosity from us whatsoever.
It sounds like there's a little bit.
It's just such a fucking funny,
no it is towards you,
but so we recorded some voices for Mitchell's vs. the Machines.
This is something that happens, you know,
especially with voiceover stuff.
You don't know if you're actually going to be like,
in it until,
they just swap you out with stuff.
So they wanted us to do voices for these appliances.
And the initial thing that they had wanted to do,
was have like computer generated voices.
That was like AI or whatever,
but I guess the voice technology was trademarked or whatever.
So those were the parts that we were going to do.
And then they managed to clear the AI voices.
So like the artificially generated voices,
they used those quite literally.
Literally.
We were supposed to be immune to jobs taking our machines.
That is exactly what happened to us.
And it's delicious because that is,
if you've seen the film,
pretty much the plot of the thing.
The plot of the thing. We're living it.
You lived it.
McElroy's vs. the Machines.
And the machines win.
But Griffin.
I will cut my Oscar into three pieces
that we can assemble Shrine of the Silver Monkey style.
Yes, I've seen this. This is a Solomon thing.
No, let Griffin keep the Oscar.
Now Griffin, I don't want to put you on the spot,
but do you think you could recreate?
Yeah, sure, sure.
Could you recreate your Oscar nominated line?
Yeah, sure, sure. Here we go.
Today I'll be playing the voice of Freezer.
Freeze!
So there's...
But you did have a line in it.
That's pretty much it.
That's it.
No, you're the guy in the hallway in the dorm.
No, I didn't get that part.
I think you did.
Maybe I did. Who knows?
But all I know is that
I am going to melt the Oscar down
and turn it into money.
That was very fun.
Can I reiterate? There is zero.
Zero anime. It's a great movie
and we are really excited.
Especially from me because I dig it in.
I'm trying to be gracious about this
and Griffin is making it so challenging.
No, no, no. You're being gracious to them
and I'm being super gracious to them
because they kept me.
This is how gracious I am.
They sent out casting crew gifts
and I still have one. I have it on display.
Yeah, I didn't shatter mine with a ball peen hammer.
Definitely.
I have those now.
I do.
Can I jump back to The Wisdom of Solomon real quick?
Just want to touch on it.
Yes!
That's what this country is missing.
Let's all take it back to The Wisdom of Solomon.
Isn't it fucked up?
Solomon's like,
all right, I'm going to cut this baby in half
and then you guys can each have half.
One of the people is like,
sounds good to me.
Do you guys want to make a billion dollars?
Sure.
Listen. Fuck, this is good.
King Solomon's like,
guys, if you're not standing already,
get on my level because it is invigorating.
My mic's just not that high.
Get higher, baby.
I'm looking down to the microphone.
Okay.
King Solomon's like,
well,
if you all can't agree on whose baby it is,
I guess we'll just have to cut it in half.
Then the baby turns around
and is like,
you're going to want to run that by HR.
Boss Baby 3.
Whoa!
Yes!
That's so choice, right?
Yes! Fuck yes!
I love this.
We can have a whole series of this
where it's like,
oh, Pharaoh said to kill all the male babies
and we got to put this baby in a basket
and float him down the river.
The baby turns around like,
excuse me? Boss Baby 3.
It's all biblical.
Listen, don't confine yourself.
Baby's day out.
The baby's rocking around on girders
and there's a monkey trying to eat it.
The baby's about to fall off the girder
and then Boss Baby pops up and he's like,
um,
don't think you're going to file for Workman's comp.
Boss Baby 3.
Boss Baby pops up and says, hey, you're better than this.
You don't have to be a clown for those adults out there watching you.
I liked my bet.
We'll workshop it.
There's plenty of time for this Boss Baby 3 trailer.
A lot of people like to talk about Solomon's Great Wisdom
because he was like,
let's cut a baby in half. JK, you win.
Cut a baby into half.
But I bet you he also had some
thinkers of rulings like, oh, man,
she did, she menstruated
on the Lord's day. Got, she's dead.
Cut her in half.
All of his stuff, they don't try to do
problematic prophylaxis on this biblical character
just assuming there's some wack
shit in Solomon's closet.
Yeah, well, we talk about how it worked
out with the baby, but it's never like, oh, cut the
house in half. Oh, well, let's cut this.
We'll cut that cow and stop trying to
fucking cut stuff in half, Solomon.
How close did he get? Was he like, I'm going to
do it. I'm really going to do it.
Why weren't... He had like a paper
cutter that's just like, oh.
I'm going to get him.
I just want both people to be like
doing this bare hands like the power team
and he just, he came up with that ruling
on the spot to save face.
You don't want to actually...
Nevermind. I don't want to tear the baby
in half. You were going to let me do it.
I saw in your face you didn't want me to.
But you definitely were going to let me,
so I'm giving it to her.
What? What are you talking about?
You tried to karate chop the baby.
We both said stop.
No, I can see she didn't mean it.
When she said stop, she was totally cool
with me karate chopping this baby in half.
What a dumb way of fixing the problem.
I'm going to cut the baby in half.
You're going to wait.
We both know that baby won't keep
working. Half a baby won't turn
into a whole baby.
He had to lean over to like the king's hand
and be like, check this out.
I'm going to go jazz on this one.
I'm going to get a little loose.
Just follow my lead.
I bet you ten...
Follow me in the key of G, my man.
I bet you ten ducats this works.
Ten bags of salt.
Follow me on this one, man.
But be ready to pull the record and laugh
like it was a joke if they don't buy it.
I'm the king. You got to do it.
It is time for a fight.
I've lost my monitor signal.
One moment, please. Bear with.
While Justin gets his monitor back in,
I was thinking maybe we could raise
the level of sophistication
here on the show a little bit.
There was a little ribaldry in there.
King Solomon. It's very blue.
I think it's time that we
maybe take some time to appreciate.
It's a work of fart.
We know what it is it's going to be.
We know your bits. We know what this is going to be.
I know, but there's a lead-in to it, Griffin.
Yeah, you got to let him work his magic.
There's art to it, man.
Sure. There's fart to it.
Now, Griffin has shown...
Fuck.
What's wrong, Juice?
No, he just burped and said fuck at the same time.
It's hard standing up because
my cords are not wanting to cooperate.
Yeah, I had a real situation
that I had to untangle while recording,
but I'm fully dialed into your bit now, Travis,
and I want you to start it.
Now, Griffin, can you
please fill the list, Marion?
I don't want to do that for you.
I'll do it. Here's how it works.
Travis is going to come up with a
a punny
a punny name
for a work of art that makes it
ribald or blue.
He's not going to say what it is.
He's going to make us say it because
that makes us complicit.
He's going to come up with a punny name
with a clue
and then that we're complicit in the thing
because we're actually the ones coming up with it.
And this time, I'm going to change something slightly.
You got to buzz in.
You got to buzz in this time.
Oh, interesting.
And how do we do that?
You can say whatever you want to.
You don't have to say buzz, Griffin.
The world's your oyster.
A scientist resurrects a dead masturbator.
But who's really the monster?
Buzz, buzz.
I heard Griffin's buzz first, but Justin's buzz most.
Griffin?
I'm going to say Wankenstein.
That is correct. Wankenstein.
Wow. Wow. Huge.
It was either going to be that or Frankenstein.
Not the most outside of the box one, if I'm being honest.
Okay.
That's the reason it was first.
Check out the balls on this guy.
He's tilting at windmills.
Oh, I got it.
Dang buzz.
Is that Dong Quixote?
No, I'm sorry. Justin?
Wow.
Say it one more time, please.
Check out the balls on this guy.
He's tilting at windmills.
Yes, Justin?
Dong Quixote?
There it is. Yes.
Oh, stop it.
Well done. Okay, it's one and one.
One and one.
A famous detective is on the case
when a man on a train shits himself to death.
Huh.
Say it one more time.
A famous detective is on the case
when a man on a train
shits himself to death.
A piece of that tip just got me, Odell.
Yes, Justin?
Is it Sharder on the Orient Express?
Oh, no. So close.
Is it Squirter on the more Orient Express?
No, no. You're both wrong.
It's Turter on the Orient Express.
No, no, no.
That's a weakness with the question.
Okay, but Sharder doesn't rhyme with murder.
Squirter does.
And Squirter doesn't necessarily
refer to proof.
I don't want to get...
I don't...
Just go on.
It makes me mad.
Okay, it's one and one.
It's like the concept of it is already so fucking rotten
that when the execution is off,
it's like, why are we...
No. Hey, no.
Just because you got the question wrong, Griffin,
don't shit around on me.
Don't make this like it's Travis's problem.
Yeah, you said dong kihoti
when I clearly said balls in the clue.
You're right. And as we all know,
dong refers pretty much mostly
to the shaft.
I have a diagram prepared.
Look over here, guys.
So just because you got it wrong, Griffin,
doesn't mean the game's broken.
I will say if someone's old balls popped out of their pants,
you wouldn't point at the old balls and be like,
look at that dong.
This is referring to, you know,
at the most sort of liberal interpretation,
the whole kit.
Right? And the caboodle.
Maybe. Maybe.
Okay. Next.
Next bit.
Next. Oh, are you done?
Oh, next bit. I thought Travis had another one.
No, I only did three.
Somebody is going around my apartment complex
and stealing all the catalytic converters.
How do I protect mine?
That's from catalytic chaos in Kentucky.
Do you want to go ahead and do your
usual thing, Juice?
Just the thing you usually say
that helps these kinds of situations.
Well, okay, yes.
Yes. Well,
I don't know. In this case.
I don't know if putting jelly on it is going to be a good fix.
It may catalyze the jelly.
This is the concern.
They get extremely hot, the catalytic converters.
Yeah. Could you glue it in?
Is that a problem?
Yeah, what's keeping it in there anyway?
It seems like it's not really in there good.
I will say, I've owned
a car or two in my day.
It's easy to take stuff out of there.
It's a lot harder to put it back in, I've found.
Because sometimes they'll take something out and then be like,
well, where the fuck does that even go?
Because frankly, a lot of it is all kind of the same color.
I've also noticed that.
And so, like, if we could color
code more of that stuff, that would be great.
That would make it easier for thieves, for sure.
You're not helping. You're making it harder.
No. Oh, but then you paint your catalytic
converter a different color.
It'll burn the paint. Fuck!
They get so fucking hot, dude.
And this, can I say about this problem?
We actually need to solve it
pretty quickly, because this problem
is only going to get worse.
With the catalytic converter
issue, with everything going on,
this is just getting worse. So we need a solution.
When the robots come around, they love eating it so much.
No, it's because the catalytic converters
got palladium, it's one of the precious metals
that it uses.
It's the favorite food of robots.
Robots eat palladium and it gets stronger.
I think so, too. I think robots
do eat palladium and it gets stronger.
If you put jelly on it, jelly will fucking burn
right off. Nothing's fixed.
Bait car. Bait car, Travis.
Let me tell you. Bait car.
This catalytic converter, it's rigged to blow.
Not for, well, that's, now we're talking
about killing people because they steal
the car part for money. How many catalytic
converters? Let me ask you guys. I just want to
just say a number. Don't think about it.
How many catalytic converters would someone
have to steal before
exploding them with a bait car would be
the appropriate proportional response?
None. Travis, you're asking
at what point is
murder okay for that? No, no, no. That's
not what I said. I said blowing them up.
It sounds like what you're saying is that
exclusively.
Blowing up doesn't have to be murder.
It can just pop in their face. Maybe an ink.
It can be like the guy who makes the bait
Amazon packages that people
steal and then it farts and
you hear fucking Bill
Ingvall come out of a speaker like,
here's your sign, and you're like,
yeah, get those fucking people.
Get those thieves. Yeah, maybe like a
permanent ink situation.
Oh, you removed the catalytic converter.
I don't know what you're talking about. Yeah, you do.
Purple face. I don't enjoy
I guess
like capital punishment, which is
what you seem to be a huge
fan of. I'm talking about spraying them with
ink, Griffin. Though that is
I don't know if it's cruel, but it is unusual.
I don't think it's cruel or unusual
punishment though. So
I would say that you know how
like the like really
fancy stock cars or whatever
like there's people who will just like
pop the steering wheel out and they can take the
steering wheel. What if you just could do that with
your catalytic converter? Like
you just slide on under there and you like
push in on it really hard and
it pops and it pops out and you can take it
with you to work. What about one of those
you know in like the 90s where they had those
like diaries where
you had to like voice activate it for
kids so that your sneaky little brother
couldn't get in there and you had to be like
dreamboat in order to like open the thing
maybe you put a voice activated lock.
I have no idea what, I have no idea what you're talking about.
You don't remember that? That was like a
voice activated diary? It wasn't a
voice activated diary, it had a lock on it.
It had a voice activated lock on it. Yes,
that's true, yes. And you would say like
you would say the code word so your sneaky little
brother, that creep, couldn't get in there
and read as you were writing about all the people you had crushes on.
You know,
put that on your card. I bet I could have cracked
your fucking code Trav easy. It was
DuckTales. I just walked up to it
and just been like,
Xanth, Xena, and then it would have just popped
right up and revealed all your fucking secrets to me.
It was actually Xena, then Xanth.
Oh, I apologize. Yeah, thank you.
Juicy okay.
Justin, are you reading about what
catalytic converters do?
No, I know what they do. Now?
No, I knew before that. Oh, did you?
I was talking about it before the pause,
Travis. Uh-huh, because you looked it up.
Review the tape. Because you looked it up.
No, I know because...
Okay, doesn't matter. That's not funny
for me to talk about that I know this.
It's not funny. You can get a lock
for them. There, if you don't want to be
funny, Travis, there. You can get a lock
for it. Oh, I thought you said
you could get a lot for them and we were going to talk
about the price. No, you can't get a lock
for it, actually. How much do you think...
Wait, okay, listen. How much do you think you could
give for a catalytic converter?
I know that it costs like two Gs to replace it.
Oh, yeah, really? It's probably less than that.
So I could probably get like a thousand...
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Hey. Yeah? Hold on a second.
What if you stole your own catalytic converter?
Oh, they'd never see that coming.
Then the thief comes along and like, well, fuck.
Somebody already hit this one.
Listen, it's not a good for your environment,
but one car
cruising around, putting that bad
air gravy
out and it's not being purified
by the catalytic
converter. It's not that bad.
Just do it. It's just one.
It's just one. It's like a drop in the bucket.
Do you know what that is? Like cranking out that fog gravy
constantly. Yeah, that bad gravy.
Just do what that kid in my dorm floor did
whenever he wanted to smoke weed.
Just put a
dryer sheet over your tailpipe.
It'll basically do the same thing.
It's going to blow some clean
cool, clean linen smell through there.
You're going to be fine. I had a friend who called that a
wookie tube. I don't know if that was something other people
call it, but you would take a paper, like a paper
towel roll, like the cardboard
part of it, and you would stuff it with dryer sheets
and then you would rip the bong
and then you would put your mouth on that tube and
you would breathe out into it. And maybe
it's just because he did call it a wookie tube, but we would
of course, like when we breathed out, just be like
vvvrtttttt.
And we would laugh
and laugh and laugh. Because it was funny!
Okay because it was funny and it was a
different time so I'm wondering if you could do that
into a catalytic converter, what would come out the other
side of it. Oh great question, yeah
yeah yeah. Maybe that's it, maybe there's somebody
stealing your catalytic converter so they can blow their weed
smoke through it without getting caught.
That's, yeah. Can you think about that? Maybe they need it more than you.
Thank you,
yes! Here's another question.
I recently received a very nice
handwritten card from my grandma.
I actually received a very nice handwritten card
from their grandma, too, so there, that's nice.
Oh, thanks.
Your grandma loves us, too.
Thanks for the good time.
We went and saw Death on the Nile together.
We had a great time.
Don't tease me, I'd love to get out there for that.
Oh yeah, me too.
She said she was going through some old family pictures
and sending them, did I mention the baby pictures
or did you guys start doing your bits before I said that?
I don't know.
There were baby pictures inside the card.
She said she was going through some old family pictures
and sending them to the families of who was in the picture,
meaning I should have received old pictures of myself.
However, these pictures aren't of me.
I asked my mom, she has no idea
who is actually in those pictures,
but it sure isn't me.
Brothers, what do I do with these pictures?
Do I send them back to her and correct her?
Yeah.
Yeah, that'd be good.
Oh, wrong!
You knew it wasn't that one, right?
Just fucking kicking the door out of your house
and just rubbing her face.
Wrong!
You think it's me?
Hey, Dweeb.
You blew it!
Blew it, Dweeb.
You're wrong, now eat them, eat the pictures, grandma!
Wrong!
Do I send them back?
Obviously not.
Or just, should I just try to track down
who is in these pictures or is it a lost cause?
I mean, there's no reason,
why are these pictures chained to their physical form?
It's time to set them free.
Get them up on the internet, just be like,
don't put them on Facebook though, that'll be too easy.
You need to put them on ancestry.com or something,
just be like, hey, got some new pics?
New pics of this.
What do you think ancestry.com does?
Because they definitely don't have-
You know how they cross-reference
facial recognition, baby photos.
No, I'm saying you put them up on the family tree,
but just put them on the miscellaneous branch
and let people come and claim them.
Well, it's like a little squirrel on the family tree
is this weird baby.
More like a nut.
What?
Yeah.
Hey, my family tree's got a few nuts on it.
Like testicles?
I was listening for,
I've been listening to encyclopedia brown books
with Charlie when we go to school,
Wake Up Her Mind to Mystery,
and the burns in that book that Bugs Me does
are so fucking wretched that I cannot even process
how bad this is.
Like the one we listened to this morning,
Bugs and Encyclopedia Browns-
What Bugs do?
Listen, shut up.
Okay, I'm trying to.
Bugs is like, if Encyclopedia Brown's like,
hey, Gundam, I know you ate this kid's cherries,
and I give them back or give them some money for them,
and Bugs is like, huh,
you better stay away from a candy factory
because they're looking for nuts like you.
It's like Bugs.
Fucking killed it.
Dude, hey, Bugs.
Bugs, dude, we don't say shit like that in VR.
Hey, pick up your face, Encyclopedia.
He just melted it right off.
Stick to punching.
Yeah, stick to punching
because you could really hurt somebody's feelings by-
I mean, fuck it.
Encyclopedia Brown is so lucky that Sally's around.
Yeah, to defend.
Because fucking Bugs would just murder him.
Walk all over him, yeah.
I came up with a great idea to do
an adult Encyclopedia Brown,
and then I realized that John Hodgman and Dave Reese
did that with their hit series, Dicktown, on Hulu.
Well, also the Adam Brody movie, Boy, Detective.
And also Brick, if you think about it.
Yeah, and Sherlock Holmes.
Did you guys know that House
is an adaptation of Sherlock Holmes?
Fuck, man.
Thank you, let's talk about it.
Because we don't have detectives anymore.
And that dude from Dead Poets Society is his Watson?
I'm gonna, can I do something else for you guys?
I want to be straight up with you guys.
Fully, fully honest transparency.
Just listen.
Listen to Griffin, he's about to admit
he's never watched House.
Fully transparent.
No, it's not that I haven't watched it.
It's that I really have, I have so,
I don't have any interest
in talking about this kind of subject.
And I was wondering if I could be excused.
If you guys are about to go on a run
and sometimes I feel that energy building,
I was wondering if I could be,
may I please be excused from the podcast?
Everyone gets one.
You want to use yours now, Griffin?
We should get a monthly get out a bit free card.
You guys were about to talk about
how House is like Sherlock Holmes.
And I'm like, where's the fucking door?
House is not like Sherlock Holmes.
House is an adaptation of Sherlock Holmes.
I felt my bladder go,
well, you just peed right before recording,
but maybe you could use me to get away from here.
Use me, Griffin, to get away from here.
Oh, it's Wilson instead of Watson.
Yeah.
Oh, that's how they get, that's how they trick people.
That's how they get around the non-existent.
They don't like that.
The Sherlock Holmes estate.
The estate of Sherlock Holmes.
Hi, I'm Doug Holmes.
I'm Doug Holmes.
And I heard that you were making a thing
about my great-great-granddaddy.
Gotta call it up.
Your character himself is entered into the public domain,
but many of the stories and elements from those stories
are protected.
Oh, I see.
But they're intense about it.
They're like, don't make Sherlock nice.
He's a weird dick.
You gotta make him a butthole.
No, again, the character is in the public domain,
so it could be like Sherlock Holmes
in the mystery of the perfect beach body,
and it's a different version.
Like, there's no rules there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, really?
We could do like, my brother and my brother and me
presents Sherlock Holmes Day about town,
and it's just like Baby's Day out, but Sherlock Holmes?
Well, in Taz, we absolutely did a Sherlock Holmes episode.
We called it that, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Everything old is new again, as they say.
You guys wanna get paid?
Yeah, let's go.
I guess.
Follow me.
Where are we going?
To the money zone.
Oh, it kinda felt like I was setting it up,
and then you kinda stepped in front of me.
I thought you were setting me up to...
Let's go together.
Okay, take my hand.
Oh, wow, there's three sets of footprints on the beach.
It's better, it's better with you.
Squarespace, what more needs to be said?
Nothing, next ad.
Well, there is copy, we do need to say...
I've been using Squarespace.
Okay. What for?
For Sydney's campaign website, McElroy4WV.com.
If you go there, you can see a Squarespace website
that I built with the help of my friend Michael.
He helped me sort of get it set up,
and then I'm doing updates.
It's so easy to make big changes, little changes.
Just like big changes in the government.
Wow.
Thank you, that's beautiful, Travis.
That's really good, Travis.
You know, it's not just...
You can use that too, Juice.
Yeah.
It's not just political campaigns.
Do you wanna use that of like Sydney McElroy
will do for government what I do on a Squarespace website?
No, I don't think I'll use it,
but I will use customizable galleries
to display images and videos in unique ways.
I'll use it to sell products on an online store.
And every Squarespace website-
What are you selling?
T-shirts.
Look at this, I've got all the size,
but I'm running out of larges.
It's a very popular size.
They're made to order on things.
You'll get it in three weeks.
They're so soft, I'm wearing one now and you had no idea.
Assuming there's not supply chain issues.
I'm saying it's really easy to do.
You don't need to know internet at all.
You just like, just go for it.
Let your heart go free.
Even if you don't have like a design background,
the elements that they have that you can pull in
are like already sort of designed and look good together.
It's really fun and easy to use.
Head to squarespace.com slash my brother for a free trial.
And when you're ready to launch,
use the offer code my brother to save 10%
off your first purchase of a website or domain.
Griffin, what's on your feet right now?
List off everything.
Just lots of open source.
Oh boy, close those up.
Bunch of, yeah, okay, travel.
Let me just close them up
because I'm Wolverine with a mutant healing factor.
Okay, are you done?
Yeah, I actually, I feel much better now.
Thanks for giving me that time that I needed
to fix my shit.
Well, Griffin, maybe you wouldn't have so many open source
on your feet if you would put on some Bombas socks.
You see Griffin, Bombas' mission is simple, Griffin.
Make the most comfortable clothes ever, Griffin,
and match every item sold with an equal item donated.
So Griffin, when you buy Bombas,
you are also giving to someone in need.
Because Griffin, everything they make is soft, Griffin,
seamless, Griffin, and tagless, Griffin.
And it has a luxury, Griffin, cozy feel.
I do like Bombas socks though, for real.
I feel like sometimes we have too much fun with the ads
and people don't realize that.
I actually, I do like these socks quite a bit.
They're very comfortable.
Yeah, sometimes people miss that it's a joke
that Griffin didn't wear socks so much
that he got open source on his feet.
I do wear socks because I gotta have my Bombas.
That's what I say, that's what I like to say.
Gotta have my Bombas.
Rachel actually contacted us and said that you say that
at inappropriate times.
She asked us to talk to you about it.
Like the kids wake up in the middle of the night
and they're like, Daddy, I'm so scared.
And I'm like, gotta have my Bombas.
Yeah, she said that there was a parent teacher conference
where the teacher said like, any questions?
And you just yelled, gotta have my Bombas,
and then hung up the phone.
Yeah, I did do that.
Well, I understand why.
Because they're made from super soft materials
like merino wool, pima cotton, and even cashmere,
which makes them the perfect cozy layers.
Duh-nuh-nuh.
And- Wait, what did you guys sing?
No, Justin got me the immigrant song.
Yeah, you guys did definitely do immigrant song.
But it was just Justin did it first.
Duh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh.
Come with me.
Duh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh.
Thank you Godzilla soundtrack and puffy that.
Come with me.
Duh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh-nuh.
Okay, Bombas underwear has a barely there feel
with second skin support that might make you forget
they're even there in a good way.
And Bombas knows the shelters
for people experiencing homelessness,
the highest requested items are socks and underpants.
So for every item you buy, an equal item is donated
so you could feel good and feel good about it.
Ooh. Ooh.
So go to bombas.com slash my brother
and get 20% off your first purchase.
That's B-O-M-B-A-S.com slash my brother
for 20% off bombas.com slash my brother.
Are you ready to binge watch something old?
The Greatest Generation is a podcast about Star Trek
by a couple of hosts a little bit embarrassed
to even have a Star Trek podcast.
Hosted by me, Ben Harrison.
And me, Adam Pranica.
We get into the critical, the technical,
the science fictional aspects of the show we love
while roasting it and each other at the same time.
We've completed an entire series
about Star Trek The Next Generation
and another one about Star Trek Deep Space Nine
and we've just begun Star Trek Voyager.
So now is a great time to start watching
a new Star Trek series with us.
So subscribe to The Greatest Generation
on maximumfun.org or wherever you get your podcasts
and become a friend of DeSoto today.
How about another question?
Yeah.
I mean, do you not have a thing?
No.
Okay.
Well, then how about we go to the wizard instead?
I'd love that.
Thank you.
Hi, wizard.
Hello.
Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
What happened?
I'm a wizard.
You've never heard my voice before.
Okay.
I'm a wizard.
Are you okay?
I'm like sort of a big dog man.
I love that.
Yeah.
You didn't know he was a big dog man in the sky.
I love it.
Thank you.
This one has an author which fucks me up.
Oh, boy, someone put their name on it.
Yeah, it was co-authored by John Keegan and Ally Rusciano.
So good.
Great work, y'all.
Way to own it.
So if you have issues with this one, you know who to hit up.
This one is how to respond to a how was your day text.
Thank you, Jesus, yes.
It's actually 14 easy ways to do it.
And I thought we could go through them pretty quick
and just kind of rank them by like,
would you ever actually say these things or not?
And this is specifically text and not just like
walking by someone like in a hallway or something, right?
Yeah, it's nearing the end of the day, Travis,
and your phone dings into, how was your day?
Text stares back at you.
Maybe it's from your best friend, parent,
or even your crush.
They just want to check in, but how do you respond?
If it's your crush, I'm over the moon.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah.
And unprompted, how was your day from my crush?
Oh, boy.
Fucking forget it.
Now my day's amazing.
Like, are you kidding me?
I would guess that the answer would be
sort of context sensitive depending on
if you got it from your parent or your crush.
Because I'm gonna say to them,
well, I've got a great boner now, to one of them.
Yeah.
Well, I got a great boner now, dad.
It's so-
I'm proud of you, son.
You've done it.
Now you're the dad.
You've overcome our family's curse.
You finally carried one of the other family up a mountain
and ate the stinky vegetables,
and now you can have the bonus.
It's-
It's true.
Noodle-limping to the second.
I've never been more proud of you than I am today.
So-
We're going to start calling you Rock Hardson.
All right.
Number one, it's been great.
How about you?
Share how awesome your day's been with this text.
There's no shame in having a great day.
Let them know how amazing you feel.
A fucking great day.
Great day.
I forgot that it's okay to do
because it's been so long since I've had one.
Right, yeah.
Well, but I would go the other way,
which is like, it's a little braggadocious.
This would be like, fucking awesome.
The odds of two people communicating with each other,
having a good day,
simultaneously right now, impossible.
Nobody reaches out to somebody else
because they're having a good time in this day and age.
If you say that it is good in any way
and do not follow that up with all things considered,
you're fucking lying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, chilled at home, so not too bad.
Sorry, what?
Chilled at home?
Chilled at home.
Chilled.
Chilled makes more sense than killed.
Chilled at home, so not too bad.
Tell them what you've been up to with this reply.
Even if all you did today was chill out on the couch,
fill them in with the deets.
Are you still standing?
Yeah.
Okay, thank you for your honesty, Travis.
I appreciate it.
Well, I go to the gym for my exercise, Justin.
This is my time for work.
I know, but when I work, I stand up.
Well, when I work hard, I play hard, yeah?
Hey, Travis, if you got time to lean,
you got time to clean.
I'm not leaning.
Okay, if you get time to sit,
then you got time to clean shit.
Here, take this Windex and go clean
while I go and do this comedy.
Squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak.
I'm an older brother.
I'm gonna start managing this show better.
Okay, I'm gonna do what I always do at jobs,
which is go around the corner and then stop.
And that energy juice, I think we all know
from the retail jobs we've worked,
is the most effective way to get somebody to be effective.
And it makes for a fun experience that everyone enjoys.
Fun experience.
I had to learn to podcast
just so I would never be in that situation.
Yeah, so once my manager, Jimmy Johns,
made me shave in the Jimmy John's bathroom
with a rusty razor and lukewarm water,
I said, time to get into podcasting, I think.
Hey, listen, I love hunting elephants
as much as the next guy.
But this has gone too far.
All right.
I'm taking these pickles with me.
The only thing I wanna poach from now on is eggs, Jimmy.
I don't think they put poached eggs on Jimmy John's sandwich.
No, that's why I had to quit.
That's why I had to quit,
because I tried to put poached eggs,
and Jimmy said, we only poach elephants.
Right, yes, that's what-
This is our new sandwich, The Fruity Little Wuss.
Okay.
It's got poached eggs on it.
He says it's good for protein.
I just like elephant steaks.
The trunk is so subtle, you don't even know, man.
Okay, really good, really good.
Thanks for asking.
Really good?
No, that's sarcastic.
Really good.
Thanks for asking.
That's really good.
Really good, man.
Glad you made me think about it.
Similar vein, good, how was yours?
Good.
There's a lot of use of smiling and laughing emojis,
and a lot of like-
Can't really communicate that.
Can't wait for finals to be over, ha ha.
Good, how was yours, by the way, is so clear.
One, I'm either gonna read that as a lie, right?
Or I'm going to read it as,
oh fuck, they're really annoyed I asked.
Good, how was yours?
Right, like you responded with as few,
not just words, but letters as possible.
Yeah, if you guys ever get this text back from me,
it means I have been killed,
and the killer is using my phone to create an alibi.
Pretty good, you won't believe what happened.
If I ever say that to you without saying,
you know, someone stole my catalytic converter,
I don't know why I would say that's a pretty good day,
but if I say, you won't believe
what happened to me today, guys.
And I know how you guys are anxious
in the way that you are, and I am, and we all are.
That's not me saying that, that is my neighbor,
or most murders are done by people.
You, Griffin McElroy, would know never to text us like,
do you have a second to talk, right?
Hey guys, got an important conversation
you're not gonna like.
And then not respond to our response.
Don't respond forever.
Okay, okay, what about you?
So just a lot of just like,
here's the quality of my day, and now I'm gonna hit you up.
This article feels like different ways
of different days you could be happy.
Is there an option on there that's like, fucking suck, dude?
Yeah, Trav, I don't know if you've noticed,
there's a pattern, these are decreasing.
Oh, excellent.
Is there one on there that's like,
hey, this feels superficial.
Do you really wanna get into it, man?
Cause I'll open up my heart to you, bro.
No, but there is the raw, powerful ennui
of same old, same old, how was yours?
Yes. I see, I see.
Big case of the Mondays, Brock.
How about you?
I think, actually, I'm gonna say
that if you ask someone how was their day,
I would rather hear someone say it fucking sucked
than same old, same old.
Cause there's a certain amount of acceptance
and same old, same old, it's like, whoa, okay, hey, man.
Bad, but in a way I'm used to, how about you?
Let's get out of here and try something,
let's go horseback riding or something.
Yeah.
Okay, so the next one is awesome, fine.
Give this reply if you don't wanna talk.
Yeah. Maybe your ex or a friend
you recently had a falling out with texted you.
A one word response is a blunt way of saying,
I don't wanna talk right now.
No, you know what's an even blunter way?
Don't respond.
Don't wanna talk to you right now.
Not so great.
If it's your mom or best friend,
open up and tell the truth.
Not so great.
Let me confide in you.
Is this mom?
Hey, does you block my number, mom?
That's okay.
It's been better.
This next one is for horny.
It was okay, seeing you would have made it better.
Oh.
Real smooth.
What do you mean?
Like seeing all of you would have made it better.
Watch out Peter Dinklage, there's a new Cyrano in town.
Oh, hey, nice.
They should make a modern remake of Cyrano
where it's just about like sexy texties.
I'm pretty sure that's in Roxanne.
I think he's just constantly sending sexy texts.
They send sexy texties in Roxanne?
Yeah, he's just sexting constantly.
Guys, sexy texties is something.
There's something powerful about
not saying the second T in the word text.
Sexy texties.
This is a great reply for someone
you haven't seen in a while.
Maybe you haven't seen their butt in a while.
To be fair, that is a good point though.
So that doesn't work if you did see them.
Seeing you would have, I just left.
The arc of this article is so great
because it's like at the top of it,
it's like brag about how cool your life is
and how shitty their life is.
All the way down to like cry for help
because you are so sad about the non-changing nature
of your life and how you feel like you're stuck
in a sort of existential quagmire.
And then it's like, get a little horny.
And the next one is any day is great
when you text me, get that dick out now.
Let's go.
I was sad before, but I changed it
with a different feeling.
That's the one I text back when I get them
from Bernie Sanders, definitely real.
Bernie Sanders.
Hey, it's Bernie.
Burn.
Burn?
You wanna go see the Batman or what?
We're still on for tonight?
All right, all right, we'll see.
Murder on the Nile, geez.
Feeling better now.
I love having old friends.
Yeah, we can go to, we'll go to the 5 p.m. show.
We'll go to 5 p.m. man, you gotta get to bed.
Sounds great, my dude, that works for me.
Hey, bring those mittens I ordered from your shop.
Yeah, we can sneak in candy, Bernie.
It has gotten too expensive lately.
Yeah, sorry they don't have Mary James.
I bet we can sneak in some Bitto Hunnies.
We'll sneak in some Bitto Hunnies, you old bird.
You old sneak.
Hound dog.
Oh, you scoundrel, are those good and plenty?
Get out of here.
What's a good place, you old hound dog?
Careful, that box is real loud.
Oh, you put them in a Ziploc bag.
That's gonna fix that right up.
You're right, this one would be better
with Marlene Dietrich.
You're right.
We're all having a lot of fun.
We're all having a lot of fun here
at Mr. Sanders' expense, but feeling better.
Well, he should stop texting, that's all.
Feeling better now, thanks for checking in.
That one's not funny.
This next one is pretty good though.
A mess, but we live and learn.
Whoa.
That is a store, somebody murdered somebody.
Yeah, that's like growth.
We live and learn.
I'm murdered.
A mess?
If you describe your day as a mess,
you should be brought up on charge.
I'm betting vehicular manslaughter is my guess.
Hit someone with a car, won't do that again.
Live and learn.
Wait, killed someone with a big, fast automobile,
didn't like it, won't do it again.
Do not recommend.
Would love to see you though.
Would've been better if I hit you with my dick.
Wait, hold on, no, jump back, jump back.
I was happy and then I was sad, then I got horny,
then I hit someone with my car
and now I'm just sort of focusing on me and my journey.
It turns out I'm super horny again.
Yeah, it turns out it made me even hornier.
Now, this is the last one and it's like,
this one you should actually expect to get from me
at some point.
You say, Griffin, how was your day?
Very productive.
Very, very productive, eventful.
The team made lots of progress
and I'll make sure to have that data to you by midnight.
That's one of the suggested response.
Is that a e-how person trying to figure out
how jobs work?
Good, and the meeting went well.
I think our proposal has a shot, smiley face.
This one feels fairly specific, yeah.
Can't wait to work more.
Can't wait to work more, love work, love doing it.
Would love to see that butthole on a text message though.
Oh, sorry, sorry, I thought you were my boss.
I didn't realize.
Whoops.
I knew he was there somewhere.
I was trying to be polite and keep up the vibe.
Yeah, man, for sure.
Diga, diga, diga, diga, diga, diga, diga, diga, diga, diga,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Oh, wow.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
I want a munch squad.
Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
I want to munch squad.
Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
Welcome to Munch Squad.
It's a podcast within a podcast
profiling the latest and greatest in brand eating.
And me, just a macaron.
I'm ready to get loud and wild with Mountain Dew.
Oh boy.
Mountain Dew is going to thrill sports fans
at Buffalo Wild Wings with the exclusive new pour,
Mountain Dew Legend.
Yeah.
Whoa, shit.
This new offering delivers a bold burst
of blackberry flavor that is, wait for it, legendary.
That's not how you do it.
Yeah, they messed up that great
how I met your mother reference.
That's not how you do it.
You messed up the how I met your mother reference, PepsiCo.
So Mountain Dew and Buffalo Wild Wings
are bringing sports fans a reason to celebrate.
Finally.
By recruiting an all new exclusive.
Don't say recruiting.
I know what you're going for.
Trying to make a sporty thing.
But it makes it sound like on the street,
you saw a soda and said, give me that kid.
Hey, soda.
Yeah, you.
You ever dreamed about being in the big leagues?
So this soda is soon to be legendary, it says,
even though they're only offering
exclusive Buffalo Wild Wings.
I guess they're leaving the legend some room
to expand on it so it's sort of simmer.
You don't want to come out the gate too strong
and shove the legend down people's throats
by saying this is a legend, right?
They should have called it Mountain Dew.
And then let it grow on its own.
Let it be its own thing.
This sentence is like maybe one of the worst ones.
Ever?
There's not a sentence after that.
Like this sentence I'm about to read
is one of the worst ones.
Okay.
Curated for those who embrace the fun
and freedom in life.
This standout, that's already-
Yeah.
Fuck yeah.
What?
Awesome.
What are you saying?
That's me.
I love fun and freedom.
Do you mean made from a syrup in an-
No, Justin, no.
Every bottle is made by a professional mixologist
in suspenders.
This standout beverage combines the exhilarating taste
of original Mountain Dew.
Whoa, what's this?
I'm still alive.
For the very first time.
Original Mountain Dew, M-T-N capital, D-E-W, Mountain Dew,
with notes of blackberry, citrus, and ginger.
Okay.
With its bold charge and refreshing taste,
Mountain Dew legend is uniquely designed
to elevate Buffalo Wild Wings sauces, burgers,
and other bar food items.
Now you can't just make that blanket statement.
There's so many different-
They have, they have.
There's a lot of different-
It's formulated to elevate all food offerings.
There's so many sauces and dry rub.
It pairs perfectly with frickels.
You can't tell me it's great for like the garlic zing
and the fucking Cajun dry rub.
It's not the flavor, Travis.
It's that it pairs well with the bones.
Oh, okay.
The Mountain Dew pairs good with the bones.
Just pop your bones in there when you're done,
it'll dissolve them all up.
Make a broth.
This makes the fan favorite sports bars
the best place for sports enthusiasts
to enjoy great food and drinks,
all while watching their favorite matchups
on the big screen.
Yeah.
Yeah, that-
This is what sports people like, right?
Do they still offer trivia?
Do they still do the-
I don't know if they do anymore.
I want to do the trivia game.
That's my favorite sport.
They used to do it.
We used to have a very small B2B place.
Oh yeah, shoebox.
Now we have a very big one.
Oh yeah?
It's weird.
It grew up.
Yeah, at the mall.
Anyway, at Buffalo Wild Wings,
we strive to provide our guests with mouthwatering-
Wait, who's this?
It's just a choice.
You do not know that that is what their voice sounds like.
Yes, I do.
What's the name?
Rita Patel.
It's possible.
Okay.
Anything's possible.
She might sound like an old-timey oil magnate, for sure.
I don't know much about no Buffalo Wild Wings.
What I do is tea.
This is the only stage for character work I have.
It's this and playing dolls with my kids, okay?
Now, I might be a simple brand ambassador
from a big company like Coca-Cola-Co,
but what I know, I know bone flavor.
And this goes with bone.
Dip them in there, eat the bones.
What's that?
I can't tell them to eat the bones?
Rita Patel is the chief marketing officer
of Buffalo Wild Wings.
The CMO.
Do you think you'd get in trouble
if we call your CMO come-o?
Yes, I do, Justin.
Probably.
Yes, I do think you'd get in trouble.
How was the weekend, come-o?
I wish you wouldn't.
I think immediately the HR representative would appear.
Did you just say the word come-o?
It's not on our list of words you can't say,
but it is now.
What is it to you, her?
Sorry, it's HR, human resources.
Oh, that explains so much.
Yeah.
Mountain Dew legend.
Okay, at Buffalo Wild Wings,
we provide our guests with mouth, water, and flavors
and exciting innovations across our menu,
said Rita Patel, chief marketing officer.
If that's true, Rita,
why did you get rid of the big pretzel
and replace it with smaller pretzels
that aren't as good?
Thank you.
Mountain Dew legend is a unique drink
that we're proud to serve exclusively at our sports bars
that we have.
We have a longstanding relationship with PepsiCo,
and we are known for bringing fans unexpected bold flavors
like the Doritos spicy sweet chili flavored sauce.
What?
I didn't know about this.
I gotta go.
The Doritos spicy sweet chili flavored sauce.
We're thrilled to continue our collaboration
for one of a kind menu offerings.
In case you're curious about Pepsi's side of it,
Scott Finlow, the come-o.
Pepsi.
He sounds like this.
Buffalo Wild Wings and Mountain Dew
both know a thing or two about passionate fan bases,
how to take celebrations to the next level
with great tasting, food, and beverages.
Okay.
Together, our goal is to elevate the sports viewing
and dining experience with Mountain Dew legend,
serving as the ultimate wingman.
Oh!
All right.
That's good, Scott.
Good job, Scott.
That's good.
Yeah, you did all right with that one, Scott.
It'll be available at all 1200 Buffalo Wild Wings locations
by May, 2022.
Apparently the pipeline is still being constructed.
So that's a thrill.
And it's something to get excited about.
Mountain Dew legend coming.
So you can't fucking wait.
Thank you.
Me neither.
Hey, thanks for listening to my brother, my brother, and me.
We hope you had fun.
I know that we did,
and I hope you're hanging in there and doing well.
And we always appreciate you spending an hour with us.
So thank you for that.
Sincerely.
And we have some information
about the 20 Rendezvous Fancy Takes Flight Tour.
So due to a scheduling conflict,
we had to reschedule the Fancy Takes Flight Tour dates
that were originally set for this month
in Washington, D.C., Detroit, and Cincinnati.
They'll now take place in November.
So the Scentsy MBMB AM will be November 10th.
The Detroit MBMB AM will be November 11th.
The D.C. MBMB AM will be November 12th,
and the D.C. TAZ show will be November 13th.
All existing tickets will be honored
for the rescheduled show.
Refunds will be available at point of purchase
for those unable to attend the new dates.
We know it sucks.
We didn't want to do it.
We had to,
and we're looking forward to seeing you later in the year.
Tickets for these shows are on sale now
at bit.ly slash McElroy Tours.
You can also see all the other stops
like St. Louis, Kansas City, Minneapolis,
Boston, Mashantucket, Salt Lake City, Portland,
San Diego, and then those D.C., Detroit, and Cincinnati shows.
Also, we're doing a virtual TAZ in May,
and at those shows, masks and proof of full vaccination
or negative COVID tests within 72 hours
of event start are required.
Dad wrote a kid's book called
Goldie's Guide to Grandchilding.
It comes out May 10th.
You can pre-order now at Linktree,
which is L-I-N-K-T-R dot E-E slash Goldie's Guide.
Go check out all of the cool merch.
It's so cool.
Over at McElroyMerch.com,
we got the mystery pin of the month,
which is going to be a random pin of the month
from the past, which benefits
the National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum.
We've got Candle Nights 2021 special video on demand.
You can pay what you want,
and all proceeds go to Harmony House.
You can check that out at McElroyMerch.com.
Also, I'm going to be hosting a live virtual show
to benefit two great efforts here in Cincinnati.
One is called Bethany House,
which is a shelter that focuses on families
that are experiencing homelessness
or at risk of experiencing homelessness.
And also, we're going to stock some free fridges
here in Cincinnati and right across the river in Kentucky
with masks and COVID tests.
And we're going to have some amazing guests.
We had to reschedule,
but we're rescheduling for April 1st.
Our guests are going to be, let's see,
we got Adam Brody, got Rob Corddry, got Montane.
We got Christina Ariel.
And then there will be two more guests
that we haven't locked down yet, but it's very exciting.
Get those tickets at cincyticket.com slash cuscares.
That's C-I-N-C-Y ticket.com slash C-U-S-S-C-A-R-E-S.
That show is going to be April 1st at 9 p.m. Eastern time.
That's it.
Thank you for listening to all those announcements.
What if we show up, so am I going to show up
and then you'd be like, no show, April Fools.
No, I would never do that.
And it will be available for two weeks,
a video on demand afterwards.
No, it won't, it's an April Fools joke.
No, don't say that, please. It's not real.
Please, it benefits really good organizations, Griffin.
Yeah, sure it does, fake show, joke, fake joke show.
Thanks to Montane for these for a theme song.
My life is better with you.
It's a great track and the music video's on YouTube.
If you haven't seen that, it's a lot of fun.
We're in it.
We're in it, we did it.
Oh, final bit, I liked doing an impression last week.
I felt like, cause I got an email
from the Saturday Night Live guy.
Oh yeah?
Wow.
Yeah.
And I don't remember his name, but that's okay.
He said it's okay if I don't remember his name,
but he was like, great voices.
What else you got, kid?
So just like, I guess give me somebody else,
like a hot, like a name that's like in the news right now.
Okay, who's like a cool,
who's like a cool impression that Griffin could do?
Griffin, could you do Pete Davidson?
Oh, wait, did you say you want to do it?
Justin, were you about to do it?
It sounded like you were about to get a hint.
No, no, I was like, oh, that's a good choice.
Oh, it sounded like you were about to be like,
well, let me see what I can do.
No, I don't have a beat.
Go ahead, Griff, let's hear your beat.
Oh.
All right, who cares?
Check it out, guys.
I'm just trying to,
we're all having trouble.
Oh, we're all having trouble, aren't we, Kim?
Classic.
Really excellent, thank you so much.
People think my wiener's big because of the way I am.
Why are you Justin McElroy?
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been My Brother, My Brother Made.
Kiss your dad, squirt on the lips.
["Better With You"]
Maximumfun.org.
Comedy and culture.
Artist-owned.
Audience-supported.