Hi folks, I'm your middle-est brother Travis McRoy.
I'm your sweet baby brother Griffin McRoy.
This is weird and I don't like this.
It's weird, right?
Yeah.
It's like when you, it's like a flat tire.
You can feel that something's just off
and it's that Justin's not here.
He's on a boat, he's on a cruise.
He said we weren't allowed to go.
Yeah, that was weird.
It was weird.
He said that only one of us could be at the ocean.
He said it was something about maritime law.
Yeah, well it's kind of like that
Kiefer Sutherland show Designated Survivor
and that if there is, God forbid,
but if there is a, you know,
that movie with the Poseidon adventure sort of situation,
well you and I can carry the torch
if there is a Poseidon adventure situation.
Just quick sidetrack.
I think it would be great if on Designated Survivor
every like season ender and then season starter
was like at the end of the season,
it was like good news Kiefer,
we found a new president.
You don't have to be president anymore.
And then something happens
that he has to be president again every year.
Okay.
And hopefully it goes like 12 seasons.
Yeah, so like the Secretary of Agriculture
like flies back from an extended trip in Dubai
and is like, what's up motherfucker?
I'm back.
Bet you thought I was in the room
when the big boom happened, but no, no, no.
Anyway, give me that president badge.
And he's like, oh, thank goodness.
I didn't want to be president.
But then he falls in a toilet and dies.
Anyways, so.
Anyway, so that's Travis and my spec script
for Designated Survivor season two premiere.
Very excited about it.
So Justin's not here.
So in lieu of his being,
we are putting up the Candle Nights episode
from last year, which we recorded as part of the TV show.
If you have watched our TV show, which you should,
I think it's pretty fun.
You'll recognize some of the stuff
because it is what we filmed.
It was our last day of filming.
We're all extremely tired.
I think it's fair to say, very emotional.
And so yeah.
Something to keep in mind.
One, it's a live show.
Two, we're recording it in the auditorium at City Hall.
So it's not like we were, you know,
it's not a state of the art recording.
The audio's not good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The audio, it's listenable
and you can hear what we're saying,
but that auditorium was invented,
it was built before amplified sound was invented.
And so there's a bit of a trade-off
and I apologize for that,
but I think it's a really fun episode
and I think you'll like it regardless.
Some other thing, I just edited the episode
and Travis, unfortunately,
I did cut the celebrity miracle bit
because that part was un-listenable
because you couldn't hear it at all,
which is a bummer.
And that's also, that's for the TV show.
That's fine, I understand.
Travis got a surprise celebrity guest
and it's on a TV show,
but unfortunately just like it's not listenable at all.
And what else?
I think that's all the sort of caveats.
We're gonna start out with our dad just hamming it up.
What else is new?
But yeah, we realized this is weird
that we are publishing one of our holiday specials
that we recorded in a non-holiday September
and publishing in a definitely non-holiday March,
but that's just how we do things.
I mean, it's the traditional candle lights in March.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
So yeah, thanks for listening.
Enjoy the episode.
We'll be back in a bit for the Midi-Zone, so see you soon.
Christmas.
Yeah, it's bad enough.
They got the Sheets thing, they got the Schmanners thing,
they got the Sawbones thing, they got the Buffering thing.
Apparently no room for the Adventure Zone,
but that's okay.
No, no, no.
Thank you for acting like you know what that is.
Hi, I'm Clint McElroy.
I am, some of the people up here
that you have seen on this stage this evening
are my fault so far, so I take full credit there.
But I serve a very important duty tonight.
For what?
Are you laughing because I said duty?
Yeah.
This is a prime bim-bam crowd.
No, seriously though, I'm here for a very important purpose.
The producers and the director and the crew told me
that if I shoehorned myself into this TV show one more time,
I'd qualify for an Emmy, so here I am.
No, but seriously, on a serious note,
Candle Nights is important to all of us,
and I think you'd probably agree with me
if you weren't all hammered.
But a very important component
of every Candle Nights observation
is our Candle Nights carolers.
Here's the problem.
We've run a little over,
and they have to do a tree lighting in Guyandot
in just a few minutes.
So, and those three people came from Australia.
I'll tell you the Guyandot joke later.
That's why nobody laughed at it.
But they prepared all these songs,
there's just not enough time.
So, they're going to do a very unique rendition
of four different Christmas songs.
Ladies and gentlemen, enjoy tonight
and welcome our Candle Light, Candle Night,
knew I was gonna do that, carolers!
["Jingle Bells, Jingle All the Way"]