The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it
Also, this show isn't for kids which I mentioned only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening
What's up, you cool, baby?
It's better it's better
Better it's better
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother and me an advice show for the modern era
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy
Hello governor. I'm your middle brother Travis McElroy, and I'm your sweet grown-up brother Griffin McElroy
We're back in the saddle again
Back states. I had this realization
Yes
That this was well we were on our hiatus. So we're the last episode we recorded would have been
like
October 13th, who can say that is the longest time I
Have gone without recording an episode of my brother my brother and me
since I was a
30-year-old man since I was
Sorry 29 years old. Yes, since I was 29. It's the longest I've ever gotten
Gone with that. You're only 30. You're only 33 now nominal man. And what I realized is I
I had been contextualizing bad stuff that happened to me in my life
With like well, at least I'll be able to tell this story on the podcast
Yeah, I see how when things happen guys
Since we record our last episode, I spent two straight calendar days doing nothing
But making 15 gallons of chili and then serving 30 gallons of chili now. Wait, hold on
Sorry, that's not kind of loaves and fishes shit. Is that Justin you made 15 and then there were 30
He cut it
Water some water and some wood shavings
Um, okay you my wife this is how long it's been my wife has forgotten
This is just the sacred time
I bet yeah
I had some people also making chili Mary made like 15 gallons of chili and then I I served 30 gallons guys
15 gallons of chili is so gross
Yeah, and I feel like it's probably the worst with chili
There's probably other foods, but like I always have these giant freezer bags and I would just like schlurp
That's not the best way to move
And then I'd have this big vat of chili that I'm stirring all day
I'm stirring this frozen chili and then I'll take it over to the serving pot
And then these people would watch me and I would beg them like first off take a step back because you were in the chili splash zone and then I said please don't watch this when you see this amount of food it's hugely appetizing and then I had to schlurp this hot boiling chili into a big pot
That draws too much attention to what a shared experience that is and like feeding pigs that are trough, right? It's just like the comparison is too obvious at that point
I wouldn't talk about this on a more politically minded podcast, but I think here I'm in safe company. Our booth was the Democrat
Like County Democrats and then our booth is directly positioned across from the County Republicans. I mean direct
Oh, that's nice
And these dudes brought two full-size cardboard standups of my man DJ D
My man DJ Trump was watching and presiding over the chili festivities over at their booth
Known chili aficionado
They didn't affix Donald
He was thinking it was a windy day
They didn't, hold on, oh no
So Donald would just go flying
He flat Stanley'd around everywhere
That's fun
He'd just go flying away, it was great
Can I ask a question? Did they at least hang a sign on DJ Trump that said like yum yum chili time or yum yum I love chili
Just standing like a gargoyle in silent approval of the chili
Bad president, good chili eater boy
We started serving at 11 and they were done by 12 and it turned out they had only brought one pot of chili
New
And it's like guys, you brought one pot of chili
That's the same way they think about politics
Yes thank you, thank you Travis
They're like one pot
They brought one pot of chili and two Donald Trumps
Listen, I don't want to tell you your business but
Maybe half the Trumps twice the chili
Then one of the dudes came over to our booth and was like do you have a cup
He said do you have a cup and luckily another candidate had provided cups with his logo on them
So I gave him one and he said thanks I got to skim all this grease off the top
It's like boy that sounds good
That sounds like good stuff right there
Seems like you guys really poured your heart and soul into this chili
I was hoping that you were going to say like they came over and they're like hey guys
Could we have some of your chili to give away
You seem to have a lot of chili like the ants in that one story
And we're like the grasshoppers in that story
And if you could give us some of your chili to give to potential voters and say that we made it
That would just be great
Yeah I've had a while, I drove a truck in a parade
Oh Justin
Yeah it was like the whole
I mean I went to a castle and stuff but no go on about your chili and your car in a parade
The thing is we know all about your castle Travis
I went to like three castles dude
Like three castles
Were they all really different
No they were basically like big stone buildings
Yeah sure
It never really got wild with the architecture
Like I walk around my neighborhood now and I'm like that building looks different
Oh look that's like a mid-century monument
And like castles man they pretty much did just like squared off stone buildings
How were the buttresses though
Flying
Wow and the battle men
Oh yeah it was there
The portcullis forget about it
What about the Bailey
The Bailey it was old
It was one old Bailey
Yeah it's been a while
I've been thinking a lot about elevating my brand in the last two weeks
Oh okay
Like and this is true I think for all of us
And I've been meaning to talk to you guys about this for a while
So maybe this isn't the show but
I think we're grown up adult men
I think we're grown up people
And there's a vibe of
Specifically me I think because I have put toys in my mouth before
That I'm like some sort of boy still
But I like I have a mortgage and two children
And so I've been thinking about like having my brand instead be like
Grown up responsible
Because it's all true it's just not the face
That it's not the public facing
It's also not as funny or interesting
It's like well maybe not Travis but
It's real and I think people want real shit now
So I'm like Janus flipping the mask around
Oh and now the guy on Grey Brays
Griffin has two faces
And so now the goofball who eats toys
And bananas
Talks about like toilet humor and stuff like that
Like he's in the back now
And then up front is
Grown up Griffin McElroy
I care deeply about grown up stuff
Can you give me an example of something that you care more about than you did
I mean just publicly care more about
Publicly I care more about than two weeks ago?
Yeah part of this new rebrand
The new Griffin experience
Like if you were going to say now I care about blank instead of Pokemon
Yeah I would say sort of like
Moisturizing
I'm huge on that shit now
I realized that I wasn't wet enough
Ever basically
Have you gone into serums?
Serums I do
I have a salve
I have an ungent that I apply
On every full moon
And that really is what keeps me going
There's a lot a lot
A lot of placenta in that one
But it keeps it tight
And very very very damp
Wait are you using plenty of centa?
Cause I've been using plenty of centa
I've been using plenty of centa since the day I turned 29 years old
Yeah I can tell
Cause that's when things really start to drop off
But the plenty of centa tightens, dampens
Revives, revitalizes
And even now I can tell I'm getting silly again
You know what I mean?
It's work, it's work to elevate your brand
But like you know
Do you guys know what I'm saying?
I feel out on a branch right now
No I feel like my brand is solid
And everybody is just really in favor of it
I don't feel like there's any holes in my brand
People often lift me up and say like
Hey Travis I notice that like
You seem to be like the best
And like most adjusted of the three
And the most like just completely
I think the word is neuro virgin
I think is what it is
You're just a real neuro virgin guy
Yeah that's what they definitely say
Yeah yeah yeah
Justin anything you want to say about your brand?
How's your brand Juice?
Mine's pretty well fucked at this point
You know what I mean?
I've done enough stuff where
I don't know that I have much of a brand anymore
I feel like I've kind of ruined my
You know what I think it was?
What was it Juice?
It was becoming a notary public
Yeah you think that's
Oh Juice that's an inspiration for me
For me that's like
Once I hit that point
I'm like once I'm a notary public
And a sommelier
Then I'm for real
Done I have put my childish things
Way the fuck behind me now
Because I can sign government documents and shit
But I think if I may
In terms of what Justin is saying to us
Griffin what you're talking about is like a redirection
Of your brand and what I think Justin is saying is
His brand became so dispersed
Between everything that he's doing all at once
That you cannot
Pin down one thing about Justin
It's like oh do you mean the guy
Who like is a notary public
And is Count Donut
Like those two things together
Like Janus the mask it flips Travis
Yes but it's like if his mask had
Like 162 faces
I think is the problem
You know what it is? I'm a modern renaissance man
That's exactly it
That's a good brand
Way up there
Extremely elevated
I like to think that my brand is like
Just lazy cult leader
Who can do it but who can be bothered
That's kind of what I'm going for
The beard has been bad for my brand too
I think so in a major way
Okay good I just want to make sure
Good for your face
You know what
It has allowed me to sort of
Insert myself
Into certain dad circles that I would not
Be welcomed into
Because while they might be able to
Talk about sports and stuff
If I see one of them's got a beard
I'm in
You want to talk about beards? Of course you do
That's all you think about
Oh just me? Okay good good
It's way cheaper than buying an ebike
Like I had to do to fit in with the
Cool city dads here in DC
Who do fucking wheelies and stunts
I don't get dads
Now we're not even doing the show anymore
We haven't talked in like half a month
What I don't get
Because I realized this recently
If you're a full blown dad joke dad
You gotta dye your hair
To a different color because the dad jokes
The number of people were like
I love your hair and I'm like thanks
I love it too but I hate ruining pillowcases
The number of like just straight up
That's not so much a dad joke as much as it is
Just like a thing that is true and I think
Annoying about hair color
I'll give you
I did a pumpkin carving contest
That I was the MC for
Man Justin your life
Has just gotten off the
Is this season two of your life
And they're just like we gotta ramp up the vids
This does feel like that break in Battlestar
Where they come back three years later
And it was like this is the mirror
Why
Thank you Travis
I had a pumpkin suit
On like
Mr. Pumpkins did
But it wasn't a David Pumpkins costume
It was just a pumpkin suit
And people would be like I love your costume
Thanks I had a wedding earlier today
Oh that's good
That's really good stuff Juice
I like that
Should we do the questions
I got a lot of like
I got some Munch stuff
Munch related stuff to talk about
I'm excited
Is it too late to change the name of the bit to Munch stuff
I just like the way
It's uncomfortable in my mouth
As long as we're elevating the brand
This is Justin McElroy's Munch My Stuff
Munch My Stuff
It can be like an old
Playstation video game intro
Munch My Stuff
And if it's a thing that
Makes you really mad you can say like
This house my munch
This really munches my stuff
Oh yeah yeah yeah
So let's do a question
I just had a baby last month
And all my friends and family say
He's adorable I obviously think so too
However due to all the baby hormones
I'm not sure my judgement can be trusted
What if I'm just surrounded by liars
How can I tell if my baby is really cute
Or if people are just lying to me
And that's from Cute Fuse in Chicago
Travis was there an image attached
Well no they specifically said
They didn't want us to like
Be biased by an image
Because this isn't about our judgement
On whether the baby is cute or not
Because how would they know to trust us
This is about how can they trust us
They should know that I don't care
That's also a good point
I want most folks to know that when you ask my opinion
On most things and you're not
An immediate family member of mine
You're gonna get the gosh darn honest truth
Because
I mean you need to be mirrored
Don't we all need to be mirrored
That's an interesting point Griffin
Because I would have said I would lie to strangers
And be honest with my family
No come on
No because I get to see you guys like all the time
And we work together like all the time
And if I say like a bad thing to you
About you that I felt for a long time
Then like uh oh
Next recording time uh oh
But if I see a stranger
With a busted looking baby
Then like you know
I can let them know that and then they can take the necessary
Steps to beautify
That baby
Step up the game get a flipper in there
Hair extension something
Listen people lie
You know who doesn't lie
Is animals
If your animals are reacting to your baby like
Like a Disney princess birds landing on their shoulder
Dogs wanna lick their faces
I think it's safe to say that's a cute baby
Cute is a human reaction though
Like we don't
If animals don't have like cute
Instincts
Excuse me sir
Like your baby's cute for a baby cat
But not cute for a human
Yeah that's fair
Well then why are dogs and cats always putting on
Cute outfits huh if they don't have like cute instincts huh
Think about that Justin
Actually I'm hoisted by my own pertard on that
Thank you
I think
All babies are
Cute like
No no well hold on even the ones that
Even the ones that aren't
Like
Traditionally
Handsome babies
They're still like they're really
Really little and they can't do
Anything right
And that part's great I agree that that's great
Their vulnerability definitely wins me over
They're so little and they fuck up
Non stop and they
Just like piss and shit
Like whenever they want to
That's like
That's big cutie behavior if you ask me
And frankly for me and listen I might be in the minority
Here but I like me a Wallace
Sean looking baby you know what I mean
It's ideal for me
Give me a baby with a tonsure
Oh yeah
Just a little
Shiny fontanelle
Sometimes you see a baby
Trying too hard and it's like yeah man
I get it you're conventionally
Attractive for a baby
Alright okay
I'm gonna blow this one wide open
You can't trust people
To tell you the honest truth about
Your baby there is only one force
That we can turn to at times like this
It's capitalism
Here's what I want you to do I need you to take that baby
To Los Angeles, California
And you are gonna put your money
Where your mouth is and you're gonna start
Pushing that baby
You need to become a baby agent
I recommend baby Joel Begley
He's just like our agent but a baby
And go to him and say
I gotta take my shot
And then you just start cranking it
If that baby's really cute
You're gonna start booking
And that is the only thing you can trust
Is your baby booking
Yep because this is also a good chance
Listen your baby might be cute right
Being cute is easy but
This is also a good chance to figure out is your baby driven
Because it's like Baby Rock said
It's about drive
It's about power
When you feel hungry
With the vowel
Wait for the inevitable
Full house reboot
When they open the roll up for
You know baby
Like Michelle would probably be a dinosaur
Or something like whatever
And then you come for that
Crown and let's see how cute your baby is
Let's see how cute
The baby auditions for fullest house
Are going to be
It's going to be the hunger games
I have quintuplets they can each work 15 minutes
Swamp them out as needed
You know what we can go through them
Work one so bad
You can keep one
Keep one that's yours
We have a PA who runs in and swaps
The baby out mid scene
Mid scene
No cuts
We have one of these quintuplets we only use for lighting
So we just put the baby there
So we don't have to get one of the really choice babies
To stand out
Yeah we got a close up baby
We got a back of the headshot baby
My name is Derek
I thought I was working with Skylar today
Derek I'm just running your lines
They're going to shoot me from behind the head
I look just like beautiful Skylar
I'm here for the two shots
Don't worry about it
Hey let's bang through this
Okay it's martini o'clock
Let's see we got some ADR here
Okay
Let me take that again
That didn't feel natural
I'm a mocap for my brother
Derek
Please ignore all the white balls glued to my face
It's hard for me to because I'm a baby and what not
I'm just going to swing at this tennis ball
Hang in front of me
Pretend it's I don't know a fun toy
That a beautiful baby would get
And I did eat it
One of the balls
Please call my mommy and my doctor
Apologies to Robert Zemeckis that we have
Backed into
Baby Herman from
Frame Roger Rabbit just back character
Again
Hey can we go to the wizards
House
This one was sent in by Zach
I want to knock first
Knock knock knock
Well the door just swung open
And a bat flew out
And the bat is the wizard
This is the wiki how it's how to blow a
Kiss how to blow a kiss
Just because it's Halloween it doesn't mean
We can't have a little
Valentine's Day in here don't you think
I think Halloween is like couples costumes
And group costumes and
Friends becoming lovers
Lovers becoming wolves
Blowing a kiss is a great way to show affection for
Someone in a light hearted way
Remember to lock eyes with the person while blowing
Them a kiss always choose an appropriate
Time to blow kisses and avoid making
This gesture to anyone who might not like it which
I will say statistically
Speaking is
Everyone
If you were to take the statistics
Of the human population which I think is like
8 some billion
Right and then you take
Out of that number
The number of people that it's okay
For you to blow a kiss to it is so
Statistically insignificant that
It is zero
For all intents and purposes
It's the lottery ticket of human interaction
They're just like once in a while once in a
Great while it might hit
A little bit and that's probably because the person thought
You were someone else that kind of looks like
You I blew a kiss
I blew a kiss to my baby today because he clocked
Me while I was taking Henry to school
And he was at the window
And I gave him a little and then I
Thought like was that right
Yeah
Did I do that?
What kind of look did he give back to you?
I mean he smiled he loves
He really is a big fan of me
Was it a smile like oh dad that wasn't
The time for that yeah it was pretty fucking
Condescending actually now that I'm thinking about it
So anyway making the gesture
I'm hung up though on the
Lighthearted gesture and I'm wondering
If there's like a way that one could
Dramatically blow a kiss
Like either in a threatening way
Or like this means something kind of
You know like when you see in like mafia movies and they get that
Like kiss of death could you do that
With blowing a kiss where it's just like hey you
Mwah
Oh no it's the black spot
What? I don't think that gets it done
I don't think this is a lighthearted if you take
Lighthearted at face value to mean like something that's just
Kind of like woo playful and a
Little poof a little poof of smoke
Blowing a kiss is not
That because I'm going to be thinking about that all day
If someone does that to me but let's make sure
We're doing it right please wait until
You are a short distance away from the person
Blowing a kiss is a nonverbal show of affection
That works best when you're a short distance away from
Someone e.g. across the room if you blow
Someone a kiss at close proximity
It may seem odd and unnecessary
That's true some
Some close quarters combat
But what's the farthest that's such a vague
That's a great that's the next
Question is like I feel like I could
360 no scope my baby
With a
Remote smoocher like
From across like a crowded theater
And I feel like I have done that
I think one end of an end zone to end zone of a football
Field clear line of sight
I could get them
The line of sight is important
It can't be full of people right because then
Unless I can stand up like on one of those bandstands
That like you know that the drum
Line leaders use and stuff like if I could get that
I think I could get them into this you don't want it to hit
Someone else no god no
Are you kidding me yeah in this
Economy this one's important
Lock eyes with the person you're blowing a kiss to making
Direct eye contact with blowing a kiss let's the person
Know you're sending it to them
Look at the person until they look back at you and
Smile when they meet your gaze hold that eye contact
While you blow them a kiss if they break
Eye contact before you make the gesture wait until they
Look back at you to try again
In front of your mouth like yeah
It's like a oh so it's like
Um it's like tipping at the
Deli you gotta wait
They have to wait until they see they gotta
Wait till they're looking like hello here you go yeah
Um
I can't think of anything worse
Than somebody leaving you
Hanging on a kiss blow
That's gotta be a tough that's gotta be a
Tough one to just turn away
In the middle like I'm like
And they turn away in the middle
Of it and then it's like someone else
Sees me blowing a kiss to
Nobody to a ghost well it's
Just like playing catch with someone without that eye
Contact you blow the kiss when they're not
Looking hits them right inside of the head they're down
I mean they're unconscious
I just had a freaking grand idea
If you're listening to this show
And you see us in the real
World
Just blow us a sweet kiss
Wow that's interesting if you blow us a
Big bold move and I clock
It no it's not bold
Well both of you do include your two brothers
Who didn't get a vote in this new idea
Yeah I feel like and this is one of those
Things that is like the secret on the
Show but for bad but for bad
Like if there was a secret that was
For bad that was like when you say
It the bad thing is going to happen now
It's like the it's like the
That's what you've done
I mean that don't just start indiscriminately
But I'm like I'm saying
Here's my consent to just like blowing
Me a kiss anytime you see me and I'll
I'll know your whole story
Yeah I'll get it and then just be like
You'll be completely comfortable knowing that
I've just like I caught it with my hand
I smooshed it on my cheek thank you so much
Now here's what I will say Justin from
That gesture it's just occurred to me
That there is not a I guess maybe a thumbs
Up but like blowing a kiss seems
Intimate in a way of like kissing
On the cheek would be as opposed to like
A high five can we long distance high
Five as a thing to replace
Look at yourself do it again Travis
Oh yeah no I did it no I did it
And I felt it no I'm not doing it
Again ever again in my life
High five is bad
Bad bad bad
Historically speaking while you're driving
Historically speaking not great
Not a great look
How do you guys receive a
Kiss blow you catch it you put in your
Pocket
See I like to I like to make my
Kiss bust up because when they blow me a kiss
I'll grab it out of the air and I'll fucking eat it
Oh that's a good one
It's a sweet little candy
Yeah it's like no I get like I'm like a beast
I'm like
It's filling me up good
Kiss your palm slowly bring the palm
To your hand to your mouth touch your palm with your lips
I don't think that's right it's
Fingertips it's not palm
For me this is where I got
Fucked up when I blew a kiss to Gus today
Is I did it very
Very much on the fingertips
I rolled it off there I rolled it
Oh now that's it oh
Griffin I'm sure we'll get to this but when
I hear blow kiss
Well I don't blow I'm sure there are people
Who and
And like waft it off
If you don't send it on its merry way
Yeah how the kiss is supposed to get to them
I'm sending it
People are gonna think you got some delicious marinara on there
I'm sending it right
With my energy but I'm not blowing
Travis oh that's interesting
If you look at your kiss
I know Justin
I know Justin I can feel it too
Historically
The way you're doing your hand with flinging your kisses
Looks bad historically
That's why I'm doing it backhanded now instead of
Maybe throw him a grounder
Travis you know what I mean
A slider right between your
Arms
I'll put it in a little envelope
And I'll seal it and I'll put it in an imaginary
And then they can open it and it's safe
That way
Position your hand after kissing your palm place your hand flat under your mouth
We know this one you gotta have a stable firing
Platform but here's step 5
Blow away the imaginary kiss
This motion will signify you blowing the kiss to its intended target
Do this gesture slowly
To create emphasis
I think that's the thing
That's most threatening because if I was
Close to that person right and we have
A relationship like physically or emotionally
Both
You know if it was someone where we had a relationship
Where we kiss each other on a regular basis
I would feel comfortable kissing them
What I would not do is kiss them and then
Blow against their lips to cement
That kiss in there
Like a kiss on the cheek so like
I'm sending the kiss
You know that that's not
My kiss is like a butterfly
It flies on its own me blowing on it
It's just gonna fuck up its trajectory
That's crazy
Your kiss can't fly on its own
My kiss is a fucking butterfly
I don't know about you guys lead balloon
Kisses sorry your kisses suck
Be mindful about your cultural
Surroundings this is good
I think in general
Hey all wiki however step 1
Step 1 keep your grades up
Step 2 be mindful of your cultural
Surroundings
Blowing your kiss is a gesture
That's well understood in North American culture but not necessarily
In others in Brazil for instance
The gesture of bringing your fingers to your mouth
As you kiss them signifies the enjoyment
Of a meal and not a sign of affection
This to me seems like
That's still okay like
If you're in Brazil and you blow someone a kiss
Someone will look at you and be like
They must have eaten something very delicious
Lately that's not so bad
If it was like
You wish that their you know
That their whole family was sick
Or something like that like that's what this
This is a cursing this is a cursing gesture
And I think as we've established earlier
On in this segment there's definitely
Some gestures you could make that are universally
Unpleasant right that everyone's like
There's no confusing that for anything else
Choose an appropriate time and place
Yeah I mean don't get
Not a funeral
Blowing a kiss is often
Seen as a flirtatious gesture
Which can be problematic in the workplace
Yes in fact I would say
It can be problematic in a
Workplace any workplace
Any workplace you don't have to work
At the workplace if you are at the workplace
Then it's not good
And also the place what's the name
Of the thing that connects all the workplaces
Outside the world don't
Do it there either cause that one can also
Like somebody might be working nearby
The only place not to do it is
Well I mean unless I'm there
Which I've already consented to blow all
The kisses you like other than that
Just like not inside a
Workplace and not outside a workplace
Other than that those two
Situations
I think there's two people
I can think of that I would feel comfortable doing this to
And neither of them
Are you guys or my wife
So my friends Bob and Bradberry
I think Bob and Bradberry we could be like hey buddy what's up
How's it going like and be very comfortable
It's cool
Like it's a cool thing
That would be like a cool feeling very
Hip way to do it I would not make a
Show of it I think there's something in the show
Like mwah
Right where it's just like you fucking
But if you're just like hey man stay classy
Or whatever I think I could pull that off I think I could
Do that I do it to my little stinkers
That's it oh yeah yep
I've started doing this thing and it
Like it makes me feel
Once again like a cool dad
Where like I'll make a drugs
They're awesome and I put my hat on back once I talk
To my kids look how great they are it works great
Hey kids let's talk about drugs
Have you tried it you know
You got any know where I can get them
Sure I will make a joke
Like for my three year old like maybe
For lunch we should have a bowl of farts and
Dot last but I wink at BB
As if to say like you know we wouldn't
Really eat farts and she like looks at me
And nods and I'm like yeah man we're cool
I want to bring back the wink
Is that something that we can like reincorporate
No for sure not
No damn it I thought
We could but you know what you guys are right
And also
The last tip here is make sure the person
Won't be uncomfortable which like
Should have been first of all the first
Tip also impossible also
I would just err on the side of caution
Which is to say don't blow a kiss
Unless it's to one of your little stinkers
Or to a dog
Or someone you have told I'm going
To blow a kiss at you is that
Do you mind then that
Could be okay right I think you would
Have to you would have to phrase it like
At some point I would like to try to blow
A kiss at you that's cool and I'm totally
Fine if we do it and then
You're like never do that again are
You willing to try this exchange
At least once to see how we both feel
I don't know that I couldn't give blanket
Consent to it like Justin has
As we are introducing this into
This sort of like social consciousness
Of our
Cultural surroundings
We have an opportunity here to
Kind of like set the rules because we are
On the cutting edge we're pioneers
So like first order of business
For me we've discussed
Technique right like get to the fingers
You gotta blow
Stable firing platform all that stuff
Yeah absolutely big thing for me
Sound is
Necessary is it
Is it creepier for me to go
Or is it creepier for me to go
I think silent
Is weird well but see then we're getting
Into sign language that is
Thank you
And I think it's an inch
Lower with the fingers and no sound
Right the only way to make it clear
That what I'm saying is I'm kissing you
And I'm blowing it at your face is like
Okay and then the receiving
End of it I think just a nod
Just like
Or a gentle touch of the cheek
Like a breeze well no no no no no
Because I don't know because I wouldn't
Kiss you on the cheek do you know what I mean
Like I wouldn't kiss you on the cheek I'm your brother
No I wouldn't kiss
I wouldn't kiss you hairy boys on your hairy cheeks
Oh it's lovely it's like
Nuzzling a big bear it's not lovely
I'm not gonna kiss you guys hairy cheeks
Stop it oh boy stop it
So like I don't wanna address
I don't want it to be I don't want it to land
On me like I don't wanna
I don't want it to land
On me and me be the one that put it there
Do you know what I mean so just a
A new look and like a
Like just curl your fingers
And a nod like I want something of like it's been
Oh that's cool that can be like a
Cool gesture of just like you
Sort of like your David Bowie
With the oar oh yeah I've welcomed
This I've got the kiss now
And you can kind of like play with it and roll it around
Your fingers like a coin oh
Yeah do tricks with the kiss
Oh I like that just a catch and a
Nod what do you think Justin's thinking about
I don't know man David Bowie
No you find the guys
There's contact juggling that's settled
On blowing kisses that's all done
We've weighed in on that and I think it's time to
Treat ourselves with a quick trip
To the money zone
Can I tell you guys something messed up
The whole time I was in the UK
I didn't receive one letter
No one sent me any letters
As I bounced from castle to castle
Just cleansing them of
Every wrongdoing that's ever been done there
I didn't receive one stinking
Letter from either of you were you sending them
No
You know I was going to
But I actually don't have the time to go to the
Post office right now oh
Justin you idiot
That's the only place where stamps are so
Sorry Justin
Idiot is a word
They use over in the UK
To mean like somebody who doesn't know something
You might not have heard it before
And because you don't know about stamps.com
Which is this new invention
Where you can get stamps and
Postage and stuff through the internet
Have you heard about this
Have you heard did you hear about that
Did you hear about that wanker
Do you just take a picture of the stamps on the screen
With your phone and then no Justin
You bollocks head you
Go
Sorry the two big ones
For them are idiot and bollocks head
Yeah Chris Brain
Chris Brain
You go to stamps.com
Right and it's the one stop shop
For all your shipping and mailing needs you get access
To USPS and UPS services
You need to run your business right from your computer
No lines no traffic no hassle especially
Important during the upcoming
Holiday season
When maybe you run a small business and you're
Shipping things out to people or maybe you're just like
Sending out a lot of Christmas cards
Or gifts or whatever stamps.com
Can help you get that done
Rates are constantly changing
With stamps.com switch and save feature
You can easily compare carriers and
Rates so you know you're getting the best deal
Every time this holiday season
Trade late nights for silent nights
Start with stamps.com
Today sign up with promo code
My brother all one word for a special
Offer that includes a four week trial plus
Free postage and a free digital scale
No long term commitments or
Contracts just go to stamps.com
Click the microphone at the top of the page
And enter code my brother all one
Word brands like it when we have a little
Fun with them right
I hope so so can we talk about trading
Late nights for silent
Nights with stamps.com
Offer a completely
Silent way of getting
My shit from point a to point
B I know they offer a quick
And affordable and convenient way of
Doing it but I do not
I am not convinced stamps.com
That your service is going to
Make my evenings any
Any quieter oh
So griffin actually it's buried deep in the
Contracts so be careful that's why it's important you read everything
Yeah when you sign up with
Stamps.com it does require at least one
Night a week you watch a quiet place and
Act it out oh wow
And not make any sound now I've never
Seen a quiet place except that I know that people
Are really quiet in it and I think Jim from
The office is in there pulling faces constantly
Yeah and you could also
Probably just get by watching the office on mute
If that's what you wanted to do instead
They don't have any way of checking up on you
That's what I found out
You guys see a quiet place
What's it about I have not
Seen that one yet um
Yeah it's one of those movies where you have to
Pay the dead kid tax at the top
Of it in order to enjoy the rest of the film
Yeah I wish there was a website
Just for that there's one about whether dogs
Die I really like that
Because that could really soil a film for me
Yeah like I don't have a dog
Yeah right yeah
For sure you know what I do
Have what do you have a fresh
Look
All the time yeah how do I
Do it a lot of people ask me what's my secret
I'm a busy guy you know what's
My secret I have the clothes sent to me I don't
Go the clothes come here
You know when your clothes you put them on
It fits just right it's like this is for me
Yes I call that this is
The stitch fix feeling
You came up with that that's good dude
Thank you you get clothes that fit you at a
Budget you're comfortable with styles you
Love you're working with a personal stylist
That you give them your sizes your
Taste your budget and they're going to send
You a box of clothing items that
Are like this is for you you're going to love
And you will you open it up you put
It on like oh my gosh I love it if
That doesn't qualify for the items
Rare fair you put them back in the
Bag you ship them back no
Postage no fees no returns
No problem no can I tell you my
My favorite thing Justin oh I love this
Happens from time to time where I'll get some
From Citrix and it's something I would not have
Picked out in a store yeah but I put it
On and I'm like oh this
Fixed me perfectly and looks great on me I
Never would have known this is my thing
But my stylist is like geared it towards
Me and push that a little bit and
I'm like yeah this is a new style that I love
My wardrobe needs have changed and so I
Drop back on my stitch fix
To like a like quarterly
Fix which works for me
And my schedule but
Also like I find that I've learned how to dress
Myself because of stitch fix
And the many many many clothes they
Have sent my way getting an adult in the room
To say hey hey is what you should
Do yeah and that's also
Nice to have an adult here to teach you how
Like the buttons work because
I can't figure out is this a hook and eye
Situation what are we doing
Yeah and my stylist walks me through
Dressing myself and it's very lovely
When you reach for something that you think will look
Good on you but nobody else does
Stitch fix is at the store when you don't have any help
Stitch fix is like the hand that reaches out
And smacks your hand and says no that's not
For you this isn't that's not yours
And it's the only rough
Part was when stitch fix kicked in the door to my house
And took away all my cargo
Shorts and graphic tees with Stewie Griffin
On them and you said
Stuff in those in those cargo shorts
And in the Stewie t-shirts
Because they have pockets and I kept
All my beyblades in those and
In the Stewie Griffin t-shirts
Anyway that's the only bad thing
Is they'll take your cargo pants right out of your
Your house and also if you have
Any of the Family Guy guys
It's over. Right now Stitch Fix
Is offering our listeners $20 off
Their first fix at stitchfix.com
Slash my brother that's stitchfix.com slash
My brother for $20 off today
Stitchfix.com slash my brother
I'm Lisa Hanna-Waltz
And I'm Emily Heller. Wow Emily we've been
Doing this podcast for 10 years
I know but hey don't worry you can jump in
At literally any episode and hear us
Talk about some of our favorite stuff
Caterpillars becoming butterflies
Martha Stewart flying around in a private
Jet full of trees. Yes you heard me
Right trees. Neighbors becoming enemies
Just kidding
Whatever messed up stuff we can find on
Wikipedia. Our impeccable taste
In everything from dogs to tv shows
To bodily functions. And horses
Lots and lots of horses. Come for
Our horned up rants about the world stay for the
Catchy theme songs. You might not learn anything
But we're a good hang. Baby
Geniuses every other week on Maximum
Fun dot org. Baby Geniuses
Tell us something we don't know
Hi I'm Jesse Thorne
America's radio sweetheart. And I'm Jordan
Morris boy detective
Our comedy podcast Jordan Jesse Go
Just celebrated its
15th anniversary
It was a couple months ago but we forgot
Uh yeah completely. Our
Silly show is 15
Years old. That makes it old enough to
Get its learners permanent. And
Almost old enough to get the talk
Wow I hope you got the talk before then
A lot of things have changed in 15
Years. Our show's not one of them
We're never changing and
You can't make us
Jordan Jesse Go the same forever
At Maximum Fun dot org
Or wherever you get your podcasts
I wanna munch
Skye
I want to munch
Welcome to Munch Squad it's a podcast within a podcast
Profiling the latest and greatest in brand eating
I am so excited to be back
Obviously things have been happening so
Fast
Just inject
Like
Pour one out super quick
I don't wanna do a story
About this but the McRib is guys on its
Farewell tour. No
Yeah it's back for one brief
Moment and
And I'm like why now
You know what I mean like why now and are you
Really gonna get rid of it
Right now and then I
Do you guys ever wonder where it goes when it's not here
I think about that all the time
Back to pigs
The pigs get them
Pigs get to keep them
Keep your ribs
We don't need them
These are yours no
Oh no the clown is here for our ribs
No keep your ribs
Keep your ribs children
Keep your ribs today
So I just wanted to tell you guys real quick
What's happening out in the world
Firehouse has released the prime
Rib steak sub
That's where they go
The five star flavor
This five star flavor comes from
Being seared and then cooked to perfection
Via sous vide
I know they use
Wait isn't this a fast casual
Restaurant yes they
Sous vide them and then let it sit
Just kick it here for four hours
While we bake your sandwich
I'm sure they started before the customer gets there
Griffin I don't think it's sous vide to order
Yeah it's fair
Now why sous vide
Well let's check in with Berthelon
A Michelin star trained
Chef and a matre
Cousineur de France
Who's been a pioneer in sous vide since
1989 Chef
Gerard
Hello is this Chef Gerard
Berthelon
It's Firehouse Subs
You want to cook up a lot of these sloppy boys
Or what
Absolutely
He says water is the best medium
To transfer heat because of how precise
It allows you to be
By searing Firehouse Subs prime rib to capture
Flavor and then cooking it for 12 hours
Sous vide
Guests receive an incredibly tender and flavorful piece of
Beef just as good as they would get in any
Steakhouse in the world
Berthelon drunk on his own
Now I also
Say Firehouse Subs I don't know how much
You paid this man to say this I could have told
You the same thing for like 50 bucks
I would have done it I've been sous vide eating
For like six years now I could have told you the same
It's good the water keeps it up real good
Yeah it's pretty good
I don't know I've been in the back
Room of plenty of fast casual restaurants
Enough to know that it's going to be
Sort of a spooky thing to have back
There it's going to just have like this
Specimen floating in a fucking
Bacta tank just like
Waiting for you to just sear it
And slice it up I think
That that would give a sort of but it's Halloween
It's Halloween
Now see I thought you were going to say a spooky thing
Because basically you just have a
Vat of scalding hot liquid
Sitting around for people
Who are maybe at best phoning it
In yeah I mean they're probably keeping that bad boy
Like what 129, 130
Still I wouldn't want that on my
It wouldn't feel good but it's not scalding
So that was
The story that I noticed like
Because I was thinking a lot about
Like meat
Yeah
So I noticed that one that steak and cheese
Sandwich that they
Are doing the prime rib steak sub
And then I noticed this is always
In the same week Roy Roger
Says they're bringing back the steak and cheese
Sandwich Oh wow
Steak and cheese
Features thin slices of beef steak with American
Cheese and grilled onions on a delicious six inch
Roll Yeah Roy Rogers
Restaurants the western themed quick service restaurant chain
Based in Frederick, Maryland is announcing the return of
A highly anticipated limited time menu offering
In introducing
A new side and launching its gift card
Promotion just in time for the holidays
Yes the holidays
Are here folks and this time the
Festive season has been rung in by the
Steak and cheese sandwich for Roy Rogers
Quote the steak and cheese is always
A fan favorite we're happy to bring it back
For our royalists you know
Customer that's the senior director
That feels like that's something else that feels like
That word means something else
That's what it means it's people that love Roy Rogers
We know customers will love the addition
Of our new mozzarella sticks and marinara dipping sauce
As well they pair great as a side or
As a snack on the go
I got a lot of errands to run
Today give me some
If you're a fast casual restaurant
And you announce something that has existed
For 500 years I think
It should just be I think the
Press statement should just be like
One to two sentences hey
Guys it's us Roy Rogers we
Do mozzarella sticks now
You probably thought we already did come have
Them yeah we get that it seems like something
We would have done before now I like the
They just casually threw in there
A scenario they would imagine like
I have one last present tucked behind
The tree let's see what it is
Roy Rogers gift card thanks
You're welcome
Son so this is the
Second press release this is how this one
Closes this is the perfect time
Of year for food that provides comfort
And reminds us of home
These seasonal
Limited time offerings do just that and are
Delicious additions to the menu
Royalists can now give the gift of high
Quality burgers beef and chicken
With our holiday gift card promotion
The perfect gift or stocking stuff
For this holiday season
Okay so we really are and then
Then I just
Drive on over by Quizno's
Press release outlet no way
Quizno's prime rib sub makes
Their long awaited return
Announced the same week as these
Other stories
Is it okay is this all connected
To the McRib retirement this is what I don't
I can't figure out
They are searching this is guys
This is house of the dragon haven't seen it
But I think this is what it is where they're searching
They're vying
Politicking to discover the heir apparent
To the McRib kingdom
And this is thrilling
For me this is super exciting
Three years after its last appearance
The popular prime rib subs are back
For guests to indulge
In the comforting and satisfying flavors
Of slow roasted prime rib
As the holiday season draws near
Are you shitting me
Are both of you all trying to be like the perfect
Holiday food
A messy cheese steak sandwich
Okay so this I looked it up right because
It stuck in my mind
Prime rib is like a
Thing that for like
Many is like a traditional
Christmas dinner thing right
But this isn't that
This is a steak hoagie
It's not that
It may be bursting with
With flavor and dry rub with
Black pepper garlic and salt
Don't brag about putting salt
On it
Three of the most basic
Things you can put on something
Salt pepper and garlic
Listing salt is an admission that you didn't put
Any other flavors on it
You would have said anything other than salt
And get this we cooked it
Like how cool man
It's got a creamy horseradish sauce
The prime Italian is made with slow roasted prime rib
Provolone cheese
Sauteed onions
The
Giardiniera
It's the pepper
It's like the
Green peppers
For many
This is a quote that is in a different
Press release than the last one
For many
The holiday season is an ideal time
To cozy up with indulgent foods
And get together with family
Surrounding themselves with comfort and familiarity
Says Mike Geisman
Vice president of culinary innovation
We invite our guests to experience
Those same feelings
At Quiznos
Travis that's the next
Experience those same feelings when they walk into a Quiznos
If you experience the feeling of
Being home when you walk into a Quiznos
That's not good
That's bad
I feel comforted and surrounded by family
At this Quiznos
If you work at the Quiznos and it's like
These are my people
That's fine
I would say even that's not great
You should know it's a
Found families are huge with us
And maybe your family is at Quiznos
That's fantastic
I'm saying if you eat a sandwich and you're like
I'm home
That's probably less than great
Especially as more and more Quiznos
Across the country are closing
And you're like
Chasing your home from state
Yeah my home
My home in Huntington on 4th Avenue
My home
Is now a place where
People go to drink wine
And paint things
That's in my house
In your house and they didn't even ask you
They are what is it paint and sip
Maybe I don't know
Yeah
I guess
It's true what they say
That the supply chain is really
Just dictating all this stuff
It's clearly somebody backed up
Too many
We got a lot of rib
We got a lot of beefs
We got some thin slices of shit
Tell them it's for Christmas
Tell them it's a Christmas
Delight
My money's on Quiznos
I think it would be fun if Roy Rogers won
Like if Roy Rogers became
The big one
In the rib skirmishes
Yeah
The rib crisis
Of 2022, 2023
Because let's be honest
We're not going to whip this thing in the next two months
No, no, no
Do you want another question?
Yeah
Hi brothers, I'm faced with a moral quandary
You've come to the right place
Our school is holding elections for student council
The two of my friends are running
I've already voted for them
But this morning on the quad
There was a guy who was campaigning by handing out mini gourds
In a massive burlap sack
To people who promised to vote for him
The gourds are really cute and I want to have one
Is it morally right
To lie to this poor man
Just for a free calabash squash?
And that's from squash squanderer in New York
Can I just say
It feels like a long way to go
To get a vote
When you could just like buy a bag of like
Mixed mini chocolate bars
Especially now
During a Halloween season
I love candy
Where are you getting so many gourds
That you can hand them out as a favor
It seems like a huge expense
You know I'm in
Politics country now
Where it all happens
Yeah
And I will say that a lot
Like a surprising amount of stuff
Here
Is like a lot of the political
Processes are lubricated with like
Fun sized Mr. Good bars
Crackles
Hershey's with almond
That greases a lot of the wheels
Cause they can't get enough of this stuff
Well and the secret is
You do a special dark and a good bar
At the same time
Oh fuck off that's too much
This is a crime
What this person is doing is a crime
Oh right Justin
Justin's been like Toby Zigglering around
For a while now
And he thinks he's Mr. Politics and Ethics
If I can pay people for votes
Yeah
Okay listen if it was legal
You can't do this it's a crime now that being said
Hand out gourds
You don't want to be mixed up
In this endeavor you can't pay people
For votes that said
If they got Adela Khan over there
Let me come by
I can't get I don't have a trader
Ricks a trader no
That's the werewolves in London
Trader Sam's nope
You'll get there
Trader Joe's I don't have a Trader Joe's around here
I don't have a Jungle Jim's you know what I mean
I gotta get my Delicata when people go out of town
They're like can I get you a souvenir
Bring you back some Delicata squash
Dude you can eat the rind thank you
But Justin I'm sorry
Oh yeah constantly
Constantly man at this point
I'm more Delicata squash than I am man
But here's the question Justin in your mind
Paying someone a tiny decadent
Seasonal Gourd is paying them for votes
In what
In what world can you use
A tiny decorative Gourd as currency
And please point me in the direction
Of that world cause I'm a very rich man
Pumpkin town
Good point yeah I didn't think about that
You can't you don't want to get
Mixed up in this business this is dark stuff
I'll say but it sounds like
To me you have two friends
Running for
Student council competing
It sounds like against each other
They said they already voted for them
Well fraud clearly
They might be different positions
Oh that's another good point
Yeah maybe it's not fraud
But regardless you can feign ignorance
And be like sorry I thought you guys were competing
Against each other and I could not choose
And I got this cutie little Gourd
This sweet little squash outside
And I told the guy I'd vote for him
Cause I couldn't pick between you two it's not fair
So I voted third party
For this one
Cause here's the beautiful thing I don't know if you guys know this
You can tell anybody you're voting for anything
They can't check
You can be like I'll definitely
Vote for you and unless that guy loses
By like one vote and then breaks
Into like the student council offices
Or whatever it goes through each
Thing and it's like wait a minute it was Todd
Todd took one of my gourds and they didn't vote for me
I'm going to ruin Todd's life
Maybe maybe that might happen
In my new YA novel that I'm working
On please don't copy this concept
I've said it out loud everybody forget what I said
Forget what I said this is mine
I mean it is Kevin Costner's swing vote
And that's fun that you reinvented
That film this time for a reboot
I'm calling mine Gourd to death
Yeah thank you
Get out of sploom house that was good stuff
Speaking of like the
Politics thing
Did you all see
That god
I'm so delighted did you guys see the attack ad
Hell yeah I did dude Griffin did you see it
Oh yeah I saw the attack ad
I got sent it
They made a lot of good points
I don't want to talk too much about it but I do want to say
The front of it is just this
Picture of gas prices with Joe Biden
Like good gas prices
And Sidney's like I love it
I had no idea
I've known Sidney now for decades
I had no idea she had such influence over
The national gas
Prices no idea
Here's what I wanted to
Say though is that this mailer does
Include the phrase
That is on a political mailer
In the world the Biden
Slash McElroy agenda
The Biden McElroy agenda
That's really really
Really strong
That's not something we made up for this show
That was like the Biden McElroy agenda
Very very good
The only way that that makes sense
Is if it's like the Biden slash McElroy agenda
And then underneath it in bullet points is
Leaving a ticket at will call
At every live show they've ever done
In Washington DC for Joe Biden
Hoping he'll show up
That's the only McElroy slash Biden agenda
I know of that exists
On this planet
Do you know how bad you have to
Be at your job
Because of who Sidney is
Married to to not be
Able to cook up a very very
Very very very
Very bad mailer
The possibilities
Are endless
We love Sidney you love Sidney
Everybody loves Sidney
This clown
This absolute degenerate
You see this guy in the pumpkin suit
Who said he just came from a wedding
He's like right there with her
You see this man in a chili suit
In a pumpkin suit who's got chili
All over his hands and face
That's in the last week
We're not even getting like
Scrolling out of his Google calendar page
To find these embarrassing things
That's a choice Sidney made once
A while ago it's been stuck with
Every other choice has been great
But she did this one time
Choose this guy are you sure
Are you sure
There's gotta be something fundamentally funny
Oh gosh politics is fun
Thank you so much for listening to our
Podcasts I really really
Really miss doing it and I really really
Really miss talking to you guys
Both you two and the listeners
I really miss doing this
So it's so nice to be back
Be back here with you and I hope that we're
Going to be seeing some of you in person
Very soon
Exactly I will also say mine and Johnson's
Birthday is coming up soon and it's a birthday
Present for me if you are in some
Place where you can vote for Sidney
Do that that would be
A great birthday present for me
Thanks Trav
Hey you're welcome
Now can you pick up on my
Let me do my fun segue again
Okay yeah
Griffin if you want to interrupt with any plugs
For my wife's candidacy listen that's all fair
Yeah set that tee that up again
Okay and then
I hope we see some of you in person soon
Here in the next
Week away
Very soon
Vote for Sidney
We're going to be in Cincinnati
And D.C. and Detroit
Not in that order though
Not in that order Travis I'm begging you
We're going to be in Cincinnati
Doing my brother my brother and me
In November
10th if I remember correctly
Yeah it's the 10th we're going to be up in Cincinnati
Doing my bim bam then in the 11th we're going to be
At the Masonic in Detroit doing my bim bam
And then on the 12th we're going to be here
In the district
In the DMV as we say
In the DMV at the DAR
Constitution hall doing my bim bam
And then the next night
We're coming back for Taz at D.C.
DAR DMV baby let's go
With Brennan Lee Mulligan
DMing Dad Lance 2
Y'all I could not
Be more excited for that fucking live show
Come out to it
If you live within driving distance
Of this show I guarantee you
It's going to be a gosh dang barn burner
The last one was a hoot
I did a thing with Roll20Con
Playing with Brennan
And a bunch of other folks including Abria
And it was great but when I was there
I was talking to Brennan about the show and I was like
Yeah I'm thinking maybe new characters
And the look on his face was like you guys aren't going to be the same characters
But I love those characters
I'm going to be the same characters
I had forgotten that he remembered
Until he said you're not going to be Guy Ferrari again
I was like fuck that's good yeah I'll be Guy Ferrari
It's going to be great
Speaking of Abria we've rescheduled our shows
For San Jose and Denver they've been postponed
But now they will be April
27th in San Jose California
Adventure Zone with Abria
Who just a taste of that
When we did Spirit Breakers for Halloween
Abria is an absolute joy and brings out
The best in us I would say
April 28th we're going to do My Brother My Brother and Me
In San Jose and then April 29th
We're going to be doing My Brother My Brother and Me
In Denver all existing tickets will be
Honored for the new dates if you can't attend
The rescheduled dates you can request a refund
At the point of purchase and if you don't have tickets
But want to go now that we have new dates
Tickets are on sale now mask and proof
Of full vaccination or negative
Covid test within 72 hours of events
Are as required so it's a
New month so there will be new merch go check
That out McElroyMerch.com
A lot of cool stuff there and don't forget to
Pre-order the Taz 11th hour
It comes out officially
February 21st 2023 but you can
Pre-order it now at The Adventure Zone
Comic.com And I just
Wanted to say one more thing about that Detroit Live
Show that is going to be on
November 11th which as
You all know is the 14th anniversary
Of the release of Star Wars the Clone Wars
Lightsaber now on the Wii
Yeah I feel like
A themed Star Wars
Episode only makes sense to celebrate
That release and we can
Say that because they pay us no matter if
People come or not like we obviously prefer
If people come but if nobody
Shows up then we can kind of like
Griffin's right but only
In this very limited scope where like
That trick works once
And then they don't do any more
After that so please do come. We will not be doing
I guarantee you we won't be doing a Star Wars show
I won't mention Star Wars up there
But it'll be in Justin's mind you would feel
It you'll feel it he'll be in full cosplay
Hey yeah thanks what if
Holy shit what if we were in full cosplay
But did not mention it. Okay
That's fine. Anyway thanks to Montaigne
Also for the use of our theme song My Life Is Better
With you. Stream that album
Making it. Buy it. Get it
Get the merch. Support
Support all art
But especially Montaigne's art cause it's
Very good. That's it
That's it for the show
Thank you so much for listening
Griffin can you inspire us
For like any quotes that you want to
Like
You're looking very thoughtful. Don't give up
Unless
Don't give up unless
No
Keep on pushing
What's the thing that the guy
That one of the presidents said where he's like if you're going through
Hell don't stop
If you're going through hell don't stop
Can't be it
I think it was
I think it was Benjamin Franklin
Who said if you're going through hell don't stop
My name is Justin McElroy
I'm Travis McElroy
I'm Griffin McElroy
What's
What's the thing