Hey everybody, Merry Candle Lights.
It's your oldest brother Justin McElroy here.
And here's your babiest,
baby, baby, baby, Griffin McElroy.
Hi.
Happy holidays, Griffin.
Happy holidays to you, my good friend Justin.
So we're fresh off the, dare I say, triumph.
Do we sound hungover?
Cause we is.
Yeah, we is hangover.
We're fresh off the triumph of Candle Lights 2014.
Thank you to everybody who came to the show
here at Huntington City Hall.
You're about to listen to the show right now.
I think you'll be pleased.
I think it's the best audio quality
we've gotten from a live show basically ever.
A wonderful surprise.
Better than the audio quality of the people
who are actually there.
Which if you're there and you couldn't,
you had trouble hearing us, sorry about that.
The room was built long before
amplified sound had been invented.
And so I guess that maybe there's a lot of echoing.
So sorry about that.
Listen to it now and maybe you'll get the goose
that you missed the first time around.
Speaking of missed goose,
since you're not physically there,
a few things you should know.
At the beginning, our dad is dressed
like his character from the Adventure Zone,
our D&D podcast.
So if you hear people laughing, that is why.
Also he's just a silly looking man.
Just so in general.
And that is, what else do they need?
Oh, we were dressed as the ghosts of Christmas
from A Christmas Carol.
So if you hear us referencing that.
That's what that was.
I'm sure you can find images of that.
Yeah, just do a Twitter search.
I mean, I don't want to introduce more work
into our podcast.
Listening to our podcast is already work.
It's kind of a chore.
So hoarse.
So hoarse, aren't we?
I know, it's a long night.
But we hope you enjoy the live show.
We'll be back in the middle
to talk about a couple sponsors.
But it's an extra-long episode,
so make sure to catch up on that too.
And it's clean.
It's clean.
If you want to share it with family,
might be kind of a weird one
since it was a live environ.
But we hope you enjoyed it.
Oh, and we also got a day named after us.
Yes.
By the mayor of Huntington.
By the mayor.
December 20, yesterday felt different to you.
It was because December 21st, 2014
was NBNBAM day in Huntington.
That's true.
That's not like a goof.
We got a proclamation.
It was signed and stamped and delivered.
So there you go.
There it is.
So anyway, that's gonna do it for us right now.
Hope you enjoy the show.
We'll be back with you in just a few minutes.
Thank you.
I am Merle Highchurch of the popular podcast,
The Adventure Zone.
You can tell because of my dwarfy voice.
The Adventure Zone,
one of the four most popular podcasts in existence.
All right, let's get down to business.
Yeah.
Did you wash your hands when you were done?
No.
Let us begin.
The McElroy brothers are not experts
and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert,
but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids.
Well, this show kinda is for young adults.
This show isn't for real little kids,
which I only mentioned so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool babies?
Hi.
Hey.
He was at half masked before,
but now we can begin.
Hello.
knew how many dubstep Christmas songs. There's a lot. You can fade the dubstep out, it's pretty
terrible. Infinity dubstep Christmas songs. Hi everybody, I'm Justin McElroy. I'm Travis McElroy.
And I'm the lead singer of the Polyphonic Spree apparently tonight. I'm Griffin McElroy. I'm going
to have to take my mask off because my breath is fogging up my glasses because I'm the coolest kid.
Yeah let's, does everybody have that out of their system? You get it? Can we take, okay.
I can't, wait, hold on. I can't take off. This is like caked on for a week. I'm gonna be opening
my presents like this. Oh we should say listeners at home, we had a hilarious opening bit where we
were dressed as the ghosts and Justin, he has a lovely green robe and a... Are you gonna garrison
Keylor this whole thing or can we just do the show? I remember in Lake Wobegon when three brothers
would really earn attention. If you're listening and you're not here, I'm wearing like a cool pair
of slacks that I got from Neiman Marcus and like a like a fashionable trendy but not too trendy
plaid shirt and then like a square cut wool tie. I look awesome. He looks really great. You know
what I actually learned? I'm wearing gaudy white face paint. Do you know how when you get a tan
and it makes your teeth look whiter? The opposite happens.
With that, what was the first thing we were going to talk about? All the show prep just
because the first bit worked so good that I was like man that was funny and that's all I can
think about right now. I spent 85 dollars on this costume all together. 90s are expensive.
Another thing I learned, 90s are expensive and that I wear an extra extra large in women's
for 90s. Perfect. These things are hard to urinate around but I suppose that's not really their
intended purpose. Should we start doing advice? Well the first thing I wanted to talk about just
to lead off is just a thank you that it's my brother, my brother and me. Happy my bim bam day
everybody. Happy my bim bam day. I cannot stress to you, goofs aside, let's get genuine. That was
a real honor. It was a really sweet thing. What an honor that was. It was like a really sweet thing
and it was emotional like this is my hometown you know. I love Huntington but I noticed on the
proclamation that it says that December the 21st 2014 is my bim bam day. It is not an annual
occurrence and that's you know fine. Most people don't even get the one day. I do wish the mayor
had told me in the morning that I got a day. That's like a snow day when you sleep till 11
and it's like I missed half the snow day. To be more accurate it's like a snow day but you just
went to class for like seven hours. It's like I got four hours of my special day left and I'm
gonna spend it in clown makeup. Fantastic. Oh wait hold on hold on hold on. It's a huge honor.
Huge oh my god. Huge honor no question. But what rights and privileges do you think we've earned
from this? For the next uh three hours you're asking? Yeah like free fruit at every vendor.
Like I don't know. Yeah at the fruit vendor. You know you know the fruit vendor.
Huge fruit vendor population. I'm just saying I wish the mayor had had shook me awake at one in
the morning. I don't know why he would be there. Griffin it's Steve. Griffin wake up it's Steve
you're missing it. Um I wish Steve had shook me away. He's got a key to the city he can open any
door. That's a great point. You look radical right now Justin. I'm saying my Justin is my fat Jesus
look. He's removed his fat Jesus beard and now he's just got fat Jesus hair and he looks uh
it looks pretty awesome. I this is the fullest embrace I could do of Jimmy Buffett style without
actually going to like his concerts. I hope you guys enjoyed the Buffett buffet in the waiting
interim uh that Justin definitely put together for you. I slaved over that playlist it only had
two James Buffett songs. Can we answer some questions? Okay uh who here has never listened
to My Brother My Brother Me before? Oh god wow so no one wondered off the streets of Huntington.
I heard one woo that started like uh so we have an advice show uh for the modern era and now
like Chilean miners we will emerge from no Chilean miners aren't still hot.
Well no. You know what it's candle nights do it again I'm gonna lean into it. Okay like Chilean
miners emerging from the ground. It's been 38 minutes can we answer a question? Yeah um we
turn your questions alchemy like into wisdom it's what we do here on the show uh so let's take some
of your questions uh some of you may be in the audience uh so if you uh hear your question
and start listening because we're gonna answer it and we're not gonna read it twice and if you
don't hear your question it was bad. You did a bad job. Maybe next candle nights although next
year is a candle night sleeping. Candle nights 2015. No candle nights next year but 2016 you
come back double hard. Every four and a half years. I have a close family this is the question
I the it's not me I have a close family member who often indulges in the eggnog a bit too much
during the candle nights it could be me it's not but it could be this often results in wackiness
followed by awkwardness then sadness like a clown like a clown Travis yes how do you deal with the
deal with the awkward situation of someone drinking a bit too much during the holidays
fun starter super fun opener for our comedy holiday podcast designated driver in dirty jersey
are you here perfect no cool lol um you know when you think someone is drinking too much at a holiday
party what you really have on your hands is a question of perspective because you're not
drinking enough unless you are as you literally just said 20 seconds ago the designated driver
that that was for either that was just a little bit any other episode any other episode would
have put a swear word in there but i didn't because it's candle you you you guys are missing
the best part of this situation what's that so the hardest thing about candle nights is not knowing
what to get someone right right right i guess yeah there's a lot of rituals it's a made-up fake
holiday i guess that's the hardest part get someone ever but what i'm saying is this provides
you the opportunity to give the best present which is your silence oh like uncle greg i'll
uncle greg i'm keeping your secret uncle greg this year not gonna tell him go ahead party dog
can party on can you get uncle greg an even better present which is that you get
drunker than uncle greg yes uncle greg i am your wingman of drunk people gonna tell
stories about me greg you let me find out i'm gonna be the embarrassment this year uncle greg
well for every drink you drink i'm gonna drink one more drink so drink away uncle greg
i got your back homie i mean he's he's earned it you've earned it uncle greg you work so hard 364
days out of the year you want your behind off again another swear opportunity that i passed
by i let it go i forget the rest of the stuff i was gonna say do you guys want to yahoo yeah
we uh uncle greg lay off uncle greg please for a second this yahoo uh if you don't listen to
the show and you were just quiet because you're nervous i get it um uh we do yahoo answers
questions they're all terrible this one was sent in by let me turn up the brightness oh i have my
glasses right here dude dude now i look like a spooky nerd uh this one it adds some contrast
yes this one was sent in by liana calon who asks how big are elves
my dad and i are arguing about this
he says that they are all little people that's not what they said yahoo you need to learn some
stuff about uh they are all little people like the kevlar elves okay ah man wait is that a thing
yeah it's elves that like a swat team elf yeah go go go go go go blasted slice by slice the pie
you would think the tree you would think the tree would stop the bullet and it wouldn't even get
anyway uh they have to protect the elf president sure they are all little people like the kevlar
elves and i say that some are human sized like legolas she doesn't believe me okay
this person is proposing because they say some are legolas size which would mean that there are
different there are different phylum of elves but there are elves that are both keyboard elves
kevlar kevlar elves oh maybe it's a maybe it's a copyright problem kevlar elves y'all know what i
mean wink you get it but on the deep ones but the idea that there are some that are legolas
size and some that are kevlar size legolas was not have you seen the movies he's not this tall
he was like wicked tall he was like super big he's a really big dude which is funny because
orlando bloom is big yeah he's uh he's knee high to a frog uh uh do you think that maybe
they're interspersed at the north pole you roll up and like every fifth one is kevlar sized and
the rest is just all orlando blooms as far as the eye can see that would make that would be a much
different uh sheen on the children's movies when kids get whisked away magically to the north pole
to santa's factory you imagine opening the door it's just 28 just a 28 year old dude sup hey
you want me to make a toy or what what do you need you just want to hang playstation vita i've got a
block of wood and a hammer that's about the best i can do um those are two tools i have
can i make it something with that maybe maybe they're partners and you need the kevlar owls
to do the little detail the two hickeys okay legolas is do the body work yeah they do like
the the big parts they build the case and then the camera and everyone like every elf is assigned his
buddy elf oh my god and if one dies the other one has to kill themselves exactly it's a life bond
between a big alpha to the north bowl i just also i need you to sign this this death don't
pay attention to the fine print we've had some staffing issues lately the kevlar elves lifespan
is 15 years and the legless is 85 so what i'm saying is i guess live it up i'm santa
how many hr issues that's why he leaves christmas eve is the one night a year santa just can't take
it anymore what is this factory i've set up what have i done with my life i get so many blooms
wasted i get attached to elves that die after 15 years i kill beautiful 28 year old men i've killed
so many legs i gotta get out of the house it's christmas eve the cookies will make me forget
about the terrible system elizabeth town was such a bad movie for him to go out on
that movie was garbage how many hr violations do you think you'd run into
at an all orlando bloom work facility because i would i would discover that magic kingdom i
would just roll and run through just pinching cheeks like that like their cheeks
but then i hit a i hit a kevlar elf and i'd be like snap and i break his neck no
and then you have to kill and then you have to kill the bloom
for balance um and that's elf on the shelf too and that's the plot of elf on the shelf too god
justin i just realized you're not wearing an undershirt either you've got a lot of looks
going on travis you look great too but no uh do you want to read another question
our extended family holiday gatherings are the usual affair
christmas after stuffing ourselves on massive masses of food our sweet nana
has forced an extensive carol sing into a tradition needless to say everyone hates it
but even worse hang in there even worse is the fact that she just sits there refusing to sing
while silently judging our worth as her progeny based on how the third how into the third verse
of good king winseless we are how do we get out of this without poisoning the mashed potatoes
it's a dark turn at the end musically morose in ontario canada okay i didn't realize that was a
method of murder i thought that was like a fun idiom like uh oh i really poisoned the mashed
potatoes this time huh you thought the canadians just had completely different idioms from us
man i'm sorry you guys i tried to get it done on time but i really played my grandma on that one
uh i'm just imagining this like emperor palpatine-esque figure just like sitting on a
throne just like yes yes this pleases me my puppets of flesh really hit the high sea skylar
sing to nana my angels of music angela sing for me
sorry what is this character it's it's the nana i thought that was clear from context
i just wanted to hear you say it's the nana um i want you to own it oh god i don't i'm just
gonna pretend that this isn't an actual thing that happens in the world because it makes me
so uncomfortable thinking about it is it possible wait maybe nana doesn't tell you where she is in
the room and it's like elf on the shelf you have to find your nana and she's spying on you somewhere
watching you sing and you don't know where she's in the cabinet like the baba duke
is your grandma baba duke we didn't even consider the possible duke no
is it possible that that your nana knows how much you all hate it but you all piss her off
so much it's like i i'm old sing the song again did oh oh he stopped it he stopped he stopped
that was good but you have to play it out like a different word that's the game you didgeridoo
okay that's good that's pretty good so hard we should set up a swear jar where if we swear
we have to put fifty thousand dollars into like a savings account and the first one of us that dies
dies gets it no hold on for every one of us that dies you put another fifty thousand in
you don't use money do you guys want to yahoo please uh what do you want do you want to yahoo
okay seamless seamless transition this uh yahoo was asked by oh it was sent in by ira ray uh
sorry what was the name jesus uh it's our first time no fat jesus fat jesus
uh it was sent in by ira ray are you ira ray
excellently delicious pretend i'm your nana sing for me for me my puppets
so does anybody know the wi-fi information for city hall the password is gov rocks
i just typed i'm the mayor on a notepad and i hope that it's my day how about that worked
for me now wi-fi it's my bim bam day i can't tell you who asked it because i don't have internet
access it's asked by name anyone i can't i'm panicking i can't think of a single name right
now steve williams no that's the mayor that's the mayor oh man i can't show my teeny griffin
do you need my what do you need my iphone cable no it's fine i'm just not going to know who asked
it it's an eternal mystery we'll call them we'll add we'll edit it in this okay everybody be super
quiet because we're going to leave some silence here and if we get edited in the name i'll dub
it over we're not going to do this forever yahoo paging mister oh cool great this mystery yahoo
user asked grandma got run over by a reindeer seriously by the way my super smooth transition
went right in the toilet um do you think this song is disrespectful to grandmothers
or just or just a nonsensical song simply meant to make people laugh
why do you think the author chose grandma instead of grandpa or any other person
would you play or sing this song in your grandma's company
in case you've never heard all the lyrics because everyone's always laughing
are they though throughout the entire duration of the number grandma got
okay i can't hear it
is she okay okay i need to know the backstory to enjoy the song show of applause who unironically
has ever laughed at grandma got run over by a reindeer exactly no come on that was even
ironic i heard it like yeah i don't want to leave him hanging sure uh god i think my favorite part
of this question is the idea of it being disrespectful to the nana and that idea of
like it comes on the radio or your playlist you're like oh oh god she's watching you're out of the
wheel it's too late it's too late i don't know why i have my hands like nosferatu there arnani
is not a nosferatu arnani is a lovely woman arnani is here is arnani here she's right there
nani now are you cool with this jam raise your hand if grandma got run over by a reindeer offends
you on a spiritual level no she's cool by the way friends hi it's justin mcroy i'm a third of the
podcast of my brother my brother and me uh if you ever want to really amp up the difficulty
of your life record a podcast for four years where you talk about basically the most horrible
things you can imagine that you can't imagine i think it comes to us from another realm then
do a christmas show in your hometown full of people then drink not a considerable amount
of whiskey backstage then put your nani in the second row best of luck no pressure no pressure
does the grandma die and grandma get run over by a reindeer
is anyone familiar hold on i'll ask and then went through extensive physical therapy
see every bone every bone from this point down was shattered does anybody know the
song better than me is she learned a new lease on life and chose to leave her family she got
another fitness membership and she looks great because she put in the work she's really doing it
and i must say it looks terrific she looks awesome but we miss her we miss her she doesn't
come around now she's always at la fitness i saw you know they were they turned this into a cartoon
i watched because i watch a lot of cartoons now new baby uh and this is you're showing your new
baby a cartoon based on grandma got run over by a reindeer it was does she know about death yet
this is how you're introducing the concept of death she doesn't die we already established
she doesn't die but in this one santa finds yeah santa finds her and she has amnesia
amnesia and he takes her back to the north pole and she becomes mrs claus what take that grandpa
burn what santa stole your girl
santa stole your girl grandpa that's your back old man santa's clumping up on you
part of this job is to gotta treat her right
hey listen that jingle bell behind you always nipping at your heel grandpa
big fat man coming up with a bowl full of jelly gonna steal your girl
it's me look up the chimney i got your woman i i made my reindeers run over i take your girl
she's mine now you never love her i love her you don't know how to treat a woman i'm santa i saw
grandma kissing santa claus and then leaving with him and i never saw her again uh we have
literally just described a big part of this job is she's not like me she's gonna come a lot more
than once a year you know what's up santa look up your chimney i got your girl it's me santa
i'm done a big part of this job ho ho ho is to come up with like allegories and illusions
that's basically the subtitle of the show um this is not one of them
that is literally and exactly the plot of misery
i was gonna say overboard no it's misery it's misery for sure y'all uh that is literally the
bottom mystery was we just did yahoo let's get a general question we're gonna dip in
to well we're gonna have to fix the mic because our dad broke it with his good with his hilarious
goof was it worth it dad i think it was uh but we are gonna have some questions from the audience
just a few uh because you guys are very far away from us and we maybe didn't think about that
beforehand so start thinking about not a bummer holiday themed holiday themed without swearing
i swear to god that's okay we can take the word okay um that if anyone breaks our streak up if
we get a baba booey up here i will lose my mind because we've traveled back in time baba boo is
still a super hot cultural reference justin bring me a hot cue off that list uh we're on the third
one ahem ahem whiskey's catching up with papa for the past five years a friend and i would
exchange gifts for no no it's not funny you goofed on it i meant the real third one with
the star next to it that we use that was our clever code to say these are good questions
did you see the star and you're like wonder what that means oh well how did that get there
uh this face paint is so hot it's like i have 15 extra layers of skin on my face
what you don't know is it's lead based oh great read the question justin right last christmas
um i come from a multi-faith family so we celebrate christmas and hanukkah there's
a name for that it's christmica uh what is the best way to fit candle nights in our
already packed holiday schedule that's from dreidels and donner in dallas i think that
candle nights solves i mean candle night solves a lot of problems just like worldwide but eventually
it will eat both christmas and hanukkah for nourishment and will keep growing and pretty
soon it's going to be the only game in town and if you think he's being figurative then you do
know you don't understand candle the physiology of candle nights the old one that is candle nights
the elder god that is that we have to feed lesser holidays to that's why we appease him to last
another millennium that is why mayor steve williams came up with my brother my brother and me day
it was not to honor us it was to keep him asleep dark unnamed uh uh far far below the mantle of
the earth uh another quick candle night snow as you know candle nights is a pan-religious pansexual
personal pan holiday uh that we made up for ourselves so everybody could have a party together
uh we know we have a lot of christmas imagery on stage that is not no tiny ten was jewish
fair enough fine that's not for lack of trying griffin and i scoured every store in the tri-state
area that was we went to the target we went to the target at mary creek and i tell you it's
ironically for god's chosen people you don't have a lot of selection
that i didn't see a single uh menorah or any sort of hanukkah decoration i should have grabbed it
while i was in cincinnati we were at a cvs and saw a kid this story is about the time you saw a
menorah i'm going to lose it no we saw can you believe it no um where do they get off what no
we saw a kit for a hanukkah house which is a gingerbread house can they not just accept the
icing is blue and white terrific nice try gingerbread house empire wait uh what was the
question how do i make room for candle nights well you come to show first off are you here
well what is going on bad start not a great start to your listeners at home we promise there
are people here some people are here you are not having a hallucination where you see other people
great stuff was it this is not bad you know we're a little drunk but uh uh we hope that
you're enjoying the the show so far sorry to interrupt uh but we want to tell you about a
couple of our sponsors here in the uh the money zone i want to tell you about hulu uh hulu hulu
is the new version of hulu they've just updated sort of their whole with a liquid you with a
liquid and um out that they tossed in there um you've tried hulu well sorry sorry sorry you've
tried hulu um i want to tell you about hulu plus please please if you know hulu plus is a new
swedish form of hulu no it's it's uh it's an expanded hulu plus is an expanded bigger better
version of hulu that has all the current season episodes of a lot of your favorite shows like
modern family the daily show with john stewart modern family modern family sorry and it's got
every episode of south park that's an exclusive to hulu plus you're not gonna see that anywhere
else if you want to stream those this is where you're gonna do it what's great about hulu plus
is it works on all the devices that your mind's eye could possibly conceive of talking about smart
tvs talking about roku's talking about gokus talking about apple tvs talking about snapple
tvs i'm talking about your xbox i'm talking about your gex box gex box the console you use to only
play uh gex gex the platformer from the mid-nineties um uh hulu plus uh will let you watch tv in the
bathroom if there's a stronger advertisement for it i don't know what it is they also have original
programming like east lows high hot wives of orlando uh the awesomes uh quick draw a lot of
really good stuff on there that you won't find anywhere else because hulu made it it's eight
bucks a month uh 7.99 i guess but come on it's eight bucks a month and you're gonna get your
shows anytime anywhere now but but but but but but you're not gonna pay dollars a month at least
not right now you will eventually because you're gonna love it so much but we're gonna give you a
two-week free trial you're gonna go to hulu plus dot com slash my brother and uh you're gonna get
a whole extra week for free yep so do that and never be bored ever again stave off the lonely
times to have a lonely times on holidays with uh and entertain your family you know what i watched
on hulu plus i watched uh elf buddies musical christmas the the uh the new animated version
of elf with jim parsons it was good it was good you know what's best it was on hulu plus you are
covered in barf right now that's baby vomit you know that's my life uh hulu plus dot com slash
my brother i love that jim parsons when he's just like when he's like bazinga bazinga what a talent
now let's say i wanted to tell you that i just watched elf buddies musical christmas but i don't
want anybody to ever know about it just send me an email or maybe a facebook message no no no
everybody's reading those anybody can read those well shoot yeah there's no way to be private and
secure in these times wait hold up twist hold this hold the phone got good news for you cut the phone
wires because that's how they get you there's a new thing it's called sythe it's a next generation
messenger app that lets you take back your privacy c y p h sythe this whole time i've been calling it
sythe you are an idiot yeah it's like the beginning of cypher without the er like seriously right and
sythe sounds like uh i don't know like a shorthand way of well it's candle night so uh sythe was
founded by uh former space x engineers whoa so that's real science they know how to like send
messages to uh to like jupiter and stuff uh so that i'm pretty sure they have terrestrial
communications basically on lockdown at this point sythe is free to use works on desktops
works on tablets works on phones uh and you can securely send photos through through syphons and
messages they got more stuff coming too there's going to be secure voice and video calling
bitcoin integration anonymous syphing via tor uh and uh it's a it's really impressive so you can
start syphing right now i'm i don't know if you want to jar into that but they're making a go of
it so here we are you can start syphing right now at syph.com that's c y p h dot com if you go to
syph.com slash my brother or we've just been alerted syph dot horse that's great that's
fantastic you'll be bumped to the top of the invite list for early access of the next version
of syph syph lock your stuff down because they are happy candle nights i want you all to have
a wonderful holiday season they're coming for you and everything that you have syph it syph it lock
it right up i've got a message for noah from bail bonds bail bonds that's barry bonds little brother
bail bail yes i am bail will i play the baseball too no bail bail you can you have no arms you have
no skin you have no skin you have skin bail the baseball would hurt you terribly what's the message
the message for noah from bail bonds uh is happy we haven't planned a wedding in a year day
happy candle nights happy 30th birthday you're the only person i'm always happy to be around
thanks for loving me and i'll do the same p.s there's a gift hidden in the house that starts
with that's w h and ends in isky so isky uh find it love bailey oh that's very sweet i got a message
for laura clues from michael and jeff uh the message is happiest of birthdays lou from your
adoring doring brothers and i think this is just put in this like to raise the difficulty curve on
us from your adoring brother m oose it's m apostrophe c o o s e m oose i think and your dearest
gwegofui gwegofui gwegofui is what brings us together today uh happy happy happy birthday lou
laura clues whatever you want to go by clue dog and happy everything to noah no you got sort of
a scattershot approach to well wishes there yeah just sort of just sort of threw the well
wished spaghetti at the wall it's all what stuck and you know what everything stuck you just wasted
a bunch of spaghetti i hope you had a great uh birthday lou and uh thanks to michael and jeff
for purchasing the message if you want to get a message like this go to maximumfun.org forge slash
jumbotron and you can set that up there's a little bit of a backlog so if you want one in the next
few months you should hurry over and do that okay so we're going to go back to the show one note
about the section you're about to hear uh during it uh as you're listening to it please imagine
our dad dressed as santa claus sneaking on stage to put a note in a boot and none of us noticing
and none of us noticing uh and just know that that is happening during the next bit
so you won't be completely lost and a happy candlelight if we don't if i don't see you again
a good morning good afternoon happy candlelight happy candlelight everybody is a joke from that
movie what was it happy truman show happy truman show to you and all your kin how about
how about i read another question let me go to her i well i have something to say really quick
um i have an apology uh to make usually at this point in the show i would do a sad limb
but but don't encourage him there's nothing funny about it whatsoever we have sustained
the elder gods to a point where we can manifest our own will in the material plane so because
of that power we have eradicated it from existence you're welcome everybody but i want to apologize
because in the holiday hustle and bustle i ran out of time we'll edit this out right
yeah yes sure okay and i apologize because i did not write one
uh really yeah i just wanted to let you know now we may move on you know that we had like a super
long time to prep stuff uh and you could have done it during the time where we were upstairs
eating subway you could have like sat down how much time goes into creating a sad lib
like four minutes four minutes i saw it yeah yeah i've seen it before i did not have
that one's unplugged so i don't know what's going on that one's inflated
wait hold on and that one's riding a sweet jet ski god if you're not here guys you're just not
gonna get a lot of this stuff that's going on travis what are you doing it looks like there's
something in the stocking it looks like there's something in the stocking you say oh thank you
you're doing the lord's work out there wait it says here that you guys helped with this a little
bit we did marry merry candle nights uh fun game for the audience listen and see if you can pick
out what's words justin and i submitted to this horrible horrible bit that has never worked 231
episodes go for travis towards the shunt before candle nights went all through the gulp not a
corn maze was spelunking not even a bum the dumpos were hung by the commode with nougat
in the hopes that corn cob boy soon would be chavis you're gonna have to slow slow down for
laughter okay so you gotta pause for applause baby the dirigibles were nestled all snug in
their butt kiss i get it while visions of quasi moto dance in their butts that was a good one
emma mon her buttress and i in my front butt are you guys eight had just settled
i just settled our belch for a long winter squeegee went out on the flugelhorn there
arose such a jack and ape i sprang from my jello to see what was the matter away to the
embryo i flew like a skeet to robin the chattanoogan and threw open the mcluster
when what's my wondering razzle dazzle did appear but a miniature griffin an eight tiny georgeman
with a little old one huh with a little old wormy so lively and quick
i knew in a moment he must be saint moist
stop it now zebra now humdrum now astral on chrysanthemum on reiterate on capitulate
how much should we charge for tickets do you remember too much he was dressed all in pumpernickel
from his head to his foot and his pianist were all tarnished with ashes ashes and soot
his farts how they twinkled oh my god his teflon how merry his cheeks were like constantinople
oh his nose like a scrumdiddlyumptious he was chubby and plump a right jolly old smackdown
and i puked when i saw him in spite of myself and i and laying his molly
is it the whole thing and laying his molly molly coddle aside of his front butt
from but twice good work job ward smiths and giving in i'm so sorry up the dead travis he rose
but i heard him exclaim erie drove out of sight
merry candlelight to all and to all a good worst thing that happens in the podcast
thank you all thank you all for sitting through the last sad libs ever and now it's canonical
how long have you been going like three years a lot of people do the this isn't funny but
we're doing it anyway but not a lot of people have the strength of will to commit
to really not making it funny we're not it's not a goof it's really not in any way entertaining
griffin and i are joking for the poetry yeah you yeah uh maybe if we do a few
more huntington live shows they'll name you like poet laureate of huntington west virginia
uh i got a yadru for everybody if you're into that
yeah this yadru mystery nights was sent in by drew davenport thank you level 8000
yadru shaman drew davenport it's asked by yahoo answers i forgot i can't see
that data because i am not connected to the website
it's just craig question mark craig craig craig asked if you gave people your greatest gift
what would that be i just did no
oh you better hope you didn't it's all i've got
my best gift then in that in that context would be a a sharp editor's eye a keen eye on the uh
the old audacity track uh god my greatest gift that's my greatest gift i would probably make
them french toast i'm pretty baller at that you make a nice french toast i would say probably
tender kisses anything special about them or just like that's all over
my greatest gift would be for me to film travis giving you the kisses because you want to you
want to remember it goes by so quickly i mean it takes 14 minutes but it seems like i would upload
them into iMovie i would use that one that looks like a map opening up and i would put some music
underneath it something real nice some five for fighting some superman by five for friends
that's what we need to kiss them for three minutes and five seconds which is the runtime
of superman by five for fighting and i'll tell you all someday why i know that information well
it's gonna work because when i kiss people um i do it like one might apply um uh glue stick
and i see their own body who does that i push on and then maintain the same pressure and then
just you maintain contact around like a slug it feels like a slug it's like that clean your
fish thing for you right remora remora i believe is what those are called you're a doctor fish is
what you're saying did you just point to your wife like tell them about the great kisses i give you
you want to come on stage and talk about my precious kisses five out of five would kiss again
yeah okay well can i uh can i get sidebar real quick super quick sidebar sure uh i know the bit
that we talked about was that we wouldn't see scanner santa when he came out to put the thing
in the booth oh okay listen listen i accidentally looked to the left because i was like where is he
and because i thought he wasn't out yet and i saw him and it scared the hell out of me
i you may have noticed a moment where i seem suddenly terrified for an instant imagine you're
just like doing your podcast here and then you adjust like pan left and there's a santa who's
just been there the whole time it was really really scary can i ask you a question i'm still
trying to get over it can i ask you a question hit me have you seen sydney since we started
no she's been spirited away to the north pole you've lost her forever
oh he stole my girl he can treat her better than you can it's just the truth he's got all
the orlando blooms she's got she's gonna be swimming in blooms that is tough
uh do another question well should we take question from the let's do a few more because
we got a bunch of oh okay well let's say this we're gonna do one more prepped question and
then we're gonna do an audience question have one ready and be ready to hustle because you've got
to make it you literally need to run don't no don't like stamp don't rush up here just raise
a hand we'll point in a direction but seriously you better come correct oh i'd be scared he's
making a list and he's stealing your wife i am in charge of making i am in charge of making
desserts this year for the candlelight celebration i love baking but i'm worried i might go a bit
overboard so i just like to know how many cookies are too much that's from countless
cookies in california oh god too many cookies what cultural references topical humor he's got
it all four cookie the answer is four cookies four per person check your heloese check your
betty crocker that's the formula that's gonna eat four you only want two um then somebody else has
to eat six i guess i'm not a scientist it's a one cookie and one cookie out policy the uh the
dessert i made two desserts before the boys came in i made uh chocolate uh uh peppermint popcorn
mm-hmm what sydney and i did after charlie went to bed and we also can be funny at any point are
you just sort of bragging about your i thought we were done with the funny parts uh did a cornflake
wreath uh and i was curious just this is fact fine this is not for jokes um did anybody make
cornflake wreaths when they were in their area is that a regional thing or is it just a west
virginian thing he used to applaud you can't ask like a bra you have to do yes or no applaud yeah
did you what area are you from i kind of made them okay we'll go state by state alaska i ate
a no upper montana upper montana no i ate a regular wreath once
i was high i don't know who this character is
mr bad claps he's a weird ghost drunk he's drunk ghost baby
i don't know hands together i don't know uh a lot of this is going to be contingent on
your bank of cookie points a lot of people don't save those up for the holidays but you gots to
because it's it's like the best time to trade them in a lot of people what's up griffin smacked a
cookie out of my hand in my own home because i was actually watching him eat chocolate peppermint
popcorn go like trying to do the cookie math in my head like that was a big chocolate chunk so i'm
going to say maybe 14 cookie points for that it was hard it was very flying by the sea we got
lunch uh you know and now food stories we were prepping for the show apparently there's a new
restaurant in huntington called cookout cookout and i what's up huntington all my homies from
cookout here we got lunch for six people it was 31 dollars thanks cookout you did it i have not
had vegetables in like three days because we've been traveling and i said could i just get like
some vegetables and there's all those onion rings so i had a hamburger with extra lettuce and tomato
so it's like a salad on my burger it's a salad sandwich uh should we get some folks up here
yeah yeah who wants to ask us a good question and do a good job right there right there
pointing ready no but behind behind right there yes yes you yes you come on up a nice cold burn
you guys can pick next okay uh what are we gonna do fill it everybody a big hand round of applause
that way yeah we're them go to where the flamingo is between the waterslay santa and the lit up
flamingo don't screw this up don't blow it don't blow don't screw this up though no pressure all
right so lots of friends lots of family getting together louder louder please or hulu plus thing
don't know how to pick it spend an hour looking how do i eliminate that problem
how did you are you looking for some hot flicks recommendations right now
i'm looking for a method to pick a netflix or hulu thing without wasting everybody's time okay
that's a thing called the cue yeah just have your cue loaded up with all your latest latest and
greatest uh uh uh picks sometimes you know you can misjudge the netflix pic sometimes you think you
want to watch uh that russian documentary about models that are really put through the ringer
and you get about halfway through and you think i didn't want to watch them really in the holidays
i has a lot of fans you know what grandma and auntie helen will love the one about the russian
models who've been put through the ringer has anybody has anybody ever gotten so frustrated
with the like the pressure that this i'm sorry i didn't catch your name sir uh jeff jeff hi jeff
that's a great name has anybody ever gotten um uh so so bogged down by the pressure that jeffrey
is describing that uh you say to yourself jeffrey i'm done i'm not gonna pick a movie
i'm just gonna play literally the first like whatever is on screen the time and leave the
room secrets of nim enjoy secrets of nim i'm out uh jeffrey out this is a true story enjoy this
judgy this is a true story jeffrey don't do this jeffrey jeffrey i i was it was christmas eve i
want to say like three years ago uh and i was by myself at uh your guy's old place uh the one that
the tree destroyed and uh it was christmas eve by myself doing laundry in your house by myself
turn on the tv and what was on the tv it was a documentary that i thought i want to watch this
it's christmas eve was dear zachary yeah that one's a slam dunk santa popped down the chimney
like oh ho oh no no they did what to the kid no so jeffrey uh we don't have an answer for you but
take comfort in the fact that no matter how bad you do it won't be worse than griffin yeah i do
have an answer for you here it is you gotta throw it out to the room and not take all that pressure
on yourself yeah because that's the problem you get like whatever the controller is in your hand
and you feel like it all rests on you and it's okay to say what do you want to watch what do you
want to watch tough guy or just turn off turn off the video on demand services turn on tv
this is always something on although everybody here first of all thanks for being here second
of all be watching rudolph nope right now and you're welcome you could be watching jingle all
the way to on abc family we have protected almost 600 people viral payload you're the only safe
people left in the world it's just us now the doors are sealed we love those we have to repopulate
we're gonna start a new society everybody start making love because nothing puts hey
nothing put dirty words there will be adult situations it's whoopee time because nothing
puts people the mood better than a fat jesus telling them to make love and jeff good job
man you're done did it crushed it let's get somebody from them maybe oh yeah wait wait
you pick griffin well no this person's already moving in yes do it finish yes come on come on
down come on it's a great coat i sneezed earlier and i wiped my nose and i had this paint on and i
forgot to put it on i almost walked out without reapplying and it looked like i had done reverse
cocaine hey what's your name hey uh ben thurston from richmond virginia what's up richmond richmond
crowd no okay what's up for the past year or two i've been involved involved i don't know exactly
how to say it i've been riding you're doing great so far hang in there i can't hear you it's fine
okay with moped clubs oh sweet which uh essentially are a motorcycle club light so
motorcycle club is basically motorcycle gang i'm familiar with okay when a moped was yeah
it's basically like a motorcycle with pedals how is the club going like please finish your
question we're haranguing um a lot of my friends who are not involved with the moped community just
don't get it exactly they're called more pedestrians that was all right how dare you
uh and you're asking well is should i listen to what they say never no is that was that it because
no listen what i'm sorry i didn't catch your name what's your name sir uh ben thurston
bit just ben is fine ben yeah we're not getting married ben we're just doing a podcast
ben when you feel the wind rushing through your hair at 15 miles an hour
do you think when you're getting somewhere moderately faster than logging
when you see when you see a recovering grandma uh jogging past you do you think that their
their jives their jabs are gonna their japes are gonna penetrate your psyche they're not
you're gonna be thinking about one thing one thing only and that is freedom do you know
ben real talk if i may ignore everyone else who okay can i use the bathroom yeah here's the deal
ben what that is is you found a thing that makes you happy and that you enjoy and for whatever
reason there are people in your life that look at something that you to take unashamed happiness in
and they don't feel that and so they mock it and they won't accept the fact that you are
third like you are unironically unashamed of how much you love do you ironically ride the moped
now you interrupted me a few times so well tough buddy hey it's my bim bam day it's how dare you
i'll interrupt whoever i want if the president walked in and be like hold up wait i got a butt
joke to make well okay keep going we were getting serious for a second it's not mockery it's it's a
serious um they're worried about you yeah he's too he's too real we lost him uh uh is it dangerous
i saw a tom wolf novel in his back pocket the other day he's too far gone we'll never get him
back i'm going to shift to the other side of i also think it's possible to begin to love something
too much and that becomes like your defining feature are you moped dude you're not wearing
moped attire i don't think you do have a hole in your jeans is that from a wicked accident
you just spin out on 60 going 15 every time anything gets brought up you somehow compare
it to mopeds and you're like oh yeah who wants to go on dinner speaking of going out
have you guys ever gone out on a moped i think mopeds mopeds are rad i think they are fuel
efficient how what do you get what do you get with your ride i've never i've never and i actually
don't have a scooter there's a difference gosh you're the freest person i've ever met
uh i think you are living so right and if anybody gives you trouble you call me here's my number
he's a creepy ghost i'm a creepy ghost i will haunt them i'll float around are you ever worried
that the people in moped club will know that really you just ride a scooter and they'll find
you out no because he would go much much much much much much faster than them way way super
fast and he would get there like surprise the spring chicken they'd be like our legs are tired
because we've been pedaling our motorcycles um i don't think you know what a moment but don't let
us get you down you're living so right and i'll beat up anybody who says differently
griffin mackerel guarantee big hand applause for ben everybody
you know the um good news is about ben's club is no matter how that goes it can't be worse
than the scooter club my friend jason elders tried to start in college my friend jason tried
to start a scooter club and it was late and he decided we were gonna start a scooter club
uh that scooter club total got up to one and it was jason and eventually jason's scooter got
repossessed and he's such a nice guy he helped the nice man loaded his scooter into the truck
as it got repossessed i also don't think i should have you're right i made a bad adult decision
you're right i'm a great take this from me i can't be trusted i was jason here jason are you here
no somebody jason is here he told me he's here
one time i watched justin wreck on jason's scooter going negative four miles an hour
while he was screaming the night writer theme song it was the funniest thing i've ever seen
the funniest thing i've ever seen in my entire life i wish everyone in the universe had been
there to share in that magic moment with me uh should we get another let's get someone on this
in this i saw no that person what yes yeah the one who just pointed to your head wait what i
can't tell right there right there right there okay no you ma'am yes yes yes come on up sorry
a lot of false flags there sorry everybody fill the silence fill it i've been doing shows in
this theater since i was 10 years old you know my first one was
i couldn't remember i was hoping she'd be up okay cool good segue hi what's your name
hi my name is jamie hi jamie hi jamie welcome to the podcast thank you um i have a question
about christmas eve okay sorry i'm ahead of breath don't recognize it as a holiday but go ahead
but i do like the preface i think that's night 16 of candle nights is yeah so i have a question
about the 16th of candle nights yeah where do you find all the sheep let her ask her question
sorry go ahead with your question so i'm jewish and my fiance is christian and so uh his family
we live far away from his family so sometimes for the 16th the sheep night of candle night right
yeah if you say the sheep night well right okay sometimes for the sheep night we would go visit
his family but this year we're not so we're just by ourselves him a sort of christmas person and
me not a christmas person i have a great documentary you could watch that night if
a kid dies sorry if you haven't seen it a kid dies it sucks go on so we don't really have any
big plans for the holiday um we're gonna do presents on the 17th okay um oh okay i forgot
the bit we were doing yeah so we're gonna christmas day we're gonna do some christmasy
stuff we don't have plans for christmas eve and another non-jewish friend of mine invited us to
no a jewish friend of mine non-christian i'm gonna take notes okay griffin your notes are
the scribblings of a crazy person we they're all adventure zone notes it's like it's like
train robbery goblins sure why not please finish your question we are the rudest human beings on
the planet but it is my bim bam day so what's up so we don't have christmas eve plans we were
invited to like a sort of christmas orphan non like for the jews and muslims sure yeah
um the question is so he's got like a nostalgic attachment to christmas eve but we don't have
christmas eve family plans you don't have the trappings exactly okay so should we go to this
non-christmassy party for folks who aren't visiting their family or should we spend
christmas eve just the two of us and our cats how many cats are they cool oh two yeah no they're
super cool okay well that's a horse of different color which is ironic because that was the line
that justin said is lord growly oh my god you're right wizard of oz anyway to answer the question
that the person directly in front of us just asked uh oof um man that's gonna be hard because
your your your boyfriend is gonna roll up like time to knit a stocking for everyone
because that's what i've done my whole time on this planet is your boyfriend here
yeah he's over there so hey hey uh here's what you guys have got and it's it's it's a really
great opportunity to now just do whatever you want and then let it shake out what becomes a
new tradition right you can really like wheat and chaff this and say like we're gonna do these ten
things i liked four of them we'll keep those four and the other six we don't have to deal with that's
a problem how many traditions do you think have been started by people doing something once and
they hated it but no one wanted to admit it to anybody else they've been doing it for 10 years
and then the next year they're like we need to sing in front of nana again right we gotta sing
in front of nana i guess are we gonna have time for our annual dear zachary they're going they're
not gonna sing in front of me again oh god they're so bad so bad i don't even want to sing with them
uh yeah i mean you guys can make your own traditions now and that's a very special
process but i totally get wanting to that was my leaking i'm about to disagree that's my noise
i'm about to disagree i think it's better to be with a bunch of people to be fun oh yeah yeah no
i'm not saying to be alone i'm saying make the traditions with other people boyfriend
and your official title boyfriend thing you craig craig you can enforce your traditions
because wow you're really putting craig on blast right now i love you but if you what did craig
do to deserve this listen here you jerk word and that's the best i could do but in all honestly
like if you try to recreate those traditions like you can do them but you can't expect
the same results as it was when you were i don't know i don't know what went travis transitioned
like guy at 2 a.m and you're both really drunk and he's like no no you listen to me sit down
it's my turn laid back in the bean bag it's mbnbm okay all i'm saying is that it's the
expectation game of you can roll up and do your tradition and relive that experience but it's with
a new set of people in new variables and it will be different and inherently the tradition will
alter because you have new people is the tradition could there be a tradition that you're maintaining
that's something awesome already like oh my whole life on christmas eve i get turnt i get turnt
let's go to a party it's like what do you do craig what's his name can you just tanner tanner
okay i'm gonna stick with craig stick with craig um what do you do what do you do craig he's like oh
i get oh i get totally totally turnt and they're like yeah sure and then you all do it together
that's how traditions get born this year for thanksgiving i went and hung out we went i just
crushed it with the this is how traditions are born that was great we went to an orphan
thanksgiving thing and uh my new friend where is everybody find all these orphans my new friend
we sam came downstairs and he goes so uh before dinner do you guys want to shoot bow and arrow
and the answer is yes yeah always so we went in the back of their apartment complex well not
there shot a bow and arrow into a cardboard box that's because we're adults yeah that's sweet
do stuff like that you'll be fine yeah okay thank you i believe in you thanks joey
what do you think every year my family gets together to decorate the tree
we all eat cookies and stuff it's great there's just one problem you know what i'm gonna read
a question no there's just one problem i hate decorating the tree i'm bad at it
but my parents insist i help this year i tried to hang out in the same room reading
a book while they decorated hiding from christmas they were not having it and forced me to help
am i a bad person for not enjoying this part of christmas yes am i required to help yes that's
from decorating dingus in minnesota can i uh sorry just to break the flow of the show can
we turn the house lights off because i can see everyone and it's giving me the yips
give me a turn off those lights please please sweet jesus people disappear i'll do it there
they go there they go it's just us again goodbye uh back in the bubble how how how is anyone bad
at decorating a christmas tree it's litter are you putting everything decoration up and it's
six inches away from the tree and they just drop it on the ground they're putting everything on
one branch it's like a beautiful christmas horn steve you just put them in your beard again aw
steve you ate the popcorn garland and then you just kept eating ornaments right off the tree
like some sort of giraffe also i want to say this i love that you said okay i'm bad at it i don't
like it so this year i hung out in the same room thumbs up and read a book thumbs down was the book
how to be good at basic human tasks like putting baubles on branches could you at least watch the
baubles being put on the branch say good job you see it you see it good job good good bubble
placement nana here's the learning curve for baubles on branches once one time and you got
the logistics of it down you hung them on the wrong tree you went next door you broke into
the house next door and put it on their tree how are you so bad at this why are you a cat
that's been transformed into a human today you've knocked them all off that's the opposite of what
we wanted it's a pretty funny podcast i'm just watching it over here and it's pretty funny we
do a pretty good let me try one hold on could you crush up all ornaments and throw them in the chimney
the kid does this best i don't know what to tell you
justin did a great thing with his face uh but we need we need subtitles i really like the idea of
like a christmas tradition where it's all about um we're done talking about christmas tradition
so that was the last one we're on this idea of like we do it all together yeah it's a family
thing but only five of us are good at it right susan another great year banner year great year
susan stephen killed it debra i'm touched brad brad just spray painted the tree brad
with spray paint brad solid d minus better than last year you threw it at the window and she
stood up the window on it brad you got trapped in the tree you got stuck in the tree you're stuck in
the tree get out of there oh brad are we done are we done yet yeah it's uh it's been uh it's been
about you guys want another one are you done you spent all right last one i've always last one
that's the closest we get to to ongoing yeah what what it's starting to seem like we shouldn't do
another one gang griffin oh well yahoo if you got one you guys want to yahoo a regular question
cool that was not good planning on my part i'm sorry so who makes cornflake wreaths
it's shout out your home state uh oh god this is really hard this one you think yeah all
right this one was sent in by rachel spurling recognize that game everybody take a moment
a moment a moment of silent reflection and appreciation of the game there it is rachel
spurling thank you uh it's asked by yahoo ants oh did it again it's i can't read it no internet
uh this is what it was like in olden times
uh marshall asks marshall lynch marshall lynch asks how do i come up with my own punching combos
i'm sick of using other people's i thought like holiday you drink punch
so we i don't know wait griffin i'm gonna veto give me another one give me a different one
a different yahoo yeah give me a different one you got a lot give me another one you just don't
want this one i'm so interested throw it back it's a little too small about that isn't sick
of punching combo i had a whole bunch of zangief goofs i was really waiting to bust out but i guess
i'll pocket those for the next time i can talk about zangief which will be never thanks for
the great christmas justin my the paint wore off my face i'm white with shock right now that you
could be so inconsiderate they're all terrible comparatively but okay what about that clothing
store give me that yeah sure this one was sent in by shelby lorman i don't have a fun thing for you
shelby uh justin killed all griffin's fun uh it's in uh local businesses other local businesses
is pretty good categorizing yahoo uh this mystery user uh asked good names for teen clothing store
now the question's not that good but i bet are there answers there are so many great answers
thank you for asking justin okay what does yahoo answers think she should call our teen
clothing store and keep in mind real people thought these were real good uh john keep in
mind double someone sat at a computer is like what am i gonna do today let me see tip tap tip
tap fashion writer was the first one that's writer rid er and that's a pretty sick name for uh i am
the fashion writer uh agent x said the shack okay okay well not specific lady thunder or
lady thunder is that what it sounds like with a space and without a space is that what that was
lady thunder uh western sahara what what you know how teens they like clothes and dry places
sure right they don't want steve zahn movies he was in sahara and that's your steve zahn fact
of the day if this is your first time tuning in welcome to steve zahn day here desert gems
did i miss like what's a good name for my teen fashion store and also sand
young and fun how about young or fun oh sure i'm super old your clothes
don't work for me but watch me juggle uh american teen come on uh american teen again
by a different person two different people somebody read the first time that's good i'm
taking that i just wanted to feel like i'm also contributing that's way better than what i had
american samuel said fashionable for teens so that's a very specific type of clothing
for people who have been alive 14 years and nobody else jerry says american teen
jerry postal piece says american teen guys read it read it above it's just above are we missing
are we not tapping into the zeitgeist here it sounds like the people are ready for a teen
clothing store called american teen there'll be like 13 000 yahoo answers used or she'd be like
hey boy just a gosh darn second that was my title copyright me nihar says dream world
uh whoa what about cool world muck muck lacer says rag day
it's not rad threads with a z uh that's all the good ones what are teens what about this
yeah travis's travis's teen queen boutique travis's uh inconvenient alibi
for kids what would you what would you what would you have at travis's i'm assuming you
are the owner and proprietor of you're the titular travis i am just lead investor
okay i've been looking to brand yeah i'll give you the front money one thing uh
i don't know what teens are into there's more pages but sadly no one will ever know them yes
please spooky nerds yeah okay cool i can sell this for 89 a slight mark up on the price i paid for it
god i hope this goof was worth 85 to everyone here and not the people listening because they
can't see my awesome nightie and floral bonnet new kids on the block don't my little pony not
close cereal that yes cereal but got you so if i can combine those five things yeah in a one look
look that's travis's that's lowercase t because it's trending oh yeah it's open for a half hour
a day i'm looking for investors there's no payphone outside don't bother looking
and the show's over that's the end that seemed like a bring it in for a podcast um welcome to
the series finale of season one my brother my brother a 231 episode first season no one else
has it's an arc do you see no one else has the guts to do it but we did um okay so thank
create it to do to close it out we've come on griffin's literally falling up
apart uh oh god is it almost midnight my ectoplasm i guess most notably thank you all
for being here oh my god hunted city hall auditorium uh uh there are people who got on
a plane to come to this regretting it did anybody come more than 100 miles just raise your hand
um okay anybody cut more than 200 this is the worst more than 300 400 500 i know there are
people here from switzerland are you here switzerland they didn't make it okay i was
gonna say switzerland well there we go hey buy that's a dream that's bananas i'd ask if anybody
came from further than switzerland but there is no place further than switzerland read a book
because it's a made-up country it's uh so thank you all for coming thank you to our nani for
being here and everybody else who we know but mostly our nani our nani mainly for being here
hi nani uh thank you to everybody for coming thank you to mayor steve williams mayor steve
williams give it up thank you city hall staff thank you city of huntington thank you chase
the gorilla foot productions thank you everybody who volunteered there's so many people so many
volunteers thank you our daddy uh he's on the adventure zone with us this is another podcast
listen to it teresa and rachel thank you thank you the billions corporation josh there are ages
thank you michael sullivan for running our tech he does another podcast called slightly more pants
i hope they come back and start listening to that again uh thank you the maximum fun network
thank you to saw bones uh marital tour misguided medicine uh and uh thank you to all of you
for coming um to close out the show if you've never listened uh every time we have griffin
give us one last yahoo answer it's something to uh to grow on to think about to dream about
to live in a live in absorb to stand in to stand stand in your truth and uh i wanna i wanna hear
that last one right now griffin okay it was sent in by nick key thank you nick can't tell you who
asked it i'm sorry everybody we uh santa claus asks oh cool uh is it wrong to have a fetish for
gingerbread man i'm justin mcroy i'm travis i'm giving mcroy it's been my brother my brother and
me kiss your dad square on the lips how much fun it's gonna be oh my god
she's walking
hi and this christmas thank you very special christmas for me