The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
acquaintance be forgot and never forget them your friends and you are ready for
one silver and one gold keep going what you say your name was again
and welcome to the very new new year's episode we're killing it we're killing that big marshmallow
he's dying every year we instead of dropping a ball on new york city that seems violent we eat
a giant marshmallow i was i was thinking ghostbusters it was a ghostbusters good don't
they know they sing your love keeps lifting me higher right i got i got your love keeps
listening me higher and all blank side makes something what does all links not even mean
and like the actual phrase or the song the the phrase it means like days days gone by
or something like that no that's stupid well i mean it is what it doesn't sound right it
might be stupid but it is what it it is like when you know when you have like really old langs
yeah and you and you put up a sign because you want to sell all of your old langs before the
end of the year what's your guys favorite new year's eve tradition i like the the tradition
where we all talk like old-timey prospectors every 20th i like the tradition where we all eat them
little wieners wrapped in bacon yeah that's a good one that's a good one is that a trick
are there new year's traditions i don't know of any that's a thing my mother-in-law tries to get
us to eat cabbage every year but i don't know if that's a tradition can you talk to her about that
tradition what if we start what if we started the tradition where like in the last minute
like in the countdown of seconds you blurted out to one of your loved ones a terrible thing you
did to them that they didn't know about in 2012 but as soon as it turns over to 2013 they're not
allowed to get mad at you i love that double jeopardy like get it in right at the end of the
year yeah a little like 10 nine eight i kissed your sister six five what three two one clear
how about how about we take it one step further and any crimes you do in the last minute of the
year you cannot be you cannot be punished that sounds like something the joker could exploit
um that's worrying to me like that fucking ruins all our everything there's no trust there it's
the thing uh this is my brother my brother meets an advice show for the margin era uh we are saying
i mean we're saying goodbye to 20 does i oh god i'm not ready i know did you guys done get it did
you get it did you think i'm not asking you got it i know you guys got it but like did everybody get
it in 20 does i've been seeing a lot of reports of getting it please tell us in like an overwhelming
uh uh uh it's a wonderful lifestyle display of the effect we found in your lives just start
just start tweeting at us all the ways that you got it in 20 does i've seen so many twitter status
updates telling me how how much people have gotten it and we're not talking small potatoes or small
fries or little fish in a big pond we are talking about big fit big fish in a big in a big pond i
don't want to talk about anymore it's it's got so you're saying they reached in use the bait of
positivity hope optimism and they put those fish into that barrel right and then they shot it
they shot the fish no they shot the barrel no you i think you open the barrel and put the
pickles in it first and then you put the fish in to eat the pickles and then you shoot the
barrel to release the fish it back in a little while the horse swallows the barrel uh-huh i
don't know why she swallowed the barrel perhaps she'll die listen we're better at advice than
idioms but here's the weird thing only barely so here we go my girlfriend and i recently
purchased a delicious chocolate bars during a trip abroad to give it to gives us friends
unfortunately while i'm packing our dog found the bag with the chocolate and started chewing on it
we were lucky enough to stop before marmaduke he thinks these people he thinks these people he
could tear open any of the wrappers but many of them now have visible bite marks since then my
girlfriend and i have been arguing about whether or not it's appropriate to still give these as
gifts i opened one to see if they're okay and it had a pattern of a dent that very clearly showed
that some small animal had been chewing on it since the wrappers are mostly intact she thinks
it's okay to give and pretend to be surprised or something so the bite marks i feel guilty and
think we should throw them away and buy some new last minute gifts who is right how would you feel
if you got one as a gift that's from confectionery conundrum man a lot a nice easy one no joke i
would fucking cut all ties with you if you gave me some food some food stuff that looked like you've
been gnawed on by a raccoon what are you talking about when your friend goes are these bite marks
and you go what no just that's how french people do it no it's that fancy bite mark candy have you
not read about that have you not heard about this they have been gnawed on by small animals but
they're parisian raccoons the parisian raccoons eat nothing but mint leaves for a month and it
infuses the flavor into the chocolate you wouldn't get it you wouldn't get it in mainland you know
what just give it back to me i'll pretend to eat it your only option is like to just be straight
up honest and be like hey there's gonna be some bite marks on this don't worry my dog didn't get
through the wrapper but like then you need to follow that up with and i also got you some other
stuff too is that very whack is that good enough travis would you eat if somebody gave you that
guarantee if somebody gave you that 100 no dog spit on this guarantee but yes those are what his
teeth look like listen would you still party down i'm not gonna answer one way or the other yet
because i want to throw out another factor these aren't just like snickers that they picked up at
cvs like this is some interesting foreign candy i presume i don't give a fuck if it's caviar made
out of faberge eggs that i could sell on ebay this has got dog mouth marks on it griffin can
you stop what i'm saying is there's a level above it can you please stop interrupting travis so he
could admit to us that he would eat dog candy no no what i'm saying is when you get part of
it is like you know if it's in a fourth the wrapper is in a foreign language you display
it somewhere for a while until it becomes gross and you throw it away travis say the words hey
did you see this chocolate i look at this chocolate i have come into my den it's not american that's
why i'm showing it off is because it's not american i have i have chewed on foreign candy to show you
you i'm never going to your house again really hateful what no i just want you to say that you
would eat the dog candy i would not eat the dog can i have some standards you would just display
it prominently in my house like uh hot dogs that have spaghetti in them no i don't know that's
super gross the two things i will not eat skyline hot dogs and chewed on dog candy can i say i know
that this is perhaps like the wrong time to express this this like christmas just having
passed us by and all but pretty much with every thing time someone gives me something they're
basically telling me they're telling me i have to find someplace to put it like the best gift you
can give me is not to have the pressure of eating something or storing something so this is a good
then this is a great gift by your metric because they know exactly where to put it which is to say
the garbage put it right in the put it right in the garbage can i wanted to bring this to buy to
prove that i got you something but i'm not going to let you eat it because it has it's clearly been
chewed on but i want you to share this funny anecdote uh even though i'm not going to let
you eat this dog candy i got you a gift that almost killed my dog so that's like the ultimate
sacrifice that's basically what gift of the magi was all about oh what if you said that like their
dog tested a mother approved my dog seemed to really like these maybe yours will too
take this and kill your dog merry christmas it's dog chocolate i think how did you not see this
coming how could you leave foreign the two things dogs love to eat more than anything else are
chocolate and irreplaceable things right there's their two favorite snacks and you somehow combine
the two into a chocolate bar that you cannot easily obtain here in america and you knew your
dog was a gastronomical risk taker you knew that you knew he likes to dance on the racer's edge
is this is this sea salt i'll give it a whirl it's a little unconventional is there any dog that's
not i think if you eat poop more than once you are a gastronomical risk taker how about a how
about a yahoo answer oh long story short you need to go get some new presents you go get some new
anything this is my dog andrew zimmern um this yahoo answer was sent in by ira ray thanks ira
it's by yahoo answer user crystal s crystal s who asks what are some simple ideas for family circus
act i am looking for billy and jeffy together well i am looking for ideas for my family there
are my parents me 21 and three sisters 16 11 and 8 we have our family reunion party next weekend
and it's circus themed so we need a simple circus act that we can do it can be funny or something
really cool but simple and cheap is what we want if you have any ideas please let me know
now you can make a family circus joke now you're allowed but let it percolate for a bit you don't
just have to fire it off prematurely give it time to ruminate why don't why don't you here here's
what i'm going to suggest why don't you save the family circus joke put it in like the back third
of your brain while we're doing this bit and then at the end of the bit just like drop it on us but
don't just say the names of people in family circus oh there was going to be a whole thing
about following footprints and like who did it not me like some really specific deep cuts the
problem with comedy is that it and dubstep versus dubstep is that it doesn't have a drop is this
from your this from your thesis comedy this doesn't have a drop now what travis has provided
us is the opportunity for a drop like people are going to feel the comedy drop of the family
circus gag coming and then he's and then when they least or most expect it he's going to drop it on
them oh god i can't i can't fucking wait for out of nowhere just bill keene bill keene is the
creator so i i think if you're choosing between funny or really cool i think we're definitely
going in the first camp this is a family circus idea of a nice ever okay has anyone ever watched
their friends or family perform any kind of act and thought man that's so cool like you're not
going to be able to pull that one off if you've been working on something for years outliers
then i think that you that maybe if you have like a hidden skill you've been practicing but like
don't just try to pick up the fushigi out of nowhere yeah are you already like a professional
magician i okay so i was curious as to why the the sweet christ's name the pert the pattern
familias of this organization are like oh it's got it's got to be circus themed but i think maybe
they made a few unwise amazon purchases like justin and do have these fushigi balls maybe
they have been fushiging for six months and they have absolutely no venue in which to show it off
they're tired of getting shut down when at every family function they say hey does anybody want to
see some contact juggling and everyone says no i don't i don't want to see that now you are making
you are dragooning the entire family everyone you're related to into watching you contact juggle
the good news is probably no one's gonna come no one wants to be here for this
this is a family gathering is it a reunion it sounds like it yeah because they use the word
reunion i you gotta go erotic it's gotta be it's gotta be strange and erotic like a cirque du soleil
level of eroticism i'm not saying i'm not saying like hump your hump your sisters or whatever i'm
saying you know hang hang a hoop from your butthole and then they jump through it what i've
never seen sir i've never seen cirque du soleil but i think what if you humped your sisters and
made it like an aristocrat's joke oh oh oh oh oh oh is this a whole fan is this a whole family of
circus people i think if it was a whole family circus i think if it was that justin they'd know
what the fuck to do they wouldn't be asking yahoo answers maybe some people are some people are
what if they like to keep their family and professional life separate did you see did you
see dick gracing came isn't that sad who is that man with him that's so upset why is he are they
relate are they friends what is the nature of their relation why did he even come you're saying
50 of the family maybe the mom's side of the family the grandma's side the flying graces
the all flying graces the dad's side mostly dentists mostly dentists and accountants and
tax adjusters right and lean holders i don't know what that sounds like and taxidermists
excuse me excuse me you know you can't use more than four syllable words here yeah i get a little
i get a little tongue tied excuse me um why is there a uh what what is the venue for this
is this living room a circus performance is it at the is it at the jc's is it at the ko c
is it at the kfc i just hope it's somewhere private somewhere private somewhere indoors
can you please tell me the park you're going to be at so i could be in another state please can
you put up one of those like bug spraying tents that they put over houses and then that can be
your big top and maybe they are in fact spraying it while you're doing your thing that sometimes i
go to the park and there's guys with foam swords and i just think how dare you sir that's my whole
day now is that and you're doing that here do that in the privacy of your own home where i don't have
to be secretly jealous of you because it looks awesome it looks so cool it does look cool why
can't i be that self-assured and or done i could just fight in the park of foam swords that would
be sweet do you think any larpers listen to our listen to our lepers lerpers social lepers any
leopards um i i think that they're happy just by law of large numbers we have so many listeners i
think there's somebody out there somebody out there who's been a monster camp trap you've
been a monster camp i don't even know what that is cool cool cool uh i guess it's about time to
move on oh i'm sorry were you guys waiting for a joke no oh i i don't have anything
to do
jeffy
blah blah the dad's an alcoholic
get your revisionist family circus history out of here no it's absolutely true the first comic
strip i'm looking at right now is the kids running in from a football game the dad looks
really sad sack with the cigarette hanging out of his mouth and the caption is we each had a
little bottle of soda daddy brought his own in in his pocket that's the first family circus yeah
oh it's an early strip it's from 1962 so daddy is in fact an alcoholic so that would be a good
family circus act you could do it's just your dad gets drunk i was like what the fuck are you kids
doing please stop flipping around and shit i'm embarrassed in front of your uncle dave can you
kill your grandma and then have her appear above you in a little circle and she's wearing angel
wings and she's looking down on you and she says it's a great trick but i can only do it once here
comes the next question coming at you from me to you my fiance and i have been discussing future
christmas traditions as we face the next candle nights and all others as a married couple i am
adamant that we will not be sending christmas cards as it is an outdated tradition given all
the methods of staying in touch at this wonderful age provides us how do i convince her it is a
waste of time that's from no noel notices in north carolina what are you talking about what
a what a cringy thing to say i know it's not an outdated it's like i love it i love getting a good
christmas card in the mail with great typography especially now that my friends all have babies
it's like a great way of keeping up with babies and it is it is one of those like things that
doesn't translate to like email or text message or anything like someone could email me a picture of
their kids and it's like a big fucking deal but you send me a nice card shows you put a little
thought into it that means something yeah when that when that baby pic exists in your tangible
space in your physical surroundings then you treasure it if it's just zeros and ones it's
like who the fuck is this kid if you email it what you're saying is hey you should print this out
cut it down to a normal size and then put it somewhere i guess i don't know i didn't think
that far ahead because you probably stopped on step one i'll tell you where it has been really
good what i have used christmas cards most for is like they're a nice conversation thing like
for instance i have uh our friend slice sent us a picture of his of his uh big baby kevin
and it's a great picture because he has a little car that he's driving and there's a little tree
attached to the roof uh and it's awesome and it's cozy coop it's a great picture but like i would i
might have seen that on facebook and like scroll on by but now that it's like in my house when my
dad comes by i say hey have you seen my skin a while it's great it's in your zone it's in my
zone i've got like four or five babies just like chilling in the kitchen now and whenever i'm
great again i just look over did you get justin russo's you know i did mackey russo's god damn
that's a cute little baby i think you're misunderstanding question asker i think you're
misunderstanding the the the utility of christmas cards which is to say not there is none no one
ever got a christmas card even back in like the 60s and felt like oh thank god what a valuable
dispatch thank god you got this across thank god i can now identify their children by sight
thank goodness it's a way it's a way of like getting um you know letting that person know
that you care about them it's a it's a homecoming pic that it's a homecoming pic or an engagement
pic that's like saying just like this is what i look like this year and that's handy to know
that's that's good knowledge it really is just like a thought thing you know we got lots of
christmas cards in the p.o box this year and man i was fucking touched yeah it was nice people uh
travis was reading them to us we're actually this is how we enjoy we can't go through everybody who
sent us a christmas card um but you know who you are but you know who you are and we actually all
sat in one room in front of the fire drinking some eggnog and reading our christmas cards that is
throwing them into the fire tossing them into the fire casually well only the shitty ones
only the shitty ones who you are yeah if it had a white baby on it it was not going in the fire
let's just put it that way why what is it why does it always why is it always within you but
you always like that with you uh i got another question is that a good tip for question asking
just make sure the card has a white baby on it no matter what include a white baby include a white
baby or a baby in white face oh my god stop i was griffin i have to tell you something i am
currently wearing the slippers you got me for christmas and it is like it is like cruising
around doing my morning puttering on a cloud on a mobile cloud that was all rachel well thank her
for me these look exactly like justin's feet on the inside and so we caught him i finally understand
that song you know that one conny song don't let me into my zone with also jz also starting jz i've
often i think i misunderstood that as some sort of like um mental state that you get into where once
you're in it you're unstoppable no i think these slippers are my zone right the original transcript
of that song was conny saying don't let me into my slippies and they said that doesn't sound very
good that's not a good rap song it's it doesn't have a very good meter and also mr west people
are going people are going to make fun of you if you say he's on an album jay-z was like i don't
know i kind of like it i kind of like it this is gonna be a good cd we're making together conny
this is gonna be a good record watch the slippies watch the slippies please don't
and then we're gonna we're gonna watch the slippies tour but we mostly just stay in our
sweaty pants just chill let's just watch some catch up on homeland and stay in our slippies
all day order some za just bro out bro just bro'd out man that fire is getting a little low conny
put another log on that let's see what see what birdie's up to now uh one man should have all
these slippers you do you know i said that but you actually are right i i have too many slippers
conny thank you for pointing that out to me do you need me to refresh your cafe au lait
now you remember when remember when after katrina conny was like george bush doesn't care about
sock shoes and it's like i guess you're probably right hey i was in a 3.5 year relationship my
first one ever congratulations and was dumped a little month over a month ago should have read
first justin should have finished the sentence read a little bit faster it was far from a perfect
relation a sizable chunk of it was long distance we didn't have much in common and i think when it
ended neither of us were really happy i've started seeing a new girl and i'm feeling pretty happy but
i can't shake the feeling that i might just be rebounding i don't want to make such a predictable
mistake but i also don't want to rule out the possibility of finding the right girl how can i
separate real feelings from the rebound and that's from love longing in long island i don't believe
in the rebound like i don't yeah i think that rebounding is either you either make the decision
before you get in the relationship like i want to rebound or after the relationship is over you look
back on it and say yeah that was just a rebound relationship well yeah that's that's the only way
it works that's the only way that that what you've just described is the only two ways that situation
can shake out no what what i'm saying is like you're never in the middle of a relationship
that you're really happy in and it's going really well and go you know i think this is a rebound
right it's not a classification that the relationship falls under like no hold on if
i put together this element and this element oh it's a rebound relationship i mean like i i i
married my wife on the rebound like she had just split up with her very long-term boyfriend when
when the two of us started dating and like if i had um for some reason shun that relationship
because she was on the rebound or or she had done the same i i would have missed out on like the
most important relationship in my life so i i'm not i'm i'm loathe to sort of say like dismiss
or try to categorize this relationship too much i i mean she recently has just gotten out of a
two-year relationship three weeks before we started dating and we've been together almost
three years and we're engaged now yeah you're engaged what congratulations i meant to tell
you guys yeah thank you um i do i think there's something to it though i think i think when you
get out of a relationship that you're not exactly happy in you do kind of go buckwild you do go a
little out of wild like i don't think that's a myth i'm not saying that the next person you date
i'm not saying the next person you date is the is a mistake but there's a much higher chance
well i mean i i will be honest with this and say that truce and i did then like move in together
like four months later and you know moved a lot faster than maybe we would have if we were both
like you know coming off i don't know coming off of long-term singleness but i mean that's not bad
that's not a bad thing i don't regret that i think it just makes you a little bit more
open to the idea of happiness would be a better way to put it you know what i mean where you're
not maybe as trepidatious you're not maybe or you go the other way and you are you know much
more afraid of it and that is usually what kills your happiness i i just don't i i think you should
be careful about don't overthink it if you're not happy in the relationship by all means get out if
you're happy the relationship who cares how it started who cares how long it's been since your
last relationship you got 3.5 years of experience yeah uh with with relationship there's no uh non
compete on this put your skills to use don't don't like get so bonered to like find someone else
that you ignore the lessons of those three and a half years though like those three and a half
years that's a lot that's true that's a long ass time you probably learned some shit about what you
want from a from a partner from a partner so don't don't like don't ignore that you know
don't just go looking for the first first thing with holes oh god yucky my favorite fair shallow
booth like uh i'm i'm talking about i'm not talking about like a mr bucket i'm talking about
like a living human being i if you do fuck a mr bucket though that'd be hard i bet that would be
hard yeah because he's always like he's always like spitting spitting the balls pop out of his
mouth so good luck trying to keep him in right um the uh if you if you if it was bad at the end
that might feel comfortable for you you have to have keep your head on a swivel and try to see
griffith's right see if you see the same patterns because if you see the same patterns you may have
just gotten back together with somebody who is like the last bad relationship so don't do that
mm-hmm just if you're happy don't think about it too much don't try to overanalyze happiness just
be happy and you know what you may get sucker punched in a month you may think like oh man
ah crap i this was a rebound relationship i messed up but you could also sabotage yourself
now by being really happy and then being a good relationship but now trying to determine whether
it's a rebound relationship or any nonsense like that you're going to end up screwing yourself
over by overthinking yeah just just always think of the fact that in the mba you get points for
rebounds oh that is true so how bad can they really be just improve your stats just get your
stats up you can't get a triple double unless you get three three three rebound two rebounds
it's three rebounds two you get points probably guys when the other guy's bouncing down the court
and he throws it and he does he just misses all the hoops and then you get the ball back a guy
comes along and punches him in the dick i am so tired of turning on google and having the first
google news story that pops up be like this player punched this player in the dick it's tuesday
yeah tomorrow there's going to be a new one stay tuned can 2013 can everyone's new year's
resolution be not punch someone in the dick maliciously while playing basketball
it should be pretty i can take i can take the pledge
where this where this promise ring i'm gonna wear a promise ring that explicitly states
i will get a celebrity youtube video about not punching people in the dick
hey just in basketball terms hey it's me tofa grace listen listen keep it when i on the court
when i bought on the court when i'm balling i'm never balling which is what i call punching
someone in the balls on the court when me and toby mcguire are balling and shooting and toby keith
and marissa tomei uh when we're all balling on the court the craziest the craziest basketball
celebrity basketball tournament ever except for any tournament involving the harlem globetrotters
it would be the craziest you're correct keep it on the paint can we just say that
keep it on the paint and not on the taint put your fists put your fists away put your dukes down
and put your dunks up that was good dunks dunks not dunks dunks not dunks guys i have a yahoo
answer is pressing okay and depressing it's sent in by will before it thank you will
it's by yahoo answers user flocks who asks a business question
would it be nice if subway sell three inches sandwich for a dollar
in december they have six inch for two dollars so it would be three inches for one dollar if you eat
half it's perfect for when you're not hungry but you do want to experience the subway ambiance
i want an excuse to talk to the sandwich artist i've got my eye on you know this do you know how
when you finish your subway sandwich be it six or twelve inches and you are full as fuck but you're
sad because there's no more sandwich to eat this is like a little boost this is like a little booster
pack you're saying this is a way to get a nine or 15 inch sub i'm saying yes round up just tie
this to my other sub please with substring you're a sandwich artist you should be able to swing this
make it a sandwich modern artist what making it an l shape i don't care get as gay as you want to
with it get gay with this mixed media sandwich i don't care if you make it look like a duck face
i don't care the guys at the plant make fun of your extra sandwich let me get a six pack of
subway nuggets which is what i call three inch sandwiches listen i want to eat a four hour but
i'm gonna i'm gonna eat a foot long but instead i'm gonna get four three inch longs because i
want to eat four of something oh god i think i'll feel fuller and there's more paper that way
three inch subs at subway maybe that you know what that would be good for a sampler if you
want to like try four subs yeah i know but i mean but then you're quadrupling the amount of time
that that sandwich when you order a chicken when you order a sloppy sloppy ranch chicken
chicken bacon when you get one of those they have it streamlined in their brain this is how
food service works it is a manufacturing line where they know the fastest way to slop it and
flop it down and get it from the from their table to your mouth they know the quickest way to do
that when you are quadrupling that process i don't think subway's gonna go for this can we just be
honest and say that the worst thing about going to subway is the smell you have to stand there
and stand eye to eye with the person making your food as they like contempt with every extra topping
you want you're creating more work for them and you can just stand there and watch them judge you
um i used to work next to a subway used to work at a tcby next to a subway which is like
the healthiest job i've ever had and um i was getting my lunch one day and uh a lady that was
making my sandwich cut her finger like through the plastic glove with a knife and was like oh
fuck and then put her hand behind her back and tried to make the rest of the sandwich with one
hand what like she's like she's on top chef like yes very much like she's on top chef moreover she
got blood on the fucking like i saw you you were holding my sandwich when you cut your finger
through it like no there's no way there's no way by introducing a three-inch sandwich you're
creating a lot more opportunities for that sort of thing to happen correct that's what that's
where i'm at that's what worries me i think you i mean the biggest concern and i wish i wasn't
as worried about this as i am but with with the three inch sandwich you also run a good chance
of getting stuck with the little curved knob nubby end that's not really worth a dollar god it's not
worth a fucking penny it's not worth the stomach acid that you would use to digest it oh god you
lose all you lose so much sandwich real estate you lose so many teeth trying to chew that nubby
nubby nug oh it's so gross this smell can we all i've brought this up twice now and nobody
addressed like recognized you do you guys not agree that subway is like the fucking stinkiest
place on earth like you walk into that place and you walk out and you smell like you smell like
the shoes of somebody who's been working at olive garden there's a gas station about two blocks away
from me that is a gas station and subway restaurant um combining in one building and i swear to god
every time i walk into the building it does it smells like sandwiches and vomit simultaneously
did you not a pleasant smell did you just bathe in peppuccini i did not i promise you i did not
it is the subway bread smells i guess it's the bread i think that must be like the yeah i think
it's the bread do you think jared smells like that all the fucking time do you think i bet jared
can't get fucked for that very reason and also because he looks like a looks like a nymph he's
got all that weird hangy skin oh my god you know it's all i just hang it like if he extended his
arms he could catch a breeze and fly just float away goodbye kids thank you for leaving you smell
like you smell like so much peppuccini now the air smells like it i hate you jared hey listen
damn flying squirrel hey listen let's go let's make some money guys in the new year you know
what my big thing is uh you're gonna are you gonna tell us yeah i'm gonna tell you don't need to guess
because that would be actually unsettling if you did weirder fucking it's gotten so vanilla
from me and all my girls that i really i want to try to integrate some new some new things all my
girls and guys that i'm out there making love to either making love to or just wait you are
confused you are confessing to adultery on our podcast you're like casually discussing infidelities
listen these things used to seem unsettling to me i remember being a square like you
and then i bought uh i got myself a uh uh twist up nipple sucker for 1698 at extremistrace.com
that's my favorite ray stevens song it opened my eyes and oh yes they call him the twist up
nipple sucker this little beauty opened my eyes and extended my nipples uh and and and it was just
the start of my journey and i think in 2013 i want to get i want to get like i want to see where my
boundaries are i will find your boundary in 2013 quick question okay does exploring uh new outlets
in the bedroom force you to cheat on your significant other no there's no connection
between the two okay i i just i like to murder people after sex whoa that is i'm pretty sure
that's praying mantis i can't believe you caught me uh i got one yard has been after you now listen
extremistrace does not support praying mantis style murdering your partner after your multiple
why are we talking about it during the advertisement that they paid us for
someone is calling interpol right at this moment i've got him i got the praying mantis uh
they've got everything extremistrace.com they don't have i heard a rumor they don't have lube
they don't don't be don't get it twisted they got lube they've got dungeon furniture unless you
want to get it twisted at which point they have stuff for that they do have that they have things
for getting it twisted they have sex aids which is not what you think did they have um so i was
making muffins the other day uh-huh and i ran out of boy butter can i get do i have to go to the
heb to get more boy butter or can they help me out in that regard no you don't have to get boy
butter at the store and uh uh suffer through the judgmental looks of darling the cashier you can
get it in the privacy of your own home they have a ton of silicone do they have country cock they
have country they also have i can't believe it's not butter and i also can't believe what it really
is they have uh they have swiss navy lubricant which is the only lubricant on the site with a
confrontational picture of a man holding the bottle and stare you dead in the eye the rest of
them are or have the have the uh the sense to just leave a bottle there and let you judge it on that
one it's like you ever been fucked by a jpeg here's this picture here's a great thing about
extremetrains.com uh first off the girl on the front page is wearing a santa hat which i think
is festive secondly if you use the coupon code middle list you're gonna be able to save 20
percent on uh on your purchases there so that's great i i would love it if if 2013
was it went down in history as the year that began a sexual revolution um when you say began
you mean you mean like continued and expanded right like what do you mean i i'm saying it's
foolhardy to think that 2013 is the year when people are like first start going like i'm
all right let's try it's time to give up our deeply protestant almost amish like ways um
you know lights off you know one one position crying afterwards and we just need to like
revolution i think we need to move beyond the classic you know dinner dancing love making
murder hide the body i think we need to get good but let's break our cycles this year you know yeah
i i agree for so many reasons uh so go extreme restraints.com use the coupon code middle list
and you're gonna save 20 and you help keep us in business you help keep them in business
so it's all it's a win-win win and the third win is for how big your boner will be that's
all your lady boner or your lady boner if that's they have those you can buy one of those too
who cares hey this year i'm invited to three different new year's eve parties and i have
no idea which one i should go to here are the deets on each let's take turns party one is a
fancy dinner party it's in quotes because i don't know if it's ironic fancy or genuine fancy and it's
hosted by my male best friend who i've been in love with for years but he has a girlfriend now
and i drink and get sad party two involves my female best friend and some mutual friends i
sort of know trekking into new york city on new year's and singing and drinking our hearts out
at a karaoke bar but besides my friend i don't like many of the other people and i really can't
enjoy karaoke unless i'm plastered party one is a fancy dinner party no no griffith no i wasn't
paying attention party three involves just i thought we would read them in like a random order
okay we did it just happened to be the first one and then the second one party three involves just
hanging out a group of people i like a lot and haven't seen in ages we probably cook drink watch
some bbc sherlock and maybe play some clue but this doesn't seem nearly as exciting as the other
two options that's from nebulous in new jersey and you're out of your goddamn mind you have among
your options the best party yeah you could go i can hang out at a party that will make me sad i
can hang out with some dicks i don't like or i can have the best night of my life watching bbc
sherlock and recreating it while playing clue and getting drunk with your friends and cooking with
your friends that you haven't seen in ages that you love what are you what are you fucking like
why are you punishing yourself okay to be fair i'm gonna play devil's advocate here and say i
totally understand okay hit me because new year's has all of this baggage behind it where you have
to feel like it was an epic thing on any other night this would be a really clear choice but for
some reason when new year's rolls around i go through this too where if i'm presented with
several different options but one seems more low-key than the others i feel like i'm doing new
year's a disservice interesting okay i can see that i can see how you'd want to feel connected
to the world at large on and you wouldn't necessarily uh want to hold up i i can't think
of any honestly like i i can the the new year's that i proposed to my wife is the only new year's
i can think of that wasn't in some fashion a slight disappointment i remember being like 12
and enjoying the shrimp plate my mother had put out that was pretty great i remember one time i
was at a church lock-in at midnight and i missed the ball and stuff because i was hiding under a
desk because we were playing hide and go seek um i don't know my favorite new year's are always
spent in my friend's basement with all my buds playing playing games i made an rpg maker
those are those are really good years i'm telling you man it doesn't matter what you do just don't
be old just don't be don't get old like us this is to quote matthew mcconaughey man he said man
at the beginning of it it doesn't matter what you do bud all that matters is who you're with
when you're doing it bud he said again i can't stress this enough just don't get old don't ever
get old don't get old like us you gotta stay young if there's younger people at one of these and
they'll let you drink their youth then go to one of those also i want to throw this out if you
don't know whether a party is ironic fancy or serious fancy you're gonna pick the wrong one
by making the choice you will actually shape the party don't just don't go to those parties
go go play clue i'm always friends i always always want to play clue and nobody likes playing it with
me uh you know i've made i've made the mistake in the past of when i was presented with several
different options attempting to do all of them in the same night so like we go to one place from
like eight to nine thirty and then we travel to somewhere else for 15 minutes and be there
till like 11 20 and then try to be somewhere else when the ball dropped and spend the rest
of the evening there it was awful it was a horrible decision yeah travis travis pulled
the travis pulled the goldilocks he didn't do a good job of it you're not i plan on the thing
give yourself permission to to not obsess about making the perfect choice just make the one that
sounds like the most fun and it sounds like you've already made that decision yeah you know you know
the right thing to do and you know what do me a favor also in 2013 let go of this guy yeah he does
not deserve you move on with your life can girl can let can um let go this guy in 2013 is that
the motto i think that's a bit wordy i don't think we found it yet how about just let go 2013
let go and then we can play that fru fru song that was on the garden states
that was a good that was a good song could you sing a little bit of that for me drink up man
my nothing i'll get it in the year you tell tell yourself goodbye and then you go
but it's but they put it through like a tuning filter this is what it's called and so it sounds
like uh like microsoft sam is singing to you get go get go jumping
i think that fits every circumstance pretty sure that's the matilda soundtrack
no it's actually the georgia the jungle soundtrack justin okay nobody know what what the fuck is he
saying there i don't think that he knows what he's saying at that part i don't either but i think he
says frumicera at one point what language and also what does that mean in that language well
frumicera is the ghost in fiddler on the roof oh jesus christ do you guys know what he's actually
saying there no nobody save nobody on i don't think that's true nobody save nobody on no that's
not about baseball it's about baseball no runs no strikes e ra 3.30 batting average dukes down dunks
up keep it on the paint keep it off the tape oh boy hey griffin you got any more yahoos you want
to do or you want to do another regular question or what i got a lot um jesus um i have one about
mcdonald's but we just did fast food first down three to go um i don't think any sports commentator
has ever said first down three to go this yahoo answer was also sent in by ira ray who is uh
quickly becoming who wants to know a gold member platinum platinum member justin how are you always
gonna make that joke yes and it's not a joke it's a tick it's turrets basically this yahoo is asked
by project x who asks how can i be more forest gump style no not being an artistic and the way
that gump is i'm sorry one more time no not being an artistic in the way that gump is but by the way
he wins respect how can i be a good person like gump is and win girls but not by being artistic
here you go college humor forest gumpin style just go ahead you can do that for free you can
have that one i love i love when we get a question that just by asking the question
negates the possibility of what the person is asking happening what do you do you think the
fact that he could use a computer you mean no i'm saying right the fact of saying how can i be more
like forrest gump you know not like artistic or anything but just nice so girls like me and stuff
hey guess what that ain't happening that's the thing about gump though i what of all the people
to want to be like right try to get chicks is that the only thing you want to get girls because
there's like other be like a cool rider in greece too like you could do anything like that there's
more tom hanks characters you could have picked i'm gonna narrow it down how do i be more like
the guy from pig there are more characters in the movie forrest gump that he could have picked
you can pick lieutenant dan you got that that uh the lady from saigon and marium
right he gets magic legs get magic legs oh spoilers who sorry guys he could be like in the
movie big did you got okay have you guys watched big recently not okay i mean i listen here's the
thing about big that i didn't realize she she fucks a little kid she fucks a little kid yeah
she has sex with a boy and then who's a man and then watches as that man transforms into a boy
in an oversized suit what they never address is the uh shortly thereafter her spiral into dementia
just must occur right just look and you know that mary kay letourneau uses exact excuse well you
don't understand you see when i met him how he was a man how was for a brief moment he was an adult
man and it wasn't weird and then it got we find the defendant guilty um you got zoltan
how was the court i wish to present my next surprise witness zoltan zoltan to the stand
please how how was big tom hanks comfortable enough by the way i hope that this yahoo answers
askers okay with the fact that we are just not going to talk about that anymore nope how was
big tom hanks already comfortable enough with his now okay i need to clarify i need to clarify
something real quick before we move on okay do you mean tom hanks from the movie big or giant
tom is an affectionate nickname you have for him big tom big tom how did biggie tom in the movie
big big tommy hanks big big tommy hanks in the movie big as tom hanks got it who he played how
did he that really happened to tom hanks you guys it's basically true story how did he get
comfortable enough with his man dick to like know how to use it on a woman and not be like um uh oh
no he was thinking about baseball during sex because like that's all that he he was 12 that
and that's what 12 year olds think about his baseball he was also thinking about power rangers
how much game does it i don't think a little kid could grow up that many years that that quickly
and then like two weeks later be like fucking a grown woman and know like what to do down there
i don't i don't know he's just getting used to having hair down there oh god you know that
issues too if you had a weird tom hanks bush just sprout up like nothing weird about this
conversation let's talk more about tom hanks's pews go on what do you think the curtains match
the drapes have you guys seen cloud atlas yet he sculpts his bush into eight different characters
bushes and depending on if his bush is good or bad he either moves up or down the scale
oh my god he had to wear hammer pants on this set of castaway
he's so method he refused to trim his own bush for the same amount of time the guy in castaway
would have mr mr hanks big tommy hair and makeup and downstairs hair is ready for you
you can go back to your trailer please forever
okay it's in every contract though like if you want tom hanks i'm gonna i'll cut it with his
bush i'll cut it with that ice skate no tom you don't have to during the filming of joe versus
the volcano he was just constantly terrified he just didn't want to burst into flames out there
highly highly flammable do you think he had a weird crew cut down there during force gump
oh yeah oh man cut it clean high and tight
now i'm just kidding you would never trim his pubes no
well then he loses his power right his his affability is tied to samson
sorry pubic samson pubic samson got it got it his affability comes from the length of his pubes
if you try to trim them down you get uh you know you get a you get a angels and demons or a davinci
code you let them grow and and and get crazy down there you know you get yourself uh uh
what's a good what's a good time it's bachelor party bachelor party okay money pit yeah you
get a bachelor party now in the polar express will there be digital pubes will i will there
be some sort of animator some sort of artist they actually wanted to do the polar express
in 1994 and the technology could do everything except individually render tom hanks pubes
underneath and then a little company called pixar came along and developed really advanced
pube technology they originally were dixar and then they switch in the movie toy story
from certain angles in certain lights when the light is cast in a certain way across the woody
figurine maybe when he's looking at the bottom of his shoe we get a little pink of his jeans
it's to infinity and beyond indeed you could get lost in there now i want pubes too tim allen says
are you just reading my favorite children's book
man that was a good blu-ray the toy story blu-ray oh with with the hd you can really see the bush
oh man yeah it's righteous bush i think everybody came into this came into this episode without
having a new year's resolution and now their new year's resolution is to stop listening to my
brother my brother and to try to erase the last 10 minutes from their memories good luck never
gonna god this is gonna be one of those running gags that i'm gonna get real real tired of anytime
with tom hanks movies on tv someone tweeting at me about the size of this bush i can see it
i can see it you're right all that can't see it whatever you do listen people at home whatever
you do all jokes aside do not stare deeply into it don't you'll see your own death all that i'm
saying is that tom hanks has never gone full frontal in the movie we've been waiting for it
god knows when he when he does it looks like he's wearing fur pants that's what i'm saying is that
we have no way of disproving this so he was actually full frontal through most of the burbs
you just the camera was such a way okay the camera adds 10 pounds to your bush i'm done okay
that's it we're done this is my been my brother my brother and me uh an advice show for the
modern era thank you so much for tuning in yet again god knows why you do um if you're uh if
you're gonna get fit the new year i would highly recommend heading over to uh photography.com
fitocracy.com we got a my brother my brother me group there just search for it yeah we can all
uh we we got 135 members right now with 6 000 workouts between them wow so if you want to get
fit come on join the group um i'm gonna hop back in there try to get fit first of the year travis
i know you're working out some you should yeah i feel like that's cheating though because i like
do it a lot is that what you're supposed to do yeah you're supposed to uh you log your workouts
and then you get points for everything you do and you can like level up in your fitness it seems
like something you would you would dig trap um but anyway that's fitocracy.com and just search
for my brother my brother me and the groups um thank you everybody sorry trap go i was just
gonna say and guys in all seriousness go check out extreme restraints if you still have it at
this point they're awesome and they are just sponsoring us they send us nice emails all the
time and talking about how great all of our listeners are and how happy they are to be like
advertising and god knows we're happy too so so yeah so go check it out extremistrains.com
keep on code middle list we love you um thank you to everybody tweeting about the show thank you to
dcby11 uh nikola courtney cave child hallways coy more uh alex solak sergeant smitty space invader
pop how esquire every bear kith and kin books just think uh everybody who who listens to the
show and tweets about it and helps to spread the word um bit.ly forward slash it's my bim bam
is the link to our sampler i'm gonna update that this year uh if you would like to suggest
something get a form going on uh uh maximum fun.org in our forum section uh just get a
thread of those bits you'd like to see included for the sampler and i'll check that out see which
one you guys like while you're there while you're on the maximum fun.org uh go listen to the other
shows on the network stop stop podcasting yourself throwing shade jordan jesse go judge john hodgeman
risk the memory palace all bullseye all great great programs for your ears and they're all free
so go go listen to those and in 2013 one of our new year's resolutions is we're going to try to
do more live shows because we've really been slacking off um and so if you have suggestions
for either cities we should do it in or venues we can do it in in those cities make sure to post
those on the forum as well just don't be a dick about it we're not coming to buffalo you know
come on come on we're we're busy guys that's bush league i want to thank i can't even hear that word
anymore i want to thank john rogerick and the long winters for the use of our theme song it's a
departure which is on the album uh putting the days to bed which you can find online and uh you
should you should buy and listen to i've actually got back into it i don't know why i got the bug
maybe it's because i listened to john rogerick and john colton's christmas album which justin got me
for christmas thank you justin you are very welcome um there's also a t-shirt there's a
t-shirt in the box um and just thank you everybody seriously it's been the best year ever yeah you
guys are the best um um thanks for sticking with us sorry we don't have a new official motto but
but we'll find it in 2013 we'll come up with something we'll come up with something um i
really like keep it on the paint because it can apply to like so many things just find yahoo
answer was sent in by christopher cook thank you christopher it's by yahoo answers user indian
government sucks who asks how brits can live in uk which is full of haunted house
oh i'm just a mackerel i'm travis mackerel i'm good for mackerel
this has been my brother my brother may kiss your dad square on the lips