The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother, and Me, an advice show for the
modern era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
And I'm Hollywood hitmaker, Griffin McElroy, the youngest brother.
Well, boys, just got back from another meeting with the producers and director.
Oh, of our podcast?
Of our podcast. They have some big notes, especially as they're heading into Max Fun Drive.
Last week, it was my heel turn. This week, they want more storylines. They said not enough
storylines.
Okay.
Some more, it could be behind the scenes, it could be in front of the scenes,
it could be in the middle of the scenes.
Well, this is great news because I've just become like a sexy doctor.
Like I've just become a sort of sexual doctor.
That feels like two different things, Griffin, a sexy doctor versus a sexual doctor.
Okay, so yeah, that's good, Trav. I don't like diagnosing give medicine to help people sexual.
Do you know what I mean? It's just like my body looks good and all the patients are like,
please. And I'm like, I can't. I am happily married.
Okay.
But I'm also, I'm pretty darn good at it. Like I can do an IV. Oh my God, guys,
I had to get some blood work done yesterday, not COVID related, do not sweat.
I'm going to continue to sweat as your brother because I don't know why you got blood work done.
Yeah, just for funsies or?
Yeah.
It is an allergy panel. It's like the nerdiest imaginable reason to get blood work done.
Yeah. Anywho, the person who was taking my blood was quite chatty,
and that's their prerogative. I'm not here to, you know, shame them for that.
But they were doing a lot of characters, I'll say. They were doing a lot of skit work,
let's say. And at one point they were looking for my vein and they said,
Ooh, that's a nice big juicy vein. Gonna get a lot of blood out of that.
And started to do a vampire thing. And like for the remainder of,
from the moment the needle entered my arm until the moment I left the room,
she spoke in a vampire voice and she did, I swear to God.
And it was one of the top five worst things that's ever happened to me,
because can you two imagine a more sort of hostage scenario
than having a needle in your body and you just can't, you can't move.
And also they're going to try out some new SNL audition tape tactics on you.
This is the difference between Griffin and I, because Griffin's,
Griffin's, let's say fear here, Griffin's discomfort
comes from him seeing this as this person trying out new material on him,
where I would be thinking like, if I was a vampire,
the job I would get would be drawing blood from people.
Well, no. And so who's to say that
this isn't the reveal? This isn't the prestige.
I don't know how, it's a fair point, Travis,
but like I can actually not imagine a worse job for a vampire
because you're going to be so tempted by this shit.
And I hope that this lab has their shit on lock enough
that like if blood goes missing,
I want my stuff on the books somewhere. I only have so much blood.
Well, maybe they just take a little bit extra, you know,
the juice is running and in this case, the juice is your blood.
Sure. The juice is also running on the MaxFun drive,
which we're going to talk about a little bit later on this episode.
With this MaxFun drive has very chill vibes.
That's the feedback we've been getting is a lot of people say that like,
when we ask for money, it's like going on a beach vacation,
which is so cool. And if you want to join the network now,
go to maximumfun.org slash join,
look at all the different reward tiers that you can give at on a monthly basis
and think about supporting the show and the network as a whole.
So go to maximumfun.org slash join.
It's me, the head of the network, Reggie Big Shot.
I heard you need a little drama to spice things up.
Boy, here's some for you. Sorry, the cigars are catching up on me.
Here's some.
Please don't say that again.
The cigars are catching up on me.
They're catching up on you?
Catching up on me.
Listen, that's not the point. My personal health,
that's not the point, kids.
No, but I am worried about you. Are you okay?
Yeah, I love you.
I loved it when you were going to bring it at the beginning
and the old days of ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, ma'am.
I loved at the farm, farm jokes and you did a lot of blue stuff
about lots of different marginalized groups of people.
I love that.
Loved that, yeah.
You gave us a lot of positive feedback.
I'm not so crazy about the new stuff.
And honestly, boys, the well's running a little dry.
So here's the deal.
If you don't raise enough in this max fund drive
during this episode of ma'am you're out.
All right?
You are a caputskic.
Let me finish, tromble.
Travis, let him fucking finish, Tromble.
Tromble, you let me finish. Thank you, Greedo.
Listen, if you don't raise enough money
in this episode of remember bam you're kaput people gotta go to maximumfund.org forward slash join
and they gotta push back and save our show save your show my show law and order p-o-d-c-a-s-t
but i how i made my bajillions that show is fine it's in its 30th season and uh so that my show
is not danger it's your show that's on the ropes now but mr big shot if if our show please call
me mr reggie big shot mr reggie big shot if if you were to cancel our show then who would take
care of all of these orphans who i have dubbed travis's kids uh that that comes to my grip of
orphans mr yeah they come to my community center every day and i i teach them about driving i'll
make them he's teaching these seven and eight year olds how to drive mr big shot and i mean
all fords are like not just driving cars but like driving golf balls forklift yeah driving people
crazy i'll put them to work you don't need to worry about that i'm gonna turn them into human
human doors for a month wait you would you would cut them open and store cigars inside no way if
you put there's nothing better for the temperament and tenor of a fine cigar in the pocket of a young
child i have so i load up their dungarees and their levites with all my premium smokes and then
let them uh sit in a in a very humid room and it is how you get through and people i'm so sorry
to interrupt mr reggie big shot but it's all right gun to some warming up together and people just
let you do that well if if your show's canceled their bill you know wouldn't just stop me that
doesn't wait hold on me through that riffin and justin and i are the only people stopping people
from using children as he left you know him as jumbles jumbles jumbles not be in the show the
real star he left the room he gets scared whenever i come in he hides under a table like
we're doing a nuke drill back in my childhood he's under the table right now just pissing his
pants he's under the table and dreaming you know we have to pay for that now that's fifty five
thousand dollars mr you don't have to pay for it it's diegetic it came from the tiny dave matthews
that lives in my shirt pocket oh hey i do know about that was a cigar i do i do know about the
sickness you did get mr reggie big shot because you were on the boat that they dumped the dave
matthews banduki onto and that's sort of like your origin story that's why you are the way you are
i just wanted to say that i'm i'm like hugely in love with uh you and can you please describe
exactly what you look like me yeah yeah oh okay all right just me imagine four cans of uh paint
stacked on top of each other fuck yeah okay each one of those is like one of my legs all right
and then on top of that imagine oh sorry just to clarify sorry to interrupt segmented like that
huh yeah do you have signature legs okay imagine a big old crusty sourdough loaf that's got a
little bit rugged that's my oh you like you liked that yeah like living my favorite thing about you
mr reggie big shot is that you seem to be feeling yourself a lot yeah you've got a lot of uh sexual
energy coming off just your confidence your confidence is very attractive he's crying under
under the table he's under the table and crying yeah i am i'm feeling i'm feeling feeling my sexy
it's been a great few uh months for me oh how's it surprisingly yeah what's new what's been going on
you know all the bad stuff that's been happening yeah it's all been good for me in ways that are
hard to explain well try we'll try we got time my head looks like charles groden's head with like
one for one just one for what no one for 1.3 distorted in all the wrong way like in a carnival
mirror like a beautiful carnival mirror of hatred yes so wait oh just to be clear it's like charles
groden if charles groden was fueled by hatred and slightly distorted the marketing says your
people love charles groden that's true we got a lot of grotes in here a lot well familiar listen
i'm watching the donation counter it's going down you're not enticing anyone oh no people are can't
oh they're can't they're not canceling they're leaving the family that is in your in your pylons
listen the point is this if i don't see those numbers where i need them to be you're gonna
start putting cigars into children's pockets i think richard richard belzerd wants another pay
bump so uh is he alive let's check that let's double check that we'll get our fact checkers
on that don't worry about that just real quick orphans richard belzerd's fine he needs a pay bump
and uh all the rest of the cast of law and order pod casd uh what they'll want to meet it so listen
get the numbers up yep or you'll kill richard belzerd get the numbers up good enough
i'll let you meet christopher maloney i know i've been saying these two busy to meet with you and he
is but i'll carve out some time in his schedule it's a nicer word i like to do the carrot and
the stick so the stick is you're canceled second part first prize is christopher maloney okay second
prize is you're canceled um yeah we'll make that happen i said you're not just talking about like
you're gonna buy a cameo of mr maloney are you no he's made crystal make time for me um i don't
know if it sweetens the pot at all but i will trade you three orphans for like 10 minutes hang
out with christopher maloney no i've got plenty right now i'm stocked up so don't sweat it wait
then why would you take my orphans for humidor's listen listen uh-huh i gotta get out of here
okay it's been a pleasure um kind of turning into beetle juice a little bit so i gotta listen i i
gotta go yeah get the fuck out of here hey you know what i miss him like it's weird because when
he was here like i didn't he didn't go down he didn't go down the stairs he just shut the door
he's listening there okay great he kind of he stood there he fell well he tripped a little
bit which is kind of does confirm my suspicions that he was quite drunk um during his appearance
on this show should we do questions yeah that would be nice i was i was kind of enjoying just
you know freeform a little bit but uh i'd love to i'd love to get in you know justice right
fuck this show now the show can begin also my third i have a trip planned once things return
to normal optimistic once things return to the new normal perhaps to go on once we've established a
new society yeah uh once to go on a bachelor party on a houseboat as a prank we have purchased
a dissolving swimsuit however we are at a loss as to how we can get the groom to wear in the
water without him becoming suspicious what should we do that's from bear bummer in canada well good
news is you've probably given yourself i don't know 36 months uh head start on this show we'll
get the whiteboard out and we'll uh we'll start devising a an intricate an intricate plan now i
am going to say i have not done any research into this perfect um but based off of things i know
about things that dissolve i'm willing to bet that perhaps the quality of material of this swimsuit
may be noticeably different dead giveaway situation yes standard swimsuit material
not i'm going to live in fear every time i enter a body of water that i have been pranked and now
my meat and two veg is about to pop out and that is no good i do think what it boils down to is
uh of of top of my head presents to give i can think of i got you this swimsuit
is uh it's a real left fielder that's a real curveball as they say uh i i can think of maybe
two friends of mine but if they got me a really cool looking swimsuit but even then if i was a
company that made dissolvable swimsuits i don't think i'd put a lot of time into the design
process we gotta strike gifting the swimsuit like that's not gonna work and so now we're
getting into a scenario where you have to steal all of his swimsuits and then when it's time to
swim you're like oh don't worry you can borrow my pair actually that's it that's a fucking great
idea and that's gonna work you can borrow my paper thin like pair of syndrome hey it's the
only one we got do you want to get in the fucking river or not what if your friend is like i'll just
swim nude um you guys have been talking a lot of shit and now i'm gonna give it to you real okay
dissolving shorts stag do holiday party bachelor joke prank swim shorts we're gonna head on over
to ebay okay world's largest hundred dollar repository to talk about what is uh depicted
in this image as the original prank short okay this is coming to us from a seller called stag
do shorts and the only thing they sell is dissolving shorts that's a cool business you
made it's a cool business they made there are copies of our item being sold on the web please
be careful you only get one chance at this which is so true which is so true
oh i can't one chance a prank short you do it once it burns his dick off it's like
unfortunate fool me once shame on you i will try again jump in again
prank your mates with these shorts once in the pool a chemical reaction between the special
thread and the water dissolves the thread making the shorts just come away at the sides leaving
your friend naked in the pool huh shorts can be worn as normal but within seconds of bin in water
the fun starts watch your friend's face go from confused to embarrassed as he scrambles to cover
up all you need to do is hide your friend's short best done before you get to hotel offer them your
spare pair and it's all set try my full lifeguard set make your victim the pool lifeguard oh no
jumps in same will happen no the other listings that's a fucking that's a fucking wild way of
doing it yeah what a high risk scenario bachelor pool party hell yeah not you dylan i know it's
your special time but you got to be the lifeguard that's what you do when a group of friends go
swimming someone's got a lifeguard yes now i am watching a video of this happening oh trav trav
and uh it's this poor man appears to be in the middle of a hotel like a very public place yeah
as his clothing is actively failing him all right and i would say that this goes very quickly from
oh he's got kind of a smirk on his face what is happening to i'm gonna get arrested i'm i'm in a
public place and my all my bits are gonna be out we should probably make it clear the three of us
are having a lot of fun here this is uh it sort of ethically reprehensible and genuinely uh should
be a legal sort of uh thing and you shouldn't get your friend's privates out um as a joke uh
that's that seems like that's we're all on the same page i didn't want people to write in and
be like so you like this particular like this uh no it's inappropriate to get anyone's bits out
without their explicit consent i will say they have a few more safety recommendations here
oh boy how well mentioned first off is this at the end it says keep dry which yes iron iron on
cool with no steam why the fuck am i ironing this on what for formal dissolving shorts occasions
hey try on these crisp crisp yeah try my crisp pleated shorts do not let your ma'am wash them
to make them nice for you going away yes this happened did it if the in the unlikely event
of a problem with the shorts they must be returned for inspection that's a cool it's a cool gig yeah
these shorts didn't fall apart i'm a failed dissolving shorts inspector i love it you gotta
throw these away i'm watching the same video that travis is watching and it's just kind of a bummer
because just all of his friends laughing and it's like get it your dick and he's like i yeah i guess
so this youtube video is i'm now looking at a man's whole balls on youtube i didn't know you
could do that on youtube yeah don't do this don't do this thing that's actually the easiest uh
option i'm glad we all got there together uh can i do a yahoo you know what would be fun
what's that you wear them and under those you have another slightly smaller pair of swim trunks
that say like happy bachelor party they're not today friend but even that's a that's an even
longer walk isn't it travis because it's like you have to make them think you're wearing dissolving
swim trunks which they may not know is a thing so that's a hard seller just like boy i hope these
don't dissolve when i get in the water like some swim trunks are named to have you guys heard about
those dissolving syndromes these aren't them right you guys would tell me right yes these aren't my
normal swim trunks but um do they feel funny here i go cannonball i don't know i'm gonna get i feel
terrible i can't believe you my friends will do this to me when we're here to celebrate derrick's
nuptials how could you we're all just trying to have a good time and you're trying to expose my
genitals without my explicit consent look at this derricking gotcha gotcha my pp's not out nice try
though um what are you talking about you pranked yourself chris yes and i almost had me here's a
here's a yahoo that was sent in by several folks thank you everyone who sent this in it's yahoo
answers user josh who asks what's next for knives yes knives are completely useless in this new age
of guns and drones in my opinion they are going to have to change the designs of knives and add
interesting and useful new features to compete with guns and drones what do you think is the
next evolution of knives i enjoyed this question more before i read this additional information
because i like knives more in the abstract rather than as hurting hurting tools tools for hurting
i i would also argue that um knives still do things that guns and drones don't do
oh sure yeah stab for one yeah cut yeah point poke poke that's a that's about a slash slice i
mean that's about it no you like you use it to uh you know what if you are a a person who is lost
in the wilderness it's a lot easier to use a knife to like cut down stuff for shelter than a drone
uh or a gun yeah or a gun totally i think if you were ordering them knife would be easiest to cut
down some branches then gun then drone in that order i think that the issue here is if you if
they want to make cooler bigger better gun they can just make a bigger gun problem with knife
you make a knife too big it's sword it's a sword so it still does need to be a knife
um that's all proportions though isn't it hmm oh you're saying if you're a bigger person
if the hilt is also gargantuan then you could still say that it's a knife yeah or you could
have uh if if paul hogan's around you could if he says it's a knife he gets to indicate basically
what's not a knife and what is a knife he's really busy yeah he is pretty busy i you know what i like
you know what i like when they have those knives that do other things but they're not just knives
it's like here's knives in here and also uh it's a bottle opener and also it's got like a little
wrench in there that's fun to me but maybe they take it further and it's like it's a knife and
it's a sandwich right or like it's a knife and oh god oh wait this is topical let me try again can
i try again yeah please it's a knife the knife sandwich thing was uh pretty stupid okay but let
me try let me try let me try again this is really topical with uh a lot of viral stuff that's been
going on on the internet right now so uh okay it's it's a knife but then you go to pick it up it's
cake what okay this is actually a perfect thing is it yeah this is a perfect time for me to stop
the entire show and at i missed it the thing that the inception of it and i only caught the after
shocks of that particular meme and it has it before i i couldn't piece together that it was
some sort of meme and i thought i was kind of losing it for just a little bit so what's going
on there with that go ahead and walk me through that please well it all began that sounds pretty
boring are you sure you want him to do that if he could do it in 12 seconds it began with a viral
video where it's like oh this looks like a roll of toilet paper no we're cutting into it it's cake
this looks like a bottle of lotion oh we're cutting into it it's cake but at no point did
they say look at this it looks like cake no it's actually a roll of toilet paper that would have
been way more impressive to me that's true i can wipe my butt with a kick uh i'm sorry i'm gonna
stop the podcast i'm gonna stop the stopping the podcast to say griffin walk me through that real
quick i don't want to fuck this this episode in particular has been like here's a funny awesome
badass thing that i just said and you're like show your work fuck that i think uh we've danced
around what's next for knives and what we can do is sort of knife innovators sharper i think you're
you eventually you reach a sort of like atomic like limit there like a sort of a sort of like
you can split an atom right and that's dangerous because those motherfuckers are all over the place
uh so second like a second blade but oh i've got it like a but but running perpendicular
to the first blade or like coming out the side of the hilt or back on the back like you're uh
like you're um uh the freaking red the guy the gentleman from uh phantom menace yep
ms mr maul i believe is his name dr maul esqire i knew he was a zebrack but i couldn't remember
his name that's fucked up now i i let me pitch this i i and i'm gonna picture it try to describe
it and i don't understand how the inner workings would you know work but imagine a tube right and
you load the knife into it and it is pressurized in some way that you can release that pressure
and the knife shoots forth from the tube and bears itself into whatever you're pointing it at
i mean i'm again i was more thinking about kitchen innovations but i have had some trouble
with sweet potatoes that i imagine knife gun would help me out with damn you think whoever
invented the bayonet was like i'm gonna take the rest of the year off this is the best guys guys
guys guys guys check it out you know how we since we got gun and like we've just been sort of rolling
over like hulk me has been going wild since we got gun but we all kind of still miss sword
check it the fuck out i did a kick-ass job today uh i i enjoyed that in the movie the old guard
did you guys see that flag with charlie's throne and a bunch of other people in it no no um yeah
it was good and they they they've been alive for a very long very long time and they're very good
at murder and they always bring gun but then also ax is with them they bring ax too and it
seems weird sitting point out like gun can't do everything they need to do they they need
ax still to to come to come to the party i wonder if it's like a security ax like it just makes you
feel better i guess well if gun acts up and turns against you it's like a little old lady who used
an ax to chop up all her guns exactly there's not a lot of moving parts in ax you know it's hard
there's not a lot of points of failure for ax gun who even knows how that who knows what the fuck's
going on in there it's like my computer stick heavy part sharp edge done we love it you know
what i love what's that juice the maximum fun network okay and our extended podcasting family
got it um this is the max fun drive where i know it's weird that's the subtitle i know it's weird
it's been weird for months it's not less weird now but if and and basically it works like this
the shows that you listen to on the maximum fun network are funded and made possible by you and
um i know that you probably hear that a lot on like npr or whatever is very true a maximum fun
is 100 directly true on npr they're fucking fucking lying thank you yeah they're not they're
they're fine but some of them might be we don't know might be but uh we we rely on you to pledge
a few bucks a month if you like the stuff that we do or other shows on the network do
please consider joining maximumfund.org forward slash join is the link um they have tiers as low
as like five bucks a month if you can pledge five bucks a month you get like a bajillion hours of
bonus content it's absolutely buck wild and if if you can join at ten dollars a month you can get a
max fund membership card and a cool pin and all the bonus content so um it's a very it's a very
tantalizing offer and it really i can't actually express to you how important these donations are
to our way of life um and to being able to make this show as our job and do all the other stuff
that we do um it is all possible thanks to people that that are are joining the network and and
helping support these shows and i really i can't thank you enough it it it honestly means the world
to us we have a lot of fun here but it is uh it's a big deal um yeah i just said it maximumfund.org
slash join i don't actually know if you said the url but uh click on the link of my voice and go
to maximumfund.org slash join and look at the different uh pledge levels and uh help us out
if you can uh how about another question can you know i love that thank you so much that i was
about to it's so funny i was about to say it and then you can i can i get a hand on the ball yeah
trap yeah i desire another question to be delivered to me upon a platter of gold it can never just be
the thing the finest questions no humanity bring me up a spoke question uh my mom texted me today
and said she wanted to get into bitcoin she asked me whether it was a good investment and she started
small i don't know why she wants to get involved with this stuff and i'm pretty sure bitcoin is a
scam my question is is it ethical to help my only mother invest in investing cryptocurrency and that's
from cryptoskeptic all money is a scam when you think about it guys go off because it's all just
made up bits and boops bullshit oh this piece of paper is worth this much metal go off go off it's
fucking nothing that said i think bitcoin is even more so bitcoin is absolute i mean yes but okay
i can answer some of these questions i i know the exact right time to get into bitcoin was three
months ago every single time at any point in history the right time to do it was before you
ever started uh doing it right so so that that is that was a challenge bitcoin is one of those
blind spots for me where if someone who was older came to me and said so justin what is
the deal with bitcoin i feel like i would have to just sort of freeze in this and remain perfectly
still and silent until they thought i was something was wrong with me and they left the room because
that would be so complete would be my ignorance that i think it would lower my stock sort of
permanently in there like when their internet broke right they wouldn't come to the j man they
wouldn't listen to my recommendations on tv shows like any well and the problem is is even if you
were able to explain it to them they would believe you less it would they would it would
seem more like you were fucking with them than if you just stood there silent like a statue
because the truth is bitcoin basically boils down to um i'm gonna send you a jpeg and i'm gonna tell
you how much that jpeg is worth then someone else is gonna say hey give me that jpeg and then i'm
gonna tell you how much that jpeg is worth it's it's it's all based on like perceived i'm actually
feeling more calm listening to you talk makes me feel more confident yeah right i actually travis
thank you i do feel like thank you for cheering me up i do feel better uh listening to you try
to explain that's all it is it's all perceived desperately clutch at any sort of cognizant
thoughts about bitcoin perceived value because the irony is as we these three goobers sit here
and even just say every time we say the word bitcoin bitcoin becomes a little more valuable
it's just it increases a little bit because it's like i've heard about bitcoin that's something
right that is something that is all it is i can't get your mom into it now she'll be rich in five
days i uh heard through the grapevine about the uh very serious twitter hack that happened last
week where uh a bunch of different big accounts got got and those big accounts did ask people
to send them bitcoin and it's bad it's a terrible uh it's a terrible invasion of privacy and given
twitter's sort of uh global political importance i guess that's like a harrowing thing but i do
just want to dial in uh-huh that this probably did work on some people some people were uh
successfully bamboozled by this and i do wonder if barack obama's tweet president barack hussein
obama a lot of people forget about these things important to me if he got anybody with i am giving
back to my community due to covet 19 all bitcoin sent to the address below will be sent back
doubled if you send back one thousand dollars i will send back two thousand dollars then there's
the bitcoin link then president barack hussein obama said only doing this for the next 30 minutes
enjoy why really why does me why does barack have all of this bitcoin saved up why does he do that
why is he doubling it why is it just for the net why is he doing a supermarket sweep
bonus round why did he tell me to enjoy sending him the money so he can double the money how
why would that be the only exchange why not just i'll send you let me hey say hey and i'll send
you some bitcoin why is the exchange part necessary at all i am giving back to my community
my community of people who have and know what bitcoin is enjoy for 30 minutes i'm your president
barack obama and your former president and i do want you to send me the bitcoin but do not sweat
because i'm going to send back twice as much as you send me i know what bitcoin is you see these
swordfish sunglasses i'm wearing and i want you to enjoy this and my cousin doug has a great
investment opportunity that he says is a sure thing so all i need is your bitcoin and then i
will invest in this slug racing circuit and then i oh shit we're broke ah damn it fucking billy
gates tweets it fucking elon musk tweets it and is like hey i have bitcoin come and get it
for 30 minutes enjoy then i think like those fucking nerds probably know what's up president
barack obama swooping in and being like i also have bitcoin come get it 30 minutes baby i've got
30 minutes worth of bitcoin travis um i'd love to dive more into your knowledge of an understanding
of bitcoin um so griffin do you understand bitcoin mining uh it's where they use graphics cards to
get the bitcoin and keep me from being able to find the graphics cards travis can you tell me
how computers make bitcoins with bitcoin mining and i griffin yeah i want you to judge and i want
i want you to hear travis's and then i want you to hear the real answer and then you judge which is
just fucking wild now okay i want everyone to know i could do the thing where i'm like i don't
fucking know i'm a cool jock but i'm going to do my best purely yes please from context yes
i'm going to say bitcoin mining is when there's like some ai just searching around the web looking
for just it's kind of like the loose change of bitcoin wherever there's like point zero zero
zero zero zero zero zero one percent of a bitcoin or whatever that someone has like forgotten about
or maybe while they were doing a transaction it got rounded down or up or whatever and that
that ai just scoops it on up and saves it for this sounds fucking wrong okay so here's the right answer
here so you get a there's all these really hard math problems okay on the bitcoin network there's
all these really hard math problems and they're so hard that the computer has to both work very hard
but also get lucky to solve it and the the um the chances against them doing it is like one in 13
trillion so it's very unlikely that they can solve this very hard math problems but if they do they
win a prize okay wait so hold on so there's a computer goodwill hunting its way through a
website and like standing before the whiteboard and trying to get lucky which what that even means
in the terms of computing is both baffling and terrifying to me and the computer is trying to
get lucky and if a computer solves a math problem a very hard yes thank you really can't very hard
math problem it gets some the computer gets some with the prize yes well i mean technically belongs
i'm sure i mean the computer does not have rights whoa all right all right but so its owner would
own the uh um you know the bitcoin but yes that is that is how i understand it is that the computer
the computer doesn't really does a bunch of hard math and eventually gets it right and gets a
little prize that's a bitcoin huh i think amazingly and i i this is of course uh completely subjective
but i think my answer made more sense than the thing you said justin's envisions a world that
makes me much happier because is there some sort of deranged mathematician trillionaire somewhere
that's like i i cannot die until these impossible formulae have been um discovered who this is
who makes the question bitcoin makes the question no okay they only really they only release
a few but okay this is not fuck this is fucking true they only release a little bit of extra
puzzle bonus puzzles they release the puzzles on the back of their menus they release the
puzzles in what's called a block reward and the block reward is halved every uh 210 000
blocks around every four years so in 2009 it was 50 in 2013 it was 25 in 2018 it was 12.5
and uh somewhere this year it'll be 6.25 right so they only release a few puzzles
a few new puzzles they're releasing less puzzles just to get the bitcoin out there but who's
making up the puzzles justin the the computer creates the so the computer creates a puzzle
it can't this is this is probably the creator can be surprised i can't solve and also the
puzzles get harder every two weeks they just throw an extra three in there i didn't know there's
three in okay this was an x but now it's a z fuck you you are you are 44 000 times more likely to
win the powerball jackpot with a single lottery ticket then you are to pick the correct hash
on a single try which is the correct putt to solve this fucking puzzle you will not solve
this puzzle do they have any word searches no it's all jumbled but it's hard but it's hard ones
they're like this is like nine letters so hopefully that helps hey just let your mom listen
10 minutes she's out just just in case our investments in bitcoin don't uh pay out i would
like to invite us all for a quick sojourn to uh to the money real quick before we do ads folks
this just occurred to me that you might have listened to that whole cryptocurrency section
and thought you know that's not like a cry for help from the macro so i should explain how
cryptocurrency works to them and uh you you would be wrong oh wow what a swing and a miss that
interpretation would be you could not be further off my friend nope actually you know what i'm
perfectly happy where i'm at i'll say i'll say this if you do you do need those just dump them
in my mentions and this is a service i can begin to provide to you justin and travis because i
i ain't popped in on those bad boys in a bit i do i i send it to me and i will i will send the
information out to my brothers i can be point of first contact i i'd actually rather use this as
a test because if you send it to us we'll know you skip the ass yeah oh yeah and that and it
makes you a an immoral thief yeah basically so please do not send it to us we don't want to know
how it works please uh you know who else isn't welcome in my mentions is uh plaque and uh tartar
build up and these guys are my teeth's worst enemies but do you know who my teeth's best
friends is is quip quips the good electric toothbrush that uh it covers your your all
your oral care essentials uh it's got these timed sonic vibrations with 30 second pulses
to guide a dentist recommended two minute routine and uh if you got a little kiddo smaller mouse
smaller teeth they got a little quip and it's right it's the right size for you uh i don't
i i don't like that that assumption was made griffin because just real quick baby dot even
though she is six months does have the mouth and teeth of a 40 year old i know that about her yeah
and it sucks because it doesn't look very good no it doesn't now but when she's 70 and she's
yeah sure it's gonna look amazing uh the the quip brush head toothpaste and floss refills are
automatically delivered on a dentist recommended schedule every three months for just five dollars
each a friendly reminder when it's time for a refresh and to stay committed to your oral health
and shipping is free i have been using equip for a couple years now and uh it's it's really really
nice back when i was traveling the freaking little mirror mount turns into a holster for it is real
slick um now it's mostly just a mirror mount but it's a good one if you go to get quip dot com slash
my brother right now you can get your first refill for free that's your first refill free at get quip
dot com slash my brother that's get quip dot com slash my brother quip the good habits company
hey you guys know what i always say what if you're in a hitch you gotta fix your stitch you've heard
me say you've heard me say that right i've heard you yell that yeah i yell i've heard you sort of
scream that i got some sort of primal animal frustrated sure you know because people are
wearing shows like they're wearing clothes and shows that aren't their size or style and like
they paid too much for them and they're like i don't know where to get other clothes and i'm like
if you're in a hitch you gotta fix your stitch because then you could just go to stitch fix and
they're coming in that focuses on like getting you the clothes you actually want because they
have a personal stylist that will work with you to get you clothes you love and get them to you
effortlessly it's a completely different way to shop uh and you'd like fill out your own profile
just go to stitch fix dot com slash my brother and you'll pick out looks that are personalized for
you colors you like uh styles you like and a budget you like you pay a twenty dollar styling
fee for each fix which is credited towards anything you keep schedule at any time there's no
subscription required plus shipping returns and exchanges are easy and free get started today at
stitch fix dot com slash my brother and you'll get 25 off when you keep everything in your fix
that's stitch fix dot com slash my brother for 25 off when you keep everything in your fix stitch
fix dot com slash my brother when you're in a hitch you gotta fix your stitch it's not catching
on it says it right here in the car i'm reading it it's green it says do not skip do not skip
travis man my throat is still messed up man it's terrible um so hey this one comes to us from the
uk and this is weird because normally the uk does not make it into a lot of um a lot of munch squads
but this one is from heinz uk and so it was sent to me by graham roebuck who just all around jeez
just the all-arounder can't be stopped salad cream ice cream huh heinz launches heinz creams
DIY ice cream kits now it's important for you to know heinz creams is with a z is z at the end
of heinz so a z at the end of cream what's sauce for the goose is sauce for the gander uh july is
nationalized cream month and whilst trips to ice cream parlors may look a little different this
year heinz has launched a selection of diy ice cream kits using a range of heinz sauces you can
make your very own heinz creams at home and celebrate national ice cream month from the
comfort of your kitchen so you go to their fucking website and there's a there's a place right there
where the crime is where you it says click here to do crime uh-huh and when you click it you go to
a page that is heinz creams and um if you let's say you wanted the mayo cream and i and i don't
and i and i don't but let's say you did relish the creamy taste of heinz good mayonnaise
it's actually heinz seriously good mayonnaise but the seriously is in brackets so i took it
upon myself to leave it out for comedic effect relish the creamy taste of heinz you can't say
we're talking about toppings you probably shouldn't use relish no as a as your okay relish
the creamy taste of heinz seriously good mayonnaise in an ice cream this make your own heinz creams
kit includes the equipment you'll need to make a heinz mayonnaise ice cream it includes heinz good
mayonnaise sauce a branded gift box a recipe card what if it didn't have that yeah it's like i don't
know you fucking figure it out here's some mayonnaise and a win and it's not pre-measured
let's be honest it seems like portions are way off it's wild i feel like the person writing this
press release had benjamin button disease and jack disease because it's like with each paragraph
they're sort of like age seems to be going backwards put good mayonnaise in cream sauce
in ice cream yay it also includes a reusable ice cream tub uh that's profane so you make mayonnaise
ice cream in it then you're like don't don't don't toss that vicki i'm gonna save that i
want to use it again for anything else and lastly a limited edition engraved golden scoop and spoon
it doesn't say what's engraved on it but i'm assuming it's the word perfect
i can only imagine um so let's go back to this press release here uh i will let you
know i'm looking at the website and the bad news is that the heinz ketchup creams
is sold out i can't get that anymore you can get bbq creams huh you can get saucy sauce creams
these are all challenging there's a saucy sauce creams and then there's heinz salad creams what
is salad cream it's a tangy taste it's like uh salad dressing no i think i put that together
but like there's lots of different types of salad dressing well this is salad cream you get it it's
it's like it would be a good ice cream is is the good way to imagine it um so they've they've
listed the it says the tangy taste of salad creams makes it one of britain's most loved sauces and
now it's a heinz creams that zing we all know and love can be paired with the delicious sweetness
of summer strawberries on top of refreshing ice cream huh um heinz bbq creams is sweet sticky and
tongue tinglingly delicious oh water and flavor of classic heinz bbq sauce in a heinz creams
teamed with maple syrup pecans and perhaps a sprinkling of bacon bits and this sweet and
smoky ice cream will really pack a punch hey just real quick when i put something on my tongue
if the reaction my tongue has is to tangle that is body that is poison that is bad body to reject
it that is a bad thing to happen oh it's my whole mouth is buzzing um david chalbert the senior
brand manager at heinz sauce says this summer is looking different for many of us and while we might
be staycationing or staying at home more than in other years it doesn't mean you have to miss out
on the joys of a good ice cream heinz sauces are here to help hey david honestly you're right about
the first part this summer is looking different for but fuck you for thinking the answer is do
you want to make a ice cream out of mayonnaise does that fix it yeah everything's up in the
air now ice cream out of mayonnaise did we fix it it can't hurt right listen everything's fucked
do you want to make ketchup ice cream in your own house we've tried no one's no one's watching no
one's watching anything goes they think of it this way once it's all back to the new normal
you're probably not going to want to make salad cream ice cream you probably won't do that you'll
be so happy to return to this to the life you knew we give you the ultimate summer mashup heinz
cream a diy ice cream kit with an added summery squeeze of one of your favorite heinz sauces
so you needn't miss out on one of the sauciest of sweet treats or six during a summer of social
distancing david fuck off it's not the ultimate summer mashup you absolute maniac it's ketchup
mixed with ice cream stop it we might we know it might seem like a bit of a crazy combo to some
but with heinz always at the forefront of innovation anything is possible hey david if
if anything is possible could i request a vaccine could that be first on your list
you fucking ketchup wizard you think if anything is possible you think when david turned in the
first draft of this press release press release somebody said like do we want to add any qualifiers
here where you just said forefront of innovation do we want to put like forefront of like dressing
innovation or something yeah sauce innovation no innovation no anything is possible we're the
bleeding edge of all technology both food and medical and we're gonna make this summer work for
you if you this is just like the bud light um the bud light asking robin robin things if if i call
you and i'm like hey this has all been really hard for everybody i'm just checking in to see
how you're doing what are you up to and you say i'm making mayonnaise ice cream i'm going to call
the authorities to come like check on you yeah because i'm worried that something has gone
terribly wrong i bet it's good though it's probably good is the one where you said the
bacon bits that got me a little bit the bbq ice cream with some bacon bits and pecans yeah i mean
yeah i'd be pretty good listen if i could order these to america i probably already would be
i find that i find the idea like the ketchup and barbecue sauce i can almost i can almost see my
no i'll see you away there we're into like it's mayonnaise like that's hard that gets a little
more challenging if it's like mayo creams and just the number of z's on this page guys it's
quite a it's tough there's a there is a lot of z's in this in this i bet a thousand island ice
cream 45 z's on the page um hey can i do another yahoo yeah yeah of course um geez i got a two
here i'm debating which one's the best i mean i don't know that this one is the most sort of gut
bustingly funny but it is a conversation that i'm curious about that i feel like justin's going to
have a lot to say uh sent in by several people again it's by yahoo answers user misty who asks
what is the best place to work in at the mall huh well the answer i think is obvious but
i just want to fucking talk about this i just kind of want to send jokes out yeah can we just
send jokes out of the room for about 75 minutes earlier in the episode so i think there's a
precedent established okay you know what let's just say i was in all i a jokes fuck off yeah
fuck off we're gonna settle this i have worked a couple mall jobs do you call your phone jokes
no i don't call my phone jokes that's a very good idea though if i could program it to be like hey
stop it i i've worked several mall jobs and i think right now don't need your bonafides
just need an answer if i was going to pick a mall job i think it would be
like a cell phone case kiosk whoa what yeah it feels low impact like i don't think you're dealing
with customers left and right it's a very narrow window of information you have to be briefed on
you get to sit down for a lot of it very little oversight over what you do most of the time when
i see people working there they're like on their phones or in some cases even like you playing
games travis you've just hit the you've just hit the biggest issue with it when i see people working
there if you put yourself into the cell phone kiosk what you've basically done is put yourself
into a human zoo yeah you are an exhibit at the mall museum constant constant scrutiny everyone
looking at you what are they looking at the phone what are they up to and it's that thing of like
that judgy thing that people do where it's like i can't believe they're on their phone when they
were just on their phone like 15 seconds ago and they just don't happen to be on their phone right
at that exact second they're it's an incredible level of scrutiny it'd be a terrible job you've
picked arguably one of the one of the most stressful i mean i disagree only because i
stand by the low oversight thing like that for me and any job i've ever had is a boss who is looking
to make themselves especially in a retail environment looking to make themselves feel
essential and so they are just looking for things to point out so that they feel like they're doing
their job if you're at the cell phone kiosk or the hillshire farms kiosk or any kiosk your boss
is going to be able to fucking clock you from a hundred yards they can monitor your progress
without you even there are no corners there's not the telltale like who's what what kiosk boss is
like checking in if you own a kiosk i think you didn't buy it because you were ready to be super
hands-on travis they're the face of super sterling silver of course i'm going to check on them they
are the front line of customer interaction and i'm i'm in charge of making sure that our customers
always walk away with silver and a smile there is a chaos whatever engraved gift as the uh at the
uh kinwood town center here in cincinnati where the product that they sell is glass cubes where
the center of them has been laser etched with some kind of photograph of perhaps a beloved pet
or a child or a memaw that you want to remember and i see that every time i go to the kinwood
mall and i think that's a front for something there's no way that they sell enough engraved
what are you doing today going to the mall cool can i come along sure i guess if you want to watch
me stand around and look at cubes for an hour well i'm trying to i'm trying to pick the perfect
grandma tesseract uh i'm trying to i'm locking my grandma in this in this holocron she's wronged
krypton and i need to yeah yep haven't seen memaw since i banished her to the phantom zone all that
that's my memaw's horcrux 29.99 at the kinwood mall believe it or not uh okay so that's incorrect
griffin i mean here's what's here's here's what's making this tough for me uh i feel like uh like
an auntie ans is is thrilling you see an auntie ans and then you probably do i assume you get to
eat some auntie ans at some point or at least you get like a dope discount but at at what point i
love the smell of an auntie ans down the you know wafting down an airport terminal or something like
that sure but that smell i imagine after i'm gonna be really generous and say like three weeks is
going to be like a complete nightmare i'll see any any any restaurant any food service you are
going to run into that definitely happen at the og uh love the breadsticks love the chicken scampi
love so many of their offerings could not stand it after you know and not only while you're there
the problem is especially with something like that pretzel smell it permeates eventually gets
in you that's right it's it's gonna get in your clothes which will then get in your car which
will then like you take you change you'll have your uniform at home and like your home will
smell faintly of pretzels it will haunt you my friend tommy red used to work at fazoles
and if he stored his uniform in the cab of his truck when he would give me a ride to school i
would insist on riding in the truck bed so so vibrant was the smell of this fazoles uniform
this this bizarro uh anti-air freshener um it's gonna make you hate if you work at a
food you love you're gonna hate it a few weeks in if you work at a place you hate you're gonna
hate it more so food service is incorrect i'm gonna give you my hot take and you got you all
can you've had approximately 400 jobs so i'll i will defer to you this is not one i've had
but it is i'm pretty sure of what the the best job would be and that is the vape shop at the mall
so vape shop is fucking cool because you just sit around and vape and if you're and your boss
opens the door and they're like what are you doing just sitting around and vaping you'd be like uh
yeah i am i'm both advertising our product and becoming more knowledgeable about it and i'm
sitting here cranking some major fucking cotton yeah and spooking the the the guy over at macy's
uh uh uh i think that the vape shop would be a very chill place to work morally i don't know the
science is out yes when you're loved but that's it that's the perfect fix is when your loved ones
are like uh the science is out but what science we have you know it's it's i'm i'm worried about
you you can be like hey it's for work they actually made a rule at the vape shop at the
honeyton mall at first they were allowed to crank cotton 24 sev and then they made a rule that you
couldn't crank cotton at all and to watch the the discrepancy in employee satisfaction was
so palpable it could be felt at the american cookie factory it was so so distinct did this
go from like wow this is a fucking very good job to i've got to get the fuck out of here and indulge
my addiction to aerosolized nicotine um boy between the bitcoin and vape chat this episode
has it has a particular sort of flavor to it once again you can tweet this one griffin macaroy yeah
hit me up with all those um hey and while you're doing that as long as you're on the internet
consider going to maximumfund.org join consider uh becoming a member of the network at whatever
level you are able that you feel comfortable with if you want to support us and the shows we make
and the maximum fun network as a whole uh we have been doing this for over 10 years now and we are
only you know able to do it as our jobs and have able to make it a bigger part of our lives because
of the max fund drive it is a a truly very important thing to us um so please consider
maximumfund.org join look at the different levels look at the different uh pledge gifts and um yeah
think about it and and thank you bad news boy it's me i snuck in this time okay we read you big shot
listen yeah bad news your one your one membership show no yeah i've just one more person you know
what i'll give you another day if just one person logs on to maximumfund.org forward slash join
and uh joins the family as it were i'll save your little show okay can't promise maloney can't
promise that no didn't do good enough for that but one person just one that seems pretty low
wow are you that person me that's right listener i can see holy shit um i i'm using some real dark
you're slipping into hugo weaving mr big shot a little bit a little black hat stuff that i my
nephew hooked up for me and i could see and i could see you're not going to that web the web
you're all that i told you about so i need you to head on over there and join the family
and save these boys and they're orphans the cigar orphans yes and thank you to john roger
in the long winters for these for a theme song it's a departure off the album putting the days
to bed and um and thank and thank you thank you so much for listening uh griffin do you have a
final yahoo yeah i mean this one was sent in by am i can't thank you emma it's yahoo answers user
josh who does ask would cremation even work on water pokemon my name is justin mcelroy i'm
travis mcelroy i'm griffin mcelroy it's been my brother my brother me kiss your dad square on the
lips maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned audience supported