The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother mean advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin Tyler McElroy. I'm your middlest brother Travis Patrick McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother 30 under 30 media luminary Patrick Davis Tyler Griffin McElroy.
Right before we started like literally a half a second before Justin went in he whispered
trust me into the microphone and I do but I am scared as hell I think a little bit don't be
scared don't be scared it's just I haven't I can't I couldn't tell you guys about the intro
okay without spoiling the intro all right give it because then we'll miss the the I don't know
how I've managed to sit on it this long but here it comes the best thing it happened yesterday I
was flying after visiting my brother and his beautiful new baby oh yeah I forgot to text
but did you get home all right yeah I'm fine um I don't know why we do that we all text each
other after we get home from a fight like hey I got home all right as if like what's the what's
the opposite I mean I guess there is an opposite right but it's so powerful because you were so
worried about me all day until well I mean that doesn't hold up in this one because you defo
didn't text or anything but I just always assumed that we as macarons just have no object permanence
and like that's why we need people because as soon as they leave our sides like they're gone
they're going forever until we get the text that's like I'm okay I'm fine thank god you're
more you're more likely to get in a car accident than a plane accident so like should I text you
guys like got back from Arby's it's all good don't worry about it you don't do that I don't
for a long it was a long way away Arby's if it was a destination Arby's hmm all Arby's are
destination Arby's just sorry what was the greatest thing you ever saw in the airport
thank you jeebus uh so I went through Houston and I had to take a little tram uh on the way back
from front to from terminal terminal Houston's a buckwild airport by the way Houston looked at how
every other airport was doing it and was like nah we're gonna try a whole other thing you gotta take
a tram to all the terminals and all and our gates board like 10 10 in a group and you gotta wait to
go down to them it's bizarre it's a weird airport uh but I'm navigating this bizarre system and who
should I see on the tram next to me but mister Craig T. Nelson I got a Craig T. Nelson sighting
fresh uh brown leather jacket of course approximately eight feet tall wearing a very
large ring in Texas the prime primo Craig T. Nelson what was his security detail wearing
uh it was uh Louie and Philip which is his nicknames for his biceps because he's Craig T.
Nelson is he towned he's 72 years old he looks fucking fantastic yeah I there is no way this
human man is 72 years old he looked like a demigod yeah he looks amazing which is you
wouldn't think I think Craig T. Nelson has had some times where um I mean I don't think he was
as toned as cut in uh poltergeist for example um but I guess like I guess as he reached his silver
years he was just like it's time to get serious about my health and so Craig T. Nelson got really
um diesel got really yoked I'm into this I'm so jealous just and I'd love a Craig sighting oh it
was like such a good Craig sighting and the best part of this Craig sighting um is that we were
going to the same gate so like not the same gate but the same because the way they do it there
it's like 10 in a group so like we're going to the same area I guess you made me think for a
second that he was going to the same gate as you and he was getting on a plane to Huntington with
you to go see what Huntington was all about no y'all would know about that um it was kind of
weird that went like I did okay this is embarrassing I did have a moment where I was like
I got a tv show I could go say hi to no abort abort you can't hey uh fellow tv star um it's me
hoops remember my show I uh anyway we're going the same area so I got to just observe Craig
in his day-to-day um perfect gentleman obviously um Houston is an absolute nightmare in terms of
shopping it's more restaurants and shopping than gates I walked past three burger places
to get to my gate we take care we take care of you here in Texas um but any I did see I only saw
one person sort of like make the connection because they felt like they had to and uh I heard
the person like he's walking this way and the person's walking towards me and this person just
goes I love your work that's good and I think that's code for I forgot what coach was called
I forgot the show coach I forgot your name I forgot the name of the show coach your work
your work sports teacher my one shot um I did learn from the swirls later that he's uh or was
on Parenthood yeah he was all over Parenthood um also on Grace and Frankie I mean either but
that's the problem I mean and I just kind of reiterate Craig's he wants to look fucking
great great yeah if I looked like Craig T. Nelson looks now and you knew my age you would be like
he's a really that looks that's a good looking 36 like yeah I would be I would swat bodies with
Craig T. Nelson Justin let me ask you a question because this is a calculation I do anytime I
see like a recognizable um celebrity I do a calculation in my head of is this is this the
type of celebrity are they at a place down their career are they the type of person that if I walk
up to them and talk to them they will be happy that someone came up to them or will they be like
uh again I'm just trying to walk almost never will they oh good an interruption my favorite
I'm gonna disagree Griffin because I think there's two ends of the bell curve we're like over here
where we are we're happy when people come up and talk to us yes over here we're like
the kid from Jerry Maguire is he's probably happy when people come up and talk to him
you know what I mean but what about in the middle if I had if I had a fucking walk on roll on coach
where I had four lines in one episode where I was sort of a tertiary character you could not talk
to me you could not approach me you know why because I had hung out with Craig T. Nelson and
I'd gotten some of that stardust on me and then that makes me unapproachable so um yes as as of
right now I am to approach me come on come at me but if they ever reboot coach and I'm on it even
a little bit that's it you missed your window uh Craig T. Nelson does not tweet a lot in case
your I almost tweeted at him and uh his last tweet was in 2011 oh well can you read it um word for
word please I've got a lot of requests to weigh in on the PSU scandal as a former coach I think
we need to protect our kids at abc news yeah I mean that's not a not a bad take yeah this is
very important his first tweet was the man only did seven tweets got in got out did his art got
out you didn't overstay his welcome his first one said my personal assistant told me I should be on
twitter I'm still not convinced this is a good idea and it seems like he never quite bought the
bought the company in line there I have a very sorry Joe good I have a very important question
okay when he says a former coach was he actually a coach in real life at some point
how do you mean as a former coach capital c like as one might like David Tennant might say as a
former doctor that doesn't mean he was a doctor in real life at least Craig T. Nelson saying that
as someone who has embodied the role of coach I have a lot of thoughts on this Craig had a lot
of pretty good tweets in this time it is it is wild um it is wild three-month dalliance with
twitter all of which came in 2011 let's go through his whole body of work then why not
let's buy the whole thing so there were there were a couple of applause and I'm so I'm not gonna
uh okay no actually I'm gonna read all of his tweets this is the entire uh tweet
bibliography of Craig T. Nelson uh his next tweet I can't wait for fall tv to start
check out my new show parenthood nice no that's good a lot of people are like it's like
I like tv just like you like tv mm-hmm and check out my new show parenthood
um his next one is a tweet to Charlie Day says thanks for the shout out on it's always sunny
I really like the show great good good tweet presence so far yeah he's connecting he's figured
out how to like connect with other influencers this is good this is I'm proud of him actually
this is a this is a very buckwild tweet um uh-oh it says is it turning on us at Fox News
and says you should consider following noted author slash outdoorsman Larry Dablemont he just
joined and I love his stuff so what if I could just get this clear hold on Craig T. Nelson is
tweeting at Fox News to tell their Twitter account to follow a guy he knows named Larry
that just joined because he's a noted outdoorsman and he loves this stuff if you click through to
Larry Dablemont it is now registered to someone named Eric Cohen so Larry also this is this is
Craig's fourth tweet and he's telling the Fox News Twitter account has to better utilize the
medium of Twitter um the next tweet dear coach fans I will be he may as well just said dear
everyone dear everyone dear coach dear coach fans I will be making a special appearance in Springfield
Missouri for cider days hashtag cider days I don't know what that is but I'm sad I missed it six
years ago next tweet this man brings it all together he says at Larry Dablemont my agent
encouraged me to read your blog I love it maybe we can get a hunt in when I come in to Missouri
for cider days this is like an ARG what's going on and then he talks about the PSU scandal the end
of cranking out that's that's seriously the seven tweets you meet in heaven that's the only seven
tweets you need is what's up I don't want to be on here but here I am yeah I was on coach I found
this dude anyway this is cool um hey dude hey Fox you should follow this dude hey dude you want
to go home when I come in town for cider days by the way come at me if you're a fan of coach
I think the PSU scandal is really is really really uh bad it's really bad what happened over there
coach out but I I tweeted all I could tweet there's nothing I've hit I oh see that's the
thing you got to spread out your seven subjects of tweet over like several years and he used all
seven twitter subjects up yeah and what Larry Dablemont Larry Dablemont part two and a scandal
he like he hit all the bullets crushed it crushed it I should mention two things the first one is
that is not a verified account oh god there's every chance that might not there is no it is
the best it is the best evidence of Craig T Nelson's twitter presence because I was going to
tweet out and be like Houston what's up check out the whataburger it's dope as hell um but I didn't
do that because he had been off for so long and I thought that would have been a little bit pitiful
secondly welcome to max fun drive week part two uh sorry about spending 13 of your minutes I have
one last thing one last thing one last thing do you think the t in his name stands for twitter
because he's so good at it and then one actual last thing is the answer that question is no
nobody knows what the t stands for because once somebody speaks that out loud he's banished
from this realm can I also say just one I also just want to say I'm sorry for saying that Jonathan
Lipnicki was at the other end of the bell curve of career for most I feel bad about that now I
actually don't know what he's been up to we don't know all I know he's working a bunch it's I reached
it in my brain that was the poll I'm not proud of it I'm so sorry Mr Lipnicki if you're listening
I'm so sorry I'm so so sorry welcome to max fun drive welcome to max fun drive everybody
including Craig T Nelson who I hope is listening at this point and Jonathan Lipnicki who I hope
Johnny Lips uh Jonathan Lipnicki is cut out of wood now he's fucking crazy he's he's also yoked
him and him and Craig T Nelson hit the hit up the iron church together getting ready for Incredibles
2 which is gonna be a live action movie uh anyway so max fun drive huh max fun drive we get paid for
this if you can believe it and it's all thanks to you uh our beloved listeners um we'll tell you
more about the max fun drive in a little bit um we would have more time to do it now but we did
spend 14 and a half minutes talking about Craig T Nelson Craig Twitter Nelson man Craig Twitter
Nelson we uh can we get him verified please can we please verify this six-year-old Twitter account
um max maximum fun dot org forward slash donate is the place to go you'll get all the details
there we're gonna go through them again but it goes like this if you like our show if you like
other shows maximum fun um they take money to put together and this this uh is the one time of year
that we come to you hat in hand say please help us make these radical shows so if you can help us
go to maximum fun dot org forward slash donate right now uh and you get exclusive permission
to skip the next pledge break but uh we're gonna tell you all about the cool stuff you can get
there's gifts there's everything go there right now and get all the details but we need to start
our program because of the extended extended period of time we spent talking about Craig
Twitter Nelson uh here comes our first question I've been dating this guy for a few weeks and
I went to his apartment recently I found out that he lives with two other people but zero tables
there's not even a kitchen table their kitchen area is just a pile of groceries
it's bothering me that my boyfriend doesn't own a table anywhere in his apartment oh my god
how do I buy a table for another person without it being weird that's from tabletop troubles in
Topeka well first of all congratulations to these folks doing it in the Japanese style that's really
cool this is not the Japanese style it's important that everybody they definitely got tables the
tables are maybe a little bit lower than you're used to but they are elevated off the ground
this is an this is an incredible opportunity for you yeah because it's like you're gonna give
them a transformative gift something yeah what if they just don't know yeah what is this what
what is this four-legged high floor what the high floor do you mean the table that I bought you
the up floor um I'm more okay what's more upsetting the lack of tables or
or their kitchen area is just a pile of groceries yeah I'm confused by that like
do they not have a refrigerator either do they live on paper street like they don't have cabinets
they don't have counters how the crap it are we talking here are they in some kind of Frank Lloyd
Wright house where everything is the same level there's no couches there's no counters this is
my new house nasty kitchen and what I've done here is there's no furniture so you just keep all your
your eggs and stuff right on the floor right it's called flat town call it yucky flat town
um I don't I think you should get start off small start off small with like an end table
that you put in the middle slowly a nightstand perhaps um I was gonna suggest actually maybe a
card table because what that does is like I want you to try out this life but if you don't like it
then you can just throw it away or put it in a closet or something let it fold fold it up and
and put it away and then you don't have to ever think about it again so it's not like a you have
to live with this forever kind of situation you only need one really good table right
mm-hmm oh we have a we have a coffee table and a dining room table and like a kitchen counter
and really the coffee table is the only one we really use so you just need the one good table
like what do you play your board games on you just set it down on the floor and hunch over it
that's not good for you or your back you know maybe this is like a life whatever the life-changing
joy of tidying up or whatever the book's called where life's actually think life-changing magic
of tidying up I think yeah when they walk up to their tables they put their hands on it and they
thought does this bring me joy and they thought no this is just a flat surface I hate this actually
guys I got an outside the box one for you does this table bring any of you joy and it's like
you know what kind of thick no all we we just throw our bills on there and then we they piles
up it looks terrible let's not table yeah let's not does this guy does this bring you guys joy
all it does is it sits in this little compartment we never look at it are you talking about the hot
water heater yeah fuck that thing get the fuck out of here I hate you hot water heater it's just
taking up space it's just taking up space and we never see it oh boy my shower is so cold now but
fuck that hot water heater I'm too proud to go back also my metabolism is raging I feel amazing
it's wild my skin is clean and clear and under control um does this bring you joy no it stinks
all the time get rid of it this is the trash can you wanted to get rid of the trash can where's
the trash go all over we did we sort of dissipate the stink by hiding it all over the house
no I can't see what food we have yeah but it's the refrigerator yeah but it hides the food away
I want to see the food it's gone get out of here you joyless cube does this bring me joy it's hard
and I fall on it oh that's the floor now you've gotten rid of the floor it doesn't bring you joy
but I do think it is important to be around for sure now just taking up space no wasting everybody's
time um get them a table you need a fucking table now I'm turning I'm starting to get kind of
frustrated now get them a table is it maybe the apartment's like cramped or something and so
they don't have a lot of table room but it's such an essential you gotta have a table it's
the table's a chair's best friend here's here's my theory this is my working theory on why they
don't have a table when Teresa and I moved from Cincinnati to Los Angeles we got rid of our old
microwave and said we'll just get a new microwave when we get there okay then we got there and did
not immediately buy a microwave and then time began to pass and the momentum of not having a
microwave built up and built up to the point where in the entire two years we lived in Los
Angeles we never bought a microwave because after a while like it there was just no pressure to do
it because it like it already been six months we just hadn't bought one yet and then when we moved
back to Cincinnati the house we moved into had a microwave uh in it already like attached to the
oven and like we remembered oh fuck yeah microwaves are incredible how did we go two years without
one so my theory is these people moved into this place none of them had a table and they said oh
we'll go get one of those and then like they just didn't for a while and now like just time has passed
and they've begun living their lives without a table and they have forgotten how fucking efficient
having a section of the floor raised up to a reachable level is the up floor it's wild um can
you read this next question because i was going to do a yahoo but this next question is funnier
than any yahoo could ever dream to be i just found out the guy i'm dating puts his belt on his pants
before he puts the pants on his body all time am i good or do i need to end things now before i
realize he's actually an alien that's from dating et in boston that's the wildest literally a million
roaches living inside of vincent d'anofrio alien yes yes yes sugar water sugar water sugar water
for sure definitely definitely definitely 100 a bunch of d'anofrio roaches you need to get out of
the house swat maneuvers slice the pie don't let him see you he's a bunch of roaches in his skin
man you have to go you have to go go go go go quick the cab's outside i called it for you already get
in there he's a bunch of roaches in an alien skin suit i think she should probably alert the
authorities oh yeah first because you don't want him to run this grift on some other unsuspecting
earthling person i mean there are some specific authorities you need to call and they are the men
in black because i mean it's it's it's i don't know how you get in touch with the men in black
i don't know what like no what if she calls the men in black the men in black are gonna come and
they're gonna like do the flashy thing to us and all of our listeners and erase this episode they're
gonna erase the episode they've definitely done it before too don't you think yeah that's what
happened to the portland audio from our last live show from our last live show um too close to the
truth we got too close so we did get into some next level shit well they only flashed travis
because we only lost his audio how could a person do this to me how could a person do this to me
i've been trying to run through my head like sometimes we get questions like this and you
think like okay i can see one factor where maybe this is why they do it because this would be but
i cannot imagine an element of this where this system is better where you'd rather have floppy
like just a denim mess that you're trying to thread your yeah your leather friend through
like do you want to start do you want to start your day with some needlepoint like i would rather
i would rather not i would rather just go ahead and put on my pants if that's okay with you
it's it's it would be so much harder to do it's very difficult to get it in your floppy loose
loose trousers and it's so weird to do it's not good i don't understand especially when
you picture this person just sitting there in you know they're i was gonna say me undies but
probably not me undies but that me undies seems above the level of this part they're just sitting
there and like you know their um briefs just like calmly silently threading a belt through their
pants now i devil's advocate and i'm using that term literally because it's possible this person
is actually the devil um sometimes it can be hard to get it in that back loop that you can't see so
good that's right under your sacrum or whatever and so maybe this is this person's maybe they're
on some next level shit right like we always got to give them the benefit of the doubt maybe they're
on some next level shit i have some trouble getting in that loop not a lot of trouble that
has led me to institute some pretty major life changes like this person has but maybe they just
like tried to get into that back loop one too many times it was like fuck this i'm doing it off my
body from now on i'm done missing loops i'm done with the whole thing but but missing loops is one
of the top 10 reasons that you have an so like you get into relationships so that you have someone
else in your life to say like hey you missed a loop you missed a loop stupid um all right i'm
gonna don't can i read a yahoo now or is do we have more things to just drag this person for
i just don't i'm trying i feel like okay i feel like our specific brand of comedy is two things
one so random just really like like family guy used to be yeah but the other thing about it is
that it's positive i want it's like travis said i want to come up with something before i want to
leave some sliver of light so this person is just not like we've just banished their beloved to
some sort of extra realm and i really would like to come with some sliver of light that might
give them like just let them sleep because this is a comedy podcast and they're not going to act
on any of this but they do have to sleep next to this person i want to give them something to cling
to here's what you should do here's what you need to do once again i think just like the table
scenario tell this person like hey have you ever thought about putting your belt on after you put
your pants on and then watch the light come over their face as they're like yeah this is another
it's another opportunity to change this person's life maybe um i have a changing joy of putting
on your pants and then putting the belt on putting on putting your pants on normal like a person
marie khan marie says you should um touch all the articles of clothing and let them sort of tell you
what they want that you should thank them after like if you wear your shoes all day you should
thank your shoes and um sorry who's this saying who's saying these wild things marie kondo for
of the author of the life changing magic of tidying up okay um which traps and i both
reference now um and i guess we're just that we're just kind of a fixture yeah um but she
says you should talk to your clothes maybe he talked to his pants and they were like oh you
know it'd be so nice treat me so right hey douglas um as long as i've got you here um you know it
would be just delectable if you would use those two sweet sweet supplying fingers to pry open
uh the belt loops on my waist ring and then just slowly slowly make it listen douglas
make eye contact with me where's the eyes where are the eyes on you where are pants eyes
there the pants eyes are the uh the wind button the windows to their soul yeah the button you
gotta stare at my button while you do it douglas and just slide that throw just belt blast me
douglas to blast me you sweet human boy then make me george make me the george my life purpose
has been served my server please douglas my service is done make me george free me from
your business casual dealings douglas let me be on a lake make me george please douglas make me george
douglas i want to go to a lake i want to play jarts as jarts frolic with me douglas
frolic in the lilacs with me douglas make me george please and and when my time in your
service is done you do not give me the goodwill you burn me up because i will not take another
you douglas no douglas no douglas i will not it is not how i out into a canoe and set fire to a
douglas i like the idea by the way that someone finds someone else's handmade jarts and goodwill
is like oh hell yeah that's to have them for sure these are good i'm gonna take these to a lake are
these bespoke been looking for some lake where um can i read this yahoo from level 9000 yajujuju
davenport yeah it's from yaju answers user sorry something's gone wrong because this answer did it
did get taken down but i found the cache so i'm gonna say this one's from douglas thank you douglas
it's uh but for asking this thank you for your courage douglas asks is willam defoe trying to
tell me something in my dream i forgot about willam defoe when i seen spider-man for the first
time i was nine when i seen the movie and when i got introduced to him again when i watched
mississippi burning i had this dream about him i was laying in my bed and closed my eyes and the
next thing you know it's black i can't see a thing then suddenly willam defoe pops into my dream from
nowhere he's smiling at me and so focused he mouthed something to me that is hard to see
he mouthed something to me that is hard to see it was like he was saying thank you to me what does
this mean um there's only one answer to this lala yahoo answers user lala uh gave the answer a new
change in your life and the asker actually rated this answer and gave it two out of five stars
so they were not satisfied with this so i'm hoping maybe we can do a little bit better than mala
um before we get into it i have a quick quick uh question there's a kind of would you rather like
we always do on the show every week would you rather have willam defoe smile at you
or like frown at you scowl at you i can't decide which one is better or worse either way it's a
it's a story um this if willam defoe comes into your dream though and mouths something that you
can't quite hear because you're in the upside down what's what's what's that what does that even
what does that mean is that really willam defoe's like consciousness that he sends out he's a dream
walker okay now we're getting somewhere um i want to i want you all to hop in the time machine with
me we're gonna head back to may 4th 2015 uh episode 250 of my brother my brother invest in the biz
and now i thought this question sounded familiar to me but i was only partially right this is a
question from episode 250 for no reason i've been crying over willam defoe i was in my room watching
one of his interviews and when it finished i turned over to watch tv a few days later i burst
out in tears and i don't know if it was me thinking about willam or it was something else
i haven't been paying attention to him as much as i used to uh i have been doing it for a few days
my boyfriend knows the reason for my crying he's comforted me about it my friend maggie told me to
stop crying and to shut up about willam defoe i've looked up to him since i was nine years old
i'm 17 now though my boyfriend said just remember i'm here for you if you need anything or if you
want to talk about things like celebrities then i'm here for you if you guys are gonna say it's
your hormones it's not i can tell you this isn't going on for days i go outside a lot so don't
say it's that either could someone please help me is crying over a celebrity normal what is willam
defoe okay doing i mean what is he doing he's definitely projecting himself into like some
sort of midnight channel-esque sort of shadow world where he can walk between our consciousness
when it's raining at midnight willam defoe pops up on the tv and tells you um the day you'll die
and the name of your true love so he gives he gives and he takes and also what time spider-man
one is going to be on tbs the answer is always always always always always tbs we've got spider-man
one that's that's their fucking motto um so i don't i don't want to be mean to willam defoe
but i think he's i think he does i think he's you know a shadow that walks between
our collective subconscious you know what i mean yeah i don't think that's mean yeah i mean if you
think about it have you ever you've seen william defoe a lot right i mean not in person exactly
yeah we've never seen william defoe in person isn't that interesting isn't that curious now
just suggesting that anytime william defoe is in a movie he's been uh portrayed in motion capture
by andy circus no i'm saying that he is only lives in movies and tv oh and in our dreams
apparently apparently he's apparently tv movies aren't enough for him anymore and he's just
started to come into our minds directly when alexander graham bell discovered the electronic
transmission he sent a recording of what happy birthday or mary had a little lamb and it was like
mary mary had a little eris fleece was white as snow and then it was like hello daniel daniel
it's me you've set me free it's william defoe i exist here in the midnight channel and ever since
then just everything fucking dallas watch dallas look in the background there he is yeah it's him
he's just looking for a door looking for the door out steve guttenberg opens his printing press he's
so stoked he finally cracked it he stole that wine press technology from the italians and he
made it his own and turned it into a printing press he's so stoked and he lifts it up after
typesetting the first page of the bible and what's there is it the first page of the bible
it is not is the face of william defoe staring him back it made in like ascii art of this guttenberg
press exactly i thought you were gonna say in the in the is it three men and a baby that scene where
there's the shadow behind the curtains that like nobody knew what it was and everybody thinks it's
a ghost no that's william just looking for looking for the looking for his starring role in the
picture he's a good actor though yeah all right work he's a good actor for sure i mean i'm just
saying like have you ever seen him be bad in something never never he's just so consistent
spider-man for sure definitely was not good in that no he was sorry justin he was very good in
that um okay agree to disagree that's fine i mean i think it's a little overblown he played the
green goblin did you want like a reserved quiet performance no my problems with his performance
were probably sam raimi centric to me yeah let's uh let's let's take a moment to talk about the max
fun drive instead of talking about actors for like a fucking second here on this star watch podcast
yeah don't worry we'll get back to it yeah we're gonna get there don't worry um so the max fun drive
is let me see let me back up uh maximum fun.org is a podcast website it's let me just start again
maximum fun is a podcast website and you go to it and you click on the right hyperlinks and then a
widget's gonna start playing your favorite guys now griffin you've lost me what is a website you
type in the right aol keyword and you click on the right widgets and then the guys are gonna start
going maximum fun is a podcast network it's got a website maximum fun.org those two are related but
they're not the same thing maximum fun has a lot of uh fantastic shows uh and every year they
uh expand that that family of shows uh to offer you new uh new audio delights and uh once a year
we come to you uh and say hey can you help us make this thing um and we ask you to do that by pledging
a certain amount um of money that you can give us per month to help keep these shows operational i
mean for and and let me put it to you this way at five dollars which is the lowest uh donation level
you're going to get access to a bonus archive of audio that has a lot of things in it there's like
seven episodes of my brother my brother and me there's uh videos that we've made there's clips
from live shows there's an exclusive clip from our cso tv show uh that you can only get by donating
to maximum fun um there's i mean there's uh and that's just our show there's a absolute buck wild
amount of stuff on there and you can enjoy all of it if you can donate just five dollars a month
even if you only listened to one show if you only listen to my brother my brother me it breaks down
like a buck 25 uh per per episode um and that really uh it means the world seriously and listen
i've also seen people say i i can't give anything and like i understand that i've also been there
but just knowing that you wish you could and that you're tweeting about it and you're telling people
about the show like it means the world to us i i i love max fun drive um not only because like
you know the energy there's all these like fun bonus episodes that go up because i'm also
a fan of the shows on the network but seeing people tweet about how much the shows mean to
them and how much the network means to them is like i love it it makes me feel very special
and it reminds me of um why you know why we make the shows and why we do the things that we do
um if you want to give a little bit more at ten dollars per month you can get uh an exclusive
enamel pin made by uh megan lynn cott uh and there's a a specific pin designed for all of
the shows for my bim bam it is a cool looking snake that says zag on them on it um and i think
now that we've passed 10 000 right if you're a donor to the network you will also get an
opportunity to buy additional pins and the proceeds that are gonna go to uh yeah then
the proceeds that will go to charity so you don't if just picking one stresses yeah there will be
an opportunity to uh complete the set um at 20 dollars per month you can get the keep in touch
kit that gets you nine custom note cards plus envelopes uh it's got uh designs by brian sonny
d fernandez there's a four color rocket pin a getting their rocket stamp and a rocket shaped
candle that was made by uh erica huff friend of the show for for rose buddies um and we have a
lot of her candles and they smell real real good so um that's what you get at 20 dollars per month
there's higher tiers but we'll talk about those later but yeah it just if you if you have the
means and you spend a lot of time with us um just think about supporting us at whatever level you are
comfortable with um even if it's just five bucks at five bucks you get like a bonkers amount of
bonus content so uh i was wrong by the way it's 10 episodes of my brother and brother me oh my god
episode of one i know one episode of big gulp um that we recorded live uh and us riffing a couple
of videos um a live show from austin and that that exclusive clip um and that's just our show
the other shows have tons of stuff on there too it's i want somebody to go through and
add it all up because we're it's multiple days at this point easily um maybe into the weeks
and not only that but like because it's max fun not only do you get like the donor bonus stuff but
there's always all kinds of extras that happen throughout the two weeks we put up our pilot
episode of the macro brothers will be in trolls 2 um i've done a couple live stream things i've got
more coming up i'm going to do a nail care nail painting stream because that has been in high
demand because we hit a goal and if we hit 20 000 which is our new stretch goal max fun is going to
do uh an event a show i guess of sorts in the grand canyon with jesse thorn me stewart wellington
from the lop house and aaron gibson from throwing shade um we're going to fly in five donors chosen
at random get them some burros we're all going to ride to the bottom of the grand canyon and do
like a max fun show event and be bucked off of the burro to fall all the way down the grand canyon do
you want to die with my brother do you want to die with me we'll go out in a blaze of glory
and burro sounds style um so just do it now while you're thinking about it maximumfund.org donate
and thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you to everybody who's donated and upgraded when
you donate you get to choose the specific shows that you listen to um so and your money goes
directly to the shows that you choose so you are directly supporting us and um we invest that money
back in the show like we cover our travel expenses with it sometimes i just bought a new sound board
um that i i spent that good good money on so um you're doing that but you're also like supporting
us and helping us like turn this into a job turn this into a career and try out new stuff and
launch new shows and um just just sort of spend more time doing this so again maximumfund.org
slash donate um and thank you again thank you thank you thank you without meaning to i have
once again made the first kind of like four questions on a theme of people doing things
that are inexplicable i didn't mean to but we've just been getting so many questions lately
that i think like subconsciously i've started building thematic episodes interesting yeah
um so let's continue with our theme hey brothers so my dad doesn't own a cell phone claiming he
doesn't need one cool instead he'll use the phone at work to call us and tell us when he's coming
home if my dad is anywhere else though and needs to contact us he will either ask a stranger to
borrow their cell phone or ask an employee to use their phone just recently my dad called me and the
caller id said it was mcdonald's i don't want my dad to inconvenience these people any longer
how do i convince my dad to finally get a cell phone and that's from secondhand anxiety in florida
i'm getting thirdhand anxiety from this obviously we recoil from this but is there not a part of you
that thinks like boy that that might be nice yeah it would be nice to be the sort of person that
you could look around and say well everyone else has cell phones i don't think i need one someone
there will have one literally everybody else has them so i think i'm okay there'll be somebody else
around that i can use their cell phone i can't imagine living that i really i can't imagine it
now i have i have thought many times about like you know you go into a movie and like you you know
you silence or turn off your cell phone you should turn it off and i have like a little panic every
time i do of like what if somebody needs to get a hold of me during this hour and 45 minutes and
like i think about what if i just didn't have a phone ever right and i could just like go to dinner
without worrying about oh i felt a buzz in my pocket what if it's important i better check it
because there was a time in our lifetimes where like if you weren't home people would just call
your house and leave a message and maybe you heard it like five hours later and that was fine and
everybody was just okay with that that's cool i like that kind of like wouldn't it be nice to
just have the freedom to not do this for a while but to do that but then also be like hey can i
borrow your your phone this thing that you're doing there's the rub this is our shock at this
is a very privileged like position to take right like cell phones are fucking expensive and like
of course not everybody has one that's kind of a um kind of a whack assumption at at the same time
though like um if i get a call and the call is from mcdonald's that's gonna be maybe the
worst moment of my life because i'm going to i i don't know that i will answer i probably won't
answer that call sorry dad or maybe i will if i expect like oh boy a car from a call from frish's
big boy well this is my dad um that one's gonna be my dad because one time you're gonna answer
your dad what would that call for mcdonald's be like hey did you have some nugs last week yeah
oh boy if you answered there's gonna be one of those though right trav where you answer you're
like dad will you please get a fucking cell phone and it's like hi we're doing a customer
service about the shamrock shake and i'm sorry it's it's it's that part to me is un untenable
your dad is pulling a power play here because think about it think through it if he needs a
cell phone he can get one if you need your dad that's tough nuggies oh you can't get this man
this man is saying to you like no you can't have me i'm i'm elusive i want it to be special when
you nail me when you when you when you manage to to corral me into talking to you it should feel
like an event because it's your dad is holding himself hostage from you exactly yeah exactly
but he's also valuing himself higher so that when you do manage to get a call from your dad it's
like seeing craig t nelson at the airport it's that level of excitement got my dad found him
all right he's at mcdonald's go move move swat team go activate here i here's what you should
do i thought i think i have an answer okay you should tell your dad that you've been getting uh
like some uh like uh telemarketers and some you know kind of scam calls and you're not answering
calls from unknown numbers anymore but i mean that doesn't work that doesn't work the caller
id tells you that it's from mcdonald's then that's all the answer if you call me from that mcdonald's
because it's a number i know and they use the code word ducktales then i'll know and i'll
code word ducktales then i'll know um i think you should pay someone to to to tag your dad oh
i think you should get someone like graffitium no i think you should get someone to tranquilize
it up on my dad tranquilize your dad okay well that's very expensive what griffin is suggesting
is a tale i don't think a dad tale is necessary i don't think every time poor um oscar the dad
looks at his rear view mirror and sees like a white camaro the same white camaro that's always
there i don't think he needs that in his life that seems like a lot what i was suggesting was mark
echoes get up on my dad get up on my dad and put your art up on my dad your spray that i'm suggesting
that you tranquilize him and you give him like an uh a gps tag geocaching so geocache your dad and
then call then you can just like call the nearest phone to your dad wherever if you need him you
just see what phones are around there yeah and call and say like hey can you yell the name oscar
very loud to try to get oscar the dad over here so i may speak with him about whether or not he
wants to go see rogue one this afternoon please if you have a moment um i have a very related
yahoo that i'm i would be delighted if you all would let me read okay i was sent in by Amelia
Burger thank you Amelia it's by yahoo answers user derk and it's it's a similar vein of like
how to how did folks get in touch without phones right but the wording of this question is maybe
the best derk asks how did people know when to meet back in vampire times i know
i know that they wrote more letters you gotta let me get through it i know that they wrote
more letters and stuff but back in vampire times how did you make plans with friends
did they just wait around all day and hope that they ran into each other
you could make all the plans you want the vampires are gonna ruin them
i mean you could write a letter it's like meet me at ye olde arby's this afternoon but a vampire
is just gonna be waiting there to to harangue you hey meet me there at 2 p.m can't do that
can we make it 2 a.m the sun the sun is an issue the sun is bad for vampires so i mean this is
before i'm gonna set that let's set the let's set the stage it's vampire times there's no
there's no electronic communication which of course means william defoe is still trapped
in that that uh that that you know spectral cage somewhere before alexander graham bell let him out
um and i want to get in touch with you uh i want to get in touch with dad to go see rogue one
do i just like go to the theater and just like hope he like do i just yell out my window like
dad dad dad rogue one rogue one and just like hope that he like falls under the thrall of my
voice somewhere or is it do i do i like uh fucking the end of uh christmas carol just
like pay a boy just be like go find my dad and invite him to the theater to see a live
performance of rogue one you have to send your familiar you gotta send your renfield
right your renfield goes and like delivers the message to your vampire dad and then vampire dad
like gives him i guess some bugs to eat or something and then renfield returns to you and
then actually can i tell you something it was actually a much more efficient system than we
have now i suppose so um in many ways in many ways it wasn't but in many ways it was if you
think about it but like in vampire times how did folks know to meet up though it's a good question
i mean that's why we had public how like public houses right was that a thing i've heard that
term before are those just houses where people could be at and yeah you've been up there for a
bite maybe this is what maybe this is what town criers were doing this is what john criers were
up to where you would go and you'd be like hey town crier can you holler for my dad and just
tell him meet the theater live performance of of rogue one um at at 4 p.m and then we're gonna
run the fuck home before sunset because we don't have movies yet so we're just reading the script
yeah it's a rogue one out loud um and we're gonna get the fuck home before the sun sets
because it's gonna get choppy out here say say you're in your amazing like dave is at pinkberry
everyone dave's at pinkberry like that's what the town crier does he just
broadly announces your locale he's just flipping through index cards just like
greg is at jamba juice susan is at j crew and she's waiting for michelle
well tyler's at orange julius a lot of juice stores back in vampire times
really gentrified here timothy has been killed by a vampire michael has been killed by a vampire
okay i have i have an actual question for you if a vampire was stalking and trying to kill a
specific person okay would it be easier for the vampire to track and kill this person back then
when you there was a limited number of places you could be and you probably should tell somebody
where you're gonna be or else it's gonna be like a whole thing or now when we have like technology
and twitter and everything and like foursquare and what have you when would be an easier time
for a vampire to find find people um here's what i'll say i've got in my house which i i just don't
i don't leave this house because i food is sent to me by blue apron and then i stay inside the
house all day and hang out with my wife and my baby and i play zelda non-stop uh and persona
non-stop and so i just don't leave the house and vampos can't come in here without permission which
i am not going to hand out lightly to a vampo thank you so but i think back in the day it'd
be like time to go outside to the well chomp dead okay you know that's a good point because the
follow-up question i have justin along those same lines is do you think it was easier back
in vampire times for a vampire to gain permission to enter your house because everyone was like so
dumb and trusting and now everyone just hates every other human being and it's a lot harder to
get somebody to let you into their house like if somebody came to my door now not only would i not
let them in i probably wouldn't even go to the door like they'll leave if they have something
for me they'll just leave it there like if they haven't told me they're coming over i'm not letting
them in i always kind of assumed that the vampire has to be invited in thing is something that
vampires made up and spread around because it's so fucking funny can you imagine nothing like it
would be a nightly hilarious event for you to like see some dumb human standing in the window
like neither neither neither you just like pounce through the window and eat them like that's gotta
be the funniest shit yeah um man what happened all the vampos then though because it's not
vampo times now where did they go i bet they're on wall street and that topical because they're
bleeding us dry am i right because they're bleeding us dry yeah man on wall street i bet
they're all bankers money never sleeps suck because they suck blood i guarantee that's
that's got to be a tagline for a movie somewhere right vampire bankers these interest rates suck
something like that something along those lines trading stocks and biting knocks do you mean necks
that's a bad rhyme having having having sex and biting necks and now it's like sexy
like wall street like powerful power mr big mr big up at the top turns out he's a vampire the
whole time and he's the one who wants to be with you um i have a friend that i frequently hold on
i think rachel locked herself out one second there's joe's witnesses right outside my window
so i'm gonna be down here for a little bit okay what are they doing griffin are you okay
they won't leave they keep knocking this is this is literally germane to the
conversation we were just having about not wanting to open the door for strangers
are you okay i mean i'm good i just don't i don't want them to know i'm in here you don't
have to talk to other human beings yeah we're good we're good though let's just move on i bet
jehovah's witnesses by the way would not be so fucking cavalier if we're still in vampire time
absolutely not i i think justin you would find that most people wouldn't be yeah not just yeah
that's a good point let's go ahead and move on to keep do you just take the real
deep do you just take the reins for a little bit i'm riding this one out
i have a friend that i frequently communicate uh via text formats i am twitter text messages
and this friend frequently as a way of expressing playfulness or a joke sincerely
uses the winky emoticon semicolon close parentheses yeah we i know what it is it gives
me the absolute heebie jeebies it makes me feel bad to look at every single time what's a cool
way to get my friend to stop being a text grosso and that is from skeeved by semicolons
i think i don't know people have quirks anymore can't people just have a quark
a fun quark you have to sand the edges off of everyone oscar doesn't want a phone he's a dad
that's his law he could just live it why can't he just live it why can't this person just use
a similar emoticon if they want to sexy wall street vampire just wants to trade stocks and
biting the ox why can't we just let them do that and be them it is murder so that's actually yeah
that one's a crime that was what this isn't fighting the knock doesn't have to be murder
you can stop shy of draining the person that's true let me get a smack a roll of that good good
neck honey um so this do they do this irl and that's another sort of emoticon that means
in the in the flesh world um do they winkle a lot you know do they wink a lot
does it make you lol or does it make you you which stands for uncomfortable um can i oh you've just
remind me i've never i've never had an opportunity to share this story and i really want to it was
very brief anecdote i was listening to uh npr and they did like an ad read for i guess a play that
was going on locally about like you know text and the internet and stuff and the announcer said um
with plenty of jokes uh it'll give you lots of laugh out louds and i just i assume that the text
said lols and they just went ahead and said the whole thing it's one of my favorite things i've
ever heard in my whole life that's so good excuse me laugh out louds that's my if you could review
our podcast and just say that it gave me laugh out louds i would appreciate it um it's it's it's this
is this is this is some this is an easy fix this is a one sentence fix hey that thing that you do
it's like not how you're supposed to use the thing so just think about it like google that
emoticon and its proper usage and then like maybe you could stop doing it because it's inherently
like sexy playful when you wink like we've got a lot of winking questions i'm so old i don't know
what the problem is what's the problem i need like i needed that you should probably see this
question is still buffering because they they could probably handle it that is an excellent
i don't i don't actually know is it bad let me pitch this justin all right two scenarios
had a great time hanging out last night like colon parentheses smiley face oh they had a great time
had a great time hanging out last night winky emoticon yeah it's it's it's it's different
for sure there's a different vibe i texted i just texted you two boys okay yeah
this is innocuous enough i just texted having a great time recording with y'all
and then a winky emoticon the wink makes it seem like there's an underlying secret like having a
great time recording with you all and my balls are with my balls like hanging out in my pants
um i i um i once did a business dealing of a lar like a house transaction with uh a couple
and listen a wall street vampire over here one of the people in the house transaction uh use ellipses
at the end of every text oh man like every single text there was an ellipses so and we were talking
a lot about like house stuff like we'll have someone look at the wiring dot dot dot so are
you mad about it yeah are you really not gonna do it i don't understand that's like the most loaded
yeah uh three periods you can put in anything there's no room for furtive disappointment when
you're dealing when you're spending a bunch of money on a house i guess i always i always think
of the ellipses in that scenario is like the thing that people do in like really tense horror movies
where it's like we haven't seen him in weeks dot dot dot yeah exactly old man at the gas station
that's like you don't want to go up to that cabin um winky smiley winky wink oops i did the wrong one
but you want to fog eggplant peach eggplant peach that's my wiener that's your whatever
taster's choice um how about another yahoo yeah um this one was sent in by ah shit there's a
lot of really good ones how about this one from irham wisessa thank you irham is by yahoo answers
user charmista asks does adding flavor to water makes it juice well i want to drink more water
and only way i think i'd enjoy it is if i add flavor but would that change the water
into juice and not give me the same benefits as plain water i like this you get that you get the
commercials for that's the you know smart water turbo drops or whatever and it's like add this
to make your water less boring this is this isn't your dad's water this is turbo drop cool water
and it turns blue and i guess it has a flavor to it does it stop at that point does it stop
being water and now it's like well it doesn't make sense to drink what you're supposed to drink eight
cups of water a day um you can't eat you can't drink eight cups of juice a day right we're gonna
make a lot of jokes here folks but i want to be honest this is travis pulling back the curtain
for a second i don't know yeah i know a lot of the times we don't know we sort of figure it out
by just sort of bouncing off each other just being a couple goofballs here's a here's a question
right okay so like if i get a diet coke with lemon which is the only way that i get diet coke
if i get a diet i know if i get a diet coke with lemon and i put some in it it's diet coke with
lemon if i do that with water i'm i'm hurtling towards lemonade i'm like yeah there is a very
thin line of deviance from water before it loses the label i feel like this is true because every
morning i take eight cups of water and i put some ground up shit in it and now it's coffee
it's not water anymore that's it you guys just unlocked it you guys just unlocked the fucking
secret and i was hoping we would get here but this is like i'm like morpheus right now like
welcome to the next level boys because every drink is just water with some stuff in it every
drink in the world is just you go to one of those fucking make your own flavor adventure soda
machines and what do you think happens in there you're like i want a orange fanta with a cherry
splash and a little bit of mountain dew in it that's just they're adding syrups to carbon to
water that has been added bubbles to it and it's all water folks just with different stuff in it
you know what i mean that wine wine is just grape water that grapes ate and then they got old and
squeezed and then that water that took a different form is grape stuff came out and now it's wet ain't
it it's wet and red and it tastes weird but that's water in there sorta um here's a yahoo i have a
yahoo answer from oh there not it's not on here i don't know where you would see it i've never read
one is every drink made out of water yeah that is the question here um and the only this divergence
from that is pretty much everything you could want to drink contains some water there are potable
liquids such as glycerin that you could drink even though they are a hydrous which i guess means don't
hydrate you then it's not a liquid i'm sorry liquid means water plus something it's all
remixed if you drink fucking beer that's just remixed water does somebody put their fun spin
on what about milk no it's just water with uh cow leave with cow stuff in it yeah cows drink the
water and that help if a cow doesn't drink water they die straight up that's what's that's what's
up and a lot of people won't tell you that i'll tell you that's your face cows die if they don't
drink water they drink that water it nourishes them and it goes down in their teats and it
mix up with the cow stuff and it juices out and then i drink it and i get very sick what about
clearly canadian that might actually damn that might be the exception no it's just water they
added bubbles to and distinct canadian flavors and it's exciting canadian water next what about
lacroix lacroix is water with like the most faint a droplet uh i actually think that lacroix doesn't
have flavoring in it and it's all fucking like psychosomatic like you see a green new clothes
yeah you see a green can you're like this tastes like lime and you drink it and it's like no it's
just kind of like bubbly water but you're like mm lime yummy yummy yum no it tastes like green
can because that's what your brain sees next um i have some i i have something that might be
germane to this and it's like think something to think about along these lines every uh basically
every molecule of what we of course we have the same you know most of the same water molecules
here on earth as it will have been on earth did you realize that pretty much every water molecule
that you drink was at one time peed out by a dinosaur i think about it all the time justin
that's a pretty i think that's very empowering i think it's a pretty rock and roll thing to be
able to start your day with a big glass of dinosaur piss we are all made of star stuff and dino pee
we're you're like i'm how are you gonna start your day you fucking amazing creature well i
think i'm gonna drink some dinosaur piss and fucking kick ass all day long like yeah that
sounds pretty rocking that's actually a really good idea most water molecules haven't been
drunk by people before you're not drinking second-hand water from people you're drinking
from dinosaurs yeah you're infinite and powerful think about that the next time you're in a pool
and somebody says something like oh don't pee in the pool you're like oh fucking t-rex already
pissed in here shut up dennis dennis you dick pissed it all out did you guys know that the
original name for josta was dino piss but it didn't test well so they changed it to justa
serge almost nabbed that one too serge was like let's be honest it's dino piss um thank you all
so much for listening to our podcast uh we want to one more time just remind you that the max fun
drive is going on this is our last max fun drive episode we'll be back to our regularly scheduled
programming next week but right now if if you like us if you like our show and you can spare
a little bit of cash um you know five bucks a month all the way up to two hundred dollars whatever
you can afford so we talked about we talked about the five dollar level and the ten dollar level and
the twenty dollar level i would like to tell you about the thirty five dollar level it is one of
my favorites i know and here's the thing all the rewards stack so at thirty five dollars you get
the bonus content that you get at five dollars the pen that you get at ten dollars the cuban
touch kit that you get at twenty dollars but you also get a set of engraved beer mugs with the max
fun rocket logo right on there now i say beer mugs you can use these for any beverage you want
it's all gonna be water-based so some kind of water-based beverage in there no glycerin um
and it's going to make just a stunning addition to any glassware collection that you might have um
and then at a hundred dollars you get all that stuff plus you get entered into the monthly
culture club and what this is is every month a max fun producer or max fun host someone that
works with max fun is going to pick some form of media maybe it's an album or a movie or a book
something that means a lot to them and you're going to get sent that along with a note as to
why they picked it so it's like everybody is enjoying the same media that month binding you
all together cosmically then at two hundred dollars a month which listen i realize two hundred
dollars a month is is a pretty uh not insubstantial sum but it goes a long way to support the artist
an artist that you love and for two hundred dollars a month you get all that stuff plus
free registration to max fun con 2018 and max fun con is the fucking best thing of the year we love
going to it it's like summer camp for cool kids it's the best and you're going to be registered
to do that in 2018 because you're a 200 a month donor um whatever whatever level you can support
us at like we we appreciate you so much and we do take this money and uh we invest some of it back
into the show and buy new equipment and and stuff like that but mostly like the support we've gotten
from our network is the reason why we've been able to like we started out it was just my bin
bam on the max fun network and then we started doing adventure zone um i started doing rose
buddies travis started doing uh shmanners and trends like these and a bunch of bunch of other
podcasts justin started doing saw bones like we've expanded and been able to do all that stuff
because of the support that we've gotten from y'all because we can treat this like a job we can
treat this like a career um and and we're just so grateful that we've been given the opportunity
to make all this fun stuff because of the support that y'all give us now before we wrap up and i
know we're heading towards wrap up i do want to just read a question we don't have to even discuss
it i just like it so much we'll save it for next time no i griffin please please let me say it
all right please please an exterminator just came to my apartment he was throwing little blue things
under my kitchen counter and i asked what they were he said that they were calcium packets because
when mice eat calcium it goes straight to their hearts and they have a little mouse heart attack
his words why does it go straight to their heart because quote mice have no bones just a skeleton
end quote my exterminator said mice have no bones just a skeleton and then proceeded to explain
that rats have an exoskeleton he did this while spraying my home with chemicals am i good and
that's from skeletal head scratcher get out of the house right now you have to he then proceeded to
put his belt on his pants on the floor before strapping them onto his body my belt's come a
little loose uh if you'll excuse me from the room on my planet bortelotron 6 mice have an exoskeleton
now please allow me to belt my pants juice would you be more into justin's definitely afraid of
mice would you be more into them if they had an exoskeleton more because then i feel like
it's a fair fight okay do you verse mice yeah the scary thing about mice isn't they're gonna
hurt me it's that they're gonna like they're so fragile i think that's what scares me interesting
yeah but if they could like fight back i'd be like oh game on mother if a mouse just came out
in the suit from alien they would also be clankier and probably slower like easier to keep tabs on
right and they would talk also i can't believe how many times you have to say this don't hire
somebody to kill the mice in your house you got to befriend them and open up a fun cheese factory
like in mouse hunt with nathan lane yeah that's it just think about them they're just little guys
they're just doing their best last time maximum fun.org forward slash donate if you can help us
out it would really mean the world um but that is gonna do it for us uh thanks john roger come
along winter she's her theme song it's a departure off the album putting these days to bed it's
really good it's a really good track oh i want to say if if you're listening to this on monday
if we were able to get it out in time tonight cincinnati ohio at the rook in otr um there's
the max fun meetup um i am going to be at it um play some board games it's a board game bar um
play some board games i made some baked goods uh some chess bars um some peanut butter cup
cookies i made them during a baking live stream last night and i'm gonna bring those for everybody
to eat um 7 p.m at the rook um i think there's like a 20 minimum for us to like use so like
you need to like buy some food there some drinks there and stuff but uh come out and hang out
tonight if if you listen to this in time yeah uh they will i'll get it up soon uh this final yahoo
was sent in by brooks oglesby thank you brooks it's by yahoo answers user sorry something's
gone wrong what a bad website franklin asks what does david spade mean to you my name is
justin mcelroy my name is travis mcelroy one time he flipped me off what stop the podcast stop the
ending turn off the song what happened why do you do that um i was on a trip with my choir to new
york in high school and we were walking through new york city and he was coming out of the trl
building or wherever trl is formed and we were like oh my god it's david spade is formed where
they artisanally shape and mold it yes with the oompa loompas put together trl nobody ever goes
in nobody ever comes out and we saw david spade and um i believe he was maybe fresh off of joe
dirt perhaps uh and we all said oh my god david spade and he turned as he was like getting into
like a black escalade turned to a group of about 35 teenagers ranging from 14 to 18 turned to us
looked at us smiled flipped us all rock star gave us the finger and kind of a like wave
so fine to his car and and his driver drove off drove them away yikes i'm griffin mcelroy this has
been my brother my brother me kiss your dad square on the lips i can't stress enough there was no
malice in it i don't think maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported