Like Chilean miners emerging from the depths to a triumphant round of applause to my brother
my brother me and invite you for the modern era I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy
I'm your middle is brother Travis McElroy I'm your sweet baby brother Griffin McElroy
they probably they probably applauded like a lot when those miners got out
yeah I'm not sure you guys Christ sack up to that which if you're in that audience how do
you know like when to stop applauding like do you think by like the 33rd one how many were there
that's an excellent question Griffin because there is like there's a moment where everybody's
like losing it right because they're like oh the first guy is the first guy is like yes and then
probably about a minor 20 they're like okay but then like 21 comes up holding a puppy and you're
like yeah and then 29 is like I think we're almost done guys let's bring this one home but
then after they were all out there had to be a moment at the end of the chair one for everybody
yeah for us we are some snacks where they were like well bye bye I guess go now do something
else like honestly I mean you're still miners you gotta go back to work in the mines like you
don't have another tomorrow tomorrow I guess not that we're still milking the miners back
yeah and the miners I am already the most sweaty that's comedy ain't easy wash it what I love
Washington DC I love it I love being in the D anytime I get a chance all this government
anytime I get to visit the DS I'm psyched about it you guys have an invisible barrier of just a
rich invisible fog of humidity that exists here it's like at this off the sea level and it's just
perfectly my underwear height and now I'm sitting it's face high time about your foggy bottoms it's
a local reverence I saw it on one of the subway platforms I'm saying it's something of a comfort
to me cuz like I watch TV and I see politicians on TV I think they're so powerful I see like
Mitch McConnell up there like women shouldn't have library cards and it's like and like everybody's
losing their minds like yeah yeah yeah but then like he walks off stage he's like my gooch is
ruined like I know as soon as they go in the back room it's like you're not so powerful anymore
cuz you're like oh my grindle is soupy like so much baby powder Kevin Spacey mommy Kevin Spacey
like walks off the set he's like Clio that was great work my under my gold goose is souped it's
so bad bring me some more of my acting trunks and I don't know well can Kevin Spacey pretending to
be I don't know why he's still in character when he's not playing Frank Drebben or whatever because
he is a method method he is method Justin whether he's hot or not he's got a soupy goose and that
is just true we do now we talk more about Kevin Spacey's taint before we get into the questions
and we got we got a lot of fun stuff playing for you this is the usual stuff but it'll be fun we
were leaving our names yeah we did that part we did that part who this is still the charming
intro there by license before the question okay we were we were leaving a restaurant last night
after eating dinner I was not here for this and I still do not think it happened Travis has
photographic evidence we leave you a place called Asia 54 I don't know if you've been but highly
recommended pretty good it's great what's great we saw Rob Reiner not there not there at our hotel
ninety eight point five nine eight point five percent Rob Reiner anyway hold on it was either
a hundred percent Rob Reiner was zero percent Rob Reiner it was not one of his failed clones
okay it was not club Reiner you mean Carl Reiner nobody's nobody's quite sure so we're leaving a
lot of clones have the Jack disease or we're leaving the restaurant and as we are leaving
this guy jumps in front of us and says be careful there's a raccoon in this tree now I'm listen I
may be from West Virginia but I've been to a big city before I know how this ends pal this ends with
you try and hit me up for cash right so my okay so I walk past him I love not exaggerating by the
way that is literally how he reacted yeah sure sure pal well there's a fucking raccoon in the
tree and before we continue on with this you need to understand I want to paint a picture for you
there's not much more but this raccoon looked terrified care this was not a taunting villain
of a raccoon this look if you had told me that raccoon was nine months old I believe yeah the
man sounds like the aggressor in this well now here's the thing we got more info as we stood
there dumbstruck he said this raccoon was chasing me down the street and then he this raccoon was
chasing me on the street and then he ran up this tree so now I'm waiting for him to come down to
anything exact your revenge any stand you gotta settle this he looks at the tree says get down
here I don't know what like I don't I do not know what like if he was drawing this on a whiteboard
the plan you know I don't know what step one yellow raccoon step two record come down step
three question mark step four vengeance vengeance yeah you get your sweet vengeance I don't that man
was vice president Joe Biden you forgot to call you here Uncle Joe Uncle Joe Jamaica you literally
we literally put him on the complex we put him on the complex wait Joe he's didn't he didn't make
him come in halfway our show yeah it's not too late we'll check in at the end yeah what our show
is we'll turn questions out can we like into wisdom and here's our first one who wait who here
is this your first experience with my brother my brother and me I see hands okay all right big
shmanners fans we we we turn quit we answer questions it's fine we do we do our best we try
damn it we try we try my young po buddies nerf picked my younger brother has recently decided in
his adulthood to begin going by his middle name while I have no problem with this choice in his
personal and professional life I am torn as to how I should now address him he insists that he
does not care one way or the other should I continue to use his first name or attempt to
break 29 years of conditioning to use the new moniker that's from doubtful designator in DC
that would be are you here wait you here like eight different people right yeah how many y'all
got younger brothers who just changed their name is this a rampant okay I need everybody to be
quiet because I don't want to muddy the result I need to know the first name in the middle name
his name okay okay and what's that wait oh I was about to ask last name it was gonna incriminate
him it was David Lee but oh shit yeah that's a good yeah can I ask the last name I didn't hear
that but it wasn't Roth so we're fine okay I'm glad that you went where I went yeah that would
be I got it I got it okay names aside it would be crazy if I was like hey guys what's up how
was your Christmas a cool I'm Bryce now wait okay it's not my middle name I should it would
be Andrew but that'd be weird hey guys Andy here here comes Andy the baby okay this is once again
this is the baby's brother drew this is the benefit of having the question asker in the
room that we don't get once again just the question asker yes or no question was this done
because they felt they needed like a business name or was this like I need a change of pace
and also what business is good for leave and not for then not for David name like David good for
lease we may not get the answer that's a business or personal all right okay I get that he said
personal got it so there was a month so there's a day he wakes up he goes to the shower a brush his
teeth he looks in the mirror he's like oh hello Lee I get I guess was that joke was funny for the
last half of the audience wait what was it say it again coward oh you didn't that's the last
time anybody's yelling anything by the way this is not that kind of show yeah this ain't a back
and forth it's not back and forth it's kind of a conduit do you guys wanna Yahoo answer from the
Yahoo answer service wait okay do you hear that Yahoo okay wait I'm cool moving on super quick we
should have at least a sentence that could qualify technically as an answer possible and whatever
yeah come on ever people you're still thinking about this when he said it doesn't matter it's
crazy to me get more life things in your life to worry about you need bigger problems this is a big
problem if you were like I'm Patrick now that would take me a year and I would never do that
Travis is an amazing but he said he doesn't care he doesn't care if he doesn't not he doesn't care
he's he's David at home he's Lee about a David in the streets and a Lee in the sheets I had to
think through that to make sure that was the idiom is that even an idiom does that qualify
okay I got a I believe that was in poor Richard's old man yeah David to bed lead to rise Julie
Martin sent in this Yahoo thank you choice by Yahoo answers user Parley Wilkinson who asks okay
Harley are you um you know what could be parlay you know what it is the fucked up nobody's nervous
okay law question this Yahoo answers user ask law question and the law question is hi guys I'm
a juggalo so I can assume y'all down with the clown I love that cocky drink by the way I just
said the word juggalo it's gonna be a while hi guys I'm a juggalo I have a hatchet man screensaver
for my phone hey that's weird phones kind of don't have screensavers I've got Dilbert's desktop
games on my phone for when I leave it on too long without interacting with my phone there's a crazy
maze and some pipes come out and make weird shapes it says Derek's phone in 3d block letters and they
wiggle back and I have a hatchet man screensaver from my phone my text notification is whoop
whoop which is what we say when we see another juggalo my fur I think I said it wrong oh wait
hold on fuck y'all yeah guys the fire marshal will shut this building the fuck down if we all
start doing juggalo mating calls my friend who is not a juggalo says that if cops pull us over
they can have probable cause to search me if they see my screensaver or hear my notification is this
true thank you for your help guys I really appreciate it smiley face I love this like
all right kids I'm gonna let you guys go with a warning this time but make sure in the future
please step out of the vehicle now the other side of that is whoo whoo indeed yes yeah carry
along I go go go for Faygo you know secret handshake that they have I don't they won't I
don't know their secret handshake I think the answer is like definitely yes like if I was a
cop and like I saw like if I saw some of this iconography I would be like I think I'd like to
see what's inside your car maybe this is a reasonable search and seizure because I really
would like to see what's in there maybe they just want to see what it's like from their point of
view like I just want to live in your shoes for a minute how's it going it's like a hieroglyphic
the hatchet man is but and it translates to roughly I love drugs and murder and murder drugs
I love murder drugs drugs that get me like crazy to murder do you mind if I just in your car to
see how things go over there what I love about this is the other side of this is that there's
definitely an orientation day where some chief of police says people that goes if you see this
hatchet man you will ask to search the car if they say whoop whoop in any form or fashion we
don't know the pronunciation you will ask to see their trunk now if it's just a bumper sticker with
Sideshow Bob in it you fucked up you lose your badge for that shit whoop whoop how about how
about another question just yeah hold on activate the iPad oh lock screen should have turned that
off he had a screen saver up our friend believes she has a life-threatening nut allergy but has
never been tested everywhere she goes she refuses to eat anything that may have any type of nut in
it however all of her friends think it's just in her head how do we get her tested so we think
we all know for sure if she's allergic or not Jesus that's from going nuts for sure and Gabby
hold on y'all here what is your day-to-day relationship with this friend where you're
like hey this done they're like no and you're like I'll get you one of these days she doesn't
want to eat nuts it's cool yeah your options are get her to eat a nut or like put up like
a put her in a big bag and like carry her to the hospital where they do the nut test like
those are the that's it I'm gonna I'm gonna lean away from the get her to eat a nut one I'm gonna
lean away from the big bad one they're both shitty they're like one of these days you're
gonna keep pushing it and pushing it and she she's just gonna say god damn it I don't like nuts okay
and that's shorter to just say I'm allergic because I don't know because then everybody's
gonna be like what about macadamia yeah I don't like those either I don't like any nuts I don't
like the concept of nuts I don't like any nuts I'm not a fan it's only nuts nut allergies are no
joke well they're not they're super not unless I think maybe it's fake and then I think we can
make jokes out of it but maybe it's not fake if you don't want us to make jokes about it get
the test that's the thing then we owe you an apology what is your friend basing it off of if
not a test I'm just like I look at a nut and I just get a bad feeling okay but flip side what's
everybody else basing it off of where they're like I saw her eat a Snickers one time I was swears
so rapper was gone she said it was a Milky Way I don't fucking believe it she threw the rapper
away she's just eating a big log I saw Snickers it could have been a Mounds but I'm pretty sure it was an Almond Joy
is your friend here oh shit
hey hey wait did you just call us here for nut allergy intervention we love you so much Debbie
eat a fucking peanut hey but listen no don't no wait no wait we're on a high-energy show here and
there's probably nuts in the lobby and oh tonight's the night tonight's the night time to dance with
don't eat that nut it's two to one majority rules I can't go to jail I don't eat the nut
let's talk about email composition to a podcast show what are you talking about your friends
imaginary nut allergy potentially imaginary because the phrase who will also be in attendance
would be fucking rad sadly absent it's too late for this one but if you're coming to if you're
coming to New York tomorrow you're like this guy does he's not gluten intolerant he'll be there
though put that second part in cuz like the material party with the most information here
it's a person who thinks they'll eat a nut and die they probably know more about this situation
than you do so sorry do what we're doing our best up here okay as long as we're sharing things so
we're recording here live at the we're recording live at the Lincoln Theatre here in Washington DC
and it's been alright RIP what RIP somebody asked didn't somebody one of our Lyft drivers
and it wasn't ours ours was cool ours was it Dwight's Dwight your Lyft driver hey everybody
it's my friend Dwight Slappy sitting exactly where Lincoln was sitting yeah yeah co-hosting
things about sheets Dwight real quick when you told your Lyft driver you want to go to
the Lincoln Theatre what'd your Lyft driver say no no he was not shot here that would have been
ironic I think oh man in my own dang theater beans our Lyft driver I'm we're telling Lyft
driver stories now to keep Travis from telling his fucking sad lip I will our Lyft driver was
awesome he was so so great but at some point him and Travis got in this like really deep
conversation about like homeless populations in urban centers and it was like no it was great
is you know it was cool idea I was like I was trying to break it up and he was going having
a really nice conversation one thing though his GPS the voice for his GPS it was T-Pain
so try to be like oh man skid row like it was horrible like there's just no respect for I wish
every time that happened trust is like but then the dude would have been like they would just go
into the woods and get up it was bad it was a bad juxtaposition hi everybody thanks for
listening to our Washington DC live episode and thank you Washington DC for coming out and making
us feel just just so wet and wild and thank you vice president Joe Biden for standing back in the
shadows and vice president Joe Biden I appreciate the fact you realized this was our night not your
night and if you'd like made some big grand triumphant entrance and you would have overshadowed
us with your giant shadow it would have become your night as you recorded your podcast cup of
Joe we're gonna get through the money down here very fast because I'm sick as fuck y'all got me
sick way to go I'm just kidding probably wouldn't you it's probably you know sky germs up in the
airplane time and I'll see you were licking the subway in New York I was licking the polls but
that's that's how I do it I just was just not fucking here I don't even know where that I
believe is talking to the mayor of West Virginia well as we announced that our New York show we're
doing a show with see so TV yes and we're gonna be filming it in Huntington so I assume Justin
way to talk to the mayor about that just give my heads up like there's gonna be some camera crews
it's getting a fucking crazy in here yeah we I guess this is our formal announcement on the
podcast proper we're doing a TV show with see so which is a new streaming app with comedy content
on it and they're gonna let us do a show for them it's gonna be coming out next year and it's gonna
be in Huntington West Virginia and we're super excited about it go check it out I check out see
so now and our show will be coming soon s e e s out let's get to the paid advertisement so I'm
gonna tell you about trunk club I have a trunk club experience here in LA they have a little bit
of a brick-and-mortar like you can actually go in and try stuff on and I think there's a couple of
those throughout the country and here's the thing nobody on earth knows how to dress themselves I
mean if you've got an especially if you've got a crazy body like Travis right I've got I've got
Jets and angles and knees I don't even know about but the people at trunk them they not only know
what to do okay I literally walked in and said I like work at home and sometimes I do live shows
and like I go and like meet people at stuff and I do a lot of coffee things and sometimes I record
on other people's podcast and Brooke was like okay cool here's like eight outfits that are all
perfect for what you just described and damn it they were like shoes to socks to belts to shirts
to pants like every step of the way they were perfect here's what I want you to do I want you
to go to trunk club comm slash my brother and you're gonna type in your measurements you're
gonna talk about what you like what you dislike and you'll get matched up with your own personal
stylist they're gonna pick you out some clothes it's gonna look fresh as hell it's not just like
you're not just online shopping the this stylist is gonna figure out like what's gonna look good
on you and if you live in Dallas New York LA Chicago or DC you can stop by a trunk club club
house and work with that stylist in person for free and if you don't what they're gonna do is
they're gonna ship you the reason it's called trunk club they ship you a trunk of clothes you
try on the clothes you keep what you like you send back what you don't and you only pay for what you
keep that's a great it's a it's a great little thing you can get started today go to trunk club
comm slash my brother again trunk club comm slash my brother and start getting your your load out
looking so sharp so right so tight so wet so wild I want to also tell you about Warby Parker no one
on earth knows how to put glasses on their face that's just a fact where do they even go what do
they hook on to up your nose no stupid be careful I try to poke both my damn eyes out damn it well
now you need super glasses with the eyes get the eyes built into it yeah the eyes built into it and
then maybe they spring out a little bit but here's the thing you guys Warby Parker glasses not only
they are amazing but you can get contemporary prescription glasses not just like your fakie
hipster glasses starting at just $95 and prescription sunglasses at $175 you go to like
your lens carters or something it's gonna cost you $8,000 it's gonna cost you so many dollars
but now at Warby Parker Warby Parker under $100 for prescription glasses also they do a similar
thing in trunk club you get sent five pairs of glasses shipped directly to you for free try them
all on get a feel for them and then get some feedback from your buds you have five pairs for
five days and you mail back to Warby Parker what you don't want keep what you do want so just go
to warbyparker.com slash my brother all one word start your risk-free try-on experience today don't
wait warbyparker.com slash my brother got a personal message here if you want to get a message on the
show go to maximumfun.org slash Jumbotron and find out all the details on how to get up there
this message is for Jeff Justin and Brian and it's from Matt who says to Bri just and Jeff my
brother's three what better way to mark the sick fact that you were all born on the same week than
with a paid shout out on your favorite podcast love your unbirthday brother Matt Matt I know
what that's like dude do you think wait do you think that these are like literal like relative
brothers that they just all have birthdays spread out throughout across years of course but all in
the same week I think this may be like how me and Joe Biden are brothers uh-huh like if I ever saw
him I just like yell my brother and he'd be like yo brother well I guess it's also possible there
it's triplets and one was born on like 11 58 p.m. on Monday there's a lot of different about
possibilities all I know Matt I know how hard it is to be lost left out in the cold every November
8th rolls around and I just cry into my pillow I just cry and scream so hang in there but to the
rest of you boys happy happy birthday holy shit what this next message is for the brothers macro
yes us from Rick Swanson brothers you are amazing you brought me countless hours of entertainment so
I wanted to give a little something back I came to the 2015 candlelight show but didn't get the
chance to talk to you the lantern talked to you at the lantern as you were tied up with other fans
sorry if you remember a 40 ish guy staring awkwardly at you that was me I do noodle up you
unfunny fucks hey Rick I want you to know what you don't realize or maybe you do is that this is
doubly nice because one you sent us a nice message and two you paid us to read a nice message to
ourselves yeah I'll do that any day of the week I put next time Rick come up and say something yeah
well I also get it cuz the the the post candlelight after parties are a just fucking like mosh pit it
gets wet I could also probably say that nicer come up and say something yeah come up and say
something if you ever see us out and about or like after a show or something I every saw that
someone say like but I was too nervous to say so we're just like three schlubby dudes yeah just
holler say hi just holler let's get back to the show there's a lot more show to get into next week
there will be the New York City live show there's some fun ass stuff that happened oh we should
mention because I think I left in a little bit of the build-up to it there was a sad lip here we
contractually had to leave a bit of the episode out and that was the bit that we all decided to
leave out cuz it fucking sucks every time it was just too good humanity wasn't ready for it so you
didn't miss much and here's the rest of the episode see you next week and talk to you later
and love you bye do you guys want to Yahoo yes okay this one was sent in by level 9,000 y'all
drew drew drew Davenport thank you drew Davenport drew make it out to this one drew you here no the
fuck did drew call ahead and tell you to say no if they ask this one is so fuck kind of giving it
away a little bit in the username because the username is Equus Princess welcome to Pony Corner
everybody welcome back to Pony Corner Equus Princess asks have you ever given up on a horse
why what was this horse like it's a real piece of shit we talked so much about horses are great
and beautiful perfect flawless every uh sometimes they're not though well hold on that might be that
you're not good enough for them yeah that's possible yeah but that deserves a horse but even
that even if you have somebody in your life that you try to live up to some days you just can't
sometimes you have to look up and say hey Bryce today I can't I I can't with you anymore today
I can't with you today Derek Derek Derek Derek are you going by your first name to the horses
middle name yeah the horses Bryce Derek horse Derek are you finally right there at Corsington
the third Derek it's been a year and a half are you finally gonna eat oats for my hand it
got Derek damn it no after all this time Derek I give up on you Derek today was supposed to be
about my son not about you damn it Derek you've broken my son's birthday party and you trampled
over all the guests Derek I'm out you're out you're done I give up on you can't I wash my
hands of you Derek and I do wash my hands after we spend time together because who knows what's
in there you're in horse it just horses veins and bugs how how do you I know how you mentally
and emotionally wait how give up on a horse tell me how you just get fucking like you just can't
with you anymore Derek I don't know how you physically give up on a horse because it's not
like you can just like load them in the car and drive them into the woods and then like let them
out and be like bye Derek idiot cuz they'll cuz the horse will chase you and they're gonna be
just as fast where where do you where does one take a horse to say the phrase he's your problem
now the obvious answer is of course the pound hey hey hey let me in I can't with this guy right now
I see you in there let me in I'm gonna be back in 24 hours don't tell I can't stay away this
Yahoo user Caitlin Johnson don't put your real name on Yahoo said anything is possible if you
just believe come on we're better than that it's time out this is horses real piece of shit and
there's a fuck this horse I hated it so much for so long so much my life was spent just hating my
horse I'd be lying in bed not moving just hating just hating just hating tail tail horse if you
believe in the horse and yourself then you can get the job done so like Equus Princess is reading
that being like I'm gonna stick with this thing and it takes years and years and years and like
this horse is like 20 years old and horses like dead it's like I had that horse and not other
horses for so long I bet after that boy that like after a certain amount of time your expectations
for what is not shitting us from a horse really drop and you're like didn't bite me today best
friends yeah good horse today I think I would give up on horse pretty quick which isn't good
I'm just saying my expectations are so very high yeah but the second they like I don't want to eat
oats from your hand it's you're done then you're done what the fuck what the why the fuck are we
here Derek if you're not gonna eat oats from my hand you were so expensive yeah Griffin how about
you uh read another Yahoo okay this one was sent in that wasn't very good so I'm gonna do it again
and you guys really gotta give me the squad like on a hard let's try one more time we'll just edit
around this hey Griffin about uh how about one more yeah this is for the edit you gotta do it
really good like pretend like you don't know that I'm gonna I gotta believe that if I let you go you
would actually do it yeah okay ask me that give me the fucking prom I didn't know where we were
cutting okay hey Griffin how about another Yahoo I enjoyed that one I'm really excited about this
one Justin here it comes the moment this show I've been most looking forward to this Yahoo was sent
in welcome everybody yeah here's the thing we're going a little bit more I feel like I need to stay
up for this we're going a little bit more promise the venue none of us would stand I love much got
so much promise the squad yeah I love my squad so much you know this about me I am worried that it's
still in beta ooh we're still bad it's ready to take out live y'all ready for it right okay this
time we're going a little bit more fast casual president on my fast food we're taking a trip down
get your flowers that need planning cuz we're going to the Olive Garden here your olive flowers
get your olive flowers ready to plant we gotta play it something oh Olive Garden is okay the
Munch squad is a show listen to the last two episodes like I want I want the 98% of people in
this room who don't know what the fuck you're talking about the walkout going they just took
this weird talk about halfway there they talk about Olive Garden for 10 minutes do they do
that this is my first time Olive Garden is doubling its offering of breadstick sandwiches
and bringing new twist to an Italian classic cuz after you have breadstick sandwiches you're like
this is good I wish there were twice as many to choose from cuz it wasn't already hard enough
to choose I need you to start from the fucking beginning and explain to me what a bread is it
just a little just a tiny just a little like little guy sandwich pipe that you just fucking
to hit your but hey check this idea cut it down the middle put a hot dog in there you're gonna
have that one for free OG it's a breadstick sandwich I think the bread is made of breadstick
bread yeah that's fucking a sandwich you just said breadstick is not a type of bread but that's
cool beginning this week iconic Olive Garden menu items will transform it's parmesan chicken
farmers on has evolved into Parmesan Johnny Otto transform with new varieties of the legendary breadstick sandwich okay Johnny
apple seed or like fucking Paul Bunyan gather around children get this here the tale of the
breadstick this is what popped it off though my me and my lovely wife saw this in a commercial
they're also offering brand-new deep dish spaghetti pies it looks exactly how you think it would like
a big piece of angel fruit cake made out of spaghetti and frosting cheese so listen and
frosting cheese last summer America fell in love with the breadstick sandwiches when they
were debuted at Olive Garden restaurants and on food trucks touring the country we gotta
get this to the people you can't contain this in an Olive Garden these breadstick sandwiches
and spaghetti pie are too good so the Olive Garden never ending family table across the
nation to give fans the opportunity to gather together and sample the new menu items sounds
like a cool afternoon it kicked off in New York City where I'm sure did great the way
you're sitting right now makes it look like you just ate a deep dish spaghetti pie I got
the quote here and this is really the in case you're curious they're doing a spicy Calibrian
chicken breadstick sandwich and eggplant parmesan breadstick sandwich that's not pretty good
anyway here's the quote and this is what the munch squad is really all about it's about
taking the words of the experts who create food and getting their opinions about scooping
up the barf of bad PR and then showing it to you like a proud cat look at this look
at this PR barf we got this for you last year we were thrilled and our guests enthusiasm
for our breadstick sandwiches and look forward to sharing our latest breadstick and spaghetti
innovations I want to break that down bit by bit we were thrilled we've really done
it because what that let me translate that for you are you fucking eating it you weren't
supposed to oh god he's liking it he's giving it to his kid that was a joke you're on you're
on punked and you were scooping it into your ma I am horrified can I put thrilled I yes
it seems it was kind of scary yeah nothing that's from Jose Duenas executive vice president
of marketing for Olive Garden unbiased he would like it yeah since nothing brings loved
ones together like food food we're excited to help our fans create amazing memories around
the table with our never-ending do you remember when grandpa died I'll never forget that time
I ate spaghetti pie but how everybody looked anyway that's the much squat you um you used
to work at the OG I was a line shift the OG for a month I was supposed to be a dishwasher
and when I went back to get trained I saw the guy who was the current dishwasher take
a ramekin of minestrone and a jam it like a shooter so when they asked him who I was
supposed to be working with I said uh the line shifts and that's how I got hired as
the line ship at all only the best most trained hands are gonna touch your weird spaghetti
pie let's consider let's continue this psychosexual tour to the American psyche cannot do you
want to do this Yahoo real quick before we get to audience questions by the way we do
audience questions at the end of the show and we'll point at you guys when you raise
your hands and you'll come down the mics please no bummers please no buyers if you're sitting
there and you're thinking I'm not sure if this is a bummer it is it's one can I read
this Yahoo by Rachel Rosen uh game recognized game Rachel Rosen uh thank you Rachel it's
by Yahoo answers user Simon who asks if you had to wear a picture of food on all your
clothing forever what would it be the obvious answer is whatever a breadstick sandwich or
spaghetti pie yeah spaghetti pie sure so let's take those off let's take those off the table
and put them in the garbage can where they belong here's the twist that I didn't think
about before which is I immediately pictured like t-shirt right or shorts but this is like
on your tuxedo like at your wedding no it's a piece of outerwear that yeah it's getting
yeah all your clothes yes it's I'm a spaghetti pie boy and you know this about me so do you
want to convey class in your one food you want to convey like down to earth I'm gonna
count to three and you say the classiest food you can think of one two three filet mignon
oh you you guys aren't in the podcast well you are now I have to go in and edit that
out let's try again because you guys are like spaghetti because you got spaghetti oh fuck
I blew it I choked whatever what if for the rest of your days everybody could just know
you as mr. filet mignon oh me mr. filet mignon I'm the filet mignon guy people get weirder
names like the guy who decorates his house every Christmas you know that guy is that
his name like the way who like does it you know he like does it and he becomes that becomes
this whole thing like his whole thing can I holy shit yeah none of that was nothing can
I get a picture of two strands of cooked spaghetti that form the shape of a Nike check it just
be like check it out yeah it would be on everything it'd be like a Nike tuxedo yeah it would be
a it would be a Nike Batman costume because it's Halloween fuck what if you wore a Reebok
shirt then you look like an idiot yeah man I'm really glad Griffin we did this one before
going to I had questions didn't have legs sometimes they don't got legs you know you
know maybe that'll be some house lights can we get the house lights up okay so this is
the time we've got two mics down here some move to whichever one is closest to you well
no no no we'll point at you yeah this ain't no TED talk I saw this I see two hands there
was a man who was raising two hands you had yes you yes pointing to yourself now yes yes
yes come on down I can't see we can't see shit hello yo yo hey what's your name Chris
hi Chris is it a bummer though it's not a bummer okay okay Chris what no no please what's
your fucking query oh I wanted to ask you something so Chris what clothes what food
would you have on your clothes all the time yeah dude do answer that though like pesto
or something really you got really let me lay it out for you Chris what you just said
because you just blew my fucking mind I didn't think about this like if somebody can you
like what food do you want I'd be like grain hey I'm on the spot here I'm sorry so I'm
not big ups on like the lore of my baby I'm my dad that's okay I'm diving back but don't
go to D so what's the what what makes a wet stunt what okay so I'll start with I'll start
here in DC they all wet yeah you picked a really bad time to come to DC I stepped out
of our hotel and I got a lift and that was a wet fucking stunt because the time it took
me to get out of the air-conditioned lobby to like cell reception zone there was the
the freshness seal had been it gets bad really quick it does it does Chris picture a stunt
okay now picture it dripping wet okay it's really anything and so there has to be some
liquid my bad picture a dripping way okay don't put words in my mouth that's not a
way it's done is it I do want to ask you Chris I don't want to put you on the spot
okay what do you intend to do with this information it's it's just vexed me for a while okay but
you're not like gonna like go fucking like hang gliding with some new experimental rig
that you've invented and back this seems pretty way I'm hey hey I might I don't know okay
you're not responsible so don't worry about it that's right you heard that one thing you
all take away from this tonight we're not responsible yeah play the disclaimer enjoy
your nuts yeah all right thank you Chris thank you help at all thank you it wasn't really
an advice I saw this beard oh come on beard hey there my name is Peter hi Peter hello
Peter my Yahoo Answers username is Equus Princess oh that's a beautiful beautiful shirt I need
him to be removed no what's up how can we help yeah so I lived in Philly for a long
time and my nice yeah okay kind of rude so my German Shepherd kept finding what appeared
to be human bones in our yard let him finish sorry I'm gonna say let him finish this is
really important can you get can you just eat that you're a tall man get in there just
eat that man yeah so so she seemed to be finding what appeared to be human bones that were
potentially confirmed by my sister-in-law who's a doctor yeah looks like rib bones
or something and a murderer no it's just and and then and my uncle we moved to DC and
it stopped okay and then just a few days ago my wife was home with the dogs and the dog
found one rib bone and then was it a different location later or a couple right and the next
day there was an another bone that that showed up is your dog killing the people that's the
only thing that makes sense yeah it doesn't make sense your dog David fucking Caruso
like well so so here's here's the case I dig it the thing that the thing that I'm concerned
about is we just got back from Seattle and we get more monitor on us from the crowd mics
yeah I heard you say Seattle yeah the thing that bothers me is that we just got back from
Seattle my wife and I okay and we took a small side trip to Lake Sammamish okay where's that
that's where Ted Bundy abducted a bunch of people and and that was that that was at my
wife's request okay and then the bones wait is this a cry for help do you need to come
up here with us there's so many parts of this episode that are gonna be in like a courtroom
somewhere so so am I good yeah you're great okay you totally what could possibly happen
it's gonna be like okay I do I do have a question that I have to have it answered when you're
done with them do you when you're done with them do you just throw the human bones in
the garbage well what would you suggest call the police yeah I would run some tests at
the lab say that say I actually am a scientist I work for the NIH so I could probably do
that all right all right the nuclear Institute yeah why are you asking us about what to do
with the bones in because I gave you my money and I'm here to ask a question I don't come
to you and I'm like I did a yahoo during a live show about having a picture of food on
your clothes it sucked what should I do about it because I know I just shouldn't do it I'm
not gonna you know I hope we helped no I don't know I don't think we did like even close
to anything like helping at all why'd you keep watch you keep all of them until you
got skeleton going at least like half a skeleton and then see maybe it's a person your dog
killed it'll be like one of those 3d puzzles right yeah hey Chris who does your dog hate
wait no who did your dog hate that isn't around anymore anybody no am I have a friendly
dog that okay thanks guys thanks let's go farther back let's go farther back further
back okay back okay wait no no way back no no way back in the middle there you raise
your head stand up yes yes yes no no wait all the way back come on yeah yeah this is
a super nice theater I can like see it real good now the lights are up good job Lincoln
theater people you you got it really pretty in here hi what's your name hey I'm Becky
hi Becky hi Becky um I it is not a bummer I just wanted to clarify um that's what people
say when the first half is it's not it's not okay um so I uh I have a painting uh and it's
not haunted or anything it's just a painting that was my first fuck who's the who's the
painting getting older I have a I have a doll that's also haunted um no I have a painting
the problem is that it is a painting of me um it was done by my my brother-in-law I know
it's great it's great to have a painting I was like four years old just a super cute
you know just a painting of my head region um you know so it's just this like painting
this like you know bust painting of four year old and I was like super cute oh you're four
I am currently four I'm no in the painting you were four yes yes I think we've established
there's a painting of you yeah and and I kind of don't know what to do with it yeah for
sure no totally right there with you dog super yes because like I feel like if I were living
you know I'm living on my own for the first time I feel like if I was living with like
you know husband and kids it could be like up there with the family portraits or whatever
but I'm just in an apartment no yes by myself I don't know that I'm gonna have any advice
you I'm just like yeah dog that's rough like what you've got is what we call a showpiece
ah and what that means is when someone visits you the first time you have to take them into
a room that's completely empty except for a painting on the wall where you just stand
in front of it and go one day I'll get back there I think you're overestimating my my
rent budget where I can just have spare room sleep in your bathroom ah that's the solution
can you put the painting in the bathroom oh like on the toilet like I have to confront
it before they little speech balloon it just isn't nice I feel like that's that's disrespectful
to the painting like my brother-in-law did it it's a nice painting he did it was nice
of him it was a oh my god is he alive see so yes okay he's get him to well I don't want
because I got you okay preemptive get him to paint another one on the same picture of
you behind you like today looking on like so proud you're like oh look I did it recursive
paintings of myself forever I think you have to have a party where you unveil it to everybody
and then who first of all whoever sticks around that's your real friends but I'm thinking
about it now and like fuck dude if I had something like this in like my first place where I was
living by myself and it was like let's go over to Griffin's place and hang out with
this weird painting that's fun like that you could if you can own it's a hard needle holy
shit cuz like if it goes if you miss the needle hole then you're fucking Kathy Bates in misery
or something but if you can get it right in there then you've got like the dopest prop
comedy like literally ever here's the phrase you have to practice oh that get the delivery
of those two words down and you're gonna miss but then you have like a holiday party at
your place you have like a holiday party and you put like a little Santa hat cut out on
top of it it can like transform with each like new thing Super Bowl Sunday like seasonal
decorations on baby me painting own it all right your friends come over and the frame
is empty and you're like I don't know gotta get him real used to it okay own it and hide
it and then hide it all right Justin you I just did you just did oh I'll pick one let's
say wait wait wait wait okay we're so fucking bad at this just do something over there there's
a hand right yes you pointed to yourself in the shirt yeah that's nothing you can't just
say in the shirt you're all wearing shirts everybody's got shirts in here I hope hi how's
it going hey I'm great how are you what's your name Carrie hi Carrie how can we help
so I just got a present in the mail the other day from a not super close family friend it's
a co-worker of my mom's and she got me a pair of tap shoes she sent me a pair of tab shoes
in the mail I've never tap danced but I don't want to be a dick what do I do wait this is
an important question are these tap shoes brand new they are brand new in the box holy
shit like these Carrie feeling here's a bunch of clay why I just think you care about it
I don't know there's an old there's an old curve on a good quote that random ass tap shoes
are dancing lessons from God maybe you need maybe this is a sign you know like maybe it's
time for you to really take stock and say like I like that because maybe the family
friend realizes something in you that you don't realize in your slightly so this is
your my mom's co-worker who I've never met maybe she came from my mom okay wait no this
is a question how do I tell my mom not to give my address yeah maybe she saw a picture
of you on a desk or something okay maybe she's something what's your mom's name Kathy cat
Kathy listen I'm looking at the picture of your daughter and I'm going to tell you something
just one more question you're not going to believe me but I'm going to tell you the one
thing those are tappers camps I'm looking at a curvature they are on the calf these
are the gams of a tapper I am sending her the shoes Kathy do not try to talk me out
of this those are tapas legs can they let me ask you if your mom arose you you know
she will she's gonna call you a month carry all the tap shoes working out you have the
legs for listen to me trust me on this one is a tapas this is Deborah by the way it's
Deborah listen we haven't met I'm gonna ask you a question I feel like I already know
the answer to you've definitely put these bad boys on though right yes and I suck at
tap dancing but how do you get to Carnegie Hall probably by pissing off my downstairs
neighbors yeah definitely because I think about it now like it would be like I get the
box of tap shoes from a total rando and I open it up and Rachel would be like those
tap shoes I'd be like yeah and she'd be like who are they from and they're like already
on my feet I don't fucking know what my dad's weird friends but I can't stop dancing oh
god oh god who's Brian I don't fucking know watch me go I can tell you who's Savion Glover
is though how was that yeah we have time for like one more who has a super good one super
good one okay no wait hold on raising your hand up very high still very like the highest
stand up and I want to tell you it's you yes it's you come on down I got a good feeling
about that when you said super good there's a lot of waving okay take your word for it
really good wave yeah no pressure damn hi hi thanks I did my best you did great what's
your name Emma Emma okay okay so I live in a really big apartment building and there's
sort of a hallway there's a hallway and there's just me and one other person at the end of
this hallway okay and it's a old apartment building lots of policies we're not allowed
to have pets okay my neighbor has a secret dog oh shit I've heard it I've seen it I've
seen them trying to hide the dog from me what do I do wait hold on I need a couple things
how big is the dog it's a little it's a small dog this could be anything give me the it's
like the size of a breadbox yeah they have a rectangular dog quiet relatively quiet at
night yes during the day especially when I'm coming in and out for work not really how
absolute is your sense of justice judge dread
because it sounds like it might be pretty absolute maybe wait hold on to Emma's credit
I felt like she was asking how do I let them know that I'm cool with it they don't have
to how do you get some of that juice on the side like some of that money on Saturdays
don't even trip like can I since I know there's a dog can I like go and be like I won't tell
them if you let me like hang out with it yeah yeah that is exactly what I want to paint
a picture of people at home literally every person in this theater was like yes that's
fucking blackmail you know the only thing better than a dog Griffin the only thing sweeter
than a dog a secret dog every single procedure was like yeah blackmail that fool I don't
care if it's like the most adorable blackmail ever blackmail it's definitely blackmail gray
mail at best man um I guess blackmail your neighbors is it annoying is the dog is the
dog I had a secret dog once for like four days your dog was no secret it was not a secret
dog it was everybody knew about this dog including my neighbors who did bust us I was in college
just rough stuff is a rough situation I got a good scam for you get a dog your own and
then when the landlord's like do you have a dog you say no I think that's the neighbors
you didn't hear it from me but I'm pretty sure they got a breadbox dog over there um
yeah just don't blackmail them I don't think I'm getting mixed messages here that's the
fucking theme of the whole show yeah yeah thanks we appreciate you thank you so much
all right listen Lincoln theater you've been great thank you so much thank you to John
I want to say a big thank you first off to Schmanners I want to say thank you to saw
bones did you guys get a chance if you didn't we got tour posters that are just for this
viewer today and tomorrow we have them especially tour there's two of them yeah it's a two
er and they were done by Taylor smile who you may know from still buffering yeah it's
so good they're amazing if you haven't checked them out I was but those should be available
outside what else anything else fellow thank you to billions who is our to you say thanks
to John Roger call on winners for you to the theme song yeah it's a departure off the album
today spent to you all it's been a long time since we did a live show it's been like it's
been like six months or so we're super nervous you guys have been like very good thank you
so every time when we wrap the show up we have a final yahoo and then what we do is
on the next episode we come back to it we kind of talk about it and Griffin has one
of those right now I think yep someone sent him by Connor Cronin thank you Connor really
Connor y'all are some Jags sometimes because I never know what if it's real or not thanks
for coming and everything that's your dad so happy on my toes sometimes Jags it's fun
note to go out isn't it you guys are jerks anyways thanks for coming out it was raining
by a poster we're worth it buy a poster you bunch of Jags who answers user Amos John who
asks is Ferdinand Magellan the first to circumcise the earth I'm Justin McElroy I'm Travis I'm
Griffin McElroy this has been my brother my brother and me kiss your dad square on the
lips
fun dot org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported hi are you a fan of Star
Trek the next generation well that's weird because it's a corny show but my friends Ben
Harrison and Adam pranika do a lovely podcast about it it's called the greatest generation
and it's on maximum fun dot org I thought that this podcast was a bad idea but I was
wrong please listen to the greatest generation on maximum fun dot org