The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to My Brother, My Brother, and Me, where we have sprung into fall.
Is that? We sprung a leak. I fell into fall. You trip, you trip forward.
Hold on. We jumped up, we reached for fall, we missed it. There's a lot of leaves and branches
and debris on the ground, and so you slip and trip forward into the fall hour, and then in the spring,
you have to wind the springs of your clock backwards. I will make a confession for you
right now. Everyone has that childhood, that fun childhood memory of their poppy or their peepums
raking up a big pile of autumnal leaves and leaping into that pile. I have no memory of
ever doing that, and I am worried the ship has sailed. I'm worried that if I were to now leap
into a pile of leaves, I would be perhaps given a lollipop. Now what you do is you you rake up
the pile of leaves and then you just like slowly lay down in it and go to sleep. Yeah, it's a good
that it's a good place for a nap or actually not because uh one time the last time I jumped into a
pile of leaves in Ironton, Ohio, a spider bit me right on the hand and it swelled up and I never
even looked at leaves ever again. I can't look at leaves. Take note, Ironton, Ohio. Full of spiders.
Yeah. You're on watch. You're on notice from Griffin because of the spiders. For arachnids.
I think the true celebration is the the arrival of the PSL in your closest SB. It's back. It's
back. It's better. Griffin, can I tell you? Thicker than ever. Can I tell you guys? I hate
to make this confession to you but I'm I for me in my heart in terms of fall beverage consumption
it the PSL has been dethroned. What? But um it's been dethroned by the SCM. Yeah. I'm
I'm way. A salted caramel macchiato. A salted caramel mocha. I'm way. I'm so close. Way way into it.
Yeah. It's good but it can't beat that pumpkiny flavor. I love the pumpkin. It has probably a leg
up on the PSL in one department and that is that the PSL really does get thicker every year. It is
pretty much uh it's a it's a pumpkinish sludge. Yeah. You know what I mean? It's like a squash
based triple thick milkshake. There's a half a pumpkin in every cup. I think that. It's bad.
Part of the problem is that I'm 31 almost 32 and I am I can appreciate complex flavor combinations
like salt in coffee and I think that you guys maybe aren't there yet. That's the new thing
isn't it? Is salty. I can't eat. I can't like I ate a crunch bar the other day and it was covered
in cardamom and I was like ah what come on whatever happened to the good old days where chocolate was
chocolate and we didn't need to you know throw sea salt all over we didn't have to every every
snickers bar comes with the comes with one of those pepper grinders and you just put coat it
in some sort of strange spice get out of here with that good old days. Sometimes I feel sometimes I
feel like the salted chocolate is like an emperor's new clothes kind of thing where they're just
waiting for some child to be like hey you ruined chocolate hey you put salt on my chocolate sir
yeah you're right it really is for I feel like it's for 20 and 30 somethings who are like I know
it's salty chocolate can you believe it I'm eating it too. I'm really only one of the Hershey bar
can I just get some fucking chocolate please. Yeah that is that is it is a testament I think to
to where our society is at now that we can't even us indulging ourselves has become so unspectacular
that we have to like we have to put a put irony into our into our desserts. Well it's like there
must be slight amount of punishment it's like that idea when they put like the the like red pepper
in in chocolate and you bite down and it's like oh and there's cayenne in it yeah like can I just
get some fucking chocolate why do I have to punish myself and like oh I want to vomit thanks for the
chocolate. I think they're like I think all the ad wizards were like uh seems like uh this this
chocolate's pretty unhealthy can we get some sodium up in it like a bunch of it how much
sodium can we get in this. So much you can feel it between your teeth great. So you've been listening
to three Andy Rooney's talk about candy. Did we introduce ourselves? No. Okay I'm your oldest
brother Justin Andy Rooney McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother Travis Andrew Rooney McElroy.
I am Griffin McElroy lead singer of the band Rooney. I think it I think Andrew Rooney should
have been the main villain in Bioshock. Is a man not entitled to the sweat of his own brow?
No says the man. Would you kindly tell me why there's so many Japanese? Where Andrew Rooney?
Where are there in Japan? Yeah it's where they are. I was I was I was in my private hydro bubble
dome yesterday and I thought I'm kind of thirsty and I thought that's crazy Andrew you're you're
underneath the water. Do you ever think things like that? No says the man in Washington. I don't.
Oh man. Well this has been my brother my brother and me. Tune in next week. Tune in next week when
we I don't know do probably pretty much that again just with different voices and hope you
don't notice. No this is an advice show and we're going to turn some questions into wisdom right
now. Here it comes. Oh here it goes. I have a slight problem. I talk way too much. Not because
you guys hear how good my voice sounds this morning? Yeah really good. Let me try again.
I have a slight problem. I talk way too much. Not because I'm insecure or socially awkward.
I just hate the idea of silence in a conversation. I've noticed recently that it makes me seem
stupid as a young college student who considers herself intelligent. I have a lot of interesting
things to say but they come out sounding ridiculous when they are said after a long long rant. What are
some ways I can make my gift of gab more meaningful and intelligent? That's from loquacious in the
lone star state. I personally. Justin loves a good long awkward silence. I love to dip in there. He
just likes to soak in it like a hot tub. He's one of those people that whenever there's even a brief
silence in a conversation he will address it and say like oh it's you know that it's a good
friendship when you can just sit there and be silent and it still feels just so so good.
I said it was 1368 sir please pull up to the next window. I think that the way you can
transmute your gift of gab into something that'll make you a hit with other people
is instead of. I know you're joking when you talk about having a lot of interesting things to say
and I'm sure you do but if you can turn that gift of gab into asking questions you know wanting to
fill the conversation up with asking people about themselves or you know filling any spare silence
with a question about the other person an invitation for them to talk about themselves
you will you will be more well liked and people will want to spend more time with you. I was
thinking yesterday about an old bit by Mitch Hedberg, Dear Department Hedberg and he said I
don't have attention deficit disorder but I took Ritalin and I found that I just had an extra long
attention span. I would tell people there's got to be more to that story and if you can be that
kind of listener if you can use your use your gift of gab that way then people are always that is the
ideal person to have in a conversation and like I know that I have dealt with this too like I
tend to talk no I know and the important thing to keep in mind is that while you have many
interesting things to say so do the people that you are oh do they for sure they really though
well I mean if they've just finished a long long rant and pause for a brief second and you go
oh there's marsupials and they have pouches and they're like mammals but then you know maybe
just let them finish their idea and then be like man that was great and you said that it was
actually your cousin the whole time and like make it about their story make it about what they've
said the secret to human relations is that no one cares about what you are saying yep with very rare
examples no one wants everyone's just waiting for their chance to treat you to the thing that
happened to them because unless someone's delivering instructions like and even then
even then it's like hit or miss back in the day like okay back before radio and tv you had to rely
on humans for your entertainment you would say like you've got to hit come on you raconteur
hit me up with a story to entertain me like now anytime that someone's talking is a time that you
are not watching the x factor so like you don't need humans to entertain you anymore you need
them to give you relevant pertinent important information and you'll also see this is one of
my favorite phenomenon like you'll hit a word in your story and watch the person you're talking to
something click in their mind that reminds them of a story they know and then it's literally like
you're watching a fuse yeah count down until they stop listening to the thing that you're saying as
they just fucking cock it in the chamber like wait for their chance wait for the tactical precision
strike to enter like oh oh oh yeah yeah speaking of your dead brother uh did you have you seen
the curious green the the green man benny green man what's the what's the picture by these plants
timothy button timothy button you can always tell the uh the the when a person is doing this because
when you see your when your story starts to divert from the point they were going to tie to it you
can see them in physical anguish it's like you're it's like you're going around highway curves too
fast what were you saying about tiny cars you said something about tiny cars hey do you remember 25
minutes ago when you were talking about that other thing have you seen that new benjamin green man
benjamin green man
so if you can if you can start use your gift to the gift really is asking questions is a lot harder
than talking i've i've found this as i've tried to ask more questions because a lot of times
questions can open you up to some pretty awkward interactions uh sometimes the answers are not
something you want to get back um but so so use your use your your speaking talents to try to
figure out uh questions to ask other people also another thing to keep in mind when it comes to
the conversations is there is not like a you don't have this like basket full of topics and
you need to get your entire basket empty before the end of the conversation it's not super market
sleep and reverse and so like you may have a bunch of things to say but if you have to pass by
you know some topics of conversation it's gonna be all right the only reason i actually like talking
to travis is because i'm always hoping he's gonna slip a dope metaphor in the combo like super market
sleep and reverse super market sleep and reverse yeah are you guys on yahoo yes yep this yahoo is
hidden by nicole b thompson thank you nicole it's by yahoo answers user gracie who asks
what should me and my horse be for halloween please no headless horseman i was thinking about
dressing him up as a dragon but i think the wings would be too complicated and i have four weeks
until the show he's a brown oldenburg gelding with four black legs oh and i'm a girl thank you
smiley face emoticon where are you going that you need a horse costume uh it sounds like some sort
of some sort of uh horse-based costume contest so like like like toddlers and tiaras for horses
yeah right here's the thing you could make a dope centaur costume but you would have to cut off a
significant portion of the horse and and i would i would call it a very important portion of the
horse which is to say it's pretty much its head and everything all that part thinking portion yeah
the think meat that makes his leg meat run well they still have their tiny uh uh forebrain yeah
sure aft brain i don't know hey hey guys what's up yes check this out okay foals and something
that's like a crown that starts with f i don't know what you mean i'm trying to do like foals
and fedoras foals and fedoras thank you that's not good no dress your horse up like dick tracy and
you go as flat top okay uh that joke would have been fun i was gonna go with uh hooves and hay
bales but it what that doesn't make any sense i i really feel bad about it so here's what you can
be as a camel you can be a shitty camel you can be a shitty one hump camel you just put a uh tan
blanket over you and then you're gonna want to secure that you're gonna want to secure that with
some um some pipe tape and then just uh just be a shitty camel i think the obvious answer here is
you dress him up like a person and dress yourself up like a horse a horse right and then you put
him on your shoulders oh and you can't wait wait wait wait wait hold on wait wait wait slower
continue and then you're the horse and he's the person continue but slower what part of slower
do you guys want to try to sort of get travis when he clearly to throw in some detail yeah
maybe like uh what kind of music was playing at the time or is it voice to me hey is it the
lighting is it real sloppy down there hey do you guys want to hear the best answer voice to men
to horses yeah what is it uh yahoo answers user just say low says you could be a fairy of the
forest dress up in a skirt slash dress that has a leaf pattern or a skirt size dress that you would
glue leaves fake or reel on to if you choose to wear a skirt you could wear a pretty blouse for a
top put some leaves in your hair with maybe some orange red or yellow glitter if you're allowed you
could go barefoot for a better effect for your wings anything with a halloween story would do add
some sparkles and leafiness to them for the horse's costume you go bareback add a saddle bad with
leaves on it or use your regular saddle and tape some leaves to it there's more but this person is
basically just saying throw some throw some leaves on that leaves on your leaves on everything what
is the costume a bush horse horse bush it's a horse that jumps in a pile of leaves manbush
nature's greatest wonder my brother my brother means your source for references to obscure
90s comedy the stoopids be there keep it locked in the name of the lloyd we gotta go on in the
name of lloyd oh you could dress your your horse up like stanley stupid okay yeah from the hit
uh 90s comedy you're gonna it's as hard as it is to find a halloween costume that you as a human
being can wear and then have people notice the clever reference that you've made imagine doing
that for a horse that horse has to be some sort of horse right now let me throw this out you know
how they have those things uh like the costumes for dogs that just spit over their front two legs
and then they have like arms yeah those are fun business suits and those are fun yeah i like those
why don't we get like that like horse size so it fits over the horse's head and the horse's
front two legs and then it's got like arms and it's like a horse businessman or like horse yoda
man i just thought about running into that at a party and it gave me the shippers like a like a
bipedal standing up person but with the horse's gigantic head do you guys ever think about how
big horse's heads are and then just get scared apropos of nothing you could there i don't see why
um i don't see why the the horse can't be dressed like something that people dress like i remember
one time a costume that i thought was pretty good was i saw a guy dressed as judge lance edo
from so you want to dress a horse like judge lance edo from the jay simpson trial i thought
that was a pretty good costume so you could just dress the horse like what's something people dress
up like now probably dog the bounty hunter uh-huh oh my god horse the dog the bounty hunter don't
mind if i do what do you dress as a hunter and you dressed your horse is like a wall mounted like
head on a like a like you had to put something around his neck so it looked like his head was
mounted on a wall that's that's not macabre yeah yeah and you put the rest of them in a wall but
then it's like pretty good put them in a box just stand still horse i don't know i think that i i
think that that would be a pretty good make it somehow like a plaque out of cardboard and then
just put what about a zebra i mean i feel like zebras right there you know that's like a minstrel
show for horses oh my god what what come on you guys come on did you see what daniel
was wearing i couldn't believe it's so bold then two days later you see lady gaga wearing the exact
same thing she's so edgy she's so edgy she's in zebra face it's unbelievable she's in black and
white and black and white and black and white and black face and unbelievable didn't they make a
movie about that called bam zoozled yeah oh thank you what there are 10 people out there that will
laugh at that joke no there are there are 10 people who go oh yeah like bamboozled and then
they'll turn off our show and then they'll throw their computer away just so i can quantify did you
just say bam zoozled yeah i did okay in a zoo where like in a zoo okay all right i think it's
all right i think there's meat on them bones thank you justin man i tell you if you did not
have cinemax in the 90s listening to our show i don't even know how we had it our parents didn't
pay for your free weekends or something they're like specific free weekends if you could go back
into the annals and like cut cut i could rebuild all of our pop culture knowledge you could you
really could i don't know what a hunger games is though i feel like there's very specific gaps
basically here here's the flow chart did it have tom arnold in it if yes macaroons yeah was tom
arnold and bamboozled he i know he was in soul plane yeah he was definitely in soul plane um he
was in true lies uh tom arnold was in everything yeah yeah do you guys you guys feel like we've
ds you guys feel like we've drenched all the meat off this bone oh christ yes let's do another
thing okay so let me i need to take a moment then ask you something griffin you people ask us a lot
they seem to notice that you guys end up talking about horses and ghosts a lot yeah and it's like
yeah that's true and i think man i wonder how it happens and it just dawned on me that like
you are the one who's continually introducing horses into the conversation we don't get any
like listener submitted questions yeah like hey my brother my brother me horses if the three of us
were sitting in a room travis and i would be talking about like life and sure love and growing
and every few minutes griffin would like lean in and say yeah and like horses right let me uh let
me hit you with this what uh do you remember the first time we talked about horses uh and i found
that yahoo or someone found it but either way i claimed credit for it it was like i had i had
staked my mining pick into the ground and just uh just a torrent of i guess horse blood shot into
the sky shot into the sky and then i was like yahoo i'm rich i'm saying we have found red gold
we have found a deep deep pocket of natural comedy gases and i am ashamed when it runs out
we have to start fracking for horse questions yeah yeah honey might honey does this ice taste
like horse blood to you this is strange anyway that's why also there of all the people in the
world speaking out against horse blood fracking of all the people groups there are in the world
to make fun of i feel like horse owner and horse enthusiasts um equestrianistas are uh the funniest
and also it's the safest because none of them are listening to the show correct okay you can love
your horse just don't just not as much as your kids and it's not as much as your kids or your
family or your dreams it's important i know it's it's tempting because when you ride a horse it's
like it lends you its wings i gotta go back and remember some of those bumper stickers
has everybody on this podcast ridden a horse i have yes what was what did you like it uh i rode
bear back because i was on a farm i was on it for about uh i'm gonna say nine and a half seconds
before it bucked me off and i thought it broke both of my balls broke them in half
it's the worst pain i've ever experienced down down there
uh i when when i rode a horse it was at a place called bob's happy trails horse farm or something
like that definitely was that the shawnee state park happy trails horse farm yes something like
that yeah and shawnee state park did they call it happy trails horse farm because it's where the
horses go so that kids can ride them before they are killed before they actually you actually ride
them to the glue factory and drop them off and walk they say happy trails tiger i guess that's
the name for a horse it i i'm sorry is ben's maybe it's under new management though because it's been
a long time since i was there it's been 20 years but ben's happy trails horse camp i see but yeah
the only time i ever rode a horse i just remember feeling it's really it's really it's a really
the only time i ever rode a horse i just remember feeling it's rippling muscles and warm skin
betwixt my thighs and then i stared deep into its classy eyeball and i grabbed this chinkle
chinkle uh-huh and started praying to oh don't stop slower slower for me please the horse in my
thought a little funny it was tender it was tender no don't back off of it now you might be listening
um was it jtrh nbr or what was the deal just was it was it jtrj nbr or you guys know it was
um we actually i don't think we talked about jtrh nbr on the show no you got to listen to
the set dish if you want that yeah that nug if you want it that nug that choice
justin tell us about your happy trail experience i wrote it i got a boner i don't i want to oh my
god it's you can't be blamed for that because you're riding on just a mass of rippling muscles
it's like it is simultaneously like riding a bunch of vaginas and also like a gun
it's like riding a living cannon yeah yeah made out of vaginas that's what it's like a vagina cannon
a vagina cannon justin tell me where the where the horse's pubes trimmed in like a tasteful
line going to its penis why can't we just ride horses why do we have to fuck we don't have to
i'm saying we don't have to we get you because god gave us domain over all the animals i'm still
trying to figure out the title it seems like an abuse of our privilege then i'm still trying to
figure out the name of the farm a happy trail is it but is like a wish thing happy trails horseman
camp it's called happy trails because the horses are about to die and the trails are pretty happy
i just want to say as funny as it seems like to make fun of a person who loves to have sex with
horses there is it's america there's and it's earth and it's this reality there is somebody
who falls into the cross in the venn diagram sliver who is of our show's listeners and people
who like to have sex with horses and is not amused i would hope that that person has a good sense
i don't know the line must be drawn here there is no i'll apologize to furries about my ill-advised
ill-informed rants about furries i will apologize to jugglers or should i say juggler about the
shit that we said about jugglers i am not gonna i am not gonna go so far as to apologize equestrophiles
nope we we do not stand by our previous calls for violence against the furry community no
that was a that was an ill-advised joke we love furries now a demo for jugglers and i totally
support people who want to have sex with jugglers yeah if you want to have sex with a juggler go
nuts uh that's between you and your god but uh yeah i think we can take a pretty bold stand
against having such horses you know this might be a little uh little controversial but i just do
not support horse fucking all right well well wait wait wait wait wait it's okay between horses
let's that's how that's if if we were if there was no more horse fucking there wouldn't be more
horses and that's at the end of the day that's what you have to keep in mind but yeah man man
or woman i guess woman is all right if a horse wants to bury his powerful horse shaft into
another horse's quivering waiting horse vagina yep i think that is i mean give me a sell tickets
to that i don't know why you are going so fast with this i keep telling everyone slow down we
have an hour you know what i mean that is more than enough time from there's no rush there's no
need to rush this dance yeah yeah we're just in a this is i'm trying to rush straight to a gallop
and you guys are you guys are more of a cantor um
well that was half the show on one question let's move on horses moving on a few months ago i moved
from ireland to michigan and almost everything has been great should i should i should have a
brogue don't do it i should probably keep reading keep reading what do you think about my brogue
should have a brogue no keep reading i think you gotta go bro he's talking about okay when american
people meet me and hear my accent they always ask me to say stuff didn't they often you should have
a stroke right there in the middle of the question how should i react okay so when american people
meet him they hear the accent they always ask me to say stuff then they often do their best
oh no oh golly what a kerfuffle uh how is my face red or should i say green irish
how should i react to these requests should i be polite or should i tell them to go to hell
that's from different in detroit you know what we talked about earlier about how everybody wants
doesn't want people to talk you're in one of the rarest positions where people actually do want to
hear you say stuff yes but my friend marianna mcgee who also co-hosts in case of emergency
with me like every she's got a pretty noticeable australian accent every time that she goes out
somewhere some douchebag he's like where are you from okay now say uh throw another shrimp on the
barbie now say and it's like it's like turns them into like a sideshow act like a puppet it's the
grossest thing and and the dude thinks that he's laying down mad game yeah like ah she she likes
how cute i think it is she likes how xenophobic and narrow-minded i am she loves that shit i'm
really gonna segregate her from the rest of the group yeah awesome can everybody just be like
cool about accents yeah chill out i guarantee i bet i i've never traveled outside of this country
because it's the greatest country on earth um but me i bet that you don't go to like england
and someone goes oh my god what is that an american accent well no because your president
and stuff our accent is the grossest but i also bet that no one over there like you don't roll up
and someone's like oh what is that an irish accent weird no because they're they get that shit all
the time because they're writing up next to it they get that's what i'm saying could we maybe
just pretend like it's not the first foreign person you've ever met i think plus they they
see it on tv and stuff a lot uh because all their tv shows are i think our accent to people
on not on this continent or this continental mass i think i think it just sounds like every
time we're talking like whenever we're talking it just sounds like pizza's just fallen out of our
mouths i think it's a muddy i think it's a muddy sloppy sloppy diet dialect i don't think anybody
likes listening to it maybe when these people are like demanding that you say stuff in your irish
accent then you respond to them with what you imagine an american accent to sound like yeah
and be like okay and that's my impression of you how do you feel we all best friends to like a
british person we basically sound like the cockroach alien and human skin from the first
men in black movie a lot of times when we have conversations like this in uh our international
listeners take it as a cue to write in and kind of fill in some of the gaps uh in our in our
international knowledge i just want to make it clear on this point specifically i i don't really
care what you think our accents i like so please don't the only thing that i i really want you to
do is take the sugar like that okay i remember you know what i can remember being um a young boy uh
griffin won't remember this i don't think travis will either but i have a very clear memory i don't
have a very clear memory of the first time i discovered i had an accent because i was like
10 years old and i was at the beach um it was i think it was like an all-inclusive resort or
something where people there were like a lot of activities planned for the kids so the kids would
would do things separate from the parents and let the parents i don't know what parents do either
by themselves watch tv or something uh so uh we were leaving for the day for the week and uh some
of the kids i'd hung out with uh said oh we're gonna miss you justin we're uh we love your
accent and i and it was literally like it was like the end it was like the end of usual sustrans
like it's like guys are so say like wait a minute i do i have an accent i have an accent like for
christmas like two or three years ago dad gave us like all of our home videos converted to dvd oh
yeah and i sat down with teresa to like watch and was like honey come watch you know here's all my
memories as a child and i had i had always known that like we had an accent but not until that
moment was it thrown into so harsh reality as the video of justin and i playing on the jungle gym
oh yeah and it's like hi father you motherfuckers you motherfuckers turned the word daddy into a
four-syllable word you sounded like old prospectors thing if we weren't like three and six you would
assume that we were doing like the worst comedy routine ever there are a lot of bad that if you
watch this in malcolm gladwell's book the outliers he talks about how you need 10 000 hours of
experience to become an expert in something uh i like to think now my brother my brother me is a
show made by comedy experts but if you watch these because we've done hold on because we have done
10 000 episodes go on no believe no but we've been trying to do bits for our whole lives if
you watch these bit if you watch these tapes you could see a lot of half-formed comedy ideas and
all of my jokes now make about as much sense as they did then there is an idea there is a uh there
is a tape and then watching them now i just like i i oh it's hard to watch because i can see the
setup and then the execution just falls flat i said there's one tape where travis is i'm gonna
put him at four and travis says knock knock knock this one yeah knock knock dad says who's there
here travis says knife yep that's his knife who and travis says would you rather work nightly or
knifely yep what does it mean we'll never know what does that might as well be said in hieroglyphs
but see if you had fucking done that if you had done that on a stage and just taken your bombing
as hard as you would have it would have been like andy kaufman-esque like brilliant so you're saying
four-year-old travis was just a comedic genius yeah we all griffin used to have griffin had a
great bit when he was four or five the cheese no no i don't remember the cheese bit every time
there was a camera pointed at griffin i would say cheese he would just go cheese and it didn't
matter if it was a video camera or a regular if i was at a funeral or a pinhole camera i used to
look at eclipses don't care uh no griffin had a pretty good bit where he used to come up to you
say is there a baker under your bed and you would say no and then griff would say have you checked
they would say no then griff would say then how do you know there is not a baker under your bed
and you know some people was adorable and hilarious for me it was terrifying and i often
lived in fear to fear because they were in bunk beds and griffin would hang his head down at four
o'clock in the morning and shout this into travis's face i uh i have a confession that i need to get
off my chest after okay probably 22 years okay oh wow i stole the baker under your bed joke from the
movie rocket man i stole probably my most minute joke that whenever you talk about how funny a kid
i was i stole that shit from harlen williams took it right from him are you telling me this
yes i hate you took it right from you hate your fuck are you serious 10 years old you thought oh
my god this kid's on another level nope you know who is on another level is harlen williams
he while he's on another level for a 10 year old that's great because when i was seven i
used to think that griffin was like a young harlen williams
mm-hmm holy shit griffin yeah now i'm being usual suspects again now i know kaiser sozay too
sozay again um i didn't uh sozay we all so say we all you have suspects those
oh god can i go to the money zone yeah i guess yeah i guess stranger whoever you are i don't
even know you maybe you were adopted take good care of this precious baby for me
hey i want to tell you guys about wait you haven't seen dot com uh that's actually wait
you haven't seen on itunes also and you can follow them at wait you haven't seen and that's wait the
letter you haven't seen um and i want to tell you about ross has seen every movie twice tucker fancies
himself a pop culture expert but has not seen anything not jaws not pulp fiction not scarface
or even roadhouse it's time for tucker to see the films that everyone else has seen they watch the
films discuss its pop culture significance and occasionally bust into freestyle rap
to observe it only occasionally racist kidding and always entertaining if you want pretentious
dinks who spend hours discussing the artistry of one shot this is not for you well so wait you
haven't seen have they seen harry and the henderson have they seen rocket man have they
seen rocket ribbed all of its comedy you guys you don't understand i did you a fucking favor
i waited i i went deep deep into the rocket man minds and i came out with all of the comedy
or that existed in it and i'm gonna be honest it was not it was not much it required a light there
was a lot of cruft i uh i just i think it's really i think it's really indicative of the
box office success of rocket man that griffin has been cribbing this bit yeah and it never occurred
to anyone i actually talked about that extensively on icoe and every time i've ever told anyone about
griffin i've mentioned the papers on your bed and not one person in all of these united states has
ever gone well you mean you mean the rocket man actually uh jessica lundy put me on blast once
she's like i remember that one from on the set harland harland dropped that one on the set
and i don't think he'd appreciate you
this man has been brought to you by amdb um i don't know come on give me some come on now i
had to watch you did obviously i mean you did watch the movie i guess jessica lundy also in
the stupids it's all six degrees here people six degrees to tom arnold six degrees of deceit
people come up to me and they're like i bet you can't link tom arnold and harland williams
like sit your ass down dumb bitch one lundy uh so sex toys they are i like to think that we
here at my brother my brother and me are part of the normalization of adult play
things uh i think they're already pretty normal but go on well us and 50 shades of
gray are really helping to normalize toy play it's funny you should mention 50 shades
okay i'm not saying that we are responsible for this but on the home page of extremistrange.com
there's a banner that connects you to items inspired by 50 shades of gray now travis i'm
gonna go out on a limb and say that's probably inspired by the massive heart-stopping no i have
to success the occam's razor this and say that we talked about 50 shades of gray and
extremistrange.com last week i believe we made this happen i i want to see something in the
hero section of extremistrange.com the there's the online marketing terminology for this sort
of thing oh i thought you meant items inspired by the show heroes no i want to see something
items inspired by my brother my brother and me oh you can just buy you can just buy the book
on extremistrange.com that is i suppose an item inspired by 50 shades of gray
here's here's that they got they got cat suits and and everything that you think you think you
know about i bad news is you don't know anything about it so like you think catsuit oh sexy like
cat woman yes they've got that but then they've got another one that covers up your whole body
like i don't even know i don't have a i don't have a it's like a no man like it takes you out
of reality or something like you phased out and it's scary but maybe you can fuck it i don't
can i fuck this can i fuck this shadow man go for it i don't know i'm not gonna make rules for you
the rnd scientists at extremistrange.com are are willing to answer that question for you can you
fuck it um can that rnd by the way stands for rumping and dildos i there is a okay so
where is it okay so if you want a steel bra with leather straps you can have that it's 240
dollars and there's a check box here that says for add a four inch nickel plated die cast snap
for 295 i want to be there with those married couples looking at these like i don't know honey
do we need the extra do we need the extra four inches or you think you're going to be okay
okay times are tight times are tight i mean there's a lot of affordable options you guys
would not believe how inexpensive anal beads are they are giving them away they're cheaper than
you think and and hey um uh the good news about all these prices is that we can knock 20 off for
you use the coupon code middlest and you're gonna get it's gonna be like way cheaper it's gonna be
like crazy cheap 20 right 20 percent well 20 cheaper yeah i mean it's gonna be awesome
extreme strings.com is the website it's e-x-t-r-e-m-e-r-e-s-t-r-a-i-n-t-s.com
dot c-o-m forward slash studio strip forward slash geo cities forward slash tripod
forward slash actually do yourself and your lover a favor and go check it out today treat yourself
train that ass i'm looking at the strict leather large dildo harness and that's out of stock so
don't miss out on the like the something else the army hardest harness with dildo or something yeah
you don't don't miss out just get it get that female plug you've earned get the anal trainer
set it's on sale now for only 23.80 we've all been very disappointed in your anus's performance
slightly we want to enroll it in a seminar um and by seminar i mean a gradually increasing in size
series of um but valves i guess is what's a good way to describe what these things are but but
missiles we're just gonna ram jim up in there you're gonna be good to go you're gonna be a
very productive member of the company you're welcome you're welcome yeah you're welcome
extreme space dot com coupon code middle list me and my pals are in the throes of a masculine
evening we had a big old barbecue with burgers and wings photos attached thank you uh and now
we're watching the usual suspects and drinking beers whoa that's crazy inception but there's a
problem for our post bbq suite we ended up buying a lemon meringue pie while delicious we are all
agreed that the lmp is a far from testosterone inducing post-dinner treat we'd love to hear
if you have a recommendation for a manlier dessert we presume as members of the volume
loving american nation that you'll have a better idea than us sissy brits that's from effeteater
in southeast london well you've come to the right place i'm fat might i suggest each of
you eat your own cheesecake that's what no see that like that hoes into sex in the city territory
for me everybody having their own individual cheesecake just for women that's what most of
the series was about everybody just eat a pint of haagen-dazs yeah exactly that's that's the vibe
of that why don't you four just jerk each other off what a sweet sweet dessert that'll be
i don't understand that i think the obvious answer is deep fried things is that too is that too well
i think well the obvious answer is to not assign goddamn genders to the dessert that you're eating
you madman like why is this bothering you so much griffin because it's it's i think it's sexist to
say this sweet light treat is a woman thing and these these hearty barbecue ribs are for dudes
only bros only with these ribs now griffin that's that's wonderful that's beautiful and you're very
open but have you never just like had a dude's night like yeah i i will have a night where i
primarily hang out with my dude friends but we're not gonna eat like a key lime pie and be like oh
what are we doing i man this is tough because i think that whether or not you i mean you can you
can do this without assigning gender roles to it i mean you can just say that you're having sort of
a a hearty a hearty night i will say that i don't think a lemon ring probably goes with barbecue
yeah that's crazy if you want to talk about flavor pairings you're yeah that's not i don't
think i i think if you're saying like this is a themed like outdoor cookery you know
old school kind of dinner then yes lemon meringue probably does not fit the the theme god you know
what i know that this is kind of a weird question but now i'm sitting here trying to think about it
like a like you have all your guy friends over it's just boys night out you know and you're
making some ribs and drinking some whiskey and i'm trying to envision a dessert you pull out that
it's not like what are you doing well that's the thing that's why back in the day then bradberry
and bob and i would have like a cookout day the dessert is more meat like you just eat meat you
fall asleep on the couch there is no there is no like way to transition that conversation of yes
good steak i like to eat it i've got something sweet i need something sweet on my teeth here's
my suggestion because whenever i do a cookout party this is what i go with get some bananas
all right slice them open without peeling them stuff some uh chocolate chips in there and wrap
them back up in foil pop them on the grill for about 10 minutes is this a real thing you do pop
it open either yeah it's delicious that's really good it is amazing and it's like grilled bananas
you know stuffed with chocolate and it's badass because you're like eating it in foil and it's
like fair food simple as shit still still shaped like a cock yeah i mean there is that i mean you
can do the same thing with apples too corn apple soak it in like brandy and syrup whittle it whittle
it into a cock shape and then put your dick in and put your dick inside the wrap it up in foil
pop it on the pop it on the the grill for a while i wish there was a way of and maybe i don't know
what the what you would call this aesthetic but i wish there was a way of separating what you
would traditionally apply as the you know call the the dude you know pastiche the the steak
the whiskey the jason statham movies what have you i wish there was a way of separating that from
um just dudes yeah like like i understand this is an aesthetic and i think that women should be
absolutely able to enjoy it too i just wish it didn't have like you're saying gender roles
attached to it right like called like an evening of badassery yeah i i don't know you like you
even like i don't know uh badass seems kind of presumptuous for eating steak and watching
kevin spacey movies like just seems like i don't know hold on hold on hold the fucking phone
yeah did you just give kevin spacey a carte blanche badass status i know i said it i said no
travis did i'm saying it's kind of self-important for watching for what badass this describing
yourself watching a kevin spacey well don't fuck what about don't fuck with spacey
he he could fucking wreck you did you see him in american beauty he was getting jacked
what if what if you called it just like an evening of male bondage okay now okay hold on uh
we'll come back to that the first time i heard k-packs i assumed it was somebody's frat nickname
from college a guy named kevin paxton and everybody called him k-packs k-packs
k-packs hey man i hope griffin had said that one very well i love justin's self-editorializing
it's just a note if hopefully we'll hear that written in red ink cut this i cut this that's
totally funny travis uh male you've you've actually explicitly put the word male
into the thing that i'm trying to execute like an evening of person bondage okay no what okay
evening of bondage because like you're bonding together but you want to say bonding yeah it's
not about it's not even about the bonding like i don't know i don't get down on the sense of
fraternity so much as just a sense of like eating food that is bad for you even it's bad for you
like eating some steak and having a martini and watching k-packs a good question but why can't
you just say like we're having an evening we're doing stuff we're getting together it's important
to let people know what they're coming like what they're coming into yeah you want to you want to
establish the the the vibe what would you call it justin i don't know i'm saying i don't have a good
answer i think we got to use a totally gender neutral word for like it has to be gender neutral
like nachos and steak then what if we just called that like dump and it's like a very it's a we're
taking a dump no no it doesn't have to be that it's just a word that sounds like the thing that
it is it's dump night come on over for dumb and then if sunday sunday sunday um dump
don't worry your fancy khakis we're taking a dump
i'm gonna take that word back from the way that you did honestly the juvenile way that you guys
are using it i just i'm gonna open a fancy chicago restaurant called dump does it have like three no
it has one one you with an umlaut jump i just come on down to jump we got steak we got steer
we got stick a job kpx um oh the walls are just lined with plasma screen showing the my the
choices we got all the freshest angus sticks and all the choices cuts from kpx a job
oh i just wanted a word to describe manly that is it doesn't exclude people with vaginas that's
what i'm saying i don't think that that's asking so much just what about jump but to be fair i mean
to be fair this is not just dudes are not the only guys who do this because every so often the
ladies here in cincinnati will have like a ladies night where like they do a clothing exchange every
year and they'll like literally no joke sit around and like give each other manicures and pedicures
and talk about boys and drink wine and like you know to me that sounds like fun yeah that sounds
like a good time i know but it's not about but it's not about like yeah i would love to go to
that too man clothing exchange i'd love to get some new duds but like i'll talk about boys all
day Orlando bloom Orlando swoon we're like i'm in but so then when that happens me and the men of
cincinnati we go play pool and you know we go see a band and play shuffle each other off
it's tuesday you know um griffin you got a yahoo yeah let's hop to yahoo we've only done one yahoo
give me another one wasn't funny let's do like a funny this one was sent in by
just put in like horse or ghost or something um this this ghost was sent in by emily wall
thank you emily wall uh it's by yahoo answers user ghost of or should i say joseph who asked
uh my ex called me out saying that i'm not a juggalo on facebook
i tried how dare you man i've tried everything to prove to her that i am one and she still
keeps saying that i'm not one what can i do to get her off my three asterisks
which means dick what i was gonna say maybe you could learn to curse like an adult yeah
you think juggalos are very reserved about their cursing to get her off of my butt my family
help me help me murder jay how do i get this how do i get this lady off of my my rear end
she's a real pain in the backside um i'm just getting really p.o'd right now
you know uh is the problem that okay did did she accuse him on the social network facebook
of not being a juggalo in his day-to-day existence or he's not she accused him
is he not repping the juggalo lifestyle i think that she was saying when push came to shove
like at the breaking point he would he would crumble and he would not you ain't no twitter
low is what she's saying yeah right sure he claims to do it he talks the talk of course
but could he walk the walk he so and you say you mean like when he's at the gathering he's repping
hatchet man yes but on facebook he's just like complaining about gases and stuff on uh when he
when he goes into work at 7-eleven is he is he living the juggalo lifestyle sure is he openly
is he openly juggalo so in the in the world in the in the his night his native habitat he's you
know slippery dick dave but on on the book he's just he's michael just michael his mom follows
him on facebook he goes by regular dick michael just completely normal dick michael um you know
uh a writer is a down ass juggalo or juggalette who is down to ride for you or with you and i
think that she is that what does that mean that is r y d a what does that mean what does any of
that what does a down ass juggalo or okay but who is down you said two words in those three words i
don't know well like a down ass juggalo you know depressed no they're like you're a soggy butt
hold on i need to check the cross surface and see what down means okay there is no down is
not covered okay we let us assume that it means like cool can i tell you guys the top two injuries
in wikia in the juggalo wikia uh for juggalo terms okay the first is axe a motherfucking serial
slaughtering weapon used for honor and to split your shitty dome piece haters okay that is fair
that's the same it says as marion webster now hold on this fucking tool is the shit
you want to split some haters dome no problem so that dictionary out you just got dictionarized
bitch a is axe b bigot an extremely prejudiced person very attached to their own blue system
that is the only entry for b is the word bigot that means the thing that means they think they
made up the word bigot that's crazy that's an old thing we've been saying could we um could we use
it in a sense could we could i could the origin of that word i used yes i used my axe on that bigot
who died thank you who then got who was then root word and perished uh root word big
i hate you juggalos here's here's an entry for c cherry pie this means a virgin then it says
listen to cherry pie for reference uh no thanks juggalo wikia i think i get it
you may not have put this together because it's when it's uh now i do want to i don't want to
act like i'm not repping the clown love uh i i'm down with the clown uh for life i actually think
the juggalos are a i uh misrepresented people who are kind of fun and i'm not anti juggalo i'm pro
juggalo oh juggalo i thought you were saying juggler no sorry everyone sorry jugglers just
kidding oh man do you think we have any juggalo listeners oh we have one and it's this guy it's
the same guy these girlfriends online being like you listen to my brother my brother me known
juggalo haters you ain't juggalo i do i do i like the juggalos i think it's a fun i like how they all
get together and like beat the shit out of tila tequila it's like a fun it's like a fun game it's
like a they just they just threw garbage at her no nothing wrong with that you guys i think okay
let me ask you this are you really better off it would you be better off in a world without juggalo
okay well that was easy this has been our comedy podcast my day to day yeah in your day to day
life this has been our comedy podcast my brother my brother me thank you so much for spending your
time with us uh uh yet again we we sincerely sincerely appreciate it we want to welcome a
new podcast the max fun family it is uh it's called risk true tales boldly told and uh and
and it is our it is our news edition hosted by kevin allison who you might know from i don't know
the state which state no that's a joke it's a it's a television program not a great joke but
yeah still a joke um but but uh yeah so risk is is the news edition to our family i like that show
and uh i can't wait to welcome them to our to our bosom um thank you to everybody tweeting about the
show our show not their show fuck their show we win yeah uh thanks to uh little socrates instant
gems sweet doom yeah pat note in color dar2d2 uh dan jaco these are songs in my cowgirl uh
uh nick haskell so many graham off brian we really appreciate you uh and love you very much
um i want to thank john roderick in the long winters for the use of our theme song instead
of partial off the app and putting the days to bed if you secured ticks to max fun con east
you are going to get a chance to bro bro down with john roderick um so so thank him in person
for the good jams for the power jams uh we can't do it in person because of a restraining order
which is uh unfortunately why why we will not be a max fun con east a couple people have asked
we went to max fun con west and we want to leave room for all the other podcast kids to be there
so we are in luck them out with our charisma you're in luck though because it is an amazing
lineup and you will have a great time so don't even worry about it and just know that while you're
there uh look up at the heavens look at the beautiful uh clear sky and see the moon and
know that somewhere out there we're dreaming of you that's probably not true um if you'd like to
ask oh uh mail mail call excuse me gents mail call uh some things we got to our we have a mailbox
it's mbnb am po box 54 huntington west virginia 25706 did you get any more veiled death threats
no more veiled death threats i did get you keep that postcard by the way because i would like to
frame it no i threw it away because it's horrifying uh tiffany and denver writes us with a picture of
a horse that's delightful uh let's see kenjamin kenjamin thank you for writing this is a postcard
of a girl saying i know how you must feel brad but kenjamin wrote us a very nice note we got
some comics uh sent sent to us uh through the mail uh from andrew fulton so thank you andrew
for the uh the comics and then things got a little weirder we got a dvd of a japanese wrestling
sampler nice uh leo sent us a picture of a cat oh no sorry the cat is leah the card is from jill
and jordy hoit came in the mail uh alex from tempe sent us uh some amazing papercraft of uh
pamela anderson with garfield head and garfield with pamela anderson head thank you uh that is
now sitting on my desk so thank you to everybody who did we get a brochure about pet turtles we did
get a brochure about pet turtles i did not know who said that but thank you for signing us up
is it not i don't really enjoy have people not gotten the fucking we can't say it i'll edit this
out but we really want people to send us money right like that's why we did it so that people
could just send us money unsolicited yeah i don't i don't want weird like i don't want the fucking
thanks for the postcard i guess but how much i can't spend this you know just send us i don't
know like i don't want money because then people think that's a joke and they'll send me like
monopoly money and i'm like hardy hard that's gonna go in the post office trash can i need like
cash baked goods something like grants would be great something untraceable i just need something
i can trade when the revolution comes sky high stacks some something i can barter with you know
just something to get us out of the country give me some of that barter paper they called money
you guys want to yeah please god save me for myself uh this finally i who was sent by emily
wall oh man it's so good they're these the following 11 words i feel like summarize this
human being more than any 11 words could ever summarize any other human being it's by yahoo
answers user trevor who asks is it possible for a ferret to hide a fushigi ball i'm just
mackerel it's been my brother my brother and me kiss your dad square on the lips
keep your heart three stacks keep your heart hey keep your heart three stacks
keep your heart man these girls smart three stacks these girls smart play your card