The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
It's a new craze, and good girls do you wanna? Just say, hey I wanna. Just say, hey I wanna.
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother and my brother mean advice show for the
modern era. I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I am, at least according to my birth
certificate, your middle-est brother Travis McElroy. I'm Griffin McElroy. Summer's here.
What? Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot. The hot season is here, summer. Check the thermostat.
The beaches have sand, and you know what that means. The drinks have ice. Then it's summer
stuff all over. And May flowers bring June powers. Sun power? Sun powers. What are the songs of the
summer? Well shit, I mean it's, I don't know that we're far enough in because I like to think that
mid-July is when the Black Eyed Peas are finally gonna get their shit together. You think they're
finally gonna get it going? Middle of July is what I expect. I think they're gonna get together.
They're gonna do the, you know, theme song to a big, the new Spider-Man is gonna have a Black
Eyed Peas joint as the theme song, and it's gonna be partially about Spider-Man, but also about how
good it feels when you're together with your friends having a party. Yeah, something about
like let's, let's party responsibly. I have been, uh, to try to get the, um, the pulse of this. I've
been enjoying, um, NBC's Songland, a show where the woman who wrote Super Bass and the young boy from
One Republic and another gentleman with a beard and a guitar help young songwriters make the next
big hits for today's artists, and I was watching an episode with Jonas Brothers, uh, tried to create
their song, uh, Greenlight with a new, um, a new song named Able Heart, right? And so they have their
choice of songs to pick, okay? Um, and that this song includes lyrics like, um, just say I got the
green light the things we do past midnight just me and you and it feels right just an empty room
and the green light and it it I just can't help thinking about so another bit they say before you
come around yeah I was feeling blue so tell me if you're down and I'll fly you to the moon got me
begging you for more yeah it's nothing new ain't nobody in the world does it like you do I just
can't help every time I would they would start to improvise about this song about fucking I can't
help but think about yeah that's the thing it's not about stock car race no sir it's about sex
and every time I think about it I just think about how these men these men who are brothers in much
the same way that we are brothers are like well guys let's fucking pump that song about sex will
you harmonize with me my brother on this song about how we get down with people can we do that
together as brothers together at the same time we'll sing the same thing in this song about pure
sex joe what rhymes with juices on my fat hog let me get my rhyming dictionary
joe you know how it is whenever you get you know the good stuff
uh-huh you know joe hey joe is it is it four or five r's in jerk because I want to get it right
for the song our new number one single it's not the thing to get hung up on in the lyrics you
just described but why is empty room invoked there that's not sexy in the original version
of the lyrics they the the gentleman even says like don't need a bed like we don't need a bed
i think you probably do if someone said hey come have sex with me and i said yes i am interested
and then they led me into a room that was just ceiling and floor and like four bare walls
they're gonna dexter me yeah yeah yeah all the lock star exterior green light um i don't think
that i could sing that song i mean we talk about a lot of adult content here i guess that's true
true not in an earnest way when you're writing that people will put us on in the background
to make love well that yeah it's not a seductive show entertainment weekly has actually named us
four years running the least seductive podcast in the business just try to have sex while you
listen to my brother my brother impossible can't do it can't just can't get the rhythm going
yeah that is what most people will always be legal as long as my brother my brother and me
is legal to be downloaded yes because it is impossible but with our anti-sex with our
fucking twisted south park humor who knows before they shut us down that's true they have been
talking a lot about shutting us down lately they're always trying to come for us but no one
else is coming for us the um the preview of the uh the next next week's episode i'm extremely
excited about because the songwriters the young songwriters for next week's episode
are going to be working with aloe black to create a song for the soundtrack of fast and furious
presents hobbs and shaw so that is a massive opportunity but wait just a huge opportunity
i would love it's probably too late to get in on the filming of that isn't that movie already done
yeah but at the end it's just going to be like boop do do do do do i don't know i haven't heard
this song yet here's a song about hugging hobbs and shaw hobbs and shaw saving lives by breaking
the law people say that you're fast and i'm too furious but i know that is claim is spurious it's
the other way around i am the quick one and you are the one with a quick trigger on the gun fast
and furious hobbs and shaw don't know anybody who's not loving y'all in the box office you're
the number one everybody come and hold this gun it takes a village i hold this gun
indris elba is in this one
we've done it songland al aloe please call us uh we're ready to get started this is an advice show
and we do questions do you want to do one i would love that griffin thank you you read my mind i was
i was about to segue into it because i felt that energy going that way but of course you and your
infinite wisdom you sense the energy going that way just a split second justin's looking for the
question i just i have heard it been said that any internship remains unpaid as long as you don't
steal enough stuff from the company i actually have a pretty well-paid internship in an office
but i still want to take the lamp from my desk when i leave the position okay i've done my
research and this desk lamp is valued at 50 it's a special brand damn that's a good lamp it's a
special brand that mimics natural sunlight so artists who work with color have a more honest
relationship with their art but it's a good lamp this lamp i like the phrasing of that like this
lamp makes me able to date my painting this lamp does not belong in a cubicle hidden around the
computer for the next intern to not totally appreciate as a hobbyist artist the lamp belongs
with me how do i steal something this large from my internship or is there a more chill way to ask
for it that's from lamp lust in little saigon damn this person's got it all figured out i
wish i was this confident about any of my life decisions first of all i would like to address
the first sentence and maybe it's just i haven't worked enough internships but i have never heard
it been said that any internship remains a pain as long as you haven't stolen enough
yeah as has been said by me here in this sentence in this question to you uh here's a chill way
okay ask your boss do you mind if i move this lamp oh good oh that's so good that's really
good and non-specific yeah you leave that what now listen this is risky because if your boss
says move it where and you say my home the jig is up i think that if you asked for the lamp as
you're walking out the door on your last day it would be so disconcerting i think for lack of a
better word it would be so jarring that the person might just say like yeah um yes yes and then you're
gone like you're already out the door um but at that point it's a huge risk right because that's
you're waiting to the last minute with my plan so it may if they say no there you're out of options
here's what i'll say here's another uh way to ensure success here ask it like this and it's
cool if i take this lamp right so good travis damn and you don't even need you don't even need
something to come before the end but the implication is like we've had a whole conversation
about the cool things that will happen when i leave and this is one even better just sort
of hold it up in front of your boss and say it's cool right you know what let's shorten and just
say huh cool yes um you could say hey i'm gonna steal two of these lamps and your boss is gonna
be like no you're not and you'd be like you're right just the one could can you can you maybe
go with like i loved this job was sort of like the best things ever happened to me and i really
treasure it and want to remember it and i'm gonna go ahead and take this lamp to remember all of
you because you were a light that lit up my yes yes you're the light in my life and this is now
the light in my apartment if i maybe just say like i brought this lamp from home and when your boss
is like but it's like all the other lamps and you say that's why i brought it in because it reminded
me of all the other lamps oh see i was gonna say you could bring in another lamp and just swap them
indie indie style swap them but they would notice that you're taking the lamp that looks exactly
like all the other lamps and you left a garfield light up lamp that you found in your sister's room
that's not great so uh you're gonna need to start bringing a really large felt puppet to work with
you now now and start getting everybody comfortable and not only comfortable accustomed to the idea
that you always bring this huge huge felt puppet with you uh that keeps you company in your cubicle
uh that you have conversations with it when you needed you know to blow off some steam
or talk about the new episode of game of thrones that hbo is sending directly to you uh and then
once everybody sort of appreciates the fact oh well that's just you know their big big felt
puppet you'll know by the way the the key there will be when you don't have the puppet if someone
says hey where's the puppet now yes now you know you're in the clear to stuff that fucking lamp
right up in that puppet and carry it out and it's never even been a thing and you know what the you
know why that's such a good idea why why because there's nothing else you could put the lamp in i
want to describe a bit of prop comedy that you could do here to get away with this and i want
you to really don't interrupt me but i want you to close your eyes even if you're driving especially
if you're driving and and really imagine this okay as you're walking out they're applauding
as you're walking on your last day say i just want to let everybody know that this internship
has given me a really bright idea and then you hold the lamp above your head about what i want
to do with my future and then you keep the lamp above your head and slowly back out the door and
they will be so confused as to what is happening or laughing their asses off laughing their asses
off thank you griffin yeah absolutely like losing it with this great prop comedy you did
that they won't even think like he'll they'll assume that you'll bring it back that will be
the assumption that's made is that you'll be bringing it back at your earliest convenience
also get a big parachute tie it to the lamp throw it right out the freaking window
first floor this isn't great if you're on the first floor it's not great just thank you you
kind of do need it to get to terminal velocity but if you're on the first floor it's not a problem
yeah i would say the first floor is probably fine second third and fourth it's probably an
issue but fifth you probably have enough yeah there's four floors there where it's no good
or you really need the wind to sort of pick up maybe tie the lamp use fishing line yes they
can't see it tie it to your belt buckle so it looks like it's hopping behind you and just
keep saying like come on come on and they'll be like the lamp wanted to be with them the lamp
chose them over us okay i know this internship has given me a really bright idea then you hold
it above your head right and then you put it back down and you say about what i want to do
with my future i'm gonna be a lamp repairman and i'm gonna start with this guy right here
and you just yank it out of the wall and walk out the door and they'll be like he's gonna be
the greatest labor pair man ever because he's really dedicated to his craft there it is one
of these certainly has to work certainly one of them i got a yahoo answer here that was sent in
by jack thanks jack it's an anonymous yahoo answers user who i'm going to call theodore asks
what i get laughed at if i call the living room the drawing room and the dining room the morning
room and the kitchen the scullery i watch a lot of movies from the 40s so i've started to pick
these things up and yes i'm aware the living room was called the parlor but i don't have a mansion
what i'm so there's there's so many things there well i mean i would rather have a drawing room
than a parlor right because i you know me i'm always sketching something and it's true yeah so
my plants my is that why it's called the drawing room maybe it's more like the drawing together
of new ideas or perhaps where you might draw cards for a game of dude it's sketching doodles
and doing fun cartoons uh yeah people love that shit back down in abby they were always just
whipping up little you know ziggies uh just that little doodle where it looks like the guy with
frizzy hair is poking his nose over the horizon what's his deal what's he hiding he even doing
here's the thing that i think through me about the further details of this question griffin
the question asker saying you're just picking up things like yeah like it's i don't know like you
traveled abroad for two years and came back with a bit of an accent yeah also the 19th century
yeah also the 1940s is really when these words came to power the 1940s during uh you know world
war ii is when we really started calling shit the scullery uh i i'm no uh historian but i'd be
willing to bet that basically for as long as you've been dining in it i think the dining
room has been called the dining room no it's the morning room because you only eaten there in the
morning anyway we're dodging the question and the answer to it is you're going to be made fun of so
savagely uh you may actually die from it yes you may actually experience death from how bad the
making fun of you is if you say if you call your kitchen the scullery and there's no amount of
explaining a way that i feel like you can do to get over this one that's the big one because i
think if you called your living room the drawing room even your family who loves you the most they
would be like hmm that was weird okay that's fine and then you call the dining room the morning
room they're probably gonna say do you mean the dining room but the second you say scullery it's
done yeah it's done fetch me my pita chips from the larder and what are you fucking saying what
do you mean how i i look at houses sometimes to kill the time until i die and i was on zillow and
they i saw one house that had a room that was labeled popcorn room hell yeah i tried to google
it and google had never heard of it so i don't know it must just be this person saying self-explanatory
did you look with their photos nope no photos just a one label popcorn room i don't know if there
were doors or not i guess there was a door but it was just labeled popcorn room did you put
in an offer right i mean did you go in a little bit under asking oh shit no i did almost buy a
house one time that when i was very young except i didn't have the money to do it but it did have
a door hidden behind a bookshelf oh i've always really wanted that if you what do you think would
be the hardest room to pull off saying that you have with a straight face because i think
it's conservatory oh yes i think that would be the one that would be the toughest to say like oh this
is the conservatory that or i think the ballroom the ballroom is tough the ballroom is tough if you
say you have a conservatory though it's just to murder someone in hands down that's my main sort
of familiarity with the room it's and which is weird because you're not conserving something
you're snuffing it for it should be called a snuffatory probably sex dungeon yeah that's
tough that's tough um you know they also call conservatory solariums that's even worse i think
i think you could get away with solarium only because people would like if you walked into
you know sometimes people like screen in their back porch or they like you know have windows
in the back porch or whatever if you walked in and said this is my solarium i wouldn't know that
you're right but i also wouldn't know that you're wrong and i wouldn't say anything you could get
away with that but if you walked me back there and you said this is my conservatory i would say
no it is not the solarium is a room where you watch the george clinty vehicle solaris yes that
is the main purpose of that but don't use your desk looping don't even fucking think about eating
popcorn while you enjoyed the movie there is a separate room for that you should know better
you have to go into the other room if you want a salty snack my favorite is like how it differs by
country like if you're in london and you say where's the water closet they'll be like oh
it's right over there but if i said that shit here i'm getting booed out of town and people
are just gonna make fun of me till i cry water down my face i didn't know this when i first the
first time i traveled internationally i went to cologne germany for a games conference and i
didn't know i didn't even know what water closet was so when i saw the you know restroom sign with
wc on it i thought like this is where wc fields goes to shit and i think they are dead um and then
i remember asking somebody like where the where the toilet was and when they corrected me i felt
like such a boob because it's that must be like somebody over here was like where's where do you
keep your shitter and pisser at where i can make where i can make my dirty trash in a hole because
i didn't say the good way to say it i guess wc must stand for worst conservatory this is the
worst conservatory i've ever seen in my life if i ever end up selling my house i'm gonna walk
people through it saying and this is the bed conservatory and this is the bath conservatory
and this is kind of the living conservatory uh and this is the scullery i work in the office
at a factory and we have random spirits days with themes i rarely participate yeah that sucks but i
woke up this morning and put on a floral tank top hawaiian shirt shorts and hula girl dress socks
for vacation clothes day hold on a second the name of that is fucking chilling and i have to
put my head between my legs that's grueling can you even imagine what it would be like if you
had imagine you got to wear these for their intended purpose now you will wear them as a
cruel joke i have made a mockery of your vacation clothes couldn't couldn't we just call it vacation
day no because then they might not show up no no no we have vacation days but they're pretty much
just for going to your nana's funeral they're not for actually like fucking relaxing because you get
four of them vacation clothes day as i pulled into the parking lot i had the sudden realization
that i only glanced at the theme schedule once jotted it down on my calendar and heard no word
of it since i'm now second guessing myself what if today isn't a spirit day should i call in from
the parking lot and go home and that's from floral in fort wayne this took a this took a chronological
turn that i wasn't quite expecting like it was it was not a a perspective shift as much as it was
like a time a time shift i think this question asker is a time shifter i like questions where
people send them to us and they're the answer is only applicable for about a five minute window
several weeks ago it gives you the sense of urgency but not you're right it's like some
simultaneous urgency and the complete lack thereof i think it is completely legitimate
for you to put on vacation clothes and then drive to your workplace and then look in there and look
at what you're wearing and think this is so fucking grim i'm gonna actually just do the
vaca i'm already dressed for it this is what this person is debating right right should i
just take a vacation day like yeah probably yeah yeah you're already dressed for it just fucking
piss off this all day this is the start of at least two different movies that i can think of
joe versus the volcano in office space look at this moment of like you know what i'm just gonna
wear my whole lion shirt to work oh also i fucking hate this place this place sucks also you know it
all comes out in the wash sometimes you'll be out on spring break and you'll wake up and you'll put
on some khakis and you'll put on a nice oxford and you'll be like oh i guess my body wants work
and then you'll go to work because it's what your body craves at that moment you gotta go
or the clothes make the person is what i say it makes them go to the places that they need to go
that day the traveling pants the ice cream suit all of those things ice cream suit you know what
you're doing that day you know you're going down to cold stone and you know that you're robbing it
oh no why did i put on this ice cream suit you put on the ice cream suit you pull the hood over
your face you say i gotta have it i would say have no fear walk into work wearing it and if people
are like why are you dressed like that just say it's a spirit day because here's the thing it's a
completely arbitrary thing and if someone says no it isn't then you say well point me towards the
spirit day authority and we'll find out that's good you could also look at the calendar and
that and be more diligent about that is a one step you need it for today yeah i know i know i know um
i'm just saying in the future it would be cool to do whatever tomorrow's spirit day is gonna be
just to give people a sneak peek of what it's gonna what how big a jackass they're gonna look
like for the next one hey guys why are you wearing pajamas i'm just saying next week this
is what you're all gonna look like so really think about it it is it is interesting to think
that it sounds like there's a really loose grasp on what day is what you could just wear whatever
the fuck you want to work any day and if someone sees you be like why are you like oh i thought it
was and it's like okay cool like just wear whatever you want this is it sounds like wild west
you're you're speaking as someone who has worked out of their home for the past several years you
you have lost perspective that is true i have worked many a job with many a dress code and man
it's uh you started i hate khaki pants so much y'all i can't i've worked so many oh khaki pants
can't get me in them these days i've turned mine into fun t-shirts i watched i watched a facebook
video where you cut the uh crotch out of it and you can make them into cool t-shirts you just put
your head through the crotch hole and you wear the legs like sleeves now you're getting it
then you get to get a little uh crop top action going folks can see your bibo my hairy bibo hey
have you been reading uh the belly button book the fuck you haven't read the belly button book
what do you think i am hell yeah is that a show my hairy bibo my hip bones cute summer look people
like it and then i have a zipper for my chest hair to get stuck in uh jesus this is so i can't
get over how grim this is it's i can't get past the like i i think you should quit probably but
like that you didn't list that among the options as a privileged position to take but good god
almighty i listen i am not saying that all like jobs suck and working at a factory is bad or
anything like that i think somebody's saying hey you know what would be fun if you our workforce
pretended like you didn't have to come to work today and you wore the clothes that you found
enjoyable and relaxing while you had to do your job like right that's mean we never get it's just
me we never get to see you on the weekend tyler show me show me saturday tyler i would love to
see who i would love to take a walk in his mind can we should we give them a job yes welcome to
your new gig you got the job uh here at my brother my brother and me industries and that job is to
follow us to the money zone it's not a very good house how else are we gonna provide for our
burgeoning staff here hey i'd like to tell you about casper okay i love casper there i said it
i'm not afraid i'm begging you here's the thing you tell me not to talk about it every time but
i'm in love i'm in love and i don't care who knows it griffin it's i love it it's the way it's the
it's the fucking full-blown oprah stank that you put on these words okay i like when i sleep on it
it and they have a brand new hybrid mattress that combines the pressure relief of their
award-winning foam with durable yet gentle springs i can't wait to sleep upon it and fall in love
all over again oh my god and you can be sure of your approaches with casper's 100 night
risk-free sleep on it trial so get 100 towards select masterses by visiting casper.com and using
brother and check out that's casper.com slash brother use the word brother and check out
terms and conditions apply justin do bone branch you like to sleep right we've already proven that
conclusively with our extensive meditation on beds and i'm in love okay i i'm in like with these
great sheets uh hey soften your heart let down your walls soften your heart and soften these
sheets what's that you don't need to because everything that bnb makes is designed with your
comfort in mind from their 100 organic cotton signature soft sheets the cozy throws their plush
towels bowling branch products have thousands of five-star reviews people are at the heart of
everything they do from farmers who grow their organic cotton to the people who vape their
organic cotton in the vapor room that they have set up there on the process because they're
considered employer they also offer a no risk 30-day trial and free shipping in the u.s you can
return them the stuff you buy from if you don't love it thank you i have their plush towels and
this is this is this is a hundred percent true when i'm drying off after my shower the bowling
branch towel dry my hair dry my face dry my arms dry my chest dry my tummy dry my back and then i
fold it up and i use another towel for the downtown stuff because i don't even want to risk it you can
get started with their products right now our listeners get 50 off your first set of sheets at
bowlandbranch.com promo code my brother now when i say bowlandbranch.com promo code my brother i'm
not talking about the regular way of writing it i'm talking about b-o-l-l and branch.com it's a
bad name which i'll continue to say in every bowling branch ad because i'm kind of curious
if they listen so don't tell me don't tell them just don't tell them don't tweet i'll know i'm
just gonna keep saying it's a bad name they should have picked something different and they should
change it until i get an email from maximum fun dot com until i get you know for maximum fun
telling me justin stop it uh stop doing that they're extremely angry with you uh i will
continue to mention how the sheets are great so good the name is rad uh and my brother is all one
word you think great sheets.com is taken it has to be right it has to be right
great sheets dot yeah okay what about uh great sheets.pizza i'm gonna fix this for them great
sheets z is trademark someone say great sheets.com that is trademarked well but they do they just
want to be sheets what about great sheets.ghost great great soft great soft stuff great soft
stuff.com let's see if that's taken that's available $12.99 great soft soft stuff.com
will take you to bowling branch so you don't have to remember it's b-o-l-l anymore great soft great
soft stuff.com and you can uh and you can use that same promo code my brother but just with
a different website that doesn't require you to remember that bowl is misspelled intentionally
i listen to reading glasses because bria and mallory have great tips you're a comics reader
and you want to use a library connected app you can try out hoopla i listen for the author
interviews i'm mad at myself that i waited as long as i did to start reading joan diddian
they give me reading advice i didn't even know i needed if you go in person to an event and go up
to an author or a filmmaker or anybody and tell them what they you don't like about their work
you're a trash baby look i understand you didn't like heroes season three that's fine i like i
don't actually need to know that information i'm bria grant and i'm mallory o'mara we're reading
glasses and we solve all your bookish problems every thursday on maximum fun uh hey can i tell
okay uh yahoo time you want to yeah i love that all right this one's sent in by nick thanks nick
it's anonymous yahoo answers user alissa who asks okay no joke i found a four-leaf clover
clover in your opinion should i eat it to get the luck out of it would that let me absorb the luck
in parentheses if you want to see the clover it's on my instagram and then they've provided
their instagram handle here's the thing if you hold the clover you get a little bit of luck over
time right spread out over time until it's all used up interesting eat the clover you do get
a big burst of luck yeah right so one big good luck for eating the clover right so the question
maybe the question is what do you have planned for the day if you're like i've got i've got the
big game coming up yeah eat the clover eat it but if you're like i was just gonna sit around
maybe hold the clover and you find like a dollar in the couch you know what i mean i'm saying
uh griffin would you eat it well i'd if it's for the big game as you know when you eat it you get
about four seconds of super good luck so i would need a whole big old ziploc bag full of these
things which i probably have to crowdsource you could do like okay you got two strikes it's the
bottom of the ninth you're down by two right you're you're at bat you got two players on
base already you see the pitcher wind up real quick you pop it in your mouth chew it up and
then you swing i mean a satellite a satellite falls from the skies and destroys the pitcher
which of course counts as a home run for the batter which is a weird rule i don't know what
they allow if the pitcher's destroyed mid-pitch it's called interference and his automatic home
run here's what they don't tell you this is what leprechauns won't tell you i'm gonna pull the
curtain back what leprechauns won't tell you is the good luck you get from four-leaf clover is
because that four-leaf clover has siphoned luck away from someone else and given them bad luck
so in that circumstance you're getting a burst of good luck and the pitcher is getting a pretty
solid burst of bad luck right like what are the odds because if you're gonna have good luck
someone else has to suffer just remember that recently looking at traf yeah i know listen i'm
telling you what those leprechaun big wigs won't tell you i'm ready to give you all the secrets
that the leprechauns don't want you to know buy my book for $29.99 buy my book
you guys like the critic
so like it's been our new segment you guys like the critic it's a pretty good segment
it stinks justin it stinks oh i love that it stinks right if you're if it's in you
you're still making content does it have to be physical contact for the luck to get on you or
what's this what's the story uh yeah i mean you have to be in possession of it that's nine-tenths
of the law read a book but the thing is is when you consume it your tummy acids start breaking
down the luck molecules oh so that's where the energy is released right big burst but then
they're gone how many three leaf clothes can my tummy tell if i've taken a three leaf clover and
glued a fourth leaf onto it now if you have four three leaf clovers you do have three four leaf
clovers so that that's another thing the leprechauns won't tell yeah your stomach is your stomach
the people working in your tummy factor you're like oh shit we got a lot of four leaf clovers
coming in whatever that's one two three twelve okay yeah whatever the fuck oh man i don't know
this job's so hard oh corn corn corn alert corn we still haven't figured out what to do with this
shit oh no i want a munch
for some reason that one gave me the feeling of like a janitor rolling in in the middle of a
meeting just like hey don't mind me just here to empty the cans i want a munch
do
that's my manhattan transfer version yeah it was really good good news for dirt bags
okay kfc's cheetos sandwich is going national baby following the limited time launches of
pickle fried chicken kentucky fried chicken and waffles and cinnabon dessert biscuits
the kfc cheeto sandwich is another example of how kfc is continuing to take food innovation
in to new heights after an overwhelmingly successful test earlier this year kentucky
fried chicken and fan favorite cheetos are giving fans nation they just they should just say dirt
bags but okay giving fans nationwide access to the sought after cheetos sandwich for just
just four short weeks beginning july 1st this is a special twist on the kfc crispy colonel sandwich
this and i think this is literal in this case dangerously cheesy combination
is made by coding kfc's juicy hand breaded okay i'm not going to tell you guys we're
much called quiz how do you think the kfc cheetos sandwich is constructed
give me your recipe for if i come into the meeting and i'm like boys we gotta do it kfc
g x cheetos make the sandwich what is it i'm going to say it's hand breaded including did
you say ham breaded because that you're on the right track it's okay i think there's cheetos
dust in it and then maybe some kind of like cheesy sauce cheetos has to be a part of every
yeah whole ass cheetos right there on top i think whole ass cheetos are on there i think cheetos
i think they will call it cheetos milk cheetos blood i think they'll just call it it's it's
hand breaded and i love how they say it's hand breaded as if i care about the fucking like
the tlc that went into this fucking yeah i think it's cheetos all the way down and and with each
sandwich we put just a little bit of irony in every hand breaded fillet yeah eat ironically
kfc the dangerously cheesy combination is made by coding kfc's juicy hand breaded extra crispy
chicken fillet with special cheetos sauce that's what it says special cheetos sauce
get that regular cheetos sauce the fuck out of here this is for jeremy he deserves the best
this and placing it on a toasted bun with a this is a quote that i fucking cannot parse
with a quote pinch of the thumb index and middle fingers layer of crunchy cheetos huh
huh i don't know what that means but that's what it said i i guess it's like how many you can get
with three fingers if you imagine that grabbing motion like that amount of cheetos out is like
on there and then it says with the colonel's mayo and i don't know if we can hold that
but i would like to not include the colonel's mayo just waiting for an expose doesn't it
yeah what did you think the colonel's mayo was this is why they keep going through the actors
so fast it's because reba steps in she's like gosh i'm excited to be the colonel and they're
like okay so we do have to tell you the company secret they open up the briefcase and she looks
at it and says no i'm done y'all let's find another one at the end you are processed and
turned into the colonel's i haven't seen reba in a while where's reba reba's gone i love the new
barbecue flavor of the colonel's mayo chaos colonel's mayo is reba to celebrate the nationwide
launch of the sandwich chester cheetah will be murdered summarily no he doesn't say that
chester cheetah will be taking over manhattan's 14th street kfc restaurant can't the police do
something what does that mean he's gonna be taking i'm gonna tell you i'm gonna tell you
travis i'm excited uh yeah well it's gonna be an exclusive all orange everything pop-up event
where customers can try the sandwich for the first time in advance of the restaurant in
restaurant availability on july 1st why does that stuff always happen in new york
it just doesn't seem fair i'm not there um both cans kfc and cheetos have dedicated and passionate
fan bases which if you have to say it in a press release is probably a lie so it only made sense
to merge these two iconic brands together did it to provide an irresistible and flavorful sandwich
that offers the best of both worlds oh my god planet planet cheese and kfc help best of both
worlds fought um it's uh they're creating delicious menu items that flan fans flock toward which is
accurate because they are sheep i am looking at a picture of this sandwich and what i want to discuss
now is the textural difficulties that this thing's gonna provide first of all it's bigger than any
human mouth like you're gonna have to attack this thing from the side good good news the people
eating this can only loosely be described as humans okay so that's fine let's just go through it
bottom to top and talk about the textural experience bottom bun that's soggy as fuck
at this point there's no way that bun's getting to you with any amount of crisp toastiness left
then you just have wet that's the colonel's mayo and you know how i feel about that then you have
whole ass fucking cheetos that's gonna be you know they're toothsome they're a toothsome bite
and there are they're gonna flop all around they're gonna be loose that's a challenge and
then you have very very heavily crusted fried chicken you get the more crunch meat crunch on
top of that and then another wet bread there's like that's so that is gonna suck there is no
way that you pull your mouth away from that thing with what you would call a good bite of it a good
cross-section good representative bite of this fucking thing this looks like a real agro crag
i would eat the hell out of this oh my god travis listen i wouldn't be proud of it but i'm saying
that given the opportunity to try it i wouldn't i don't think i'd come away well i don't think i'd
walk away from the experience at all but i don't think i'd walk away from the experience saying
like this is it this is the new chase sensation but if you gave me the opportunity to eat a cheetos
you know chicken sandwich or whatever i'd probably do it i like cheetos i like fried
chicken if we can hold you know the colonel's mess then i would totally check it out the colonel's
made such the colonel ancestors made such a big mess they're selling such a big big mess
um and also quick munch quad jr just so people don't send it to me arby's made a carrot out of
meat yeah it's just a fucking they're not gonna sell it i'm only interested in things that they
think that you a human would consume with your but want to consume with your body um so yes that
also happened it's called the merit because it's made of meat that man they sure do like meat there
huh i've noticed i've noticed a thread a sort of common thread with all of their sort of messaging
they sure do like meat and you know what they hate fucking vegetables yeah they don't like
vegetables they do love meat this next question that we got we don't normally do these like help
me like make a judgment call here but this one just baked my noodle so hard i had to include it
because i want to know what you guys think oh yeah this is this is an important subject uh
justin would you please read the question i would read it but i think that would weird people out
because it's just not what we do at a gaming convention last summer what i needed a gaming
convention uh last summer i needed to quickly grab lunch between panels i was muttering the line at
the food truck was huge so i walked to the person who was first in line and offered to pay them for
their meal if they ordered for me too oh my friend says this is the same as cutting in line and was
bad i think it's more like postmates where i paid someone to get lunch for me but on the other hand
i recognize that this increased the wait in line for the time it would take to cook my order i'm
worried my friend might be right they are so i haven't done this since then brothers was i cutting
in line or no and that's from genuinely concerned at gen con let's yes this was bad can we obviously
back can you've run the numbers already you know it was bad you've run the numbers can we can we
tweak it can we tweak reality just a little bit i got this i got one of thanos's cool stones and
i snapped my fingers and the thing changes okay what if instead of going to the person in the
front of the line and saying like hey it's like postmates you work for hey look you work for me
now instead of that what if your buddy is like like in the middle of the line or close to the
front of the line you're like oh shit hey can you go ahead and get me a burrito too is that bad no
this is what i'm saying i don't think this is bad i think what it is is it's revolutionary and
sometimes when something is revolutionary it can seem bad it can seem scary at the time but then
we look back on it in the future and it's like wow on that day they changed the game of ordering
at food trucks now here's the problem if everyone starts to do this there's going to be one person
in line who's ordering 500 meals yeah yeah and the 500 the 500th person is going to have to
get stuck with the bill which is too bad have have you guys noticed that i i my hat does do
go off to this person in one regard that i have found with food trucks that you are either ordering
um and getting your food in like a few minutes or spending a good amount of your life and missing
your daughter's high school graduation as you wait for a slimy taco have you noticed this
like there's an immense amount of variability in food truck speed that we've all just decided to
accept yeah yeah what's what's the deal can you say it like that can you do it again justin but
do it like what's the what is the deal with food what is the deal with food truck jerry never got
to do that do you ever think about the the jokes that seinfeld didn't get to do i bet he'd have
some stuff to say i bet he'd have some fun with that what no but can i just say but for real guys
what is the deal with food trucks is it a car this sucks uh it's it's obviously cutscenes if
you put your body in the line yes but it's like psychic cutscenes if you just put your desires
in the line i would argue that it's only cutscenes if you are adding one more sale between like if
if i if someone said like if someone said i'm gonna get a burrito right and someone walked up
and said make it two burritos the order time is the same now someone said i'm gonna get a burrito
and they say cool let me step in behind you and i too obviously obviously we're talking about the
other thing i have i have a new i have a new plan stand at the front of the line with a stack of 20
us dollar bills as people have um received their order in the moment in the flush of victory upon
receiving their order you offer to buy hey can i have three chips oh can i just have three chips
for this one dollar bill you won't want those three chips by the time you're done consuming
your dish just give me three chips and then i think you can just sort of give me one of your
burrito it's like food antiquing you know you're just you're just getting a little bit off the top
you're at the sampler table you're getting your points on the back end exactly exactly hey here's
here's the deal i'll stand in line with you massage your back i'm just gonna need 10 points
on that burrito and merch rights merch rights to that burrito did i say merch i meant munch rights
on your burrito uh just three chips you can have the first bite because i know how that i wouldn't
like it but i get the second slice me off one fifth of that kit kat bar and i bring me off a
well-measured piece of that kit kat bar now i'm off to dessert now you don't want my mouth on your
food that's fine i got two buckets here one's full of quarters one's about to be full of little
slices of food that my friend my new friends whittle off into it and then there's a third
bucket that's for cleaning the other two buckets don't look at that bucket it gets so fucking nasty
and don't put the food in the quarters one i don't want that metal stink all over my falafel
this is time theft don't fucking do it i think it's fine do it your friend was right don't do
it i think your friend is just afraid of the change you've made in the world the ripple that
you've begun the bad ripple the ripple of painting there maybe you're a doofus maybe maybe it's bad
maybe it's not sometimes change is scary we are fucking hanging on by a thread we are hanging on
by a thread and waiting in line for food is like ground level society do not start dismantling what
little fabric we have left as a people wait in line for your fucking churro and then get it like
everybody else okay we're hanging on by a fucking thread and we're all just going to wait in line
and enjoy our burritos all right all right you know what you've convinced me justin what if
there was 60 windows on this what is now becoming a sort of food train and you have to catch up with
the food train food train is better because that's the problem is there's just the one window
and no one's talking about that no one's talking about food train no one's talking about how if
you had 60 windows we could all just get our food the moment we want it you know what's it thank you
you know it's a kick-ass spot that millennials love to go and nosh down at is amtrak stations
amtrak stations get there after the big game head over there after church get to the amtrak station
hit up the food train okay listen can i hit you guys stop the podcast and let's talk about food
train for a second right what if there was a single train track that wound its way through
this great land we called america and there are food train stops wherever like all throughout the
country right but it's just the one train and the one train track and then when you started to get
a line you have like a single car right and people are lining up there at the carnival because it's
in town for the carnival that you're having all events will take place on the food train track
okay so you if the line gets to be more than two people in line another car on the food train
comes and joins that one and all of a sudden you got twice as many windows no one is waiting if
those people dissipate the food train goes to the next station where it is needed do you understand
it's infinite capacity and it only does hamburgers you can't special order it yes there's just the
hamburgers on your fault is it they are good hamburgers not the best hamburgers it's not
it's not burger king you can't have it your way you have it train way that's it that's the only
way available this train this idea beats so much ass that it's going to become the only legal way
to obtain food now we've entered into a program that i would like to call snack piercer and in
this one we have to we you have to live on burger train you know you never hear about how these
dystopian societies start with a kick-ass idea like food train they all like maybe it was supposed
to be like dope like wouldn't it be cool if we could just watch everybody big brother happens
you know what i mean but at the beginning it was like that would be cool like we could watch
everybody and just make sure they don't get into trouble it would be so sick if some of us started
eating the other ones of us and then it's like walking dead it's like oops you took it i didn't
mean i didn't mean all of us ah shoot dang it i stand by food train though i feel pretty good
just need some investors the oils they have hot oils inside and when it takes a turn
that's why only automatons can work on food train that thing's giving away american jobs justin
they're i'm create it's a zero-sum game travis i'm not taking away any jobs there isn't a food
train right now it's a zero-sum game you are taking away hypothetical jobs dystopian jobs
yes now what i do like is you're also creating american jobs because someone would need to build
both the train and the automatons i like that part and destroy so many buildings to make way
for the food train tracks it i i estimate to have a train track that it weaves its way through our
entire country will take let me just check my mouth here 783 years so there is that especially
just put it where there are especially because it's going to purposefully weave directly through
every mcdonald's and burger king that already exists in america also it's on roads we got rid
of roads and it's just food train what about my car you don't drive cars anymore the earth is
dying the train comes no cars there's just food train solar-powered hamburger slinging food train
is the future yes get on board now literally but don't get on board because it is there's
hot grease in here there's so many moving servos if you just like that's what i'm saying don't get
too close to food train because you will be caught up in it like an old-timey industrial worker
every surface on food train is a broiler we couldn't afford to just have single
boy every service robot train and it will annihilate you and now you might you might
want to get on because we have bulldozed every forest in america to make way for this train track
we get that if you want to get on because it's bad out here it is a if the robots are made of
metal why do we need discrete grills do you understand what i'm saying they're cooking on
their grill these hot sexy robots are grilling the burgers on their chests and peeling them off for
you a delighted carnival goer they're peeling them off each other's chests it's sexy in there
we get why you'd want to get on the train but you gotta resist the siren song of the robot food
train if you get on this sexy hot wet greasy train you will die i don't know why the scientists made
them all look like mark ruffalo i don't understand guys this sexy burger train will fuck you up fam
listen the ruffalo bots are grilling hamburgers on each other's chests and delivering them to your
town whether you like it or not do not get on this train or you will die but also do not miss the
train because it's the only opportunity this train is delicious and it is uninsured there will be no
one to care for your family no recompense will be made for your death all of our resources to create
both the food train and the ruffalo bots nothing is left for health care we are so sorry but please
enjoy this burger that's 5.99 it's all of our budget goes to food train and war because everybody
else hates us for our food train everybody wants our food train now in the case of a foreign invasion
the ruffalo bots will will militarize so they will continue making hamburgers though so do not fear
but it's sort of uh they just see people situation so it's gonna be that is gonna be bad that's also
gonna be bad at that point you want to stay away from the train uh we are still working on some
kind of way of letting you know whether we're in a approach the train or stay away from the train
situation we haven't figured that part out yet we'll get there folks we'll get there uh but but
not this episode unfortunately this one has come to a an end a screeching halt if it were uh thank
you so much for listening to it uh we hope you have enjoyed yourself uh if you want to come see
us live this uh here in the next few months you still have some opportunities you can see uh
uh july 16th we'll be doing some first off i'll list some taz readings of our new book
murder on the rockport limited the adventure zone one on the rockport limited it's a second graphic
novel uh and we're gonna be doing some readings me uh kerry and griffin are gonna be in new york
on july 16th travis and dad are gonna be in portland on july 16th july 17th you can see me
and griffin in austin and you see travis and clint our dad in los angeles please come to that show
for sure if possible um and then july 19th we're all going to be in san diego california with uh
dad me travis griffin dad kerry everybody everybody's gonna be at that one it's july 19th
in san diego uh uh tickets to those are at bit.ly forward slash become the monster i believe uh or
you can just go to macro.family and click on tours we're also doing some bim bam and taz shows uh our
july 20th taz in san diego may be sold out i do not know uh august 30th and 31st we're going to be
in atlanta with taz bim bam uh let's see september 1st orlando with bim bam september 25th we're
going to be doing the adventure zone yeah there's a lot more throughout the fall just go uh that's
in washington by the way but uh there's a lot more coming out the fall go check out bit.ly forward
slash become the monster or go to macro.family and click on tours and uh and uh hopefully you
can come see us uh and justin mentioned the murder on the rockport limited you can pre-order that
book whether you're going to those book shows or not which i highly suggest we're really proud of
this one it's really good you're gonna love it you're gonna love it uh go to the adventure
zone comic dot com pre-order it today it comes out i believe july 16th or 17th one of those
don't be the last person in the world to get one go order it now i heard a rumor everybody on
planet has gotten it but you oh no whoa thanks thanks to john roderick in the long winters for
the use of our theme song it's a departure off the album putting the days to bed sick album
killer tunes and killer riffs great beats and it's great and thanks to maximum fun for having
us on the networking go to maximum fun.org check out all the great shows there shows like uh you
know uh can i pet your dog and baby geniuses and beef and dairy network and a bunch more uh and
like we said we got other stuff at mcroy.family and including new merch and just all kinds of
just good stuff everybody ready for me to end the show yes here's the final yahoo that was
sent in by emily thanks emily it's an anonymous yahoo answers user i'm going to call scrange asks
how is it we had 45 presidents and 52 super bowls but george jefferson was elected before
super bowl conspiracy my name is justin mcroy don griffin mcroy he's been my brother my brother
me gets your dad's square on the lips
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported if you're looking for a new
comedy podcast why not try the beef and dairy network it won best comedy at the british podcast
awards in 2017 and 2018 also i love there were no horses in this country until the mid to late
60s specialist bovine arse vet both of his eyes are squid's eyes yogurt buffet she was married
to a bacon farmer who saved her life farm raised snow leopard
show download it today that's the beef and dairy network podcast from maximum fun.org
also maybe start at episode one or weirdly episode 36 which for some
reason requires no knowledge of the rest of the show