The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, welcome to my brother, my brother-mean-advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I'm your mentalist brother Travis McElroy.
And I'm Bliss Delight, an intergalactic being of all-encompassing love and light.
Guys, it's good to be back in the studio after traveling through the Ethersphere,
which is a whole thing that you guys haven't even gotten to yet.
This is the second Metamorphoses, if I remember correctly.
Yeah, you know, I came back, I took a sabbatical from being Bliss Delight,
and back then I was just sort of a ball of energy which was sort of launched into space,
hadn't even, I hadn't even hit the Ethersphere yet.
And guys, let me tell you, someday humanity's gonna get there, and that'll be a good day.
What inspired this turnaround, Griffin?
I saw the, I saw the queen last night, I saw-
Queen Elizabeth?
Yes, reincarnated into Carly Rae Jepsen.
Gang, three words, shades of Liza.
Shades of Liza?
There was, there were glimpses of Liza.
God rest her soul, reincarnated into Carly Rae Jepsen.
Okay, that's two women who are not passed away that she's reincarnated as.
She's a lot of women.
She's a future reincarnation of the undeceased Liza Minnelli.
She's every woman.
You know, actually I was at that concert too.
You were not?
I was, it was okay.
I mean, one time I saw Styx in concert, and let me tell you guys, they can put on a show.
See Travis, I'm impervious, I'm impervious to these jests.
No, I said she was good.
Bliss Delight does not recognize haters.
I'm not hating, she was fine, she was good.
Once you become an all-encompassing-
I can really see what she was going for.
Once you become an all-encompassing being of intergalactic love,
it's just like the only emotion that really, emotion, that matters to you at that point.
Once you've sailed through the cosmos-
Guys, I went to Earth Junior, the other Earth that supports-
That's only kids programming.
It supports human-like life.
I have to say, I love Earth Junior, but I'm really into Earth at night
when they start showing old Earths.
And then there's Earth games and sports, which is just like global guts.
I went to Earth Junior just to check out their pop star scene.
Not a lot, there's not a lot going on there in that department.
Interesting planet though, they speak through taste.
What?
That's so different.
Yeah, they have a spray nozzle on their palm.
And then if they want to talk to somebody, that person has to open their mouth
and they spray their flavor into the mouth.
You know, Earth Junior would leave me to believe that they're just the next step.
After Earth comes Earth Junior.
So you're saying we're one step removed from spraying taste for talking.
It's actually a really effective way of getting the job done.
Unfortunately, it's not an effective mode of transmitting pop music.
If there was a Carly Rae Jepsen Earth Juniorite human,
but she would just spray her music into your mouth directly,
fuck, that would be great, actually.
Do you think that we would just coin them as like Tumans?
Yes, absolutely.
I was at that concert too, I wanted to tell you.
I saw Justin there.
I was there, I really liked the music.
Wasn't as crazy about the decor.
My Bloomin' Onion was a little bit substandard.
But my steak was excellently prepared and the $5.99 added skewer of grilled shrimp
was worth all 599 pennies that I paid for it.
How were the rules, Justin?
Well, there weren't any actually there at the concert.
It was just right.
That sounds nice.
I thought it was weird when they had to pivot
and take the concert out of the Austin City Limits music hall
where it was supposed to take place.
And then halfway through the show, she was like,
okay, come with me.
And then we walked the whole crowd and her leading it like a big parade
to the Outback Steakhouse that doesn't exist in Austin.
Yeah, very Andy Kaufman inspired.
They only had Austin City Limits reserved till 8 p.m.
And then it was being taken over by the White Stripes, I think.
Well, the nice thing is if you're already at the Austin City Limits,
you're pretty close to Outback
because they have to put it legally just outside the bounds of the city.
They gotta keep it weird.
Gotta keep it weird.
You know, every my brother and me is somebody,
my brother, my brother, first, my brother, my brother, me.
And I really hope that this is somebody's.
I hope it's Carly Rae Jepsen's first one.
She'll be like, fuck yeah, podcast all about me.
Awesome.
I wish, ZRJ, I wish.
But instead, what we do is we take questions from listeners
and we put them, did she do any covers?
No.
God, what?
God.
Curious if she did covers.
No, she did emotion front to back.
But wouldn't you like to hear her do Purple Rain?
No, I wanna hear her do fucking emotion.
You fucking tell me if ZRJ walked out and was just like,
I'd like to do one that's really close to my heart
and saying fucking Purple Rain,
you wouldn't lose your goddamn mind.
It'd be pretty good.
You know what else would make me totally psyched,
totally just crazy for this?
Would be any other song off emotion.
Okay, two questions, super quick.
Was there an opener?
Yeah, there were two.
Oh, anybody good?
Prince.
There was Carly, and then also Carly Spray Jepsen,
who was the Earth 2 version of Carly Rae Jepsen.
And that was actually pretty horrifying
because our mouths don't possess like the-
Receptacles.
The sensors that are required to understand spray talk.
And so when she just like fucking fully,
you know, Nickelodeon Teen Choice Award,
like blasted us with Gak,
like none of us knew how to accept that.
Was it like a Gallagher show?
A lot of people left and it was a shame.
Just like a Gallagher show.
Yeah, but they missed a good Carly Rae Jepsen concert
is the only bad thing.
It seemed like you had pretty good seats from the photos.
Yeah, well, it's stands.
They were stands, not seats.
They were stands?
We had seats and we were like,
and I said, fuck this,
and they let me exchange the ticket
to be in the dance zone and got it.
Where in the concert did she drop Call Me Maybe?
Close to the end.
It was it?
Yeah.
I've been to the place that loses its mind?
Yeah, everybody went crazy.
But I mean, she closed with,
I really, really, really, really, really, really like you.
And I went, I mean, do you want me?
Hey gang, hey gang, can I talk to you for a second?
If you think for like a second
that even an ounce of this is ironic,
put yourself in a toilet and then flush it
like in the Harry Potter movies.
We are never ironic on this show.
Very rarely.
Yeah, we occasionally are,
but I work really hard to eschew irony.
Like if we talk about Meet the Deedles,
it's because it's a fucking dope movie everybody should watch.
I do want to say-
Sincere irony, that's what our brand is.
Sincere irony.
I do want to say since living in Austin,
like the entire five years I've lived here,
I've run into maybe like two people who were like,
hey, I listen to the show.
And that's really, really neat.
Last night at the Carly Rae Jepsen concert,
I ran into maybe nine people who were like,
great job, Griffin, you're here for the big night.
And I love that all of that,
like this relationship building took place at CRJ.
It was meant to be.
Of course it did.
It's a better sampling of people.
Yeah.
It's a better class of human.
Can I tell you guys my favorite fan spotting moment
I've had since we started the show?
And it happened very, very recently
when Bradbury was in town,
he and I were walking into this wizard themed shop
here in Los Angeles called Whimsic Alley.
It's amazing.
But I was talking to Bradbury
and this group of people turned around and were like, Travis?
And I was like, yeah.
And they're like, we're big fans of my brother.
My brother and me.
And one of the guys looks at me and goes, Andrew Johnson.
And I thought he was introducing himself,
but actually he was chastising me
for not knowing who Andrew Johnson was.
And to just really drive it home,
I had, this was like the day
after we put out the Andrew Johnson episode
and I'd already forgotten.
And I just went, oh yeah.
And he went like the episode.
I was like, oh yeah, yeah.
I've already forgotten who Andrew Johnson is again.
Excellent.
Like I cannot hold Andrew Johnson.
He's like the silence from Doctor Who.
I can't hold Andrew Johnson in my mind.
I want to, we need to get into the advice
because we're going a little,
it's been, it's a little laborious.
People get it.
I love Carly Rae Jepsen and the two of you.
We're also there.
You were there.
But I want to mention this Facebook post that I saw
right before we started recording from Rick Steves,
the travel author and travel video man.
Justin, you know Rick Steves, right?
From Rick, I don't know.
Rick Steves Europe.
You know Rick Steves.
He's an amazing travel man.
He has one of my favorite NPR shows about traveling.
He's a beautiful old soul and he travels
and he does TV shows about it.
And he did a Facebook post
and there's a picture in the Facebook post
and it's this old, beautiful soul man.
And he's holding a wine glass
and he's sitting at a piano
and there's some Chopin sheet music at the piano.
But wait a minute, that's not wine in that wine glass.
It's about 30 gigantic weed nuggets
and he's holding one in his hand
and he's grinning like,
next stop, Rick Steves is going to take you
to the fucking Blaze Zone.
And he has a really impassioned post about,
I'm Rick Steves and if I want to get blazed
because I just went on a trip with my whole family
to the fucking black forests of Germany
to check out their hostels
and it was a stressful trip
and now I want to come home and get fucking blazed
in my house, that's my fucking right.
I'm Rick Steves.
That's a good point.
He's got every right to go get blazed.
Oh, now look at the picture.
It's fucking dope.
Isn't that the best picture I've ever seen?
All right, let's do the show.
That's good.
Oh, you know what sets it off
is the fucking book of Chopin.
He's just sat down to play a little.
And I just, I want everyone to know,
look at this picture
and then picture the two seconds
after the picture was taken,
he just pops a nug into his mouth and eats it.
Like popcorn.
I fuck, like I'm imagining,
what I would really enjoy is being there at this concert
just to listen to Rick Steves play Chopin beautifully
and then listen to it get progressively worse.
Hey, now here's another one for Chopin.
Plink, plonk, plink, plonk, plink.
What do you think?
This next one's my favorite Chopin song.
Hey now, you're an all star.
Get your game on.
Hold on, I'm trying to save this image to my heart.
So this is as you've almost certainly gathered.
People know what's up.
This is a Rick Steves fan cast.
Time to do the damn thing.
For years, I've always had the problem
of people assuming I don't know a lot
about common knowledge subjects
or how to do basic tasks like cook or small home repairs.
In fairness, it usually only comes
from people who don't know me very well.
Still, I find these assumptions insulting
and damaging to my confidence
and would like a subtle way of letting people know
that they're out of line.
Yeah, I know how to clean a cast iron skillet
is the name of that question asker.
Travis, how do you deal with this?
I'm a fairly capable human being.
Yeah, that's not...
I feel like this is gonna be leveraged against anybody.
I don't think it would be Travis.
I'm talking about people assuming.
I actually saw a Twitter exchange last night
where somebody was like,
Travis wouldn't like something about Travis
doing construction, how badly it would turn out.
And Travis talked about how he was a carpenter,
a stage carpenter for a long time,
and he knows his way around a saw.
I don't know why...
He also said that if I touched a saw,
I would have a heart attack, which-
No, no, no, he said if you touched the table saw,
you'd die.
I'd die.
I don't know why I felt compelled to tear me down.
I do my fair share of home improvement projects.
But yeah, but I don't know.
It seems like for some reason,
people assume Travis is less capable
just because back in 2010,
he thought that the weather he saw outside his window
was the same weather all over the planet.
It's amazing how much shit like that sticks with you.
What a difference six years makes, right, gang?
Yeah.
Well, I went back to school.
Here's what I've learned.
Kindergarten.
I'm gonna tell you the truth, question asker.
Here's what you need to keep in mind.
Everybody on this planet
knows so very little off the top of their head.
Like the idea that people in this day and age
know as much as we did before we had like phones
and computers to just tell us stuff whenever.
Like people used to have to hold this shit in their head
all the time and just memorize it and know it.
So when someone does have a piece of knowledge
that they know off the top of their head,
they're so proud to whip that out
and tell you how to do the thing
that you just need to let them have that precious moment
of like, I know how to clean a cast iron skillet.
I'm gonna tell you how to do it.
You just have to sit there
and let them feel special for a moment
and then go on about your day.
Fuck that, no way.
You're saying that he should just let them
run wild on them with their trivia?
Just for a second,
because everybody's got that thing
that they know how to do
that they're so proud that they know how to do it.
If they're using that knowledge
to actively make you feel small
for not knowing the thing, then fuck them.
That's garbage.
Well, it is in the delivery
because if they're like, helpful hint time,
let me like Mr. Goodbody, Mr. Roger,
share a helpful tip with you, that's great.
If they're like, let me make you feel stupid
because I know how to do this and you don't.
Have you seen those posts of like,
it's a picture of a guy with like a beard
and it's like, if you don't know how to change a tire,
like you should shave, fuck that shit.
Like, I hate that.
But the idea of like, you know what?
Most people don't know how to do most things.
Like, if you think about all the things
there are to know how to do in the world,
how many of them do you know?
A very slight percentage.
Yeah, like three.
Rick Steves can't change a tire.
Actually, that's not true.
He travels a bunch, I bet he-
I bet that fool knows how to do most things.
I bet he's road wise, but-
I bet Rick Steves knows how to do pretty much anything.
Now, you've called him Rick Steves.
I can't help but notice.
Yeah, that's when he's blazed.
That's his blaze name?
Steves, his blaze name is Rick Steves.
What's your blaze name, Justin?
Justin McElroy.
I've always, I'm always blazed.
Let me tell you my secret.
I'm always blazed.
There's gonna be a weird episode of Mabim Bam in the future
where Justin's like, hi, my name is Derek,
and I'm ready to get a lot of stuff done today.
Are you ready, advice boys?
What the fuck?
No, this is me.
Yeah.
The part of this question that's kind of tripping me up
is that the person finds the assumptions
insulting and damaging to their confidence.
Listen, you are giving your power away,
and it is completely unnecessary.
You don't have to let anybody,
people can only make you feel the way you let them
make you feel.
I think a big part of life and trying to maintain
is deciding how much you're gonna let people in
with the way that they're treating you
and how much you're gonna let that affect your mood
and your own view of yourself.
I mean, if someone assumes you don't know how to do something
and you do know how to do it
that says more about them than it does about you,
don't let that take away your own,
you know, your own confidence in yourself
because it's, I mean.
Yeah, if you can't love yourself,
how in the hell you gonna love anybody else?
Can I get an amen?
Amen, amen.
Now let the music play.
Do you guys wanna Yahoo?
Sure.
This Yahoo was sent in by Morgan Davey.
Thank you, Morgan.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Conley who asks,
jealous of other people's boats?
I don't have a boat or jet ski,
but I do enjoy kayaking and paddle boarding.
Whenever I go out to a lake with boats and jet skis,
all that I can think about the whole time
is how much I want one of those.
People I know have them.
It bothers me so much.
I am 15.
How do I get over this?
Wow.
Does anybody else feel like this?
That's a lot of babysitting jobs.
Okay, wait, wait, hold on.
To get a boat.
So that I can understand,
because he doesn't,
or question asked,
it doesn't quite say,
are we to assume that they have a kayak
or they have some sort of non-motored boat?
I think it's possible that they have a kayak.
They have a super puffy life jacket.
Okay, but what we're gonna picture
is that they're out on a said lake
in a non-motored boat
and a jet ski or motored boat goes flying past them
and they're like, man, that's better.
If I had a jet ski,
I would make little punks like this eat wake,
like 24 seven, right?
Yeah.
This is, but, and I get it,
because when you're paddling a boat
with like your human arms
and then you see like a mechanical engineering marvel
go flying past you, yeah.
It's like you are tapping into the deepest,
most primal human impulse.
It's like, ah, no more row.
No more row.
Row bad.
Motorboat, good.
It could, but it could also just be like
this 15 year old has already made up their mind
about the trajectory they want their life to take,
which is to say ocean work.
Their life, their love, their lady is the sea.
They wanna get out there
and see what's up in the deep ocean.
And they wanna get started early.
I'm fucking into that, man.
No, listen, I get it.
And I'm not saying that there's not a beautiful time
to like paddle a canoe down a river
and you're like, I get it.
This is me, this is danger.
But listen, jet skis are made for one thing
and one thing alone, fun.
Also sweet tricks and probably ocean rescue,
but mostly fun.
And surfer towing.
And surfer towing, but mostly fun.
And also maybe like dolphin petting.
I would argue that also that sweet stunts are fun too.
Yeah, but I mean it all falls under
saving people from the ocean,
petting dolphins and sick tricks all fall under fun.
And carving wake.
Where does carving wake fit in?
That's actually work, yeah.
That's a job, to carve wake in the ocean.
Because that's what makes the waves.
So it looks sweet for astronauts?
Oh fuck yeah, thanks Jeremy.
But even when you're on your jet ski,
that rocket goes flying up past you.
You're like, well now I want that.
Hell yeah, look at that sweet wake he's carving out.
Oh shit, he drew Jerry Garcia.
Fuck that's dope.
Thank you so much.
God, that's awesome.
Hold on guys, hold on.
He writes down thanks Jeremy on a piece of paper
and just like blasts it out the airlock.
That'll get to him.
As Jeremy slams his Capri Sun.
Great wake Jeremy.
I want a kid captain.
Captain kid, the kid captain sailing the ocean.
If this kid is gonna be 15 and gonna own a boat,
he needs to fully like,
I want a full blank check kind of deal
where he's wearing like a love boat style captain's hat.
I want the jacket with the buttons on them
with anchors on the buttons,
like looking very cool, very traditional,
like very stern task master,
like captain kid, the kid captain,
15 year old out there on,
I want a big boat though.
Like a 15 year old on a jet ski,
I would think like you little punk.
Well, if I see like a jet ski is just a motorbike for a while.
I love that what you're pitching
is like a sequel to Little Big League,
but it's like a kid inherits his grandpa's pirate boat
and the crew's just like,
well, we're signed on for 10 years,
so I guess we're stuck here.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Trademark, trademark, trademark.
That's a great idea.
Also, he broke his arm
and it makes him really good at sailing.
Uh-huh.
He's the fastest sailor
because of how quickly he can turn the wheel
which powers the boat.
He can yoink the anchor and run the jib so fast.
So good.
Funky kid jib.
Funky butt loving that's a fast jib.
Did he just say funky butt loving that's a fast jib?
Which one of the three of us...
Listen, time for another Bim Bam Superlative.
Everybody's favorite segment.
Which one of the three of us is most likely to own boat?
And also for bonus credit, what would we name it?
I think the answer is Justin.
Correct?
Yeah, I think, well, just because like,
I think Huntington, you could probably house a boat
like a lot easier than you could.
And Justin also strikes as the type of person
who would see boat and be like, yeah, and just get it.
I'll take a boat.
Yeah, boat, sure.
He'd go down to the local boat show
at the Big Sandy Superstore Arena.
I just don't know that I would...
Here's my fear.
I don't think I'd use the boat a lot.
No.
I feel like I would spend a lot of money housing it.
It would metaphorically collect dust in your front closet.
I would not get out there very often.
I feel like I don't think it would be a good investment.
And I hear that from a lot of boat owners that like-
Or boners as I call them.
There's an old saying that the two happiest days
in your life are the day you buy your boat
and the day your first child's born.
And then after that, you sell your boat.
I thought you said the day you buy your boat
and then the day you either sell or crash your boat.
That is actually to say that I don't think is well known enough
for me to have turned into a joke.
The joke is the two happiest days of your life
are the day you buy your boat and the day you sell your boat,
which I thought that was a well-known enough
that I could sort of twist it in my trademark skewed perspective.
So you thought it was like a boat proverb that everybody-
Yeah, a boat proverb everybody knows.
It could be you uncultured fucks just don't know it.
This is my night at the museum where they'll be like,
oh yeah, everybody knows that saying.
It's a classic.
I want to be clear here.
I did know that saying.
Thank you, Travis.
I did know it.
Well, you guys eat at Cracker Barrel more than I do, I guess.
That's true.
And I read a lot more New Yorker and Ziggy comics.
And you read a lot more of the novelty signs
that they sell at Cracker Barrel.
So many of them.
Like I would say obsessively,
like sometimes I'll be there for hours just reading the signs.
Hey, listen, two words for you guys.
Jaden Smith.
Is that the name of your boat?
Get captain the captain kid Jaden Smith running his crew.
How good would that be?
I'd be very good.
He's not so much a child anymore though.
He's kind of a big boy.
He's kind of a Jonathan lymph Nicky.
Well, he's also a bigger boy.
He actually got bone.
Haley Joel Osmond.
Absolutely.
Can you read another question?
Willow Smith.
I'd rather have Willow, frankly.
I am naming my boat Jaden Smith.
Yeah, absolutely.
Thank you.
Captain by Willow Smith.
How do I ask my roommate who I never interact with
if I can get a cat?
I don't want to get one without asking.
That'd be pretty rude.
But we're both home at the same time.
She goes and hangs in a room.
The most we say to each other is hello
and that's how our days were.
I really don't know how to casually bring up the topic
of a kitten in that small amount of time.
Any advice on how I should approach the topic?
That's from Gmail.
So you have currently a creature that lives in your house
that doesn't pay a lot of attention to you.
Yeah.
And like you walk in, they greet you and then go away.
You already own a cat.
You own a human cat.
Yeah, you have a cat.
You have a roommate cat human.
This could be a reverse Hocus Pocus situation.
Cats.
How do you mean?
You know how the human became a cat?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
In Hocus Pocus, the movie?
I went and saw the witch recently.
I was sold that it was basically a spiritual sequel
to Hocus Pocus.
No, no.
It was not?
No.
First of all, was it spookier?
No to Jimmy.
Significantly spookier, I would say.
Like on a scale of Hocus Pocus to Sabrina the Teenage Witch,
the spookiest thing I've ever seen.
Okay.
How spooky was it?
There's a part of Hocus Pocus where Kathy and Jimmy
rides around on a vacuum cleaner.
That's funny.
It is funny.
It is funny because it's kind of a modern broom.
I don't know a problem that you solve with a cat
that you don't less depressingly solve
by getting to know your roommate a little bit better.
I just feel like-
And we're all three cat owners.
Let's be clear here.
Yeah.
Yeah, I have two cats.
You have one and a half cats.
Well, no, CJ's one and a half cat.
Yeah, CJ's one and a half cats.
And then I have a border who is a cat
that has nothing to do with me or anybody.
She is renting and what she pays is turds.
I guess she pays in turds.
That's currency.
Anyway, Amelia is the cat no man has touched.
Nobody's ever touched that fucking cat.
It's the worst.
I'm not saying that this is going to work.
I'm saying you should make a go of it first with your roommate
before you buy the cat
because it works both ways.
One, you form a bond and you think like,
you know what?
I don't really need a cat right now.
I have a new sort of relationship
that I'm trying to foster
or you become close enough to them
where you can say, listen, this isn't working for me.
I need to buy a cat.
Or third option, you get to use the phrase,
we should get a cat.
We should get a cat together
and use it to help our friendship develop.
We need this.
We can combine our names
and smush them together in a portmanteau
and it'll be like our cat that we share together.
You are absolutely correct though
that you should not get a cat without asking your roommate.
Well, yeah, Travis, I think that's illegal.
You would be amazed, Griffin,
how many people I know have told me stories
about their roommate just bringing home animals
and be like, we own a dog now
or we own a cat now and be like, well, fuck.
Shit, Stephanie, I got bad news.
I completely spaced
and I totally forgot to tell you about this,
but we bought a zoo.
Yeah, we bought a zoo.
You live in a zoo now.
There's lemurs and stuff.
I think it's gonna bring me and my daughter together
because her mom, you know, kicked it.
But anyway, lemurs, zebra, it's gonna be great, Deborah.
I mean, Stephanie, fuck.
I have a good way into this conversation
because I'm assuming that's the only thing
this person's asking for
since they obviously do have a way
of like getting in contact with their roommate.
They're not in the fandom zone.
Like they can reach them.
I would say to them,
hey, a quick question.
Do you have any allergies?
And then they would answer
and you would be like, okay, cool, thank you.
Because I was thinking about getting some milk
on the way home.
And if you're really allergic to milk,
then I didn't wanna have it in the house.
It was gonna mess you up.
The milk's for a cat.
And then walk out.
Well, you went in a different way
than I would have thought.
It's a little disappointing
because I was just about to comment
on how like disquietingly good you are
at the back door conversation.
Well, mine was a joke,
but the initial thing is actually,
I think would be pretty good
because that makes you seem considerate.
Like, oh, thank you for asking about that.
That's really nice.
But it's like you're opening this conversation
where you're asking for something
by a considerate act,
which is like a really good entryway
into an awkward conversation.
Okay, here, let's try that out.
I will be the roommate
and Justin just like throw that at me, okay?
Hey, I meant to ask you,
do you have any allergies?
Cats, I'm definitely allergic to cats.
Oh God, bring a cat around me.
I flood my attic,
by which I mean I sneeze
and I get stuffy and stuff.
Can you, well, oh, no problem.
Seriously, one time I saw a video
of a cat on YouTube
and I went into anaphylactic shock.
Good news, we're getting a skunk.
Then you buy a black cat,
white stripe on the back,
paint it there.
Your roommate dies.
It's fucking foolproof.
Full proof.
What if you just left your front door open
until a cat wandered in
and then you just have to keep it?
I can't catch this darn thing.
Yeah, fucking castle doctrine.
I guess this is what he called sanctuary.
This is our cat now.
I am 90% sure
that that is what castle doctrine is.
To go to my zone.
Meow.
I want to talk about Trunk Club.
Oh, thank God.
I just did it.
It's my elephant appreciation society.
Your time.
I'm in the Trunk Club.
I've been admitted.
I was sent a red letter
with a golden triangle on the front
and inside it just said,
you're in, here's the shirt.
And now I belong to the Trunk Club.
The power I wield is mind boggling.
What's the Trunk Club, Travis?
Oh, I'm glad you asked.
Trunk Club is basically,
you know how we have lots of questions
about where people say like,
I don't know what to wear.
Imagine if you had a friend
who knew what to wear
and you could say,
here's the kinds of things I go to,
here's the kinds of clothes I like to wear
and I have no idea where to get them
or how clothes work.
And then they came back to you
and you're like,
hey, here's like a thousand options
that you'll really like.
And you do in fact like all of them.
The way it works,
after you try on the stuff in your box,
in your trunk,
then you keep the stuff that you want
and the rest of the stuff,
you put it right back in the box
and ship it back to them.
Like no problem,
no questions asked.
And then they charge you
for the stuff you keep.
Trav, what do you,
do you have any items in your,
did you get your trunk yet?
Can I tell you Justin?
Here in Los Angeles,
there is like a brick and mortar place
that I went to and like,
one, they had a pool table
and an open bar.
It was like the coolest shit.
And two, Brooke said like,
okay, what do you want?
Okay, great.
And came back with this rack of stuff
and they were all club bangers.
Like, and I got a pair of jeans.
That's the,
it's like the first time
I've ever worn jeans.
How's that butt look?
It's so good.
Like it's how jeans
are supposed to feel.
It's like the best feeling denim,
the best fit I've ever had.
Do you sleep in them?
Griffin, can I tell you something?
No joke, I could.
No, no, but don't, but don't.
They're so comfortable, Griffin.
It's like I've always thought
I was wearing jeans before,
but then like I take the pill
and I realized I've just been wearing
barbed wire pants.
I'm a big fan.
How can I get on board?
You can go to trunkclub.com slash my brother
and you'll get set up with like
your account and the recommendations
and everything.
But the personal stylist,
like I was talking about,
who like is a real person
that will like really help you.
It's not like it's an AI thing
where you type in pants
and it's just like, yes, pants here.
Like it's a real ass person
that will help you.
It's not a subscription service.
You only pay for the clothes that you want.
No hidden charges, just great clothes.
They'll style you for free
plus free shipping both ways.
You only pay for the clothes you keep.
trunkclub.com slash my brother.
And listen, if you're on the fence
about any items,
just tweet us a picture.
No, we'll give you like a thumbs up
or thumbs down.
We're not styled.
We are absolutely not styled.
I turn to us with these questions.
Travis is now he's in the club.
I know how pants are supposed to fit.
I want to tell you all about
bowl and branch.
It's B-O-L-L and branch.
One important thing you can do
to help ensure having a good day.
That's getting the right amount of sleep.
The night before I have been sleeping recently
a lot better thanks to bowl and branch sheets
that I have been using obsessively.
If it's time to wash these
usually I'll like circulate.
You know, you wash one
and then you put on the other one
the clean ones that you have in the closet.
I wash them and my bed just sits naked
until those sheets are done
because that's all I want to sleep on.
They're some of the most comfortable sheets
I've ever slept on
and they're really nicely priced.
You're paying for quality sheets
not department store overhead.
So you get really luxurious sheets.
Luxurious, they're luxurious sheets
for a couple hundred bucks.
Go to online to bowl.
That's B-O-L-L and branch.com
and they'll let you try them risk-free for 30 nights.
There's no way you're going to want to send them back.
If you go to bowlandbranch.com today
you get 20% off your entire order
for sheets, towels, duvet covers, blankets
everything plus free shipping.
Band-Aids, bandages.
No, they don't have any of those things.
Survival axes.
Lasagna.
You're going to use the promo code
mybrother all one word.
Go to bowlandbranch.com today
for 20% off your entire order.
Just use the promo code mybrother.
I want to apologize to bowl and branch
for laughing through a lot of that message.
It's not because I find the idea of high quality sheets
and duvet covers sent to your door particularly funny.
It's because I read ahead to this next message.
If you want to get a message on the show
for a friend or a small business
go to maximumfun.org.jumbotron
and we'll get you set up.
But this message is for Eric
and it's from Big Daddy Hoffman.
And the entirety of the message is
what is dickshoulders.biz?
And I was laughing because I clicked through to it.
Have you guys visited?
Yes, I have.
I'm visiting it.
I'm there.
This is the best website in the world.
Dickshoulders.biz is maybe the best website.
What is dickshoulders.biz?
That's the whole message for Eric from Big Daddy Hoffman.
And now you all have to live with this.
This message is for Sarah.
Fuck you.
From Tim.
Dear Sarah, happy anniversary.
These last two years have been amazing
and I feel closer to you and love you more than ever.
I'm incredibly excited to spend the rest of my life with you.
Love, Tim.
P.S. I know our anniversary is October 5th,
which is exactly why I had our brothers
read this on February 22nd.
I could not have fucked it up worse.
We couldn't have fucked it up worse.
Oofa doofa.
Yeah, we almost got it.
This is another one of those wonderful messages
that's almost like the equinox.
Like we almost split the uprights between the dates
across two different years.
Do you think every episode Tim would see it again
and go like, honey, just listen.
I think you'll...
Oh, no, no, fuck, nope.
Nevermind.
And then it got enough months away
where he was like, oh, I hope it's not now.
It's gonna be worse than this.
Now it's gonna be weird.
But hey, happy anniversary, you two.
You guys, I'm so excited to introduce to you
my new baby, Getting Curious with Jonathan Van Ness.
This is gonna be a really fun look
at things that I find curious,
whether it's a menstrual cup,
it might be the Romanov family,
it might be fracking, it could be Carly Fiorina.
I don't even know.
Who knows?
It's gonna be whatever I think is interesting.
I can't wait to bring it to you guys.
We're gonna be bringing in content experts.
I'm gonna be learning the things.
It's only gonna take about 30 minutes
for you to expand your baby brains with me
and have a super fun time.
So I can't wait to see you
on our first episode of Getting Curious.
Hey, it's time for a Yahoo.
I don't...
Okay, fine.
Everybody's doing Yahoo's now.
I don't feel like it's like...
It doesn't feel as special to me anymore.
Yeah, but their Yahoo's are like,
I put Piscetti up my butt
and I'm a penguin.
Like, fakey fake bullshit.
I'm not into that.
I'm into the real shit.
Real shit slung to us by heroes like Level 9000,
Yajur, Drew, Drew Davenport.
Thank you, Drew.
Hashtag real shit.
It's by Jamie who asks...
I put Piscetti up my butt.
That's what it said.
Is Mark Hamill going to be able to do lightsaber fights
in the next two movies of the Star Wars?
I have just realized and looked on Wikipedia.
He is 64 years old.
Plus, I am thinking he will fight like an old man,
like Obi-Wan Kenobi in Episode 4, A New Hope.
Is Mark Hamill going to be too old to do the fights?
No.
Okay, first things first.
Mark Hamill's 64 years old?
Dude, he looks fucking great.
Yeah, he looks really good.
Looks really good.
But does he look good enough?
That beard is working for him.
But can he flip and shit?
You know what I mean?
But he did it with Yoda and he was like 875.
We're gonna have a CGI Mark Hamill.
Oh my fuck, how awesome is that?
Or just put him in a mech suit?
Is that a thing that happens in Star Wars?
I feel kind of bad for Mark Hamill
when he found out that it was like,
uh, we're doing this again, huh?
Can't get back in it.
Because like, I bet Mark Hamill was like,
if that is coming up,
you know that you like have to start getting carved.
Like you have to start getting fit.
How baller would that be?
Start of episode like eight,
he just like pulls back his throat
and he's fucking ripped.
Yeah, he's as jacked as Mark Hamill was
in the original trilogy.
No, more so.
And it's just like, we haven't seen Luke in 20 years.
It's just because he's been getting diesel.
No, I'm making a joke at your two expense.
Because I don't think there is a part
in the original Star Wars where he ripped off his shirt
and he had like a 13, a glistening 13 pack.
Not in the original edit.
In the fucking George Lucas wacky CGI special edition.
It was like, oh my God.
We take you live to Dagobah
where I just found this image of Luke
carrying Yoda on his back.
And I gotta say, boys,
those fish lifters are looking mighty tempted.
Yeah, all right.
That's fair, that's fair, that's fair.
Deez!
Rick Deez!
Look at Rick Deez!
Rick Deez.
Rick Deez is the wee name.
Get me Rick Deez.
That's taken.
Yeah, you know what?
This picture just made me realize
there was somebody whose face was right at Mark Hamill's butt
with their hand up Yoda.
Oh my God, you're right!
You're right!
If Yoda is on his back,
there's somebody with his hand basically up Mark Hamill's ass.
Yeah.
Oh, that's very unpleasant.
That's hugely unpleasant.
Let's just call it like it is.
That fight with Sir Alec Guinness as Obi-Wan Kenobi
in episode four is bullshit.
It is two old men just touching their dicks together, basically.
It is the worst, most boring fight ever.
And then that's why I was so psyched in the new trilogy
when they got crazy with the flips and stuff.
They had the horn-headed man that had the two lightsabers
and it got crazy up in there with the flips and stuff.
That's what I want.
I don't want two old men having a cane fight.
I want to see some fucking action, some dynamic action.
Some Diego Montoya shit.
But you don't want to see grumpy old men in space.
Right.
But here's the thing.
In this day and age, famous person...
Yeah, that would be great.
I just need to say real quick.
I know that it's unlikely considering.
But if we could get and stack back for grumpy old men in space.
CGI.
Just thinking about all the factors.
It's difficult.
It'd be a big get.
I mean, it'd be a big get.
But I would just really like to see that film.
If we could see that film.
Everyone, I think, in this day and age knows that
like a celebrity like 64 is like normal person 30.
Like I just saw...
Okay, saw Deadpool, right?
Ryan Reynolds.
Totally ripped.
71 years old.
Think about the fact that like he looked exactly the same as he did
in Two Guys a Girl on a Pizza Place.
And that was fucking like 45 years ago.
Yeah.
And he still looks that he has not aged a moment.
And it's like, okay, Mark Hamill might be 64,
but I bet he still looks better than me.
32 year old Travis McElroy.
Two Guys a Girl on a Pizza Place was like pre 9-11.
And that motherfucker looks the same.
It looks exactly the fucking same.
Rob Lowe looks actually has aged backwards.
Rob Lowe is like Dorian Graying all over the place.
Will Smith looks great.
This is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Will Smith's like his face is like a reverse cut in a tree
and have to count his rings.
You cannot tell the age of anything by Will Smith's face.
Like try cutting it in half.
You can't.
Try cutting his face in half and counting the rings.
There's no rings.
Recently, I've been invited to two, quote, passion parties.
If you're unaware, this is a thing where women gather around
and examine paraphernalia of the secular variety.
It's where they watch-
Wait, no, no.
Not secular.
It's where they watch Tyler Perry's The Passion TV special.
By my female identifying family members and their co-workers.
And it was just as awkward as I had envisioned it.
Oh, you went?
Mistake.
You said you had been invited, but then you went.
That's a whole other kettle of fish.
That's a horse of a different color.
My question to you all is this.
Despite the popularity of such events,
these rituals normal for relatives to be participating in?
No.
Personally, I consider myself a fairly well-adjusted individual
that has no issue having these conversations with my close friends.
Yet I'm immensely uncomfortable discussing my intimate life
with my family in particular.
And due to my research into this,
I'm a bit concerned that I'm the weird one.
And that's from Much Love Moby.
Stand in your truth, stand in your bliss.
Like chase your bliss.
Whatever feels right, go for it.
I don't think there's anything wrong with these parties.
And the family thing wears me out a little bit.
Like not the friend thing.
Like going to one of these parties is like whatever.
Could be a real hootenanny.
I don't really understand the-
I think the point of it is the awkwardness, right?
Because it's not like you're going to be doing some like
peer-reviewed research on different Bilbo's.
Like I think you can get on Extreme Restraints
and just look at the critical consensus on the Bilbo's
and their special features.
I don't know how much info gathering is happening at these parties.
But then I think about if I was in a room with my two brothers
and we were examining Bilbo's.
And God forbid my dad was there.
Oh no.
And we were scoping some Bo's, then I would probably be
hugely bummed out by that.
But like if someone were to invite me, I would be like,
oh man, that sounds super fun if that's your thing.
It's like if someone invited me to any event
that I don't particularly enjoy, I wouldn't go to it.
You know?
If somebody was like, come watch like soccer.
I'd be like, no thanks.
We try on this show to-
And it's something that we weren't great at when we started
and I think we all-
One might say that we were fucking terrible at it.
We were fucking terrible at it.
We try on this show to be as like open-minded
and open-hearted as possible.
And we try, like we work really, really hard at it.
But there is a part of that where at some point
you do run into a wall within yourself
where you say like, okay, this is my personal limit.
And that's not a failing.
But if someone says to me, Justin,
do you want to go look at plastic dicks with your Aunt Dana?
The answer is no, I don't.
I don't want to do that.
And I'm like allowed to say no.
I don't like spicy food
and I don't like looking at plastic dicks with my Aunt Dana.
Like those are two things I just know about myself.
Aunt Patty, that might be a hoot,
but I still am going to politely decline.
No, I don't want to look at plastic dicks with you,
especially not if there's going to be spicy food.
Please let me know what sort of canapes you're planning on.
Those are just two things I know I don't like.
Flavorful spicy, that's fine.
But just heat for heat's sake and also plastic dicks.
And big metal cocks, yeah, that's fine too.
Definitely.
We're going to have some-
I don't mind that.
I have a problem with plastic
because it's bad for the environment.
Do you know how long it takes for a plastic dick to break down
if you like bury it in a landfill or something?
You can't recycle plastic dicks for anything,
but big metal dicks, you could turn that into a park bench.
You could turn that into, I think, shopping bags.
I haven't read the literature,
but I know that it's a thing you could do.
And also please don't make the food too spicy.
I'll be there.
How long it takes for a plastic dick to break down
if you bury it in an anus,
because listen, I'm in a pretty bad way over here.
And if you could give me some sort of timeline.
But a metal dick, a big metal hog.
You could take like a hundred of those
and make the Iron Throne from Game of Thrones,
except crazier and way more hilarious.
That sounds awesome.
I want that.
What if I, what if every,
do you guys think if I started recording the podcast
in the Guyron Throne, which is what I'd call it.
Not the iron bone.
Fuck.
The Guyron bone?
No, we're getting too silly.
That's too much.
Would you be able to tell the difference?
Just sort of in my demeanor and my attitude.
Yes.
I think that you would naturally take on
a certain gravitas that you don't get
in just like an office chair.
Okay.
Justin's just linked to another image
and I'm assuming it exists and it does.
And wow, this is really good.
Well, hold on.
What we're looking at here is the crown.
The exact thing that I've described.
And, but it's sitting on it sort of lazily.
Yeah.
As if to say killed him.
Is a giant hog.
Anyway, thanks for that, Justin.
We've got to get a visual component of this show.
We've got, we've got, we've got to have some sort of.
Now imagine instead of Yoda on Lou's back.
It's a dick.
Listen, we haven't been closed-minded in this, right?
Like I think, I think shit like this
could be really empowering and fun.
But what I'm saying is like,
like you shouldn't feel obligated to go
because you don't want to seem closed-minded
for not wanting to go.
This idea that you're the weird one
because you don't feel comfortable doing it.
Like that don't, don't, that's like the worst
possible thing you could do.
Like you're actually in a, in like, in a broader sense.
And I, and I know that you're, you know,
I can tell from your question that you're trying
really hard to, to be sort of like progressive
and open-minded sexually.
And I'm really into that.
But part of that, like the biggest part of that
from where I sit is the lack of judgment.
And when you say like, am I the weird one?
You're judging yourself.
Like, because you just have a preference.
Like you have a limit.
You have a thing that you don't want.
That's completely like, that is 100% within your right.
And by saying that, that you're weird,
like you're, you're putting that judgment on yourself.
If you're not gonna apply it to other people,
you shouldn't apply it to you either.
It's just not your thing.
That's the thing you gotta know.
You gotta know yourself.
It's weird. Know what you're into,
know what your deal is, and then follow that.
Yep.
That's where I'm at.
I feel like this has been a weirdly,
you guys feel like this has been like an unusually helpful,
like I'm feeling very, very like I'm really,
I think we've really gotten help from people.
Well, let's take five minutes just as a palette cleanser
and knock out this Yahoo real quick.
Hell yeah.
From Yahoo, it was, it was sent in
by game recognized game, Rachel Rosen.
Thank you, Rachel.
It's by Yahoo Answers user, Camille, who asks,
any good nicknames to call drumming?
Hey, hey, I need help finding something cool
and preferably original to call drumming for my bios for X.
What?
Like for their X.
I don't know.
Something original called drumming for my bios.
Skin pounder, tub banger, stick thrower slash crosser.
Ya feel?
All of those could be names of dildos.
Stick skin pounder, yes.
Tub banger, absolutely.
Stick thrower slash crosser.
The least of the three, but yes, still good.
Ya feel?
Oh, I feel.
Anything helps.
So just leave anything you've been called,
heard or made up, please.
Thank you.
So we're supposed to believe that we exist in a world
in which just saying drumming isn't cool?
Right.
You need something sexy.
You know, like they call guitar players like shredders
or master splinters.
They call bassists like strang-slippers
and then they call singers throat pusher.
Throat, throat, throat, throat notes.
What if, what if, what if you were just like beat punisher?
That sounds a little extreme for me
because like what if they're just like a,
you know, sort of a pop rock sort of outfit.
Nice.
Symbol tickler.
That's not bad.
Symbol tickler, that's pretty good.
I like that.
But I feel like pianists have like tickler like on lock.
Like nobody else can be a tickler.
They are the ticklers.
Master of beats.
That's a little wordy, I think.
I tend to lean towards the grandiose because I believe
and you know, I know that my musical feelings are strong
and some people don't feel this strong,
but I believe that the drummer is the heartbeat of the band.
I know.
I feel like the drummer sets the time.
Yeah, and I feel like that's important.
I don't know much about music,
but the little bit I do know, I feel very strongly about.
I am Spartacus.
I led you here.
Spartacus is the name of my favorite drummer
from the film That Thing You Do.
What about Bop Bop Boys?
One more time.
I like it.
Can we just call them?
And if you're a woman playing, Gone Girls.
I like that too.
Except it sounds a little bit like Gone Girl.
That's a fucking great pun that I'd like cooked up,
but that's like a terrifying thing that you wouldn't want to be.
I'm looking forward to you identifying other puns as they come up.
But what I'm saying is like,
I don't know that anyone wants to be identified as a Gone Girl.
Taplads.
Taplads is good too.
Beat machines.
No, drum machines.
Okay, no, fucking stop and think about it.
Please think, drum machine is a thing.
Oh, well, here's the thing, Griffin.
You can think all you want to,
but the one thing I know about music,
it's not about thinking, it's about feeling, damn it.
Especially the drums, which is all about,
have you fucking seen Whiplash?
It's not about thinking.
You should just be a whiplash.
How about we're all just whiplashes from now on?
What about Conker Kings?
Justin's the best at this.
What about Cuban Pete?
That's not a, Travis, let's just take a backseat
and just let Justin go.
Okay, what about Bongo Bears?
Pretty good.
Give me three more.
Okay, Jim Bay Jim.
Are you, okay, nope, stop.
Okay.
Do you have a Wikipedia page open called different drums?
No, I'm just thinking of different-
The different drums that there are.
Fuck it, boys.
Snare Bears.
Back in the game, on the scoreboard.
Bass Bass.
Like a what?
Like a bitch playing drums?
It's great because it also works as bass bass.
What about cymbal tickler?
You said that.
What?
What about Jim Bay Jim?
I like that, Griffin.
I'm having an episode.
How about Rhythm Robbie?
Well, that's specific.
I think we're naming like musical garbage pail kids for the most part.
Can we call it blue manning?
Can we call the act of hitting one thing with another thing?
You could be like shaping a sword with a hammer
and we would call that blue manning.
Stomp without the trash cans.
Or stomp with the trash cans.
That would also fit.
That's not drumming.
That's just noise.
What are they doing over there?
Stomp.
Sure, I'm glad somebody's taking them to task.
Yeah.
What's up, Stomp?
Come at me.
What about drum haters?
What do we call people who hate drummers?
No, no, no.
Because if you think about it, what you're really doing as a drummer
is just like hitting drums.
Drum fighters.
What do you do in, what do you play for Coldplay?
Oh, I'm the drum fighter.
What do you mean?
Well, the drum, if you don't keep it, you know, beaten back,
will just attack and kill Chris Martin.
So I have to like constantly sort of keep it in its place.
I think it's probably the hardest to, as a drummer,
like it's the hardest instrument to convince people
that they need to be careful when they're carrying your stuff.
Yeah.
Because if they drop it, you're like, hey, hey, hey, hey.
And they say, well, you're, I mean,
you're just going to hit it later, right?
I'm just going to hit it with sticks later.
I don't see how I'm going to be in any worse, you know,
I don't see how that's any worse.
Technically, by dropping that snare down that flight of stairs,
I played the drums.
I guess I'm drumming, I guess I'm a drummer now.
I guess now I'm the Jimba Jim.
Now who's the skin pounder is what I want to know.
That's going to do it for us, folks.
Thank you so much for listening to our program.
We hope you had a lot of fun.
Super quick stuff.
McElroy shows, you can find a bunch of our shows there.
We've got, let's see, I want to try to keep these shorter.
Yeah, real fast.
We got, we got Rose Buddies is a new show
I do with my wife about The Bachelor.
I got a new video game podcast called Cool Games Inc.
I just started one called Interrobang with Travis and Tybee
where me and my friend Tybee go on rants
that take us through whining conversations.
Do one called Schmanners with my wife
where we talk about etiquette.
And we just moved trends like these over to Max Fun.
So that's very exciting.
I do a show called Sawbones with my wife.
It's a medical history show.
If you haven't listened to it,
our most recent episode was about heartburn
and like why you get heartburn.
How we've tried to treat it, it was very informative.
I thought you can find that on iTunes or McElroy shows.com.
They're all there.
I want to thank John Roderick and the Long Winters
for the use of our theme song
as a departure off the album, Putting the Days to Bed.
You can find it on iTunes.
You can find it on Amazon.
You can find it anywhere where music's sold
and it's very, very good.
It's a terrific, terrific album.
And John's a good guy.
We also want to say thank you to Maximumfun.org
for hosting our show,
as well as like a ton of other shows, a lot of them ours.
Coming up, we got the Max Fun drive.
So look out for that
and go check out all the other amazing Maximumfun.org shows.
Folks, that's going to do it for us.
Thank you so much for listening to our program.
We hope you had fun.
We hope you have a very safe and happy rest of your week.
Griffin, do you have a final Yahoo for us to think about?
I sure do.
This one was sent in by Brooks Oglesby.
Thank you, Brooks.
It's by Yahoo Answers users.
Something's gone wrong.
Call him Dave.
Dave asks, did the moon exist in the 90s?
I hate the moon.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been my brother, my brother and me.
Kiss your dad.
Square the lips.
We welcome a kick-ass lady guest.
We talk about our lives, our dreams,
and the terrible decisions we've made that still haunt us.
We've had on great comedians like Aisha Tyler and Margaret Trough,
plus screenwriters, doctors, authors, you know,
anyone who's willing to be as open as we are.
It's all a lot of fun.
That's us, Lady to Lady.
Can you keep a secret?
Neither.