The McElroy brothers are not experts.
It's been a while, right?
I don't memorize this shit.
And their advice should never be followed.
Oh, Travis claims he's a sexpert.
But if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
Because my life, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, it's better with you.
Hi, everyone.
Welcome to my brother, my brother and me, an advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin Ignatius McElroy.
I'm your middle brother, Travis Jedediah McElroy.
No jokes this time, guys.
It's just me, Griffin.
Yeah, I'm so yeah.
Griffin's lackadaisical approach to his introduction mirrors, I would say, his lackadaisical approach
to his garments.
Yeah.
We did talk about it like before, before anybody packed or anything.
I went to Skeffington's.
Yeah, Justin got himself a tuxedo.
I rented a tuxedo.
I packed three different jacket, tie, and shirt combinations.
That must be fun to travel with.
No, but they're worth it, Griffin.
They're worth it.
You're worth it.
You back there.
Hey.
Yeah, my suitcase weighs 55 pounds, no lie.
Matt, poor Matt, had a flat tire on the interstate.
You owe it to Matt to dress up.
I mean, I bought this special shirt.
You didn't rent it.
But this is you guys.
I can't move my body to the- Yeah, that is true.
I can't give a sudden hug.
Okay, let's get started.
This is an advice show.
We take your questions and turn them alchemy-like into wisdom after two years of hiatus.
We have emerged like the Chilean miners back from underneath the ground to you.
And I don't want you to waste any more time in answering these questions.
So here we go.
Now wait before we start.
Okay.
In the spirit of Fancy Takes Flight, I thought that maybe we could elevate the show a little
bit because it's been a little bit puerile lately, a little bit juvenile.
So I thought it would be nice if we maybe elevated things with a little work of fort.
Yeah.
I hope you like bits.
This one is all film related, classic films.
Okay.
A group of teens- God, I wish I didn't get so competitive about
this.
But just- Hey, don't shout it out because you will probably-
Yeah, don't shout it out.
Law of large numbers.
You'll probably get it before us.
Okay.
Don't shout it out.
Also, they're not that clever.
So many of you will get it.
Hey.
Okay.
I've been working on these for three days.
A group of teens spends the day in detention.
Each of them comes from a different social group, but they end up bonding over the fact
that they all have boners.
The Breakfast Chub.
You didn't ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding.
It was clearly The Breakfast Chub.
Okay.
That's a tie.
No, I'm sorry, Justin.
You did not ring in.
Okay.
You're right.
No, you're right.
It's fine.
It's the Breakfast Chub.
It doesn't.
Couldn't matter less.
A rebellious patient at a mental institution stands up to tight-fisted nerds, Ratched,
when she tries to stop them from taking dumps.
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
One flew over the doo-doo's nest?
I'll accept it.
Yes.
Well, we also would have accepted one flew over the poo-poo's nest.
Either way works, I guess, or doesn't work.
One more.
One more?
In this classic black and white film, a reporter tries to understand a rich and powerful man's
mysterious last words, I need to take a crap.
Turns out it was the name of his sled.
I mean- I mean, I know that- I know the film you're referencing, but there's nothing-
I can't imagine.
I mean, okay.
Ding, ding, ding.
Yeah.
It's Citizen Kane, but the sled was called Rosebutt?
No.
Justin?
Sit, sit, sit.
I got nothing.
The answer we were looking for was Shitizen Kane.
Damn it!
Motherfucker!
That one- that sucks for me and you.
Yeah.
I can't believe you didn't get it.
That was right there.
Did you all know?
Shitizen.
Yeah, they- of course they knew.
There's a billion of them.
Yeah.
Now, that wasn't everybody, though.
I would say that was only about 10% of the audience, and you're all terrible, too.
Okay, now we're going to help people.
I recently got my first job.
These are all from your region, by the way, so blame yourselves.
Take a look in the mirror.
This is what you are.
I recently got my first job since the beginning of the pandemic.
It's wonderful, but I've come across a lunchtime predicament.
I'm a messy eater, and I always stain my shirts.
When I was quarantining, I would simply remove my shirt for meals.
This worked well then, but obviously I can't-
Except for the tummy stains.
Yeah.
Obviously, I can't continue this.
What should I do?
That's from running out of clean shirts.
Are you here?
Oh, why?
Yeah, I wouldn't fess up to that either.
I did think about this when we got that one in.
You want us to say this in front of people?
You want us to read this one, huh?
Okay.
Yeah, because my gut tells me, eat better.
Just eat differently.
Do a better job.
That's clearly not on the table.
Slower, perhaps?
Or at least drier food.
Eat dry food that won't stain.
You don't deserve wet food.
Wet food is for careful boys.
Meal choice is huge.
If you don't want to improve your technique, which who has the time?
Do you open up your cupboard and there's just a wall of SpaghettiOs?
You today, I believe.
Oh no, it's Wednesday, rib day.
Rib day.
Today I'm having red wine rib gravy, delicious.
And of course, soup with no spoon.
Do you know that it's, you did have the pandemic times and you could have worked, you know,
they say if you come out of this pandemic and you haven't learned to stop eating without
spilling all over yourself, what have you done?
This is your opportunity to learn to work and eat better and I think that the window
has closed.
I mean, there's also lunch smock right there, lunch raincoat.
Get a branded lunch smock available at macroemerch.com.
It says, I'm a fucking mess on it.
I'm a wreck.
I'm a disaster.
I don't know how to eat food good.
That's two hard words to say right back to food good.
I can do it very easily now, of course.
Yeah.
Cause you're focused.
You're dialed in.
With a run up to it.
Yeah.
With a little bit of practice.
Sure.
Can you have two, can you just wear two of the same shirt to work?
Post lunch, whip it off.
You got a clean one right underneath.
Oh, but you could, then you could keep the nasty shirt at your desk.
This is my lunch shirt.
Do not smell.
Oh, there you go.
Do not smell the lunch shirt.
Do not smell.
Do not smell this shirt.
Do not open the baggie with shirt in it.
You could also, if you have your own office, you could lock the door and take your shirt
off to eat.
But oh God, you gotta check that the door is locked.
It's a great conversation starter.
But then you get, here's, here's my problem with shirtless eating.
Well, hold on, sorry.
My first of 312 problems with shirtless eating is that you eat the spaghetti-o's.
You do get the wet red stuff on your tummy and then you put the shirt back on, it's still
going to get the wet red stuff on the shirt.
I've seen you have a towel, you have a lunch towel, a classic office lunch towel.
It's weird how if you, as an adult, and I've done this a few times, if you, if you take
the napkin and you stuff it into your shirt, people make fun of you.
And it's like, I'm trying to be elegant.
This is for you.
I want you to enjoy a clean shirt.
I don't have to see my dirty shirt.
You do.
Oh, what about this?
Stained cape, right, and then at lunch, flipped that bad boy around and now it's on the front.
Oh.
Yeah.
That's good.
And then, after lunch, stained cape.
Can you just, wait, can you just, save a step, turn your shirt backwards?
There you go.
After you stained the front of it.
And then when someone's like, you have a stain on the back of your shirt, I'm like, someone
must have been eating messy behind me.
Oh no.
Oh man.
Why do I sit in front of messy people all the time?
Oh, I bet it was Doug.
I would never stain my shirt, but Doug, the person who's in the job above me would.
Yeah.
Dougie Meatballs, who works in the upper cubicle.
I recently turned 21 and I am learning that every time I consume an alcoholic beverage
or engage in the devil's lettuce, I am overcome with-
Iceberg.
And I am profound and insatiable vegetable lust.
I'm talking, I take three sips of a gin and tonic and I am on the floor of my kitchen
eating whole carrots from the bag.
Okay.
No timeout real quick, for future reference question asker, vegetable lust might be confused
for something else.
Not how I would have froze it.
Yeah.
No tomato, leafy, green, or tasty plant of any kind is safe from my monstrous desire.
Why the fuck does this happen?
What do I do?
How do I mitigate this hog wild behavior with the fact that I drink with friends who are
not immediately overcome with my same veggie related needs?
That's from the veggie vagabond.
Are you here?
Hey.
You're very close.
Okay.
Hello.
You're not normally this close when we do these, but we're going to roll with it.
Are you asking us how to stop eating vegetables?
Because you've come to the right place.
Yeah.
And just to sum up, your problem is whenever I get drunk or high, I make healthy choices.
You're not.
What do I do to stop this?
You have, you have a superpower.
You don't have anything that needs fixed.
Like do you know, do you know that when you get high, you can eat loose pepperonis out
of a bag.
Have you been eating your child's leftover Halloween candy in April?
Have you heard of a Cadbury mini eggs in the freezer?
Like that's what they're there for.
You could hear your wife say, this box of Girl Scout cookies was full yesterday.
And you go, oh, Lily, the dog.
There's not a three.
You don't have a problem.
This is a great habit unless, unless your like vegetable budget is through the roof.
That's the only thing.
That's true.
You know, in this country, we don't subsidize produce as much as we should, and we don't
have the sort of fresh local, because they're not shelf stable.
We got it.
There's food deserts.
It's a whole thing.
You thought they'd keep clapping when you said food deserts, huh?
Seaspiracy.
Look it up.
No.
Read a book.
It would irritate me if I ate all my good roasting broccoli.
And then the next, the next day I wanted to eat some roasted broccoli and I didn't have
it.
I'm like, ah, hi Justin.
You got me again.
I said, hi, hi Justin ain't going to roast that broccoli.
Hi Justin is eating it right off the stock.
And now sober Justin has to order crinkle fries from Arby's because I don't have another
side dish.
This is a gift that keeps on giving.
There's no bad part of it.
I'm trying.
It's a weird twist on Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
If Dr. Jekyll is like, I got to get rid of Mr. Hyde.
He paid my taxes on time and called my mom on her birthday.
Ah, curse you Hyde.
Is there such a thing as too much fiber?
Oh yeah.
I think it probably gives away the fact that I'm not getting enough fiber that I have to
ask that.
I've never even come close to that threshold.
What if you, what if, okay.
What if they just really don't like vegetables?
Now think on it.
You get a craving, but you don't like them, but your body wants them.
Do you like vegetables?
Sorry, hold on.
This is ridiculous.
Do you like vegetables?
Yeah.
Okay.
They do like vegetables.
I mean, one time when I was on shrooms, I ate a whole pizza, uh, but that was because
it made my mouth taste like a party.
Sure, sure.
That's because it was a time pizza and it was starting to slip through the cracks of
the universe.
You get it.
Every pepperoni had Don Knot's face on it.
You understand.
That's all of it.
And the pizza was taunting me.
Okay.
Well, have you bragged enough?
May we move on?
No, I, well, here's what I can picture, right?
You're getting drunk and high with friends and you're like, oh, you know what I could
really go for?
And they're like, oh, a hamburger.
And you're like, some broccoli rabe and they're like, get the fuck out.
I can see where that might be socially uncomfortable, but like, bring it with you, bring it with
you, have it in your pocket.
Just have loose carrots in your pocket.
I cannot think of a worse thing to do to a high friend.
Then you're sitting there and you're talking to them and you just slowly sneak a little
baby carrot.
Oh yeah.
Crunch, crunch, crunch.
Yeah.
What?
And also.
Are those Cheetos?
Well, their nature is Cheetos.
And the disappointment they'll feel when they cash the bong and they're like, anybody else
holding any good green stuff?
And you're like, oh yeah.
Brutabaga.
What color is rutabaga?
I genuinely.
It's kale.
Rutabaga's gotta be red, right?
You know what's weird?
I now have a real serious craving for vegetables.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'd love to eat.
No, not, no.
No.
You got me good.
I can't get that drunk during a show.
Come on.
My girlfriend and I have been living in our apartment for about two years now.
And our upstairs neighbor is quite obviously a gamer.
Hashtag.
He has, you say, I think you have to say it before.
No, gamer hashtag.
Okay.
He's a very nice guy.
Welcomed us when we moved in and everything, but he has always been very loud when he plays
games with his friends, stomping on the ground, shouting, et cetera.
Standard gamer.
However.
Just regular old gamer stuff.
Classic gamer stuff.
However.
Textbook.
That's not the issue.
A month or two ago, we noticed he hasn't been loudly gaming anymore.
That's right.
You guessed it.
He died controller in hand, just like he always dreams.
How he would have wanted to go.
Him and Master Chief, Thelma and Louise.
The loving embrace of Fortnite.
We actually got kind of used to his noise.
It was just sort of comforting and funny to hear someone else around.
And now it just feels too quiet.
My question is, how do I approach my neighbor and ask him to go back to his noisy gaming
for our normalcy without sounding like a freak?
Just from a little too quiet, are you here?
What?
How did that happen?
You're right behind the other person that was here too.
Hello.
Okay.
Do we have some sort of promotion where if you sit in the first three rows, we answer
your...
Okay, anyway.
Maybe they had a falling out with their gaming group.
With their Fortnite squad.
Oh, you got to patch things up.
You have to patch it up rom-com style.
Oh, this game has another patch, and this time it's friendship.
Yeah.
Patching up your relationship.
You need to do sort of a parent trap, but for gamers, gamer trap, and you like lure
them into like a raid, maybe like one of the hard ones, and you're like, I need help, and
then they all do it together.
Yeah, man.
That all sounds like definitely real gamer opportunities.
Yeah, it's like gamers stuff.
You guys get it.
Sure.
I've become a books person myself.
Maybe they've become a books person.
There've been a lot of...
Listen, there've been a lot of good books lately.
Everyone's always talking about how good books are right now.
Well, it's just like book graphics keep getting better and better.
Right?
That's true.
You need to go up there and just take all their books away.
Because if they...
Oh, yeah.
And burn them.
Wait.
No.
What?
On to DVDs.
Yeah.
Is what he was going to say.
And then melt those in a fire.
No.
Damn it.
Maybe they're just waiting for a new game that's really fun, and maybe you could make
that game.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Maybe you base it on them.
And something you know about them.
Maybe you make it out of like a cardboard box that you cut some holes in, and then it
comes with a little ball, and they have to get the ball into the holes from far away
or something.
It sounds good.
Oh, the look on his face.
Oh, the delight.
Thank you.
I ran out of games.
And you can hang over his shoulder the whole time like, this is Sergeant Bloodmash.
Yes, we need you to get the enemy base.
They're in the hole number four with the blue circle around it.
Yeah.
Kill streak.
Achievement points.
Uh-oh, here comes a babe, but you got to have DLC for it.
It's the second box they have to pay $5.
Oh, yeah.
The babe box.
The babe box you get for winning the box war.
I think the three of us are the only ones who like this bit.
You don't, but you don't have a second box, so you have to make an announcement like,
we're so sorry to let down our mini fans, we do have to delay box two, the babe box.
We just want to take all the time to make the decision.
But good news, it's going to be babe box 3D when it's done.
Hey, wait a minute.
This ball is too big to fit through this hole.
They rushed this through QA, man.
This is bullshit.
This box only has three flaps.
What the fuck?
The third flap, we're finishing the fourth one.
It's art.
You wouldn't get it.
That's part of the experience.
It's supposed to be challenging.
It's weird.
Before we start Haunted Dawn Lunch, I do need Paul to bring me another White Claw.
Thank you, Paul.
Let's see this beauty.
Meet our first contestant, Justina.
Justina, what you see is in a purple outfit with some rainbow sleeves and some face paint,
which you'll find out comes by Honest.
You're purchasing the doll pictured above.
Are those two fingers holding her around the waist, or is that some sort of weird?
Oh, boy.
Oh, God.
Holy shit.
That sucks.
I didn't even notice that.
It looks like E.T.'s trying to make a few bucks.
It sucks.
Meet Justina.
Justina was in her late teens.
Hold her like this.
Do not use more than two fingers.
Holy shit.
Meet Justina.
Normally, I should leave out the ones where they have the description of their deaths,
but I have two that I do include that, because you'll see.
Meet Justina.
Justina was in her late 20s, working at a full-service laundromat.
In her off time, she was a face painter for children's birthday parties.
Not a very good one, it looks like.
She was getting high on her own supply.
She was happy, but always anxious to see what was in store for her.
Did she break something in this picture?
Is that a bulb of garlic on the bottom?
It looks like prop bread.
One day, while at work, a very strange and potent smell came on fast.
It caused her and her coworkers to go unconscious.
Around 10 minutes later, it had built up in the building, causing an explosion.
Justina likes to watch soap operas and loves Slim Jims.
That's the way it's written.
The other people who worked there didn't get dolls.
It caused an explosion.
Justina likes to watch soap operas and loves Slim Jims.
Do you?
Okay, that may seem unrelated, but trust me, you'll see.
Does she love them from an aesthetic point of view?
It doesn't look like she has the apparatus.
I eat the Slim Jims, Griffin.
How?
With my mouth.
She communicates with dowsing rods, pendulum, and balloon lights.
What?
I don't know.
Please do not adopt her if you have ill intentions, like trying to get free face paint.
Please act-
Wake up.
Do a Spider-Man to me.
Please act-
No, I said send me a suit Spider-Man.
Please ask questions before purchasing.
I don't think you have that kind of time.
Oh yeah, don't even act like she's not 12 inches tall.
I have the proof.
Also, if you need any loose sequins, I have a couple bags of them.
I am selling a doll, not an experience.
I am not responsible for any experience you may or may not have.
That's a fun way of putting that.
Please realize by adopting Justina, you are potentially inviting a spirit into your home.
They are not toys and should only be handled by adults.
Like this.
With their two glowing fingers.
That's a great 180 from like, I'm selling a doll, it's not a toy.
Light a white candle to welcome her spirit.
You will receive the doll pictured above.
Anything else is a bonus.
What?
Whoa, I don't want-
No, I see what kind of bric-a-brac you're working with.
I'm good.
I ask only adults purchase my dolls.
I don't accept cancellations or issue refunds.
I can't imagine why not.
So that is Justina.
Thanks for coming to the show, Justina.
What a pleasure it was to have you.
Happy to be here.
Hey, can I just tell you all, I don't want to over-hype it, but you're going to love
my new boy, Little Spitz.
Let's meet Little Spitz.
Oh yeah.
That's Little Spitz, baby.
Only $150?
I'm going to watch this shit go up in real time.
Little Spitz.
Hey, what's up, guys?
I'm Little Spitz, isn't I?
Hey, they're starting to have some fun over here on Metaphysical eBay, okay?
Little Spitz was a kid who wanted to be a rapper when he grew up.
No, he did not.
Yeah, he did.
He was a doll his spirit in, idiot.
He listened to all the classic rappers all the time, like Tupac and Eminem.
He wrote his own raps.
He made his own arms.
And he would hang out.
What can't Little Spitz do except clap?
He wrote his own raps and would hang out with older kids who thought he was cool because
he rapped.
We've all been there.
This ultimately got him killed as he was-
Didn't see that coming, did you?
Got him killed as he was with his group of friends and they decided to sneak out and
go to a real rap battle.
Are these three separate pictures?
All posed like to give you a full idea.
They thought it would be like 8 Mile.
That's not me editorializing, that's what it says.
While they were there on the edges of the crowd though, a car rolled up and a window
rolled down.
What are you saying?
No, keep going.
Hey y'all, an eight-year-old rap prodigy lost his life.
If you could have a little decorum.
While they were there on the edges of the crowd though, a car rolled up and a window
rolled down, a barrel of a gun came out the window, and someone from the car yelled, Joy
Road, bitches.
Joy Road?
Joy Road, bitches, and sprayed the crowd, presumably with bullets.
With Axe Body spray.
Lil Spitz was among the first hit with the bullets, not even understanding what happened.
Now he is in this vessel, looking for someone cool and laid back.
He said, that's me.
Also someone who listens to rap music, or will at least play it for him.
That's Lil Spitz.
God almighty.
This is our last item up on Metaphysical eBay, and we are branching out a little bit.
Oh.
All right.
Tell me more, I've been in the market for one of these bad boys.
Well this is a high-ranking Illuminati Freemason Cobra Ring Silver Antique Vintage Metaphysical.
Wait, how is it metaphysical?
Well, it's it because you're going to accept this ring into your life and experience wealth,
comfort, power, influence, and all the very best things in life.
Romance, love, comfort, and so much more.
You truly can't have it all.
That's why items like this exist.
What's on either side of the snake?
Well, Travis, being offered is a very rare, very powerful Freemasons ring that comes directly
from the highest ranks of the Illuminati.
Those who are the real heavy hitters, the real power holders of the Freemasons, those
who make up half of the sacred inner circle of the New World Order.
Okay.
So Trav, let me tell you.
Oh, and it's adjustable, which is nice.
That is nice.
You would think that they would have them fitted, but no.
Who has the time?
Also nice to see that they're hollow in the back.
So you can store stuff.
From the very moment you touch this piece, you'll realize you've purchased something
truly extraordinary that will forever reverberate incredible power into your life.
The aggressive power of this amazing ring has been created with forces of magic and
other worldly technology, not only to, but a few of the most powerfully connected men
on earth.
If only Little Spitz had been wearing this ring when that drive-by happened.
He would be protected.
And other world technology couldn't make it fit?
Fascinating sidebar, you may not know this, most do not, but the government of the United
States possesses a memory copying technology, a medical device of sorts.
Of sorts?
Which is held at an underground nuclear metropolis in Roswell, New Mexico, long before it became
Area 51.
Sure.
This process is parts of the brain that never dies, but rather simply shuts off when one
dies.
Yeah.
This unusual technology turns it back on like a light switch and then siphons those memories,
creating a memory archive for that particular individual.
This wipes the memories of the brain so that no matter what medical, technological, or
metaphysical advancements may arise in the future, nobody will ever be able to access
the secret information within their memories except for them.
This has been encoded within the memory archives of its Illuminati masters, the three men that
make up half of the sacred inner circle of the New World Order at the time of its creation.
Okay.
That was an interesting sidebar.
Yeah.
This goes on for literally two pages.
There are no rituals or binding spells needed once your talisman arrives.
Cool.
This is completely ready for use.
All that's needed is you accept this small magical offering into your life to keep it
with you as much as possible.
I mean, within reason.
That's how I felt when my first daughter was born too, it's nice.
You will have the know-how to anyone or anything that stands in your way of wealth and success.
No level of magic will be able to hold you back in life.
I mean, yeah.
And it's 100% guaranteed satisfaction and fast delivery.
So that's huge.
You don't need to wait for this and it's available for just $80.
Just $80, really?
That's half the price of little spits.
I mean- Imagine if you had both little spits and the Illuminati ring.
Yes.
An unkillable rap god.
Hey, we are going to go use the bathroom.
You should use the bathroom and we'll be right back with more jokes.
We love you very much.
Bye.
Hello, my friends.
I hope you're enjoying the episode.
I don't know which one they decided to run, but I bet it was one of the good ones.
Not that one.
You know, it was kind of a dud.
You probably heard a lot of people talking about it.
I'm just kidding.
They're all sevens because we're professionals.
I want to tell you for a second, I want to talk to you about Imperfect Foods.
You know, food waste is a big problem and we could all be doing a little bit more, but
what if you could do more about the food waste problem and also help yourself too, my friends?
That is what I like to call profitable altruism, which is a phrase I just invented, but I think
it's really going somewhere.
Imperfect Foods is the best route I can think of to do that.
You can also save time in your grocery shopping.
You can eat more fresh and delicious food and you're helping the planet.
It's a slam dunk.
It's a grocery delivery service that offers a whole line of sustainable groceries that
embrace the natural imperfections in food.
You know, we're all a little imperfect by definition.
We're human beings.
Don't you want that same value in your produce?
This is fresh.
It's delicious.
It's just not exactly the perfect fit for the store shelves, but it may be the perfect
fit for your home and Imperfect delivers weekly by neighborhood, which is a unique model.
It produces 25 to 75% fewer emissions.
Could this get any better for you or the planet?
I think not.
Imperfect Foods got me hooked into some really cool produce that I can't even get in my area.
Things that are not available around here and some products I haven't heard of before,
that have become absolute staples in my house.
Try the croissant toast.
Cannot recommend it enough if you want one easy slam dunk.
Right now, Imperfect Foods is offering our listeners 20% off your first four orders when
you go to ImperfectFoods.com and use promo code MYBROTHER.
Again, 20% off your first four orders.
That's up to an $80 value at ImperfectFoods.com.
Offer code when you use the promo code MYBROTHER.
And the movement at ImperfectFoods.com and use code MYBROTHER.
While you're enjoying all your Imperfect Foods, you're going to be looking for some new hobbies.
You have so much free time here.
I don't go to the grocery store anymore.
Why not try picking up a new language?
I have been learning Japanese recently because someday I'd like to go to Tokyo Disneyland.
There's other reasons, obviously, but I'm sorry.
I am who I am.
Babbel has 15-minute lessons that make it the perfect way to learn a new language on
the go.
With Babbel, you can choose from 14 different languages, Spanish, French, Italian, German,
plus they have this speech recognition technology.
It makes it easier to improve your pronunciation.
It's a really, really fun, easy, accessible, effective way of learning a new language.
Right now, save up to 60% off your subscription when you go to babbel.com slash my brother.
That's B-A-B-B-E-L.com slash my brother for up to 60% off your subscription.
Babbel, language for life.
Quick bit of housekeeping.
Thanks, by the way.
Thanks, obviously.
Thank you for listening.
Thanks to everybody who joined and upgraded during the Max Fun Drive.
Just a reminder, we are in the midst of the Fancy Takes Flight Tour to celebrate 20 Rendez
Vu.
Tickets for all the shows are on sale now at bit.ly forward slash McElroy Tours, M-C-E-L-R-O-Y
Tours.
There's a virtual Adventure Zone next week on May 20th at 9pm ET.
The game is Dread.
It's going to be wild.
Tickets are 10 bucks and the VOD, that's video on demand, is available for two weeks
after the show.
You want to see us live, in person, well, then you're going to head out to Boston on
June 17th to see Taz.
We're also in Boston June 18th with MBMBAM.
And then on the 19th, we are in Mashantucket at the Foxwoods Casino June 19th with my brother.
My brother and me.
We're also coming to Salt Lake, Portland, San Diego, Washington, Detroit, Cincinnati.
Now, mask and proof of full vaccination or negative COVID test within 72 hours of event
start are required.
Hey, our dad also has a book coming out this week or now.
I mean, it's out on Tuesday, May 10th.
So if you would like to have a great children's book to share with a kid in your life or just
by yourself, you just want to enjoy it.
It's called Goldie's Guide to Grandchilding and it is available in bookstores.
We're going to be doing some appearances with dad throughout this great nation of ours.
Go to Linktree slash Goldie's Guide.
That's L-I-N-K-T-R dot E-E slash G-O-L-D-I-E-S guide to check in on that.
Oh, this is fun.
I don't want to spoil the surprise, but we are in a podcast with Batman.
It's us and Batman fighting crime together.
It's called Batman Unburied.
It's a new podcast that drops new episodes Tuesday and it's exclusively for free on Spotify.
It's made by Spotify, Warner Brothers and D.C. and is a thrilling take on the Caped
Crusader.
And we are in there with him, fighting alongside of him, basically.
We have new merch too.
You can check it all out at McElroy Merch dot com.
And 10 percent of all merch proceeds this month are going to go to Naral.
That is a group that fights for access to abortion care, birth control, paid parental
leave and protections from pregnancy discrimination.
That's all at McElroy Merch dot com.
And do I have to do a celebrity impression now?
OK, let's see if you can guess this one.
I've been working on it.
What?
What's the deal with hummus?
It's just mushed up beans and spices.
Thank you so much to everyone who participated in this year's Max Fun Drive.
If you're a member who wants to purchase additional patches, our annual shop is now
live.
The proceeds for this year's sale will be going to Trans Lifeline.
Anytime is a good time to donate to Trans Lifeline, but this year it feels particularly
important.
Trans Lifeline is a non-profit for the trans community by the trans community.
We're grateful that with your support, we'll be able to help Trans Lifeline connect trans
folks to the support and resources they need to survive and thrive.
The sale will run until Friday, May 20th.
Folks at the $10 monthly level and above will have access to all of the patches from the
drive.
We also have a special network patch starring Nutsy that all members can purchase.
For more information on Trans Lifeline, visit translifeline.org.
And for more information on the patches, head to maximumfun.org slash patch sale.
Hey, this is Alden Ford and Mujan Zofagari, and we are here with all the other creators
of Mission to Zix.
Hello.
Hey.
You're not going to say our names too?
No, no.
It's a short promo.
Yeah.
Now with the end of our fifth and final season just a few weeks away, we want to say thank
you to Maximum Fun and to every single one of you who has listened to and supported Mission
to Zix.
Thank you.
And if you haven't checked it out, well, Mission to Zix is an improvised space opera with blockbuster
quality sound design, a score performed by an actual 60-piece orchestra, and hilarious
guest comedians on every episode.
And as our final episodes air, now is the perfect time to jump on board.
It's Mission to Zix, Z-Y-X-X on Maximum Fun.
How can I interest you gentlemen in a wager?
Yes.
It's time to play minion quotes.
Yeah.
But this time with a twist.
So if you've never played this game, here are the rules.
I Justin McElroy am going to read to you an inspirational or hilarious quote.
That quote is attached in the memetic image that has been shared on Facebook by your aunt
and it is connected to a cartoon character.
That cartoon character will have to be guessed by my other two brothers if they guess it
correctly.
I will have to post this image, apropos of nothing, on my Facebook page.
Now what makes this more interesting tonight is we are passing it around.
We have each selected one quote so the stakes are higher than ever because all three of
us are participating in the game.
Oh, also I just realized in a second, another twist, I've been locked out of my Facebook
for the past like three weeks because of like, I don't know, because I haven't logged in
long enough and they're worried about it and I was like, oh cool, I don't ever have to
go on Facebook again.
So if I lose, I have to figure that out.
Your brand reemerges.
Yes.
Okay.
Are you ready to play minion quotes?
I'm so fucking ready.
Oh, mine.
Okay, great.
Oh, Travis is first.
I thought you said I'm first.
Travis is first.
Okay.
I'm not looking at your phone.
The quote is, I don't care how difficult 2019 has been, but the fact we woke up every day
means that God isn't finished with us, which I think is supposed to be inspirational, but
could also be horrifyingly threatening.
Yeah.
Knowing what happens in 2020, it does sound like God is threatening us from a distance.
The religious ones are tough because usually it is not who you would think of as being
a particularly religious cartoon character.
And I would argue the highest stakes ones to pick as the picker, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
I really want to get this right.
Yeah.
I live life on the edge.
Can I have a hint?
No.
Maybe just one hint?
Oh, okay.
It's a cartoon character.
Damn it.
Can I ask a question, yes or no, and you have to answer honestly?
Oh, you can ask the question and we'll see.
Is it a Looney Tune?
That's a big swash.
Tweety Bird.
I'm saying Tweety Bird.
Tweety Bird, Tweety Bird.
I'm going to say Bugs Bunny.
It's a classic.
I'm sorry.
Paul, if we could swap it, it is Moana.
I should have considered the coconut.
That was my bad.
What, you know how Moana has a close and personal relationship with the Christian deity?
You know how famously that's what the movie is about?
Okay, now wait.
Now hold on.
Now I'm mad.
She literally meets a god of a different religion.
Like she meets a god.
Correct.
A Demi-God, but still.
Well, I mean then, Te Fiti?
It's a huge part of the movie.
Yeah, and she's interacting with religious figures outside of the Christian experience.
Yeah.
Yeah, but our God's not done with her.
Our God, the one true God, Father of Abraham.
Hey, do you ever have a moment where you're like, oh, all the Southern Baptist isn't out
yet?
Oh no.
The Lamb of Judea.
Okay.
Could beat the shit out of the Rock's Mouth.
All right, Sunday, Sunday, Sunday.
Okay, this is Justin's minion quote.
Okay.
Paul, it would be easier if you just put the quote on the screen.
I can just read off of that.
Remember how when you were little, you could just rip off your diaper and run around naked
and everyone thought it was so cute and funny.
Anyway, I need bail money.
Fuck, that's funny.
God.
So I am going to, because it occurs to me that I slightly cheated.
So I am going to tell you, it is not a cartoon character.
Oh.
But it is a children's character, not a cartoon character.
Is it Moana again?
Now Bud, Bud, that's a cartoon, remember?
We just saw it.
I want to say Blippi, but I know you wouldn't do that to us.
I don't think boomers know who Blippi is and this has big boomer energy.
Is it children's?
A children's character for children's, but not a cartoon.
Family character.
Everybody can enjoy this character.
God, I've said too much.
Okay.
I'm going to shut up.
Can I ask one yes or no question?
I've already given you all the clues you need, Mr. Policeman.
Is it a human character?
Also, we referenced that Snowman movie a lot for three people who haven't seen it.
I barely seen the poster.
Is it a human character?
I mean, it's an interesting question.
That you'll answer now.
Come on, it won't be funny if nobody gets it.
Yeah, but of the people on this stage, I think I have the least appropriate tribute.
The least appropriate sacrifice is I am the only one who's had to do this.
No, it's not a human character.
Yes.
Okay.
That's tough.
Do you have a guess, Travis?
I'm going to say Paddington.
You really need?
Okay, Paddington.
Interesting.
It's not fucking Paddington.
I'm trying to think of the other deep wells that we usually draw from, and by we, I mean
boomers who put up memes on Facebook.
Think really hard.
I think you can do it.
Really?
A live action non-human that boomers would know.
Is it Kermit?
Yes!
I knew you could do it.
Now Justin, do you want to wait?
Do you want to wait until Griffin's?
No, we're going to sit right here, everyone.
I'm just going to put it on my Facebook right now, because it's not fun unless I do it right
now.
And I will then immediately comment on it.
Oh no, my Facebook's locked!
Do you want to load mine up while Justin?
Oh, you got that hair trigger.
He already had the image loaded.
Okay.
Hold on, I want to put a link to Sydney's website on here.
Yeah, I'm sure she'll love that.
Oh, he's doing it.
Okay, here is my minion quote.
Oh boy.
Hold on, devil.
Not today, or any other day.
Feeling blessed and covered under the blood of Jesus.
Like, share, and type, amen.
Wow.
Now this is your first time playing, right?
Yes.
I also, in full disclosure, I don't know where you find these, but I was looking around for
minion quotes, and I found one on the MBMBAM reddit that somebody posted on there.
So thank you for doing that hard work.
So same question, is this a cartoon character?
This is a cartoon character.
Is it a Looney Tune?
That's such, that's so- You, I gave you-
It's not a Looney- You see this, right?
It's a cartoon character.
You see this.
You're right, you should be able to get your revenge.
It is a cartoon character, it is not a Looney Tune.
I will not give you anything else.
Bart Simpson.
No.
Oh, he gave us nothing there, that was a cold, dead stare from Griffin.
Okay, Justin.
Not a Simpson character.
It's not a Ralphie.
Okay, let me hear your guesses.
Not, what?
Alvin, from Alvin and the Chipmunks.
No.
I do want the audience to keep yelling, though, because I honestly haven't-
Scooby-Doo I heard, which will be a wild- No, I haven't heard it.
Shrek, just reveal it.
It's fucking Fred Flintstone.
Now, Devril, pretty sure that the Flintstones universe is like wicked BC, like super duper
duper BC.
Back in the time when man and dinosaur lived together.
Really, Amanda?
Amanda's already commented on my Facebook page.
Don't you have work to do, Amanda?
You're getting a raise.
Anticipating our needs.
So that's MinionQuotes.
Oh, boy.
All right.
So we asked you all to send in questions that we could answer live, and we have some people
picked out.
Where's the microphone at?
I was in the bathroom during the soundcheck, so I don't actually know.
So we're going to call down two at a time- Can we get the house lights up just like 20%?
Can we go back to the part where Griffin said he was in the bathroom for both soundchecks?
Because I feel like that you didn't let it sink in.
Where is it?
It's right there.
I'm playing Where's Waldo with this microphone.
Okay.
Yes.
Hello.
Hello and welcome.
Hi.
I'm Taylor.
Hi, Taylor.
Taylor, your question- I can't believe we picked this one.
Taylor asked, who are you?
I'm just here because I bought the tickets.
So I guess we were actually, we read this backstage and we thought, I wonder how it's
going.
Yeah.
So we wanted to ask you, Taylor, what do you think so far?
And really give us the real shit.
Please be honest with us, Taylor.
Like what do you think so far?
I think it's pretty good so far.
Yeah.
Now, Taylor, I have a follow-up question.
When you say, I'm just here because I bought the tickets on accident?
No, my sibling's actually here with me.
Oh, okay.
What's your sibling's name?
Rhiannon.
Hi, Rhiannon.
Hello.
And Rhiannon knows who we are, right?
Yes.
Oh, okay.
It's a very early birthday present for them.
Oh, happy early birthday.
Okay.
Now, have you picked a favorite yet?
Oh, good question.
Well, I'm a little biased because I'm on Tumblr a lot, so I see Griffin's face a lot, so.
Oh, my God.
I will be feasting off the memory of you hesitating to remember his name for a week.
Yeah, that was decadent.
But you did pull it, Taylor, so don't feel bad.
Yay.
You did pull it.
Yeah, you did pull it.
Garf-ball.
What is it?
That's a Garfield...
Dresses Garf-ball?
Garf-ball.
That's a completely unnecessary self-own, but which of my many incredible memes that have
made it onto Tumblr?
The main one I see is, like, you holding a blank piece of paper, and people edit.
Oh, edit.
I think my favorite one is somebody saying, I'm too afraid to...
I don't know who the McElroy brothers are, and I'm too afraid to ask with your face.
Did you make that one?
Or...
Wait, no, Taylor wasn't afraid.
Yeah.
Taylor asked.
I saw that one.
I did not make it.
You did ask who we are.
Yeah.
And that's what's...
That's all that's important.
We're like brothers, and we do, like, advice.
That's the show, basically.
Yeah.
And we do, like, strong.
Skits.
We're strong.
Yeah, we're strong and capable fellows.
We're strong and we have normal digestive systems.
Those are the two things.
That's exactly what I got from everything you guys have said so far.
You're getting that.
Okay, perfect.
We eat bananas totally normal.
And...
Um, well, we, Taylor, we've embarrassed you now.
Thank you so much for being a good sport.
Thanks for coming.
I hope you're having fun.
Yeah.
Hi.
Who, who are you?
We've called so many names.
Okay.
I'm Lauren.
Hi, Lauren.
You asked us, uh, failed my driver's test today.
How could I impress the examiner next time?
Yeah.
How bad'd you fail?
I drove on the wrong side of the road.
I mean-
Whoa!
Hey, Lauren.
Very British.
Very British, Lauren.
I know the first impressive thing
you could do next time, Lauren.
For like a long time?
No.
Well, Griffin, how long do you think it needs to happen
before it's a no?
Hey, hey, Lauren, uh, can you replicate
what they said to you in exact replica?
Like tone of voice, too.
Yeah.
Um, she waited until I was done with my test
and then she was like, unfortunately,
you drove on the wrong side of the road,
which is an automatic fail.
Damn.
Whoa!
She made you keep going?
Yeah, she should have said something
when you ran over like 80 people.
When you were doing it,
when she was just like, hell yeah, fuck, let's go.
Yes, yes, this is how I do it.
Yes, go!
I'm feeling something for the first time.
This is li-
This is living.
I'm alive.
Hold my hand, Lauren.
Lauren, are you feeling this?
Um, the word that I feel like
made us select this question was,
how could I impress the examiner next time?
And I'm not sure you understand
what the examiner is looking for.
It's not America's Got Talent driving edition.
You already tried stunting,
so let's mark that one off.
Next.
Oh, super cool car.
They can't flunk you for knowing all the words
to Barenaked Ladies one week.
They can't, they legally can't flunk you
if you sing the fast part from Hook by Blues Traveler.
Yeah.
On loop.
Was that it?
Was it just driving the wrong lane that they didn't?
Cause that's an easy fix.
Is that not enough?
No, I'm saying you just don't do that next time
and you should be good.
Or were there other rules?
Cause we're real like gear heads.
Oh, you know what?
Everybody does parallel parking on their test.
Do some perpendicular parking.
Yes.
That'll blow them away.
I'm doing concentric parking.
My parallel parking actually went really well,
but that's not good enough apparently.
Yeah.
Now, Lauren, you could-
I think it sucks because like,
they shouldn't fail you cause like,
what are the odds that you'll do that again?
Yeah.
And also the fact that you did that
and they knew you'd failed and they're like,
and you still have to parallel park.
Yeah, that sucks actually.
They should've let you go home.
Did they keep writing stuff down on the paper?
Cause that's a wild part of the grift.
Yeah, did you see them?
Did you see them casually put the clipboard on the floor?
I needed that.
I won't be needing this.
No, but there are just like some random scribbles
on the paper.
So I think she was trying to like,
make me think I had some hope.
Yeah.
How long do you have to wait before you can take it again?
A week.
One week.
That is not very long.
It's been one week since I failed my test.
Drove on the wrong side of the road.
If, when you go back, you have the same tester,
spend the whole time,
anytime you're on the right side of the road,
say like, I don't know if you noticed.
Many people would choose that side of the road,
but not me.
An obvious mistake.
Clearly.
I'm not zooming into the front of the other cars.
Notice how me and the other driver pass by each other
without incident.
You're welcome.
Does that help?
I think.
You're going to do it next time.
Yeah, you got it.
We believe in Lauren, right?
Thank you.
Hey, my name is Ellie.
Hi Ellie.
Griffin, you're really putting yourself through a lot
of struggle to not burp right there.
Sorry.
Contortions.
Hello Ellie.
Hi.
How you doing?
Good.
I'm doing great.
Thank you for asking.
Yeah.
You asked, I work at a haunted cave
that is said to have 30 to 40 ghosts,
but I haven't had a ghost experience yet.
How do I trigger one?
Yeah.
I work at the Wabasha street caves in St. Paul.
Yes.
There's fans and every tour guide has had like things move.
They've seen people, they've heard bands.
Definitely.
They've heard what?
Bands.
We have big bands that play and-
Ghost bands?
Wait, big bands or big bands?
Like big names or-
Like Glenn Miller orchestra style big bands
or just like large bands?
Like Cab Calloway, like Benny Goodman and stuff.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, shut.
Wait.
Your caves are pulling Cab Calloway?
Yeah, that's a huge ghost git.
Apparently.
Can I say if I was going to have a ghost experience,
if it was totally legit,
I would also experience a Cab Calloway concert.
Yeah.
Apparently John Dillinger is also around sometimes.
Wow.
Okay.
Well, he's not busy haunting other places.
What's so dope about your caves
that makes every ghost wanna be there?
Three people were murdered there.
Well, then there should be three ghosts.
Yes.
Ellie, these other sightings
that the other tour guides have had,
are these things that they've told you in confidence
or are these things that they say
when they're giving tours of the caves?
So both, and they have pictures to prove it.
What?
Like not just orbs, like actual pictures of-
We've got a fucking scoop.
Hold on, wait.
Not just orbs.
As if someone came to me and was like,
yeah, I work at this cave.
Check out this fucking orb I saw.
I'd be like, just an orb?
Yeah.
So you're saying they have a picture
of like them in Cab Calloway.
Hey, Ellie, like if your coworkers have pictures of ghosts,
that should be all you're sort of thinking
and talking about.
Like in your life, your questions should be like,
my fucking coworkers have pictures of ghosts.
What do I do with that?
And not just fucking bullshit orbs.
Real human-shaped ghosts.
Juicy three-dimensional ghosts.
Like we have one of an old lady
walking through a table.
What?
Ellie, why are you here and not like at CNN?
I don't know.
Is this what's happening in the world
when people are like, I don't know if there are ghosts.
It's because the people who have pictures are like,
I'm not gonna do anything with these.
What am I gonna do, show these to people?
Yeah, I guess so.
I don't know.
We have not even glanced across the surface
of your question.
So you go to the caves
and you loudly announce, well, I finished all my business.
I wish there was more business to finish.
Yeah.
I wish there was somebody else with business
they had not finished on this earth
that I could assist with that particular issue.
Cause all my business is finished.
Hey, you also, you have the benefit Ellie,
of apparently there is a ghost there
who is well known for call and response songs.
You can walk into the cave and just go,
hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
There's also, there could just be a echo.
Dammit, you're right.
Oh, I could try that I guess.
Does the cave got wifi?
Yes.
Really?
Yes, we had electricity installed into it
like in the 1990s.
Wow, that was your mistake.
The ghosts wouldn't like that.
They don't like change is what we've heard, but.
Can you roll. From who?
They don't know how cool it is.
You got to get to this cave.
If the ghosts say they don't like change
is cause they don't know how cool shit is outside the cave.
Like we've got a lot of stuff going on.
I think you could roll up into the cave
and plug into cave wifi on your computer
and just turn on Netflix and just kind of wait
and be like, anybody want to watch some new drama?
Now, wait a minute, hold on.
We don't know how wifi and ghosts interact.
Maybe they're all fucking flipped out
cause they're experiencing the wifi.
Like when you switch it on
the ghost experience all of the internet at once.
A ghost in the machine if you will.
A ghost in the machine if you like.
You got to get the wifi out of there.
Yeah. Step one, Ellie,
go in there tonight under cover of darkness,
remove that wifi single-handedly,
get a bucket, scoop up that wifi and carry it out.
I don't know how wifi works.
Does that, does that help?
It helps.
It does, it does.
Yeah, I thought it helped.
Yeah, thank you so much, Ellie.
Yeah.
Thank you so much, Ellie.
Y'all look so great.
I have to say, I should have thought a long time ago
to tell people to dress nice and fun at our shows.
What were we facing?
Hey, what's up?
Hey, my name's Jake.
Hi, Jake.
Hey, Jake.
Are you sure it's not Jacob?
Cause that's what you put in the email.
It is catfish, catfish.
It is Jacob.
I was trying to be playfully short with the name.
Okay.
All right.
I think we won't tolerate here as fun.
Jacob, you were talking about a pancake eating challenge
and I want to know all about it.
Yeah, this one, we didn't know if it was fun or not,
but we did need more details, so go on.
All right.
An hour north of here is the best place on earth,
Merlin's Family Restaurant, Princeton, Minnesota.
They got a big stack.
Everyone knows that, yeah.
Yeah.
Not as hot as that cave was.
No, not.
Didn't you think you were going to get cave levels of
reactions, right?
I kind of did.
Yeah.
I got to say, if I'm going to go to one of those places,
I'm pretty intrigued by this big stack of pancakes.
How big?
Approximately five inches by 18 inches across.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
Jesus Christ.
A real chode of pancakes.
That's...
In order of pancakes is one pancake.
That's a hundred square inches of pancake.
If my math is correct.
Yes.
Well, I guess cubic.
Well, I got to run the diameter.
Hey, somebody figure that out for me.
How much pancake is there?
So what is...
Pie.
What's the pancake?
No, it's not pie.
It's pancakes.
God almighty.
So the stack being five inches, but there's four.
It's comprised of four pancakes.
Uh-huh.
Wow.
And when you eat them, when you eat them, you get...
Sure, yeah.
Yeah.
That's the way I traditionally interact with pancakes.
When you eat them, you get a shirt and your picture
on the wall of fame.
If you lose, you got to take a picture.
I'm put on the wall of shame as well.
So either way you get a picture up on the wall.
Yeah, it's pretty sick.
Is it a time challenge or just like take your time
if you can eat them at all?
It's great.
That's the trick.
You can stay for hours and fill yourself.
Oh, they don't know I know this hack.
Okay, go on.
Pancake restaurants hate this hack.
Yeah.
And when you finish it, you still have to pay for it?
No, no, actually you get it for free,
but it's like $10 anyway.
It's just pancake.
Wow.
Yeah, sure.
Any dressings on them?
Any syrups or fruit?
Butters?
One could go nuts, but I don't like syrup or butter.
Anything you add to that is just more content.
So what's your question?
My question is, so every time I go there,
I'm gotten very good at this challenge.
I'm on the wall of fame six times.
Whoa.
Fuck yeah, Jacob.
My brother and my brother and me, heroes only.
Yeah.
Heroes only here tonight.
And whether that be just to,
for the party trick of the morning
or to update to get more updated photo on the wall.
Yeah, sure.
So when they keep swapping out,
they don't add additional jakes?
No, it rotates through.
My ones from freshman year are gone.
Oh, you want them to stack it
so that you can have a flip book of you experiencing.
Exactly.
But in my training, I've found I can now eat.
Your training?
Yeah, Griffin, you don't go
and do a pancake big stack challenge cold.
You don't want Jacob to eat pancakes at home.
Come on.
Clearly Jacob loves pancakes.
He does pancake challenges.
You would deny Jacob home game pancakes?
Okay, fine.
What if the first time you ate them was at this restaurant?
Like what is this?
Where can I find these in the wild?
Hey, what's, excuse me.
My crepes are fucking so thick.
Take them back.
These are the weirdest fucking waffles I've ever had.
Your toast is flying around.
So.
My Doritos are stale and flavorless.
Sorry, Jacob, what's your question?
So now that I've trained to eat two big stacks,
this will be accomplished.
Am I good if I bring my own photo
to be presumably put above the wall of fame?
Fuck yes.
What?
Yes.
I'm glad we wasted so much time during the actual question
because the answer is yes, obviously.
Obviously you have to bring your own.
What are you thinking, boudoir?
I don't.
Champion belt, I assume.
I will say that if I had just finished two heapin' helpins.
That's 10 inches by 18 inches of pancake.
Then the last thing I'm going to want to do afterwards
is a fucking photo shoot.
This is tour manager Paul.
Right here, I put up a slide that said
this is 1,272.35 cubic inches of pancakes.
Can I say-
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Paul, Paul, I love you.
You're a dear friend.
That can't be right.
I will say, I will say, no timer.
They're not watching the bathrooms.
That's it.
Oh, what?
They let you poop.
So you can poop whenever you want.
Okay.
Jake, let me say, I just want to say,
thank you for representing what I think
is maybe human beings' most enduring quality,
which is once we've accomplished something,
say one big stack,
we must continue to challenge ourselves
even if others do not.
Yes.
You finished the big stack six times.
You went on the wall six times
and you said there has to be more in life than this.
You're going to finish two stacks and weep
because there are no more stacks to conquer.
But good news, Jake.
I'm here to tell you three stacks.
No, do two stacks and do send us a picture of that, Jake.
I got to see it.
Does that help?
Yes, it does.
The encouragement will help me join my brothers in syrup.
Thank you.
Yes.
Give me five.
Hello.
Hi, brothers.
Hi. Hi.
For a second there, I thought the mic wasn't working.
You got this.
No, I was just scared.
I'm Andy.
Say them.
Hi, Andy.
Andy, you're great.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, we got this.
Relax.
You asked-
Breathe through it.
You're as powerful as someone who just finished two big stacks.
I don't know that powerful is the adjective
I would use to describe you.
You're as sleepy as someone who just finished two big stacks.
You're ready to hibernate through the winter.
Andy asked, how do I enforce my workplace's
no touching the dinosaurs rule
while still letting people know that I'm cool
and I would also like to touch the dinosaur.
So give me a little context here, Andy.
I work at a dentist's office.
Yeah.
Yeah, just a really cool shoe store, actually.
No.
No, I work at a science attraction
where we do have real original fossil dinosaurs displayed.
Wow.
And it's very cool.
You get to be very close.
It feels you're immersed in the science.
And also the barriers are like exactly
sort of at toddler forehead height.
And that's kind of it.
And there are a lot of children and adults
who really, really want to touch the dinosaurs.
Sure.
Yeah.
I would like to touch the dinosaurs.
I would like my finger grease to destroy
a dinosaur bone over time.
Yeah.
I mean, listen.
If time and Earth couldn't do it,
what are my Dorito fingers going to do that's so bad?
Yeah.
If they can't hang, don't pull them out
if you don't want me to touch them.
So Andy, what's the problem?
Well, the problem is that I really, really
want to touch the dinosaur.
All the time.
Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy,
have you touched the dinosaurs?
Because I noticed earlier you said a science attraction
and not the name of the business because there
would be a revelation you've touched the dinosaurs.
Yeah.
No, Andy.
Andy, have you touched the dinosaurs?
Not even an accidental like, whoa.
The more we talk, the less Andy has to admit their crime.
OK, moving on.
Andy refuses to incriminate themselves.
Andy takes the fifth.
But how do you let them know it's
a normal and natural impulse in life
to want to touch the dinosaurs?
They're not perverted in any way.
I really want to be like supportive but firm, you know?
Yeah.
And as dads, I would hope he would like help.
OK, you're going to want to do a heavy sigh and then I get it.
I get it.
That is the number of times I've said
to my five-year-old who is a carbon copy of myself
when it comes to impulse control, I get it.
Hey, buddy, I get it.
I get it.
I also sometimes want to see what sound a thing makes
when I throw it at the wall.
I get it.
So on brand.
Can you, Andy, can I suggest this?
Could you have one dinosaur bone that's kind of bad?
Yeah.
And it's like a burner.
Yeah, an extra one.
We got three legs.
And listen, you want to touch the dinosaur, I get it.
Hold on, let me open my locker.
I got one back there for you that you
can touch all you want, no big deal.
Can you memorize the speech that Sam Neill gives
at the beginning of Jurassic Park
where he scares the boy very badly with a velociraptor claw
and just deliver that whenever a child wants to touch the bone?
Or really runs afoul of any kind of rule?
Excuse me, did you just drop that litter on the ground?
Let me tell you a little bit about velociraptor.
Well, that's not how the velociraptor gets you.
Here, come here.
I'm going to scratch your tummy with this.
Andy, could you sell dinosaur bone touching gloves
for $5 a pop?
Ooh.
On the side.
How?
That little private.
This would not be an official piece of merchandise.
This would be, yes, you would produce them from your jacket.
How straight is the security here?
Could you charge people to touch the bones
when no one's looking?
Probably for a little bit.
Yeah.
OK.
Maybe not all the time.
Does that help, Andy?
It does help.
Thank you.
OK.
And thank you.
Make them go away, please.
I'm so intimidated.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Yes.
Make us more.
Make them less.
Yes.
Hey, you all have been outrageously fun.
Thank you so much.
Yes, thank you all.
We have done so much stupid bullshit tonight.
And you all have been there for all of it.
And I really, really appreciate it.
Even Taylor.
And Taylor didn't know what was happening.
Yeah, even Taylor was into it.
But you all have buoyed us.
You lift me up so I can climb on mountains.
Thank you.
We want to say thank you to you.
Thank you to the beautiful Orpheum Theater.
It feels like we tricked our way into here,
which we kind of did.
Sorry you guys didn't get to see Jim Gaffigan tonight.
I know you were expecting it.
So sorry.
We want to say thank you to Paul for helping us run the show.
Thank you to Amanda.
And thank you to Rachel for helping to run the show
and doing the recordings and all of that stuff.
Thank you to our dad, Clint.
Thank you, Clint.
Buy his book.
Thank you to our families for supporting us here.
And let me see, anything else?
Thanks to Montaigne for these four theme songs.
My life is better with you.
Sidney McElroy is not with us.
Dr. Sidney McElroy is not with us.
But I really appreciate her just being her, I guess.
Now, we don't do a final Yahoo anymore, as you know.
And it's brought a really fun energy
because we get to ask you, our beloved listeners,
what celebrity impression you'd love to hear
a Griffin McElroy attempt.
OK, so on upcoming episodes, you can look forward
to Nicolas Cage and Gilbert Godfrey.
So what celebrity impression would you like to hear?
First five rows.
Oh, wait, hold on.
First five rows, so it doesn't just become.
Oh, do you have a walk-in, Griff?
A walk-in?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess.
Uh, uh, what kind of shit?
I like, I like to eat the, I like to eat the spaghetti.
That sucks shit.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I don't deserve to say my name.
It's remember, remember, remember me.
Gives your dad's square on the lips.
I'm just bringing it in, everyone.
It's better with you.
My life, ah, it's better, it's better with you.
Because it's true, ah, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, ah, it's better with you.
Maximumfun.org.
Comedy and culture.
Artists owned.
Audience supported.