The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother mean advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin big points McElroy and I'm Travis high score McElroy.
Hold on guys. I've almost got I've almost got the high score. I need to shoot like two more
space men. One second has Griffin. I did it. I want it. I want the tiger handheld game that
I've been playing because it's E3. We're at it folks. E3 is off and popping. I'm sure you saw
a lot of the big announcements later today. That tense got away from me, but you know,
video games are here to stay and I love them in a major way. Rap I'm working on about.
I love them more than I love them more than anything. All day gaming all day. I dream about
us gaming soccer video games soccer video games. What guys guys? What do you think has been the
biggest bombshell of this year's E3 that is definitely happening now and not several days
in the future and not us recording on the Wednesday before? Yeah, it's a good question
and one that made a lot of sense coming out of the of the mouth. I'm for me. I mean during
the Sony press conference crash Bandicoot's weird shorts fell down and we saw his big fuzzy balls.
Wait and that was your biggest E3 like reveal. Do you think that's my most that's my most
anticipated reveal and I gotta say Sony as they always do. They fucking followed through with
those falling down. Show me those big furry nuts. That's really delivered to. Yeah, that's
but those are not the nuts of a young being appropriate. Well aged nuts. He's been around
the block big big big beautiful nuts though. I did like when the nuts are revealed and
banjo-kazooie from the side of the stage just yelled they both in unison just yelled like nice
nice nice nuts. You know the funny thing about it is it really with the games in a new perspective
for me because the way he is spinning and gesticulating and jumping and running that can't
have provided ball comfort. Yeah that had to be really unpleasant for the balls. They tried to
do a fun thing where his mask friend floated down to like try to cover up the nuts but it wasn't
fast enough. I definitely saw the nuts. I thought what was weird what was weird about the whole
experience is that Carlos Bandicoot didn't even like seem fazed like it's not so revealed and he
just stood there like kind of shrugging like yep that the hardest part about it for me was not the
reveal of the nuts because I thought that was tasteful and on-brand but for the when he went
for 20 minutes afterwards just going what do you think what do you think I mean the audience
the audience ate it up though and I did think it was a little bit sad maybe uh when later
Ratchet and Clank came out there and then Clank revealed like big metal nuts um and not like
sorry it's not like a fun sort of hardware nuts but actual like metal balls like testicles but
they were made in a lab they were made a lab in there but then Clank was just like is this what
you got is this whatever does everyone like this and then um Sony announced Shenmue 4 yeah which is
wild it was so sick I was so excited this one is all forklifts also Sonic the Hedgehog Origins
in which he is very slow for the first 90% of the game and he gets hit by lightning or something
something we don't know we don't know what I thought was great was at the end yeah remember
the screen went black and you're like well that's it and then they were like just one more thing
and then Kratos it showed Kratos and he was like I've got nuts too and he started to peel it away
and then it was like black screen coming in 2018 and it's like I yeah yeah I'm on board to see
Kratos's nuts in 11 years yeah it's coming in a lot in a while Travis when do you think 2018 is
Travis oh I thought you said for some reason I heard 2028 I don't know why it's different that
would be quite the dev cycle well Justin it takes a while to get the right texture mapping
do you want half ass balls I'm sorry Justin do you want half ass balls is that what is going on with
with Gordon with my man Gordon is Gabe just trying to get the balls my new gun in this one
is balls he's just got perfect physics laden balls worth the wait and what's weird is they also
revealed uh saints row five very tasteful no nudity no balls they were like now everyone's
doing balls it's an it's a children's edgy game it is fucking weird it's so weird they were like
you know what we've pushed the boundary we've come back around the other side now very tasteful
uh like a downton abbey-esque kind of game from the people at saints row and what's and it's great
the next dragon age announced that too they're doing like a pokemon red blue version one where
there's a version with lots of huge balls on all the dragons and on everybody and then there's one
where it's more um pure I guess and the balls are much more tasteful balls anything any other
funny things we can say about video games balls something about mario's balls I don't think that's
pretty careless that's well trod at this point he has those things out for anybody that'll ask
that wouldn't have been a reveal at all um so I had yeah what I didn't like was seeing madden's
balls again it's like every year we have it's like ea feels like they have to show us man's balls
and it's like we get it they're the same balls as last year but they look a little bit better now I
don't know how that arc is working by the way whatever madden is doing for those bad boys is
working for him uh I will say I did appreciate that they finally just like you know just admitted
the truth and just called it what it is and announced the new ball of duty game okay and
that's it that's the logical terminus there's our stop boop boop everybody off uh on this show we
talk about video game characters balls but also sometimes give advice in between so I'd like to
get right to it about a year ago I went to a party at my friend's new place during the event I walked
straight through the screen door oh oh man oh about 20 minutes later another party goer did
the exact same thing and the door was ruined that's true okay hold on uh I'll get to the
science a second door's ruined now one year later my friend's roommate is asking me to pay for the
replacement of the door as they move out what should I do I caused the damage but so did the
other guy isn't this past the statute of limitations and that's from egregious door
smasher in Everett Washington okay so what I don't understand is how you walked through the
screen door yet left enough more enough for somebody else to penetrate like you took down
you took down a couple cubes of the don't break the ice but then somebody else came in and finished
the fight it sounds like maybe a little bit perhaps person a the question asker is on the
shorter side so when they walk through they tore out like one side and the bottom I see I see I see
person two is much taller and they took out the top section um I will say if two folks in one night
walk through the same screen door that is a design failure on part of the door maybe the mesh was too
fine you're lucky it didn't just like grate you you could have walked into it and just come out
the other side like play-doh spaghetti cube two hyper cubed right there all over the floor and
then that's another thing they have to pay that's coming out of the damage deposit is that there's
just cubes of Brian all over um I as far as the statute of limitations that gets so tricky because
this is the type of thing that like it happens and it's at a party and you had a few Beverly's
and you look over and your friend fucking Kool-Aid man smashes through your screen door and it's
very very funny and then when it's time to move out you look at that same screen door and you're
like oh yeah we have to pay for that and so I think it comes up again um well but Griffin I
would say that the statute of limitations for this is the 20 minutes it took for the next person to
walk through it because if you separated that out longer if you're like yeah I ran into my friend's
screen door and then three months later someone else did it and like it was completely demolished
at that point you wouldn't be like okay well you're both responsible now I would say like
wait hold on that is that person's responsible I may have started it but they definitely finished
it yeah but you could make the argument that it was you who necessitated the fixing in the first
place you normal you normalize the process of of Hulk smashing through the screen door your
friends saw you do it was like I well I guess it's okay I guess everybody's smashing the screen
door policy here um fuck at the same time though I can't imagine how funny this was and I think
that that pays for itself like yeah I gotta you know I gotta dish out like 70 bucks or whatever
to fix the door but um I had 70 bucks worth of laughter and funny story do y'all remember when
I did this at uncle Dave's uncle Dave's house we were we were over at our uncle Dave's house
down in Florida and um this was this was a fucking decade ago and I saw a golf cart out in his driveway
and I saw it and I guess I thought in my mind I was gonna go and hop in the golf cart and like
do a few laps around the community uh and I said out loud Grand Theft Auto and look at referencing
the game not the crime and I just went right through the fucking thing and to me it was really
really funny and that but uncle Dave got pretty upset and then later on I called I called uncle
Dave to apologize but I could not stop laughing over the phone and so I do not think the apology
was accepted or believed it's very funny to watch somebody do this because it's a door doors are
supposed to keep this from happening and when it doesn't it is very very hysterical yes we'll pay
for it fine we'll do it fine send us a bill voice and we'll and we'll take care of it clarify
just that clear itemized we need an itemized invoice itemized invoice labor not too expensive
get somebody who knows what they're doing can I do a real quick yahoo and then a better yahoo
yeah I'd love that this quick one is like it took me on a journey it was sent by Seth Carlson thank
you Seth yahoo answers user exciting nine who asks um I thought Obama was supposed to make the
commercials on tv be the same volume as the shows what happened to this commercials commercials are
still like twice as loud as shows to me this makes him a lame duck president pretty busted um metric
this is very funny huh so the FCC actually did a thing they passed a bill in 2010 called the
calm act the commercial advertisement loudness mitigation act where you get a penalty if you if
you fucking go from like oh Deborah oh my mom's come over again we got new spaghetti come on down
and get this spaghetti if you do that you get fined like a bunch of money but it doesn't seem
to I guess this is one where they're just like how do you enforce that if somebody records it on
their tv and then they send you the tv recording of the spaghetti crime and then the channel gets
the channel gets blasted they must be just the profit margins on the spaghetti must just be so
good it's like whatever it takes just blaze it I would also I would also just like to jump in here
um before anybody tweets or anything that's also just not what lame duck means in any political
content that's just because you didn't accomplish something doesn't make you a lame duck that's a
very specific thing um anyways just wanted to clarify that I like this idea of like I thought
he said he was gonna clean up the streets well lame duck mayor this is this is since having a
uh a baby who goes to sleep at like six o'clock this is my this is probably the most pressing
concern for me now which is me and me and rachel are watching the big bang theory just like quietly
chuckling like fighting the earth should just scream a good cackle out what did he say about
the flesh yeah so he's like he's like he's like uh captain mccard and cling on then dr who and
board games and then it's just like pepsi's got it just like scream like like fucking tyrese just
like shows up on the on my screen for pepsi and he's just like pepsi's got it screaming and it
knocks all of the pictures off my walls on my house and all i just replaced all the windows
in the house and those have exploded and the baby the baby's crib like collapses like a cartoon like
all the wood falls apart we i believe have touched on this in a previous episode but i'd love to
circle around about it now that you all are in this situation how miserable are tv shows and i'm
looking at you twin peaks i hate to to drag you on this how miserable are tv shows where
dialogue is mixed to the quietest possible volume and every single footfall is like a thousand
megaton bomb just i just i do want to say it's interesting that you would single out twin peaks
where the dialogue to no dialogue ratio is like pretty astounding one percent dialogue but yes
i do agree that especially if there's any kind of supernatural or fantasy element fucking dragons are
the worst like can we please level eight those dragons please when we when we were rewatching
buffy we're almost done thank christ um every time she smokes one of those vampos that sound effect
was josh was in the studio just like crank that shit did the dust sound effect fucking
pop that shit i hate vampires fucking crank it it's like i'm gonna i'm gonna kick you really
hard vampire i will see about that i'm gonna bite your neck first stab like come on guys please
i think about that teresa and i we watched parks and rec just like on loop
and it's always the same thing with the intro music and it's like hey local local government
joke let's so what do we do we need the sequel to the calm act the calmer act as proposed by
the mackeroy brothers so that their babies so their babies cribs don't explode when the pepsi
commercial comes on let me let me propose this what if it said there's just a service where like
somebody comes to your house and they just ride the volume button like they're just there they're
not enjoying the thing at all they're just like mute ah yes ah damn it um anyway this is the thing
i thought i saw this question i was like another goofball on yahoo being a silly billy but no i
mean this wasn't obama's jurisdiction i don't think but there was there's a law about this
that apparently this is just one of those laws like many laws that you can just be like no we're
just gonna keep doing doing it i have an idea i have an idea you're gonna love that everybody's
gonna love this it is a way more enforceable law pass a law all commercials the voiceover work has
to be done by roman mars oh i love this you're welcome i was just telling roman mars yesterday
that i'm gonna load up like an mp3 player and just play it like on a loop uh of 99 invisible
in my baby's room so that she will both learn um to speak eloquently but also like not get
woken up by big spikes of like yelling i gotcha i gotcha can i pitch you a different idea yes
a new law that says that every line of dialogue on every tv show from now on has to be screamed
at the top of your lungs and because then even that would normalize it even then i could i could
turn my volume down to a regular volume so that when tyrese is like pepsi's got it and it gets
back and it's like mike did you drop the car off with the mechanic no molly i forgot damn it mike
that's from mike and molly uh classic scene from mike and molly i think that would solve
the problem too okay wait wait alternate alternate government next up on tonight's show we got the
weekend how about all commercials are voiced by roman mars but also all parts and all tv shows
are played by roman mars i would do that 88 some mars adr no no no he plays every part oh um the
one who knocks um he's gonna be busy he's gonna be very busy uh here's another question i park
about 15 minutes away from work but i don't mind because it's a nice walk through a field last week
i saw a teen planting a five-foot conifer when we made eye contact he got rather weird and hid
around to the other side of it you gotta help me through this i walk past it every day now and i
don't know why he hid ideas that's from confused about the conifer holy shit three possibilities
okay y'all tell me what you think nymph dryad or some sort of satyr it's one of the it's definitely
one of the three it's definitely supernatural definitely supernatural it's a nymph it's a
nymph it's a dryad or it's a satyr it was the spirit of this tree one way or the other i mean
whatever the the form it took is i think we can all agree that there's definitely you um this is
a narnia ask mr tumness like invitation to go on our fantasy world but you had to get to work
definitely tumness definitely tumness we're looking at full-on tumness find that tree got a
hole put your head in the hole there you go down you go to the other world to the other one follow
him follow the tumness always follow the tumness you always have to stop what you're doing drop
what you're doing and follow the tumness 100 of the time gotta follow the tumness till you
reach the terminus that's what i've always said do you know how many tumness opportunities like
how many people get tumness opportunities in this life not many not many i've never i've
never fucking had one but if i did you can bet i would drop what i was doing stop what i was doing
and go get that tumness that's it i did once oh shit yeah i mean time didn't pass the same for
you guys so i yeah i was only gone for like five minutes but from my view i was gone for 25 years
and that's um when i learned french um and and cross stitching um you forgot the you forgot the
french i forgot the french part um i didn't learn it great i learned it like high school learned it
you know enough to pass um but that was it i actually um now looking back in retrospect i
probably could have spent more time away from tumness exploring narnia mostly i just hung out
with tumness cross stitching and speaking french so on the on the off chance this is in a tumness
scenario the only other explanation is that look when you're a teen you're almost always looking
for places to make out or smoke weed and so this person was probably planting a lovely tree
just to have one more spot in the world where they could go and have some some sneaky some sneak
time a little bit of sneak time okay like there's there's not enough places there's not enough little
shadowy spots and um you know elements to break line of sight in this field that he likes to
get blazed or make kisses in and so they planted this tree to have like a little zone a little them
zone i really like this forward thinking that you're pitching here griffin where they planted
uh what a five foot tall tree yep and and thought man in a hundred years i'm really gonna enjoy
smoking weed behind well travis what are they gonna do carry a massive redwood into this
field no they're right you're right you're right you know what i was wrong and you were right um i
do also want to say question asker it's also quite possible that what you were witnessing appeared
to be a teen planting a tree but was in fact a teen contemplating stealing a tree
hmm and you foiled it i want to i like to i'd like to go back and pitch the visual mental picture of
an 80 year old person taking another person into a big field where a big tall proud conifer is there
and he goes up and puts his hand on the tree and tells the story of how he planted it and how he
always been waiting for this moment more or less his entire life and then he just pulls out the
biggest duper and is like all right let's party it's time grandson it's time to do this damn thing
i planted this smoke tree for you for us this is our family legacy
um oh i was so hoping whoa we got a haunted doll watch oh it's been forever i feel like haunted
doll watch has been thoroughly munched by the munch squad let me blow the dust off the tome yeah
haunted doll janet very high emf uh i'm gonna go ahead and skype you all a link if you're
playing at home you can feel free to google don't read ahead please i would ask you can
just enjoy the pictures of haunted doll jen very active hi i gotta say she's got um
um a lot of just a lot of hair and what looks like some mardi gras beads sort of
that's binding her the first fun thing is that she's been bound by mardi gras beads in this one
janet is an active essence she is enjoyed mostly in the early morning hours at just at sunset
ill the tilapia may i recommend a janet this one has been aged for many years she prefers
to be why do you like run out of bed every morning you don't understand my janet is
best in the early morning hours and oh you want to catch janet you gotta get up before
early bird gets the spooky doll she prefers to be away from a window but what's a view to the
outside enjoy this periscope janet fuck off you're about to feel bad i feel that this is because her
essence was shut away during her life and was warned against being seen by outsiders parentheses
maybe hiding during world war i mean fucking maybe a big swing yeah just take a shot at it
uh when i put it on a show maybe against the devil when i put her on the shelf maybe like in
maybe she was trapped in a cupboard like indian in the cupboard you don't know you don't know when i
put her on a shelf with other vessels the next morning she would be on the floor she doesn't
like to be around other people well that sounds more like a problem with the other dolls being
bullies communicating with her was ellipses fluid it's so natural what does that mean just
natural sweaty janet are you feeling this i gave this this early morning vibe i gained my insights
by sitting with her over a l-o-n-g hyphenated period of time it's high it's it's heightening
the longness of this period of time and allowing the conceptualization to enter my consciousness
with my other dolls the feeling i got from them was singular i would get a strong feeling over
time much like you sit quietly in the wilderness and begin to hear sounds that you did not pick up
immediately you experience the tapestry as a gestalt rather than focusing on any individual
threads within the tapestry it was in these times that she would be the most active with me
janet doll is made from porcelain and i believe it is five feet there's no reality
what the fuck there's a picture there's a picture of it standing next to a thing of incense that it
is as big as is this a five foot novelty incense stick well i do want okay two things one go to
this and look at the pictures because what i love is you get one picture of doll by yourself and then
two separate pictures of the uh incense candle picture as if they're like which one of these
do you think is best you know what i'll do both both and then secondly justin that was very
charitable of you in describing what janet doll is made from um because you said porcelain when in
fact the material that they claim is procalian procalian is a new material um that we're we're
all really excited about the new tesla models are mostly procalian this is um not five feet tall
that's correct it's not a fucking in any way it's not a fucking blockbuster cardboard stand-up of
the rock okay it's like little doll this is such false advertising that i believe this person could
actually go to jail for how much how bad they whiffed this size estimation um also just real
quick starting bid 95 bucks or buy it now for 150 you know i don't want to stress about it
three folks watching oh that's us there's i don't like to stress out i don't want to put the 95 in
you pay an extra 65 bucks for the 150 buy it now but just the peace of mind that it brings me is
so worth it so i can have this in my door estimated between wednesday june 14th and
monday june 19th like fucking like yeah all right let's do it i'm gonna pull the trigger
well griffin i do have one question for you though um does the seller list an item condition
for this haunted doll uh let's see no no it's oh god it's there's nothing in it but in where
the additional notes are it says quote unquote new all right what does that mean in regards to
a haunted doll possibly from world war ii quote unquote new it's new this is the fresh out the
box haunted doll uh and this is also seller haunted items number four letter u thank you
very much 100 positive feedback love their service they do not address the mardi gras bead binding
no not at all no but if this doll was five feet tall the beads binding this doll are fucking
gigantic they're ginormous marley's earthly chains just binding this doll um uh hey i just i just
started a new level and i need to really focus uh so do you think we could take a quick break
and maybe go to the money zone and then a new level of the video game i've been playing this
whole time okay got it yeah let's go oh hi travis here you may be wondering but where are the other
brothers well um this is the future this segment that you're hearing right now this is um a couple
days after we recorded that last segment and justin and griffin are in los angeles getting
ready to cover e3 for uh their other jobs so you're stuck with me talking about our sponsors
this week but i couldn't be happier because joining me this week in place of my brothers
is wink um i think we've talked about wink before um it's i love it i use it um once a month i get
a shipment of wine to my house and it's not just like random um you know whatever they had lying
around they throw it in a box it's based off of what i like and not like the intricate questions
of well what's do you like notes of berry and cedar it's like do you like chocolate or vanilla
do you like uh sweet or savory questions that you can actually answer and feel confident answering
so you should go to try wink.com it's t-r-y w-i-n-c um wink w-i-n-c.com and you can take a brief
palette profile quiz um and then they'll recommend wines based on your palette and then they'll be
shipped directly to your door because wink bases the wines they send you on your taste preferences
wink will introduce you to new custom wines that are not available anywhere else it i really am a
huge fan um it allows me to you know show off to my friends a bit to pull out wines that they've
never seen and they've never heard of i'm a big fan uh highly recommend you may have heard us talk
about them back when they were club w well they've become a wink now now they are become wink um and
i'm a big fan so right now wink is offering twenty dollars off your first order when you go to try
wink.com t-r-y w-i-n-c.com slash my brother they'll even cover the cost of shipping so that's try wink
t-r-y w-i-n-c.com slash my brother to get twenty dollars off your first order now plus complimentary
shipping trying wink.com slash my brother also joining me this week one of my best friends
maybe one of my closest friends me undies um i'm wearing them right now this is a lot weirder to
talk about when no one else is with me now i'm just having a private moment talking about my
underpants that i'm wearing right now every pair of me undies is sustainably sourced and made from
micro modal a fabric that's three times softer than cotton but i tell you from personal experience it
feels a billion times softer than clouds yes that's right it feels like you're girding yourself in
clouds but softer yes um this month is a rainbow confetti print called celebrate um because they
come in all kinds of patterns and there's new designs all the time there's limited edition
patterns each month this one i'm a really big fan of i think it's really cool looking but i i'm a
fan of all of them um from you know like a plain black or green or whatever to their amazing print
they've got some really really cool designs over at me undies.com so you should try me undies today
um to get the celebrate pattern before they're all gone go to me undies.com slash my brother
and you'll save 20 off your first pair and if you don't love your first pair of me undies
they're free so get 20 off your first pair plus free shipping at me undies.com slash my brother
right now me undies.com slash my brother we've also got some personal jumbotron messages this one
is for chris the law student in minnesota the only one the only law student in minnesota hi chris
it's from david and sarah who say hey chris we love you and we're super proud of you for finishing
this year of law school as well as the whole rest of your life okay they're okay you're doing great
and you bring us all joy every day even those of us that didn't get in on this message we love you
and hope you have the happiest day i hope this message is delivered by a brother you like
oh man i hope so too it's just me i hope i'm the one um i was a little thrown off there because
uh i was confused of the uh proud of you for finishing the year and the rest of your life but
i think that they meant they're proud of them for that and also proud of the rest of their life
not because chris finished the rest of his life um but anyways yes congratulations chris good job
i understand law school is very difficult uh this next message is for michael o'hara and it's from
martha o'hara who says happy belated anniversary michael it is i your wife martha i know that we
said no gifts this year but a mere technicality could not stop me from pursuing this great idea
much like an emergency appendectomy did not stop us from seeing hamilton you are the best and i
love you that is some amazing dedication to seeing hamilton did you like take a break in the middle of
the appendectomy were you like hold on can you tie that off and i'll be back in two and a half hours
that's amazing so happy anniversary michael from martha lots of love sorry about your appendix
hey readers all of you bookworms comic geeks library junkies literary fiction lovers
bibliophiles and nerds want to get more out of your reading life listen to reading glasses i'm
bria grant and i'm mallory o'mara we want to help you read better join us every thursday on maximum
fun's new podcast while we talk about book culture and solve your reader problems reading glasses
will teach you how to vanquish your to be read pile connect with other readers and get more reading
into your busy day no matter what you read or how you read it we'll help you do it better that's
cute hey can i do a yahoo now yep is it good yeah lots lots and lots and lots of people
sent this one in thank you everyone seriously i think like six people so an anonymous yahoo user
um say janet asks how do you avoid getting water up your rear when going on certain water slides
update update update like the really steep fast ones with lots of water pressure
i i think everybody's sort of got their own way of dealing with this um me i've started to sort
of work with a kind of hydrophobic um tight sort of unders undersuit that i wear under my swimsuit
so smart that keeps everything just like gunpowder dry and so like it's not even it's hydrophobic so
like i'm going in the water from the water slide it's like let me get in that rear end but my
my undershorts are just like think think about it again i'm very afraid of you you know what i mean
when you go down the water slide the water goes it just naturally wants to snake up there
and i guess i'm asking like how you don't how you don't maybe get it
two scrunchies two scrunchies hold the trunks oh the trunks for the trunk's legs closed you know
what i mean i'm turning into a kind of a they'll kind of look like a pantaloon i think at that
point yeah that would look kind of nice and then you and then you also have a sort of tourniquet
situation which is good if like one of your something happens to the legs that's possible
on a water slide you could just do what i did what did you did uh what i did was i just had
skin grafted over my butthole so no no not yet okay not yet not yet just like permanently sealed it
just in case of water slides i now will say travis this is a lot of folks here this thing
what a crass joke travis is his biggest tube junkie i ever met he loves those big wet tubes and he goes
down them all the time so like if somebody were to kind of like water world uh kurt costner got
the gills put in just because he swims all the time like travis gets on those wet tubes all the
time and so like he does need like a a practical um easy solution let me be clear it is not
the only modification i've made i mean my whole butt cracker is now smooth it's one whole cheek
i've also had the points of my elbows and knees shaved down to help with my arrow uh die
uh you know aerodynamics uh dynamicism yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i think aqua dynamics is what you're
thinking of because it's not just it's not just you don't just gotta seal up the craft you want
it to go as fast as is possible on those tubes my arms are permanently bound to my sides oh wow
yeah no listen um and i also shaved my eyebrows off so like there's a lot of steps what's the
eyebrows for just for looks um do you think if you got trunks tattooed on they would let you go
on they would let you go down naked oh say it again if you got trunks or a you know bikini
bottoms or one piece of whatever tattooed on do you think they would let you go down naked
if you have a tattoo i i wish i could say no but
it does look like you're wearing trunks i can't tell any difference
yeah you know what i'm gonna say go ahead i'm gonna let it go i'm a 17 year old he doesn't care
so sure fuck it and i'm crash bandicoot and i'm ready to slide you must be wearing some
sort of trunks because i can't see any kind of butt crack yeah yeah exactly oh my god he's so fast
holy shit all right three two one and go and you're out what how did that what
you there was another kid in the slide you shot through them what the fuck
uh a fun thing to do when you get on a water slice the last thing you should say the person is
time me and then they'll feel like oh how am i supposed to get this information to him actually
yeah time him with none of that stuff and then another fun thing just before you get in the
water slide yeah like the window's about to close i have to go now yeah jump in but then just before
you reach the bottom kind of pin your arms to the sides so like you hold yourself in place so when
the person's looking you don't come out the bottom you must have slid and now they're remembering
sliders and how much they love and how much they love that show i really don't want them to be
distracted though it's an important job they have yeah um wow i think it's okay i think it's okay
for a little water to go up yeah it can be nice can be good it's like a bidet it's just like a
bidet one time when i was a little kid we were at a water park outdoor maybe the one at king's
island if that was if that was extra yeah yeah yeah uh and i was so thirsty oh no for whatever
reason our parents wouldn't buy me a drink and i don't know why maybe they were too expensive or i
don't know why but i have maybe they didn't love you maybe they didn't care whether it was they
they they had just bought me a drink and so like they were just kind of tired uh can i show griffins
absolutely not what a dumb question uh so i slid down a water slide and at the bottom of the slide
slid down a water slide and at the bottom of the water slide i forced myself when i landed in the
splash pool i forced myself to take a big gulp of water oh my god this is the most viscerally
upsetting like i'm not joking the most upsetting thing that has been discussed on this episode so
far and more so than travis's like butthole modifications now let me ask it's the whole
crack griffin let me ask you this one time i was leaving new york and i went to the wrong airport
and i realized at the last moment and hop back in the cab and paid the guy to as like a private car
like he was also moonlighting for carmel so i asked him to like i will pay you to take me to
newark and i was at laguardia and he was like well it's gonna be tight making it there and he
just floored it and i realized that i was planning on getting a drink at the airport and hadn't
drank anything all day and i was thirstier than i've ever been in my entire life except for the
time that i drank water out of a splash splash water park and i noticed in the door of the cab
someone left half a water bottle um there and i did pick it up and drink it because i was so
thirsty now my question to you is this wait wait hold on sealed water bottle already open no half
empty i said half empty okay that would have been quite the fucking feat um so what's worse
one of them didn't have other people bathing and lounging around and splashing around with
their kids and having fun and playing that one's chlorinated though here's the thing
justin have you thought about that your entire life after drinking from the wave pool has been
a lie a few fever state brought on by the consuming of that horrible poison and everything now is your
like your brain just giving you images to cover up for your like pool water coma like i'm still
there in the pool yeah and all of this has just been like kind of an oracle at delphi kind of
warp forward like you're you breathed in the vapors and now you're able to see time in all
of its many forms and facets well i mean possible but you have to assume then at that point that
i've been kept alive in stasis in the wave pool this entire time so yeah like a precog people
are just splash downing around oh watch out for the little tubby guy hold on let me float him
over to the other side darn it he's helping tom cruise solve mysteries you gotta watch out for
him darn it grab the umbrella what did he say drop the nickels what did he say what is he saying
i couldn't hear him over the water slide it's only he's a precog but he only can sense um
uh waterslide park crime yeah like that there should be more cheese in there it's supposed to
be three fourths of the way filled up on those nachos he's starting to wake up out of it but
we haven't solved this crime here quick give him that gross bottle of water and get him back into
it it's a re that's a that's a refill collectible refill mug that he brought from home he didn't buy
that today i'm a senior in high school my class has been pretty lame with the pranks so the other
night i gathered up some friends and decided to fork the football field and that's stick plastic
forks in it to spell some stuff or just be a nuisance we were doing well for about an hour
when several cop cars pulled up and we had to drop everything and run i managed to escape but
i left my sister's backpack behind i was using it to carry extra forks it's definitely been
confiscated by now but she doesn't know i used it should i turn myself in and get her backpack back
or should i be just the worst and pretend i have no idea where it went i risk being charged with
trespassing because i was on school grounds at 1 a.m and ran from cops that's from perplexed
prankster p.s i managed to write zag on him before we were chased off god not in our name
taking the day the next day when everyone found the prank um there are photos i look forward to
you later can i just say just uh personally i one of the things i really love about this is
the idea of forking um is very funny to me um because it seems definitely like a nuisance
but kind of like uh what uh well you know this could be worse okay uh let's pick up these 40
plastic forks and go on about our lives uh probably not 40 probably hundreds probably
hundreds and hundreds here's how you know if you're old if you hear this story and you're
like ha nice you're probably not if you hear this story and you're like all that poor guy
because there's some poor guy or lady that had to go in the next morning and just individually pluck
forks out of the football field that's a rough day you know they've got a full load and now they've
got to deal with your forks six kids spend one hour stabbing force into a football field that's
going to take one adult six hours to remove all of the force of the football field it spells out
zag on him what do you think it means it spells out zaggo name fucking kids i just don't know
anymore is this some sort of beyblade is there a beyblade character named zaggo i fucking over it
i'm sorry i'm sorry officer the the trail's gone cold wait what's that a pink chance for it it says
debra on it this cold case is heating up you're uh excuse me uh are you dr zaggo neem uh yeah
that's uh me are you here for an appointment no not really bend over that fucking desk hands behind
your back we got him we got him the fork menace please you have to let me finish this butthole
smoothing operation please no i can't stop in the middle it's essential um it's sheriff i got
another ping matrix fingerprints were found on this jam sport it's the 16th one but we think
this is a clue that's finally going to lead us to the truth it's a jam sport hold up hold up
everybody hold up amazon.com and then we gonna type in the name of the backpack brand jansport
backpack in luggage and travel gear this is fifteen dollars and eighty two cents come on
should i go to jail or should i pay fifteen dollars and eighty two cents to get a new jansport
a new fresh jansport with like no you don't you know how jansport in any backpack really
just even if you never put food in it it gets food crumbles in the bottom of it at some point
a fresh start no crumbles and also no crumbles but also no jail what if you went to the police of
like the police station and you just incredibly dramatically threw yourself on the mercy of the
officers in order to reclaim your sister's backpack just like very like i did it i was
the one who zagged upon them and that is my sister's back how could i and like really just
like tear your shirt gnashing your teeth my bet is they'll just hand you the backpack and tell you
to leave because they're very busy no no fifteen dollars and eighty two cents eighty two cents to
get out of this right the other option is you go and you think like oh it's just a harmless prank
they are always always always casting for scared straight a hundred percent of the time they're
casting for scared straight you go in there and you with your innocent cherubic i did a prank
they're gonna it's gonna happen yeah they're gonna get you sorry on the show sorry you're on
the show now you're our what if they what if they trace the jansport back to the question ask your
sister and now we got like a prisoner's dilemma and if you speak up about the backpack you know
that kind you know you know that old question asker sit perfectly still now don't move i said
don't move gradually turn your head to the right as if you're looking at something at a 45 degree
angle away from you using your peripheral vision don't look using your peripheral vision tell me
do you see john quinones because it's entirely possible you're this entire experience is an
episode of what would you do and john quinones would like to go home john quinones has a family
so if you would just poop or get off the pot so john quinones can go about his life he's got a
lot of tv to craft and he would like to move on and he's just been following you eating whatever
you leave on your plate hiding hiding on your closet shelves and sleeping there yeah cannot
stress enough though do not look directly at john quinones or he might attack yeah you'll
be turned to stone um should we do one more yahoo or nah just a real quick one well i got two this
one was hmm i'll do i'll ask both this one was sent in by amelia burger thank you amelia it's
yahoo answers user kevin zak who asks how do we make apple juice more relevant to adult consumers
we can have fun with that somebody owns an apple juice company and boy they're hurting
and then this one is by maddie sent in by maddie taylor thank you maddie it's yahoo
answers user gary the human being who asks would you like to go completely gary free
okay quick answer to question number one you call it apple i juice and now you got a lot of
Chinese what a bad joke okay that's not a joke griffin that's my honest answer now let's talk
about gary i'm going to i'm going to an island it's an exclusive festival exclusive music festival
everyone's going to be there and it's going to be amazing the people who aren't going to be there
let's see gary senise um gary um that's the only gary i can think of huh that's
that's peculiar gotta be some more gary's gary what do you see is not okay you're not invited
um gary marshall gary marshall is not able to come to the thing uh entrepreneur gary vaynerchuk
it's not there you saw right where i was going with that the snail gary from spongebob don't
you think if you google famous gary's it's weird that it's not g-a-r-i-e-s that that's pretty weird
right yeah i don't like seeing g-a-r-y-s um actually the interesting thing is the plural of
gary is gary like i saw several gary yeah so gary coleman gary oldman oh that's a shame oh fuck
hold on this website started playing jazz music gary oldman that one hurts i would love that one
stings gary bucey and you know all the others can't come do you know gary kasparov can't come
but like gary oldman that one stings did you know and this is a scientific fact there are more uh
gary's alive now than have ever been alive in all of history combined it's a hot name it's a hot name
yeah there's there's one more one more gary alive now that like if we lose that gary though it's
going to tip the scale who's older gary senise or gary oldman oh gary oldman right travis i'm
going to say gary senise i'll split the gary senise is older than gary oldman that's that's
wild it is wild so what would it be if all gary's were spirited away somewhere to the gary plane
what would that mean for me do you think that it would make you stop like you couldn't remember
a time with gary's or would it just be like moving forward no more gary's
moving for i get now i think it's that all they've been unwritten they've been unwritten
from the undone they've been on gary my friend's um stepdad is named gary and we use his hbo login
so that well you're definitely in trouble there would be bad for me i couldn't catch the new
season of game of thrones or i wouldn't have been able to see any of the game of thrones
i wouldn't i just wouldn't have folks would be like did you see this new episode i say i don't
because i have no gary's in my life i think i would love to see that angel clarence just leading
a pack of gary's just a is it a murder of gary's i can never remember around the world to show them
what it would be like in a gary free world like had there never been any gary's what what that
world would be like they would seem they would see me having brunch with my friends and one of
them was like the lannisters always pay their debts and i'm like what is what what is what
what's that mean do you think there would definitely be gary's who are like
i it's jerry i go by jerry please don't take me please i actually just found uh the guardian story
and the headline is high noon for gary why is the once popular name on the verge of extinction
and can i say looking at this list i googled famous gary's and there's a website that only has
like six gary's on it that's not very many just to put a button on this this question was asked
by gary the human being that's hard that's hard it's tough and i do want to read some of the
answers oh this is by user let the past make you better not bitter who says no you're a nice user
someone says get a grip get a grip would you gary g little big man says no way you're a good guy gary
mate um one anonymous user who's too chicken shit to use their real fucking name says yes that would
be nice piece of shit sharon s says no never weasel mcweasel says no where would the fun in that be
that be i tamed the beast says no you're my friend wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
is there in the yahoo answers world is there a community are they i'm worried there might be a
sort of union of a blessed union of souls here like ah gary's out of the gate like they they
they are all connected instantly supportive people that we've been dumping on publicly for
the better part of seven years princess buddy says no way you're a good user here and ask good
cues it was it would be boring on here without you yahoo without my gary blue blue sky says no
you're one of the nicest people on this site gary gary i love your posts and your submissions wait
what the fuck this is like you crush it 24 seven we couldn't do this without you
are there only like 12 people on yahoo answers i mean yeah
yeah yeah more or less that's why when you go and it's like um you go for it it's like my uh
my baby's doing this weird thing just want to check and see if it's sick or not
you're really asking these 12 people who all sort of put their heads together to generate the you
know the best answer for points you're asking the council of 12 the like the yahoo governing body
of which gary is one but he's also you know he's the shy one you take it before the you take it
before the fellowship of the dingus here and just see what jim they can barf out gary without gary
gary no way what's the point yeah i'm not i'm gonna i can't go on in a gary free world
they were like we're gonna change it to altaba and gary was like ah if you do that i'll leave
and everybody's like if gary leaves we revolt and they were like all right fuck it was a bad idea
what about oath gary's like nah fuck that too and everyone's like yeah what gary said
i hope gary's doing okay yeah me too hey gary if you're listening i know that we make a lot of
jokes but we really like having you around it's always better with gary here um that's gonna do
it i've always said that gary gary gary gary has 19 763 answers are you shitting me whoa
what doesn't he know he doesn't know how awesome he is justin yeah he doesn't know how important
he is to us and also like time management i think probably are you able to give us just
a sampling of some of the areas of garrett the gary is of his expertise uh no i don't want to
read any of these this dude said answers well folks that's going to do it for us thank you
so much for listening uh gary thank you gary of course as always thanks to all the gary's
listening including my friend stepdad gary gave me a good hbo login thank you i love
watching the mother of dragons out there um one time jesse when game of thrones was very
buzzy one time jesse our our boss tweeted a lannister always has sucrettes and then it's
the only thing i can ever fucking think of whenever somebody talks about game of thrones
it's like it's like a earworm for puns um thank you to you at home for listening we very much
appreciate you and thank you for rating and reviewing our show on itunes and subscribing
and all that stuff uh thanks to danielle for the cool munch squad t-shirt thanks to tommy
for his game by the rights patrick sent his book space tripping uh now tom wall
is a cirque du soleil cone juggler who tried to bury the hatchet with my brother my brother and
me on behalf of all jugglers by sending along a very cool cirque du soleil program from one of
their japanese shows okay that was very nice tom and my daughter put the stickers you send along
on her uh bed so that is painful for me to have to see every day sort of confront every night
um i do want to say cone juggling uh owns bounds it's it's cool as fuck is it really juggling
though because it's not really going up in the air it's going around a cone i think it's a
different it that's like sorcery and i'm into it fair enough all right we'll give cone jugglers a
pass congratulations tom you did it i also want to say um along with that uh thinking people who
sent things in uh jesse rob sent me um and i'm sorry if i'm mispronouncing your last name jesse
uh sent some intelligentsia coffee as well as giving me a very very helpful tutorial on like
coffee and why it tastes the way it does and how to pick the right one for the kind of coffee i
like and it was just in general wonderful and intelligentsia coffee is great and that's not
a paid plug i'm just a big new fan it's really fucking good i'm a subscriber yeah every week
do y'all remember when i tried to take you to the intelligentsia cafe in chicago we took a
train for like 45 minutes and walked forever and it was closed like it had been closed for like a
month yeah it was the hardest thing that's ever happened to me um i want to thank john roger
in the long winters for a theme song it's a departure off the album putting the days to
bed it's a really really really fucking good album go go get it and go listen to it please
i'm begging you now i'm now on my knees begging you um anything else yeah thanks to maximum fun
for having us and you can go to maximum fun.org check out all the great shows there if you want
to hear more stuff we do you can go to mcroy shows.com um and check all that out and i think
that's it all right well uh do you have a final yahoo to send us out on ditto yeah here's a final
yahoo and it was sent in by amelia burger thank you amelia it's yahoo answers user c who asks
uh don't horses deserve horse-shaped coffins
my name is justin mcroy
i'm grippin mcroy
my brother be kissing that square on the
list
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported hi this is griffin mcroy hi
this is rachel mcroy we're the hosts of rose buddies it's a podcast about the bachelor family
of products we watch the bachelor the bachelorette and bachelor in paradise yes it is garbage
television but we're the king and queen of this garbage pile we're the raccoons in charge around
here so join us on tuesdays because the tv show's on mondays and basically we'll recap what we saw
and we'll just sort of scoop the garbage around us and make a little fort out of it
no viewing required but it's it's a good tv show what are you doing