Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on the wall, I have seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool kids?
Thank you, my dear wizard.
As excited as you all are to see us, I promise we're twice as excited to see these beers.
I forgot the paper Yacht is backstage, is that going to be a problem?
Oh no!
So ruined.
Like Chilean Meyers emerging.
I'm not going to kill it.
This is my brother, I'm going to make you a show from the Bajoran era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-aged brother, Travis McElroy.
And I'm your sweet, pain-y man, Griffin McElroy.
Can I get a shout?
Can I get a shout for the Dog Pound?
What's up, Dog Pound?
I know what you're thinking, oh no, we got shitty seats.
You actually got great seats.
We're not going to look at you the whole shit over.
But every once in a while, I'll indicate to you or acknowledge that you were there.
I'm going to expect something back.
A lot of love, as they say.
Now, audience one, I don't know.
Audience one, I want you to know, I want to say a lot of thanks to the Dog Pound.
You're still number one in my heart.
Don't forget about that.
That Justin, you can't trust that guy.
You and me, we got something special going on.
Dog Pound, you know what I mean.
Dog Pound, yeah!
How are you?
This is show number four for you.
Yeah, yeah, I crossed the river going, I'm halfway there.
You know, it is so weird seeing what it would be like to have an actual job.
Yeah.
I've done something.
Yes, because doing comedy podcasts.
Yeah, sitting down and jerking off for two hours.
Oh, man.
I can't imagine the jerking off for two hours.
It would be really exhausting.
Unproductive.
Should we, I guess we should.
And do like what we do with the show, like questions and stuff.
Well, I thought we might explain that we're going to take live questions probably.
We're going to run out of stuff to talk about.
So start thinking of things you might want to ask us up here.
Not about poopy.
Not about poop.
Not about sleeping with your best friend's girlfriend.
Not about asking for gas money.
Cover.
Otherwise, it's a fair game.
Have fun.
Get crazy.
Get it right, because if not, you will be mocked.
It will be bad.
You will feel bad about yourself.
You won't feel like all those rippers.
They were ribbing me.
You'll feel mocked.
And if you guys want any of the snacks on the table,
feel free to just come up and grab them, because the last show brought us trinkets.
We can't complain we got beers.
But somebody brought like a whole thing of cheer wine from Florida that they shipped here,
which is great.
I know.
It's the best marriage.
Start.
Jump in.
Begin.
Go.
I just finished my shows to each degree.
It said there to hold for applause.
Are these people that are here?
Yes.
This is Steve.
I didn't say, is Steve here?
Because I was afraid.
Steve, what's up, Steve?
Sorry I made an art sound about your degree.
And I'll be moving into an apartment closer to my new school this summer.
The problem is, I don't have any life skills.
I can't cook.
I don't know how to iron clothes.
And paying bills is a totally foreign concept to me.
Basically, I need whatever wisdom you three have on being an adult.
Steve, I want to know something, Steve.
I've got a real question for you, okay?
After you decided to sit in the front row, was there a moment when you were like, oh,
man, I've got a question.
I don't know shit about shit.
I'm going to have to sit before a council of my elders and admit my failings five feet
away.
Why isn't there like a website that's just like, when you graduate college, you get a
membership.
And it's like, here's how you pay a bill.
Here's how you do another thing.
Because that's supposed to be everything leading up to that moment.
It's fucking not, though.
I learned all about how to measure the volume of shapes or whatever.
But they don't teach you how to register to vote ever.
Ever.
Not once.
I learned what voting does.
I learned all about what a bill is, but I don't know how I participate in that conversation.
We had a life skills class where we had to create a budget, learn how to fill out a check,
which was a lot of fun.
We had to pick real estate from the book.
We went to the same fucking school, right?
We had a budget we had to live off of.
And you had to pick real estate, and you had to make a food list of things you're going
to buy for your family.
Fruit roll ups, fruit roll ups, fruit roll ups.
And everybody in my class was picking real estate out of the book that cost like $200,000,
$300,000.
Bolin!
These are some Bolin heists.
Yeah, they're Bolins.
And even at my young age, maybe this is when I decided to deviate from the pack, I'm a
young age, and I was like, you dumb motherfuckers, you don't really live there.
I bought the dandy duplex, it was called, and it cost me $20,000 imaginary dollars.
I didn't spend one goddamn day there because I was 11.
And I'm looking around at my fellow students like, we're 11.
You know they won't make you move into this fake house you bought with your imaginary
money, save it for the little debbies that you're not going to borrow with your imaginary
money.
But I did.
I budgeted a lot of little debbies.
People made fun of me for it.
I guess because maybe I got a reputation because I brought those in my lunch every day.
We got off-brand little debbies.
When I took that one, I remember playing that game.
Give it up for Star Crunches, everybody.
I remember playing that game in high school, and what happened to me was I got approved
for a loan for like the $200,000 house, and instead I got a $75,000 house and used the
rest to buy imaginary beds because I thought it was just free money.
And then the teacher explained to me that I'd have to pay that back, and I had to petition
the class to let me return the 150 animals I bought.
And as you can imagine, they were not forgiving.
You might have had it all wrong.
You may not have had a revenue stream, but you had a zoo.
Because I had a hundred of these stray dogs.
The worst fucking zoo ever.
It sounds like we all sort of subscribe to the blank Czech school of economics.
Yeah, what a bouncy castle.
I'm putting a water slide in my house.
Do you have any idea how much it costs to upkeep a bouncy castle?
No, I don't.
Steve, learn to cook five things.
Because by the fifth day, you'll be ready to eat the first thing again.
So anybody who knows how to cook more than five things is just showing off.
I'm at the point in my life where Tuesday is tostada night, and I gained a lot of security
from that.
It's not as scary as I thought it would be when I was younger.
You know, it gives me a lot of comfort.
At least there's tostadas.
At least I have something to look forward to.
We'll always have tostadas.
I mean, yes.
One brief shining moment, and it's black and white.
I just can't put up with the new Tuesdays are coming.
Ah, sweet tostada Tuesday.
If I can just hold out until tostadas.
The light shines in my dark prison cell life for 15 minutes a day.
But Tuesdays are coming.
Okay.
I am getting a somewhat dirty look from Saltwater's co-host, Cindy Mackerel.
So I do want to acknowledge that, yes, I do understand you're seven months pregnant.
I am definitely looking forward to that in addition to tostada night.
Basically even though.
Ladies, the tostadas.
These go back and forth.
How can you ask them to choose?
You can actually learn to cook really easy by buying a slow cooker.
You put anything.
Put a bunch of shit in it.
Just put a bunch of shit in it.
And then make rice.
And put the shit from the pot onto the rice.
Dinner is done.
It's figured.
That's how I make my tostadas.
Listen, everybody I'm going to let you in on both tostadas.
See your dog pound.
You know what's up.
You put.
You get chicken.
Hold on.
So I need a pen.
I'll tell you what happens.
Chicken dinners.
Put them in a slow cooker.
A little cumin, oregano, salt, pepper, garlic.
And then you dump a jar of salsa on top of it.
On high for two hours in a slow cooker.
You are going to have tostadas.
So Steve, I hope that answers your question about how to make tostadas.
How do I make tostadas?
Are you going to make one?
Perfect.
We did great.
Good job.
Ten out of ten.
Are there white cables?
So what else do you need help with?
Cooking is covered.
How to iron.
Take a hot thing and smooth it out.
But don't do it wrong or else it will fuck it up forever.
You just got to keep moving.
Don't wait.
Oh, ruined.
Steve, life hack.
Don't iron anything.
Hang it up in the shower.
Turn the shower on full blast.
Close the bathroom door.
Twenty minutes later everything is steaming clean.
Doesn't actually work.
You know what's up.
You can also just throw it in the dryer with a damp washcloth.
It does the same thing.
So you forgot to empty the dryer so now everything is wrinkled?
No it's not.
Put a wet towel in there for ten minutes.
Oops.
It's all fixed.
This has been Steve's Life Hacks on Steam.
Because it's all this great podcast, they turn my life around and now I'm hacking your
life because they helped me so much pay it forward.
Are you doing okay by the way?
In the last record setch I revealed to Justin how I'm going to pay it forward in and he
said he was going to be sad for the rest of the day and I was worried about his podcast
because I was going to be sad for the rest of the day and he said he was going to be
sad for the rest of the day and I was worried about his podcast because I was worried about
his podcast because I was worried about his podcast because I was worried about his podcast
Edward Snowden's super hot.
I just wanna say, wouldn't it have been mind-blowing if Edward Snowden had walked around this whole time?
And that's what he sounds like, he was actually on our show, he's dangerous, I don't know.
I am Edward Snowden.
Oh, you're Edward Snowden.
I heard I had a...secret admirer.
Don't tell.
I want to contact him for acquaintances.
Never mind, I already know who they are.
I found their secrets in the internet.
What?
Sorry, I had a frog in my throat.
I love that Edward Snowden and Amelie were introduced so well.
We've been like one episode of each other and now they've fused into this.
We're very different.
I understand you, Snowden.
Sure.
Copyright, copyright.
Sorry, that's my bad.
That guy looks more like a Hollywood actor than a CIA agent.
Never mind.
He likes to have hearty shmuttering.
I don't even care what he does or say.
I just want to tie him up and do many things to him.
That's not an okay thing to say about anyone.
Personally...
I just want to tie him up and do stuff to him.
I think if you want to tie me up, you're more fair.
Well, the U.S. government has failed and no one can tie Snowden.
I know the secret way to untie every knot.
Hold on, hold on.
They cannot tie me.
Does Snowden know all secrets?
I know all secrets.
Ask me anything.
Tell me about the secret McDonald's video.
That is in the previous episode.
Continuity.
That's the continuity for people at home.
Nobody in the theater that we're performing for right now.
Personally, how do you rate his looks from 0 to 10?
0 seems super fucking harsh to apply to any...
That's like you don't have any body at all.
When I look at your face, it's just a gray mass.
It's just a blob.
I'm a chevin.
Strong, strong chevin.
So hush, Snowden journalist.
You're in the right light with your 7.5.
The few cocktails.
Snowden can't do real.
He's not an eco maniac.
You're doing all right over there.
Wherever you are.
They say it's Russia, but that's a false flag.
That's a false flag.
I'm doing fine.
I would like to meet a special someone.
To keep him busy?
To let them meet the secrets.
To enjoy the secrets.
It must be really hard to...
I don't know.
Go on.
It must be hard to find someone that will let you in.
Because once they let you in...
You'll hack fucking everything about them.
Did you see that movie, Little Red Riding Hoodie?
It was emotional.
Not really.
Are you a vampire?
I am a vampire of secrets.
For real.
Right now there's a person in the audience who's looking at the person next to them.
What the fuck?
Why did you bring me to this, Jeff?
What is this, Jeff?
First the thing about the horse dissection and now this guy...
What is this guy even doing?
I've seen that cat on television.
That's not how he sounds.
I really have to pee.
I can't do that.
You've got to use this.
Next question.
I'm a professional writer.
Wait, did we cover it?
We covered it.
Covered is Snowden Haught?
Yeah, I think we covered it.
I'm a professional writer.
Over the years I, for the most part, developed a healthy attitude in regards to reviews and criticism.
But last November, a comic mini-series I wrote got a scathing review from a Mr. Clint McElroy.
Why would he...
And it haunts me still.
Why would he put this in the show?
How do I deal with criticism from your dad?
And that's where Chris Hastings...
Chris, are you here?
Hi, Chris.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Travis is the host.
Travis takes the hostess pose like her dad.
Listen, Chris, if you figure out how to deal with criticism from my dad, I hope you won't let me down.
Can you even get our dad off your job for a second?
Dad's not here yet, right?
No, en route.
En route, as they say.
He was texting a lot of pictures of himself driving, so we'll see if...
You know, who the fuck is he?
What's he done with his life that's so great?
I mean, us.
God, that's a toughie, because normally you'd just be like, fuck that guy.
Or like, whatever.
Or like, live your life.
He's our dad.
Maybe you should just listen to him.
Maybe it was like, weak.
Not weak, but maybe it had elements that could be polished on down.
Like a bump sign chair.
Like a bumpy chair?
Was your comic like a bumpy chair?
Maybe you should just listen to our dad, whatever he said.
How odd.
Great points now.
This is a man who thought Man from Hunkle was a really sweet show.
You know what you could do?
You could criticize his comic books that he made.
And really turn the tables on him.
If you could find the comic adaptation of Freejack...
He fucking ghost wrote that, you can't say that out loud.
Oh, shit.
I'll say the comic of Universal Soldier.
If you find the comic adaptation of Universal Soldier...
Was that also ghost written?
That was Clint McElroy's drawing.
We gotta fucking edit...
None of you can tell...
We're fucked.
What else?
What else can't we tell them about?
Well, he made Green Hornet Dark Tomorrow, which was the alternate universe Green Hornet.
Where Green Hornet was of Asian descent and Kato was white.
And that was the only choice.
That was like how he put this script?
No, that was just one of the things that was in the thing.
And he did one about vampire hunters?
Blood is the Harvest.
I guarantee you can have some weak shit in Blood is the Harvest.
The title of it is Blood is the Harvest.
Yes, right there.
That was not his title.
It was about two vampire bounty hunters named Deep and Wide.
And I'm pretty sure he was gonna go with that.
Fuck you guys.
This is a pretty good comic book.
Who the fuck are you?
Where's your comic book?
Not you Chris, but the rest of us.
Where's your comics?
Dick shits.
Talk about my dad.
You're real confrontational.
You're real excited.
Real excited.
It's gonna be like Lenny Bruce shit in here.
The guy seemed angry at me.
Is that Bill Hitz? No, it's me.
It's all to my dad.
I'm trying to remember if my dad's ever like genuinely criticized us for shit before.
No, dad's problem is always he's too supportive.
So he would say like, yeah, you can be active.
You're great at football.
Fucking sober not great at football.
I guarantee.
You try to stick with wrestling, it's gonna take off.
Didn't ever really see that.
Justin, you good enough at acting that you should spend your college career majoring in acting?
What's four years?
This is the craziest thing.
I remember in high school, dad saying it's too bad you gave up on wrestling.
Because now with your Bill, now?
You'd be so good.
For half of a second, I would go, hey.
And I'd go, oh no, wait, right.
I wrestled two years and never won a single match.
So maybe it's just a no.
Then you wrestle like a sickly boy.
I beat a kid with a flu once.
But I count that as a tie.
Really?
Did you get the flu afterwards?
No, I didn't, so I guess I win.
Next question.
How about you?
Please.
Which one of these are we gonna have?
That one.
Yeah, do it.
This one's sent in by Ira Ray.
Are you Ira Ray?
Who wants to know?
Fucking yeah!
You nailed it.
Don Power, I didn't know if you guys did it or not.
I wasn't looking at you, did you?
Perfect.
This was sent in by, or was asked by Jane2000.
Who asked?
Min.
Oh, God.
I just bumped a girl as an excuse to touch her.
Awesome, awesome.
Great, great, great, great.
Cool life, cool life you have.
You can't hug, yet it's too much.
And shaking hands is too formal.
Is it an excuse to touch a girl?
We're the worst.
We're the fucking worst.
Just dudes?
Here's the thing, though.
Dude, are there any dudes in here today?
No, they're all quiet.
I don't know.
This seems like a trap.
Good instinct, dudes.
There has to be at least one dude, though, that has like,
Hey, this is my girl.
Never watch this.
It's everything I dreamed it would be.
Her knuckles are so soft.
Give me a petri dish.
Fuck, this is just the worst.
I don't have anything to say about this except it's the worst.
I'm sorry.
Oh, wait, hold on.
I mean, so many answers.
All the time, it gets my heart pounding.
Yahoo Answers, take action against this user immediately.
Where are the moderators?
Just swoop in like Batman.
No, too creepy.
Get out.
You've been bounced from Yahoo.
If you get bounced from Yahoo Answers for being too creepy,
do you even like move into the woods or something?
Because you may not.
Don't do that.
Fellas.
How do you sleep at night?
Touching is so overrated, you know?
Yeah, I'd rather just yell at a girl from a car.
If you have to say...
I'm just trying to make a connection.
If you ever have to say the words in sequence,
excuse to touch someone.
You fucked up somewhere along the way.
Yeah, somewhere by the haywire.
Because they'll know.
Oh, no.
You can tell from a fist bump of somebody that wants to touch you,
it will creep you out through your fists.
And I guarantee you,
any woman who has ever had that trick pulled on her
has had this expression on her face.
To be fair, I feel like that's how anyone should react
when someone goes, fist bump?
Yeah.
You want to punch my face?
Because it's not 1971 anymore.
I feel like any fist bump or high five,
I actually extend this to high five,
where you have to say,
what is going to happen to me in this?
Hey Pat, let me have this with you.
No, it's got to be...
You will know when it's time to high five,
and both people will know.
They will understand that a high five is coming.
This situation calls for it.
If you say it aloud, you are forced to say it.
No question.
But it could be a courtesy thing,
because what if you go for a five and they go for a bump?
You smack them in the face.
High five.
And you punch me in the stomach.
We're not friends anymore.
But I didn't get to touch you.
You got to give me that.
Because the other side of that is
if anyone ever fist bumped and the girl went,
now I'm in love with this boy.
I felt that magic spark.
Sorry to interrupt you live Justin.
Great spoofs, us.
We are nailing it.
We are...
This is so funny.
Actually, this was the second one?
Yeah, this was the weakest one.
No, I thought the next one was the weakest.
You all got some dog shit to look forward to though.
No, I'm just kidding.
They were all decent.
Thank you all for coming to those New York Shorts.
And thank you to everybody who came out to the LA Life Show.
We're going to be parsing these out a little bit
because we got travel plans and we don't want to go...
Babies coming.
Babies coming. We don't want to go a week without an episode.
So we're spacing these out.
We'll probably have another regular episode next week.
Sorry about the audio quality on this one.
I know it's not ideal, but we did our best.
The LA Life Show should be good though.
Should be so nice.
Let's get paid maybe?
Let's get paid at the Money Zone.
I know you've probably tried Hulu on your computer
sitting at your desk
while the boss is looking over your shoulder.
But it doesn't have to be a secret thing.
Why would the boss be looking...
If the boss was looking over your shoulder
at you watching Hulu, he would be very upset.
The boss is looking over your shoulder
because he missed South Park.
Okay.
Sounds like a pretty cool boss.
Yeah, he is a cool boss.
But you don't have to just do that.
There's something more than that.
You can take your relationship to a deeper,
bettering level with Hulu Plus.
That's like Hulu,
but it makes Hulu look like dog shit.
Whoa, don't say that.
Whoa, come on.
It's much better than Hulu.
You can watch an insane amount of television.
Parks and Recreation is on there.
Here's one.
Fox canceled my hit TV series,
I Want to Marry Harry.
You son of a bitch.
How could you watch this?
But Hulu's like, give us your poor,
give us your tired, give us your hungry.
We'll put that whole series up online.
No problemo.
There's like a billion seasons of Survivor
and Amazing Race we've been digging through.
They just added Top Chef too.
Nice.
Block off a day to binge.
Get in there, watch it all for eight bucks a month.
Anytime, anywhere.
iPad, Roku,
Xbox, whatever.
Goku from Dragon Ball Z.
There are over 9,000 TV programs on Hulu.
Vegeta.
Gohan.
Super Saiyan Gohan.
I mentioned eight bucks a month.
That's actually not for you.
You're too special for that.
You are gonna get a two week free test run.
Piccolo.
If you go to HuluPlus.com slash my brother,
we're gonna get you two weeks of access completely free.
You can try it out, watch a bunch of shows,
and then realize that your life has been missing
this entire time.
HuluPlus.com slash my brother.
That's HuluPlus.com slash my brother.
Man, that was a great ad, Griffin.
We're gonna have a lot of fucking sweet money
coming in from that.
Frankly, I don't know what to do with it.
Yeah, they're gonna pay us a lot of extra money
because of how fucking sweet a job we do
at HuluPlus.
I have an idea, though.
I think we should go to Simple
because Simple's apparently the best bank ever.
It's the way banking should be.
They took banking and they said,
this thing's fundamentally fucked.
Let's start over, start from scratch.
Imagine, if you will, a checking account
with no minimum balance, no monthly fee,
no overdraft charge.
No fucking checks.
55,000 fee-free ATMs.
You can deposit checks with a photo
and you can spend without it being stressful
and terrible.
Money can be fun again.
Fun money.
Thank God.
Money is back.
Money is back in a big way for 2014.
People thought I got done with money for a while,
but money is back.
Money, Simple lets you save automatically
so you can tell it I have a goal
and it will help you reach that goal
because it cares about you
and it wants you to be happy.
Just like Gohan helped Goku reach his goal
of becoming the ultimate Super Saiyan warrior.
I don't think we can do that.
Okay.
Simple.com, you know what was nice?
I'm a Simple customer myself.
I signed up and I sent a message to them
because I had a question
and they just responded in the app.
It was not even a big deal.
They just chatted right back with me.
It's super nice.
They can pay your bills.
It's like a real bank.
They're not just going to take your money
and put it in their butts
and then fly to Cuba or something.
The thing is so popular
that there's a waitlist right now,
but we can help you get past it.
How can we do that?
Simple.com slash my brother.
Go there.
Go get your banking right.
Wait till you get your money right with Simple.
That's the new thing I've been working on for them.
The jingles are back also in a big way,
just like money.
Hey, Jacqueline.
Jacqueline.
Yes, you Jacqueline.
Got a message for you from Brendan
who says,
Hey, Jacqueline.
You sure did graduate, didn't you?
By the time this reaches you,
we'll be living in a sweet new house.
I'm so stupid lucky to be able
to come home to you all the time.
So much love.
That's usually what we think
is something funny to say here,
but that just sounds like a nice situation
you have going on over there.
Jacqueline, you're nailing it.
Jacqueline's doing really good.
Got a sweet,
I don't know the nature of the relationship,
but I'm just going to say lover.
Got a sweet lover in Brendan.
Got a new diploma.
Got a new house.
I bet it's a real big,
maybe like 2600 square foot ranch style house
Oh, that sounds like a white picket fence.
White picket fence.
Somewhere that's green.
Got another message for Will.
Congratulations, Jacqueline.
Yes, so proud.
Got a message from Will Lilspoon Barley.
Love it.
That's Will Lilspoon Barley
from Jeff and Jesse.
Presumably they're the big spoons.
Congratulations.
One of them has to be the biggest spoon, right?
One of them is the largest.
One of them is the soup spoon.
Congratulations to Dr. William Lilspoon Barley
on receiving his Ph.D.
Will channeled the power of his favorite
warrior cat Bramblepelt
to finish his dissertation.
Thanks to the Brothers McElroy
for helping Will become a fake doctor.
Starting this fall, he'll be a professor
at the University of Illinois,
so might provide some future
farm wisdom.
I have so many questions
about his whole scene.
Did he get like a Ph.D.
in agriculture?
Yeah, I think maybe there was a missing bit
of information there that would
inform that, because I don't know
why being a professor
in Illinois would inherently
make it,
you know, make you more likely
to come up with farm wisdom.
I think if you're in the agriculture business
and your last name is Barley,
that's a pretty fucking good start.
Yeah, you're like halfway there.
I'm Dr. Jack Carrot.
My name is Dr. Jack Carrot.
Hi, I'm Dr. Jack Lettuce, and I'm here to
teach you about how to get
sweet vegetables from the ground.
The top gains. I'm gonna blow out your lettuce
with sweet gains.
I'm also the creator of Farmville.
So, congratulations, William.
And thank you for listening to our program.
And now we're gonna head back
to live us
and Travis
back when he was alive.
I miss him.
Miss you, sweet boy.
Uh...
I need a fucking palette cleanser is what I need.
Does anyone in the audience
have a question?
Yeah, come on down.
Do you remember the criteria?
We explicitly outlined the criteria.
Do you understand the fucking dangerous game
you're playing?
Every time you call someone up, it is the scariest...
It's the most dangerous game.
It will get savage.
Hey, guys.
We will savage you if you fuck this up.
No pressure.
Now, don't be shy. Get up close to the mic.
Yeah, I actually did get up close.
Okay, too close.
So, my roommate and I just moved in to a new place.
Okay.
And we found the last person's checkbook.
Oh!
Actually, you found Will!
You've come to the right place.
How much do I take?
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Whoa, criminal!
I thought the question was going to be like,
what's the easiest way to get back to them?
Is there information on this checkbook?
I can use to locate this person.
Here's the thing. You're going to need to write $1,000,000.
I didn't get your name.
Sam.
Okay, so you're going to blank check it, right?
Yeah, right.
Let me figure this out.
Just write $1,000,000,000.
Okay, here's what I want you to do.
Give another friend.
Sit on their shoulders.
Put a checkbook on them.
And go to the bank.
I'm a nice little tall man with a very big heart.
I'd like to withdraw $1,000,000,000.
Please.
I think you're in prison for fraud.
I would like to turn this into this mini, please.
Hello, I'm a grown up.
And I would like to exchange this for a deposit half.
Yes, my name?
Herschel?
Grown up.
That's me.
Can you ransom the checkbook off?
That's the thing.
Don't write any checks because that's illegal.
But ransom is...
You can sell it to...
You're not a bad person.
You're not going to write a bad check.
But you could sell it to a worse person.
You seem like the kids.
$30, please.
You could also just make the check out
for a non-money denomination.
But try to cash this person's check for like one hug.
And then the video goes viral.
I don't have that sense.
This man asked for a hug with a check.
You won't believe what happened next.
He didn't get it.
He did not get it.
He was arrested.
That's not how checks work.
You're just looking for an excuse to touch me.
Nice try.
I turned you down for a Facebook video.
Why do you think...
Let's have a...
Here, let's go less answer, more intervention.
Okay.
Don't commit this crime.
Sam, no.
Sam, everything is working for you right now.
You got a room and a place to live.
You can't jeopardize your future like this.
Let me throw this out.
Take these checks.
Make a framed collage.
They're just account numbers.
When friends come over, you want all yours.
You can use whatever you want.
Take the account information.
You're saying you give these checks out like party check.
Yeah, you just hand them out.
Let them tear one off as they leave.
Here's your check.
Rather than being the victim of identity theft,
you want them to be caught in some sort of
insane psychosexual web
where hundreds of strangers
have access to their checking account.
That'll be more palatable.
How do I monetize that, though?
That's a fucking fine question, Sam.
It's not a question.
It's not even a question.
It's a paper chase.
Life is so much bigger than forged checks.
There's so much more out there for you than that.
You could go through,
if they balance their book,
you could look at all the purchases they made
and then go out in the world and make all those purchases
and win a day in their lives.
And just tally Mr. Ripley up.
Yeah.
Well, spoilers.
In a way.
Sam, thank you so much for joining us.
Do we have any more?
More questions?
We've got a hot question right here.
Come on up.
This is favoritism.
Hey, how's it going?
My name is Brent.
Hi, Brent.
Well, I have a little big problem
and a little big problem.
It sounds like the audience is angry.
They sound like they're saying, oh.
I get it.
Small problem.
You know the criteria.
Yeah, I do.
Small problem and a big problem.
Small problem, I could really use a Pepsi Max.
That's the first problem we've ever solved!
Yeah!
Big problem.
I have a magically cute dog.
Now let me explain.
This dog needs exercise.
He's five months old.
He needs to expend the energy
so he's not aggressive around the house.
He's magically cute.
I can't make it one block
without the foot traffic of New York City
stopping to make a comment
and make me feel obligated to not keep walking
because he's so fucking cute.
What do I do?
I make either myself or my dog
more standoffish
or more unapproachable.
You're doing it great.
Thank you.
Come on, we're pals.
Wait, it's fine.
We're going to have to ugly your dog up.
Can you buy the dog Uggs?
Like mini Uggs?
You understand that Ugg
doesn't stand for ugly, right?
Women don't wear Uggs
to be like, I need to ugly myself up
and stop trying to fist bump.
I don't know, have you ever seen Uggs?
I got to go to the bathroom.
Holy shit, it's actually happening.
Brent, you want to hop in here?
No way.
You can advise yourself.
This is my friend.
We've done a bunch of live shows.
I thought, what if I have to pee
in the middle of a live show?
You got to make sure Brent's there.
Pressure's on.
Pack your bags, move away.
I don't care.
His question was boring.
I just want the Pepsi Max.
The Yahoo answer.
I got to say, this is kind of weird.
Totally.
It's asked by Jacob Locker.
What are you going to do when Justin gets back?
Just sigh and walk away.
Thank you, Jacob Locker.
It's asked by Yahoo.
She has 1%.
According to this,
Are you sad for someone on Yahoo?
She has negative 47 points this week.
It's a bad week for Jim.
She should find a different social media platform.
Fuck, he's already back.
This has been a pleasure, you guys.
See you later.
Do you want to talk about it?
Not much to say, my man.
Just to catch you up,
We're doing a Yahoo answer.
This one was sent in by Jacob Locker.
It's asked by Yahoo answer.
Then we made some jokes about
She's not very good at Yahoo answers.
Then everybody laughed.
It was a really great moment.
Is this like that bit in That Thing You Do?
It's really clicking with this new guy.
We did.
You already did with That Thing You Do bit.
What if my fianc gets an erection during our ceremony?
I am 35 and my fianc is 38.
Wait, hold on. Stop.
I'm going to stop you right there.
Why do their ages come into play in this class?
Before we go on,
I want to talk about erections and our ages.
I thought I liked 35.
Erectioned out.
I did.
I am 35 and my fianc is 38.
Our wedding is set for October.
Okay, here's the issue.
I love that.
Here's some groundwork.
Now let's go.
He gets erections very easily.
I am not complaining.
I can't believe you have such a low Yahoo score.
This is a very titillating question.
Was there no wink? No winky face?
No, there's not.
But I have to admit, it feels like I am dating a teenage boy sometimes.
Even if he just holds my hand,
he will often sport a noticeable erection.
So she's checking.
It's kind of unavoidable.
It can be a little awkward not to mention
when he walks around the house naked sporting one.
Okay, that live part was fucking unnecessary.
It was pretty bad.
I didn't cut that out for the event.
I am just wondering how to handle this
at the wedding and reception.
He is nervous too. Any tips?
I am just worried.
When he gets all the erections.
It can take a long time for it to go down.
I am sure people will snicker and take pictures.
Which would be good for him.
Ow! A nice boner, Jerry!
Quick, quick!
You hurt everyone!
Jerry's boner!
Idiot!
Meemaw, did you see his boner?
Jerry, you idiot!
All I can think is that it sounds like
this is a pretty defining characteristic.
Yeah.
Anyone at the wedding is going to be surprised.
Meemaw is like, oh no, it's his boner.
Yeah, we all know.
What are you going to do?
I am going to be honest.
The ceremony wasn't perfect.
But it felt like you.
If he didn't get a boner,
we will be like, who's wedding is this?
It was your story.
Your story wasn't, you look beautiful.
And Jerry had a boner.
I noticed that's what rocked
the hardest don.
His don was hard.
That's your truth.
I thought it was so fun
the groundwork to
maintain.
But it doesn't matter.
It didn't stop that.
The surface of the boner
just ripped right through that comfort bone.
You know the beast is loose.
Your hair looked perfect.
His vows.
The vows of the boner also.
I did want to mention again,
we all had a great time.
Listen.
You are going to kiss,
assumedly, at the end of the ceremony
there's a smooch.
And if touching hands, if fist bumping your wife
is enough to take the bones out.
Like a smooch?
Wait, hold on. There's a bigger problem
here that this man needs to live his life
like the boy in the bubble.
Like any physical contact.
You know what I mean?
Maybe he just needs to live at home.
I was happy he was getting married.
Because it takes a very certain kind of person
and that's the one.
Yes, forever.
That's fantastic.
Well, she's not complaining.
She listened.
Don't look a gift horse in the mouth.
Or the super just awesome boner.
Yeah, that'd be rough, man.
I don't really have any questions about horses.
It's weird, right?
It is weird.
Does anyone here own a horse?
I want to talk about it.
Like owning a horse in town?
Has anyone here touched a horse?
Dog pound?
You ever touch a horse?
Tell us what horses feel like.
Is that what we're doing?
It's our new segment.
What do horses feel like?
Are you ready?
I've been saving this one.
I live in New York City, obviously.
And walk anywhere.
Because nobody would come from out of the city
to see his show.
Who came from an hour away?
This is fun.
Raise your hand.
Who came from two hours away?
I think in New York everything is two hours away.
Three hours?
Four?
Three and a half?
Five?
How long do we make this game?
Anyone, six hours.
Find me after the show
and I'll give you one item from my wallet.
I live in New York City
and walk anywhere from 20 minutes to two hours a day
thanks to my community.
No matter what kind of shoes I'm wearing,
socks or tights,
I have bits of city grit in my shoes,
annoying me until I can find a discrete moment
to clean them out.
The worst is when I get stuck in a situation
where it's not socially acceptable
for hours on end to escape and rectify the situation.
It happens most often with my dress shoes,
so I'm frequently stuck
in a work meeting or at a fancy event
with bits of debris
making me nuts with every step.
Does this happen to everyone?
Is New York City just extra grimy?
Am I just bad at wearing shoes?
What can I do to help?
And that's from Barefoot in Brooklyn.
Are you here?
Do you have shit in your shoes right now?
Is that why you almost fell down?
Dump your shoe grit on our table.
Let us examine this.
We'll find an origin point for each.
Now, not you, but everybody else who lives in New York,
please raise your hand if this is an issue.
No, clap!
People at home can't hear hands raised.
There were approximately 18 hands.
So this is the thing.
You have come to the wrong place.
I don't know.
The only thing we worry about getting in our shoes
at West Virginia is four-leaf clovers
or friendly smiles.
I mean, it's a very different world.
A mess.
A light mess.
A missile of a mess.
I feel like in New York
they could build
on every other street
corner
like a foot-washing station
and then
those would work for that express purpose
for maybe four minutes.
And then they themselves
would be so covered in grit
and small rocks
that you would be unable to use them
for foot cleansing.
This is great because I love an opportunity
to come to a city
and then talk shit about it.
You all got dirty-ass feet!
I love it.
Big Apple dreams.
Broadway dreams.
And gross-ass feet.
What are you doing?
You wear boots and still just by the end of the day
it's like a small
gravel playground.
In your shoes.
Don't you have anything else to say?
I'm sorry. Move?
What's your walking?
Do you do a lot of foot scoops
or walking gait?
What's your gait?
Can you come down for a second?
This is creepy in a way.
Come on down and walk in front of us.
Yeah, come walk so we can...
Yes, come down here.
Oh, I've seen enough.
You're scooping stair debris.
So just start
over here and kind of walk.
I want to see if I can figure out the problem.
We have to explain to everybody at home
that she is wearing like three-foot
tall shoes.
Is the grit like throwing grappling hooks
up your shoes?
We must reach.
They should be velcro-sealed.
They're open? Okay, so let me see.
I don't know.
But I will say this, a confident gait.
I do like a confident gait. Very hot.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Between these two,
this one or this one,
what do you more into?
I would say the first one.
How about this one was sent by Ira Ray?
Do you want to do it again?
No.
Are you Ira Ray?
Who wants to know?
Are we getting royalties from that dude?
The person who wrote the original song
who nobody can remember the name of.
James Ray?
What's his name?
Jimmy Ray.
Right there on the tip.
In the song.
This young dude next to me
was asked by somebody whose fucking account
was deleted. I'm so sorry everybody.
They asked,
trampoline sex?
With like
twelve question marks.
These people are fast to know.
Is it safe to have sex on a trampoline?
I have a friend who's tried it.
Can I just say real quick,
this person just shook their head really like,
no. No sir.
Absolutely not.
It's fine, but I wanted to make sure
I really don't want the embarrassing increase.
That's a good point,
because if somebody gets up there and is like,
ha, popcorn!
That's probably a plus too hard.
Your partner bounces up twelve feet.
Can we all talk about like,
clap if you've been on a trampoline
in the past year.
Awesome lives
you guys are living.
The fabric of trampolines
is the worst.
When you bounce and accidentally do a knee bounce
and you come up and your knees don't, it's just bone.
Can you imagine
trying to like...
Well people die on trampolines
normally.
That's without the introduction of bits.
Yeah.
I'm just talking about bit related
injuries.
There's so many springs.
You get a bit
caught in one of them.
Kill me! Kill me!
No, it's just the worst!
If I got a bit in that spring...
I want to be dead!
I would start like a
lobbyist group
to get trampolines banned from life.
I used to be a confident young man
getting boners all the time.
The plot of
Superman 7 is that he gathers
all the trampolines and he
throws them into the sun.
Sorry about your ruined bit.
I feel like if you're having
sex on a trampoline, there is a chance
that you can get a rhythm going and be like,
wow, this guy is great.
There's a chance that you can balance
inopportune moments and break it up.
Dog Pound
Dog Pound knows what I'm talking about.
You're a
f**k, Simon.
They f**ked on a trampoline this morning.
You know how a Dog Pound
does?
I need myself
in the face on a trampoline once in a
while.
I can understand why you wouldn't want to introduce extra
solo. This was solo
mission.
He was just maximally
into it.
We used to play a game
where you stand in a circle
on the outside of the trampoline.
You put a tennis ball on it and it would bounce you
and you have to dodge the tennis ball.
Can you somehow have sex while doing that?
I guess my question is,
why do you do that?
How are you guys doing?
I forgot y'all
were here.
What else we got? We got anything else? It's time to wrap it up.
We can do one more. Do you want to do one more?
Audience questions.
Who's got a super quick question?
Anybody?
Dog Pound!
First off, this person is going to tell us what horses feel like.
What horses feel like? You said you touched one.
So, so smooth.
Grab a seat there.
What's your name?
I would say Ghost Life.
Your name is Ghost Life.
Pete.
I was wondering if I could get a picture
of all your Triforce tattoos.
Travis is going to take his shirt off, but otherwise...
Which I am totally open to.
Can we do that after the show?
Or can we do it during the show? Let's take a vote.
No.
After.
I mean, I can just pull a boob out.
You were voting for after.
Okay.
Pete, did you have a query to help you with that?
Or was it just the tattoos?
Other than that, your life is going great.
That's the biggest problem.
You're at 99.9% if only you could see my boob.
And get a picture with it important.
Could I flip it on?
Are you going to flip it?
Is it going to be Saturn after we're done with sex?
No, I already got my trampolines.
Perfect.
I'm going to be skilled today.
Maybe just towards Justin.
If you have a question for me.
I have three kids.
I was just wondering if you had any advice.
Pete, that's a good question.
Is there anything that you would like to know?
Give me the number one piece of pairing advice
that I can then steal,
re-appropriate,
put on a t-shirt,
and steal.
He's looking.
To be clear.
One piece of pairing advice.
Five words that are applicable.
Now.
Sex.
I know we're talking about babies,
but sexy maybe?
Number one piece of pairing advice.
Pete, give me.
Put me on the spot.
To be fair, Pete,
you walk down and sat in the chair.
You sat in the chair, Pete.
Now you do your time.
Pairing advice, Pete. Give it to me.
Don't even think about it. You're overthinking.
They're not my problem.
I'm theirs.
Yes!
Pete out!
I'll be honest. I was worried
that anybody would be able to ride to the occasion.
Pete,
you rock and nail it. Dog power.
Dog power.
How are those beers?
They're still good.
And then he reveals himself.
Pete was the hero of the show.
Pete's the hero of the show.
Pete saved it.
Pete saved the show.
Valuable.
Okay.
Folks, we are done.
I want to get a final question from Griffin,
but first I want to thank
People's Improv Theater.
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you all.
Thank you
New York for coming to our show.
On your way out,
make sure to stop by. We got a bunch of new merch
specifically for this show.
So make sure you check it out.
It's the fucking dopest.
Awesome patches.
These button packs.
The patch says Fraternal Order of Brothers,
which is actually really funny.
Thank you. I was pretty proud of it.
Amongst all these buttons,
there's some real big winners.
One is a picture of Griffin's face with
I Ate All the Potato Chips on it.
It's like the fucking best face.
There's also an I Hate Sad Libs button.
So make sure to pick that one.
And an I Hate Sad Libs button.
Travis almost busted my mouth with it.
We were having trouble coming up with how to start the show.
I was going to do a Freestyle Sadler's Ride
where I just started a sentence.
He lied.
I hate you Ron.
The buttons are awesome.
We've got bumper stickers out there.
My other ghost is a horse.
My other horse is a ghost is one of those.
But we've also got these awesome tote bags.
And our posters are out there.
If nothing else,
stop by and grab one of these postcards.
It's got a coupon code on the back
that will give you 20% off if you buy the merch.
And I think you can only get these here.
Yeah, only here.
Don't tweet that code.
We will also be out there
after the show to meet and greet
and sign things.
For like 45 seconds.
All I want to ask
is just
keep it coming people.
I want to see all of you.
That's all I want to say.
I want to thank John Lauder.
I almost made it.
I got to get the last word.
Why am I just fondling
this banana?
Why am I fondling this banana
for like 5 minutes?
I want to say thank you to Sawbones.
Sawbones!
They're singing my show
ever.
I think those kids are going somewhere.
Thank you for giving
us a home.
Thank you to the theater.
Thank you to you all.
That's everybody.
Thank you, Meredith.
It's by Yahoo Answers.
I can't believe
it's another fucking time.
Mr. Gusty asks
does the movie Air Bud
paint an unrealistic picture of
even the most athletic dog's potential?
That's good.
I'm Preston Apple.
I'm proud to be here.
Thank you.