If you change your mind, on the first in line Honey I'm still free, take a chance on me
If you need me, let me know, gonna be around If you got no place to go when you're feeling down
If you're all alone, when the pretty birds have flown
It's time right now to slow it down, put a little soul in your bowl
If you want the very best in your life
That is correct
He has a new microphone
Do you like that? Do you like this people?
We decided the smartest thing to spend your money on that you bought the t-shirts is to put it back into My Brother, My Brother and Me
So it's like you're not lining our pockets, you're lining your ear meat
So we spent $300 on new microphones and the other $300 we're gonna spend to get Eddie Murphy on the show
For just one episode
Just one episode, guest spot, nothing off limits, no rules
You would think $300 wouldn't be enough to net a performance by Axel Foley but I guess he's falling on hard times
It's plenty to get for Pluto Nash
You know what I'm saying? Meet Dave Cash, those residuals just aren't what he hoped they would be
I don't understand why Hanan Mansion wasn't as big as I thought it would be
I'm Griffin McElroy by the way, you guys didn't let me
There's a reason
Look at Travis using the power of his microphone to silence others
That's right
What do you guys say we just chill this show?
Just take it easy right?
Just hang out
Yeah, let's do a couple easy questions first, some slow balls
First let me take off my pants, hold on
Okay
Thank God he has a new microphone that we can listen to it in perfect audio quality
Alright, ready to go
This is for FormSpring, I have a mane of hair that helps break the ice with nearly everyone I meet
Jesus man, what kind of product are you putting in your hair?
Hey, my drink is warmer than it was, you broke all my ice
Lots of people recognize me because of it
But I want a job, and looking the way I do, no one will employ me
Should I sacrifice popularity for a job or remain penniless yet cool?
There's nothing cool about being penniless
I've never seen a homeless man with a great head of hair
Yeah, no one's like, hey, the moths in your hair are really sexy, you seem like a cool guy
What is that, bubble gum? I like that, looks nice
In your nose? You're a hobo
Listen, I think there's a way to have your cake and eat it too
There have got to be jobs out there that you can find employ at while being so hirsute
You could join Rusted Root, you could become a permanent member of the band Rusted Root
You could work as a bouncer at your local hookah bar
You could become a barista at an independent coffee shop
No, they frown on that shit
They don't want your face pubes in a macchiato
How did this come from he has a big head of hair and he has face pubes?
I took it like a beard too
When he says mane, I'm thinking like a lion's mane going all the way around his head
You think when you read mane, it's like rapping beats
When you read mane, you think he's got a ring of hair around his head like a lion
Yeah, like a lion
How did you get to be as old as you are and not know what things are?
You don't know things that are things about them
You don't know the things
I don't leave the house that much
Justin, that kind of thing comes with a new microphone
That kind of clarity and understanding
My brother, my brother and me, what can I do to build my confidence
So I can go out there and meet some new ladies around my age
Or is focusing on school and work now, meeting someone if I'm lucky and okay strategy for the next couple of years
It's like I'm desperate for some action
I just wonder if I'm making a mistake by not going out there and making myself available
Kevin
Well, I hope that ladder strategy is a good one
I sure hope so
Do you think it's going to be like a pizza delivery girl?
I have these 24 buffalo wings that you ordered with extra blue cheese
Hey, you are cute
Nice tip, do you want to go on a date?
Blue cheese is my favorite too
Listen, Kevin, cut your fingernails, take the boards off the windows
Get out there, meet some people
Stop living, I am legend
Get out there
It's a sad fact of reality, Kevin
But here's the thing, okay
Maybe you are going to meet your special lady
Maybe you are going to be the kind of guy who just walks into a gas station one day and there she is
But statistically speaking, that somebody special is going to be a special somebody if you expose yourself to more members of the opposite sex
That's just science
Metaphorically
Don't really expose yourself, we don't want to be a party to that
You don't know you might meet a special someone in federal prison
Kevin, you got to get out there, you got to say hi
As far as building confidence goes, you got to not be afraid to fail
Unfortunately, it's not going to be a confidence builder right away, especially if you are not good at it
Just don't fail in front of anybody
Because that will be so embarrassing
Why don't you take her into a dark abandoned alley where no one can see and fail
That's a good opening line too
I'd like to take you, I'm about to hit on you, but I'd like to take you to a dark abandoned alley to do it in
Because I don't want anybody to see
That should be a pretty good ice breaker
It's no mane of hair as an ice breaker, but it is a pretty good one
I'll tell you this, you'll get a reaction every time and that's what you're looking for
Something will happen
You're just looking for a reaction
You can get strong by being constantly rejected, that's how some people would do it
Just build up that thick hide
Really, just scars across your heart
You could just walk up to girls randomly and say, no thanks
And then walk away
Say you're mass rejecting lots of girls without ever risking being rejected
Take it a step further, walk into a bar and announce at the top of your lungs
I don't want to sleep with any of you
Walk through it and then walk out
Sorry ladies, off limits
They will flock to you as you leave the bar
Get a t-shirt that says, sorry ladies, off limits
I bet that t-shirt would work for you
I bet that would work
Young man, just use your test submission
You two work it out
Travis, go
I was just going to say, there was a comedian once who said the best way to get a woman to sleep with you
Is to walk in and tell her that you are bad at sex
So I was just going to say, approach women and say
I am awkward and uncomfortable and don't know how to talk to women
And just lead with that
That's my advice, go Griffin, go
Yahoo Answers user Tessa Mission asks
Oh this was sent in by a Twitter user Mr. D Muffin
So thank you Mr. D Muffin
Tessa Mission asks, when I move out I want to adopt a whole family from Ethiopia
I have a heart for starving children and I'm about to move out
I'm getting a 149 acre home and I plan to have a farm
But I would like to help a family out and adopt a whole family
And build them their own little house on my land
And share a little bit of land for them
I was wondering if they would let me take them out of their country without a passport or
Yeah, that's how it works
You need to make sure you poke holes in the box
Yeah, I'm pretty sure what you just described was light slavery
Mild slavery
Just maybe a little, a touch of slavery
That's like, you just described like the PG-13 edited for TV version of Roots
No, I just want to adopt this family from another nation
Are you with me so far?
They can live on my, I wouldn't call it a plantation, but it is plantation sized
A fun-tation
A fun-tation, sure
I don't grow any crops yet
But I'm thinking about getting in the crop game
You know it would be handy if they wanted to help out
What kind of crops?
Room and board
Oh, textiles
Textiles?
Mostly
So they're going to be picking felt
Felt, hemp, stuff along those lines
I'm going to build them a house though
Not a big house
More like a room
But not a small house, right?
Not tiny
And I imagine when I adopt them, at first they'll be really scared
Because they're not going to know what's going on
They may resist even
But you know, I think eventually they'll appreciate the fulfillment
A fulfilling day of work can provide
So yeah, so lady, you don't have a heart for starving children
You are a slave master
You're a slave master
That is illegal, what you just described
It's the warm feeling she gets from the terrified looks on their faces
That's all the payment she needs
Is it okay
And their free labor
Is it okay to pee in the bathroom sink if you're drunk?
I ran the faucet for a while, if that helped
Okay
Read the last
Peace
Read it all together
Making sure that you add that last word
Because it really makes it
Is it okay to pee in the bathroom sink if you're drunk?
I ran the faucet for a while, if that helped
Peace
Nick
I am
Before I answer your question
I am put off by the change of tense
In the middle of your question
Because you went from like
Right after the question mark
And then are retroactively asking our forgiveness
That's the context to me
That's the hidden meaning between the lines
Or the question marks in this case
He didn't pee in my bathroom sink though
So he has nothing to
He has nothing to ask forgiveness for
That's a good question, are you peeing in your own bathroom sink?
Or like the bathroom sink at a bar
Because that's not okay
I'm sure if we did a silent canvas
Of the three people on this podcast
We could probably find
One person who has peed
In the bathroom sink
On a regular basis
Not anymore, but used to
You're thinking just one?
Oh Jesus
Statistically speaking, at least one person on this podcast
At least one
Definitely less than three
We
Okay, I think that
I have to ask this question
What is the compulsion for peeing in the sink?
It's just there and you're just like
Especially when you've been drinking
I don't know if you're like
Throwing off society's rules
Or just saying you're your own man
And you pee where you want
I mean, it's a pretty sucky revolution
Because it's still like going on the same spot
So you're not exactly
You know
They're not making post avoid signs about it
Yeah, I mean it's kind of
It has to be an act of rebellion
You think it is, not a good one
Not like a super rebellious one
Just clean it up afterwards
He ran the faucet if it helps
I think what we've agreed on is it's not okay
To pee in the sink if you're drunk
But if you're sober, it's totally cool
Yeah, I just want it to be a choice
Hey guys, I'm in love with my best friend of two years
And I'm not sure if she likes me back
Any advice?
You should move away
Move away, change your name
Or I got an alternate
How about this?
Ask her
Pussy
Just
Why would you ask her pussy?
We need to get the punctuation straight in that sentence
Ask her pussy or
Ask her pussy
Now, get a defining rod
No
And I say that
I call you
That name, which I shouldn't be using
Female genitalia as a slang term
I'm gonna say wimpo
What about wiener?
Ask her wiener
Stop being a wiener and ask her wiener
I say that with love
She's your best friend two years
That's at one thirty fifth of your life
Statistically speaking
How about you just ask her and either get to Frenchin
Or beat cheeks out of there
And keep this in mind, when you ask her
And if she says no
You do have to move away
So there's your answer
Now do me a favor and stop listening so I can give everyone else an answer
She doesn't like him
No, that's not true
If after two years he doesn't know
If she likes him back
Dude's shy
Listen, form spring dude, just ask her
Trust me
Cause that's gonna be the best day ever
If it works
If we were her mom
Ask her mom if she likes him
Yahoo Answers user
Gally McClarr
Nah
You just wanna go ahead and
That's not a name
No, the name is David
David asks
Does a woman ever love a stalker?
A stalker
Who stalks 24-7
From childhood to adulthood
For five long years
Wait, what?
Yeah, there are layers
Whoa, there are many things happening here
I am uncomfortable with
Wait, is there more to the question?
There are additional details that say
I mean from teen to adult age
So I would say
Maybe
And also my delete key is broken so I can't edit
That thing I said just a second ago
16 to 21, I'll say
Okay
But here's the thing
I'm gonna put it in this shit and kick it down another level
Incept it
I'm gonna incept it
Is this the stalker asking the question?
Or is it the stalkie?
Oh my god
You just blew my mind
My mind is blown, you think that maybe she's like
Listen
I don't wanna give everybody the wrong idea about stalking
But sometimes
It works
Like maybe
Yeah, maybe she actually kinda likes this dude
That she sees occasionally going through her trash
But she doesn't know if it's okay to like him
She hated
And hated it and was scared of it
And couldn't stand it and then
After years of it
It's not that she loves it
She's used to it, it's like the new Arcade Fire album
You just
Wait and wait and wait and eventually
You get him
And finally you get this stalker
You understand where he's coming from
You just gave me an idea
If I ever stalk someone
I'm gonna put on a giant raccoon suit
Before I start going through their trash
That buys me like 20 minutes
Honey, honey
Honey, don't move
Don't move, but look out the window
They can smell fear
That ring-tailed bastard
Hey, I've wanted braces for a couple of years now
And have finally gone to the orthodontist
I was expecting to pay around
1800 to 2000
Squiggle marks
I believe that's pounds
Is it pound or is it lira?
Which even at that amount would be very
Really difficult for me to pay, but once I got to the orthodontist
He told me it would cost 3200
Lira, euro, pounds
To have braces
This amount would mean a huge commitment
Over two years of my life. I'm only 18
And want to go to university next year
My teeth are not extremely crooked, but they definitely need braces
Should I plunge into debt for a couple of years
With the reward of straight teeth
Or wait it out until I'm 24 to 25
Or maybe never
I don't know who to ask, please help
Thanks, David
I do want to point out
He didn't type
Not extremely crooked, but they definitely
Need braces
He says not extremely crooked, but they defiantly
Need braces, which I like
You're like, hey, hey, listen
I'm your teeth, deal with it
Give me some braces, you bastard
Give me braces
David, again, I can't
Say this enough, I know I brought it up
In a few episodes, but I was the only
Macaroy fortunate enough
To know the sweet embrace
Of braces
There's no amount
Too high for that feeling
You know how
You know how in your life
You have these random things where
Everyone's staring at my eyebrow
Everyone's looking at my
This zit on my cheek
Everyone looks at your teeth
It is actually true
Look to your grill, get that grill fixed
Because when you talk, everyone's
Looking at your mouth
It's true
You could just tell people
To deal with it
Hey, save some money
Get a tattoo on your lip that says deal with it
That would be way cheaper
That's something people are going to remember
Whatever happened to David
Who used to come around, I don't remember David
But I do remember a guy who had a tattoo
On his lip that said deal with it
And I respected him for it
Can the top lip say yeah, I know
And the bottom lip say deal with it
Yeah, and on the inside
You pull down your lower lip and there's a
Chinese character for strength
Have you thought about getting like
A grill, like getting
Gold teeth, diamonds
Oh my god, yes, that's gotta be cheaper
But if you've got a fucked up grill
And you get a real grill on top of it
You're gonna look like a Bond villain
Yes
Why are you listing things that are positives
And pretending they're negatives
Why is that not awesome
I'm saying either
Get that sweet embrace
Because it feels so good, I gotta tell you
Having your teeth move around
It's an experience
Do you think they would sell better if they were called
Embraces
Embraces? I don't think so
I would buy them, I don't even need them
Or just be confident
Because people find confidence in faults
Sexy, that's why Kirsten Dunst is
As famous as she is nowadays
She's got a grill that looks like
She stopped a train with her teeth
I wouldn't go that far
But I do know what you're saying
Confidence, if you don't pretend
It's a thing, other people won't even notice
You know what gives someone confidence?
Having $3200 in their pocket
Well
Not dollars though, I don't know
It might be really cheap
I don't know what this money means
Is it rubles, do people still use those
Rubles? I think it's shekels
Shekels?
Brothers 3, help me out
At the moment
I'm in algebra class I failed last year
And I got stuck with the same
Old bag lecturer
I need to pass this class to get my
Engineering degree, Josh from Gmail
Josh didn't explicitly state
A problem in this question
Yeah, it sounds like
Josh, you're on the right track
I'm not good at
Algebra, like if you
You've come to the exact wrong place
If that's what you're looking for
Geometry may be something
You gotta cheat, which is how I got through
Both of my high school algebra classes
Go on
You sit near a smart kid who wants
Friends
Hey Josh, I'm gonna hit you with something
Kinda pull the camera back a little bit
Let's zoom out for a second
Maybe you
Are in the wrong field
Maybe
You aren't
Cut out for this, maybe this isn't
Your right calling if you're having such trouble
Yeah, math is
Kind of important in engineering, isn't it?
Yeah, it seems like you need to know this shit
If it's this tough for you
They build bridges and shit, right?
Yeah, I kinda want you on point
I kinda want you to be like
Really bomb at this class
I would like you to leave the class
Stand up and walk out
And be like, no bridges for me, thanks
You know what has never
I've never been walking across a bridge
And had someone say, you know who built this bridge?
The guy who can't do algebra
And just felt awash with confidence
Yeah, I remember when I
Built this bridge, that was the third time I felt
Algebra, and hey, it's not my fault
I was in the same lecture, but I did drop out of school
I don't know why they didn't let me make a bridge
I am good at Legos
That's only cause it's up
You gotta let a boat through
Josh
Just stand up and
Announce to the class that algebra
Is useless, and see how the teacher
Reacts, she may
He or she, I guess old bag
That sounds like a she, she may
Wink out of existence when faced with
That sort of incontrovertible
Logic
I did that to a social studies teacher one time
Did you? Did it work?
I said, this is so pointless, I will never use this
Information, and then they just
Cease to exist
Stand up and yell
You madam have killed the frail
Old lady that is algebra
And
See if you can start leading a revolt
Yeah, oh
So you want him to kill her, lord of the
Fly style
You know what, I ain't against it, blow that conch shell
Blow that conch shell, get Peggy to
Smother, dear
Mubim Bam, I'm having a bit of difficulty
With the bros before hoes rule
Well, that's not a good start
But keep going, the majority of my friends happen to
Be female, and I only have a few male friends
Would my female friends be considered
Bros and my male friends hoes?
Thanks for your help
No
You're doing it wrong
You're doing it wrong, bros before
Hoes is
Kind of a dumb thing to say
I want to deconstruct it and take you back
You
There is, bros before hoes
Is something that men
Say to each other to make themselves
Feel better, because
I want to take you
Real deep in here, it's always hoes
Before bros
It's always women, always girls
Let's peel back another layer
They're not thinking about you
Peel back another layer though, because the bigger problem
Here is that you are
Unironically using the word bro
And hoe
I don't know which one's worse
Both pretty bad
They're both really bad
Uh, I
How about
Sounds like you're in a chicks before dicks
Kind of situation
In any event
Your male friends would never
Be your hoes, that is
It is important to know
Here's a good test
Gather all your
Male friends together at Giovanni's
Walk into Giovanni's and say what's up my hoes
Sup hoes
See how that goes over
The thing is, the phrase bros before
Hoes is something that the other
Guys use
To keep you
From like, ditching them
It's not like, it's nothing
Any guy has ever sat down and go, you know
I'd love to go home with this lady
But bros before hoes, I suppose
It does
Bros before hoes, I suppose, should be the new one
Bros before hoes
Only apply, Travis is right
It's never a life choice, like
Guy post, you never say like
I should go to my best friend
Tommy's bar mitzvah
But I have a date with
This girl who is very attractive
Well bros before hoes, it's not
Like that, it's something where he calls you
And says hey, I'm gonna
Invoke bros before hoes I suppose
Are you?
You got me good
I've been trying to think of a bros before
Hoes except after
Joe's, it's escaping me
Except after
Moe's, cause if you've had Moe's burritos
You can just go home
Bros before hoes except after Moe's
Also
It does work
For your literal bros
Yeah, always
Push comes to shove
Your real
Biological bros
And we are
We are your biological brothers
I've been doing that wrong
For years
Biobros before hoes
What you want to say
Biodome before hoes
Late to the fad on twitter asks if
MBMBAM
Is pronounced MBMBAM
Are the fans
MBMBAMBinos
I think that's kinda fresh
I'm not crazy about it
Only the dudes
I kinda like Mambas
Or MBMBAMBinos
I don't know, we need some
Fans here, let us know on twitter
What you like
If there's a different one you like
Can we pick out someone who's our greatest fan
And call them the great BIMBAMBINO
We can, someone will be
And then our fattest fan
Can be the great HAMBINO
If you
Think you're the fattest MBMBAM
Fan, let us know
We just pitched the greatest
Reality tv show
Are you the fattest
MBMBAM fan
I think that show is called The Biggest Loser
And it already exists
So if you are
MBMBAM's fattest fan
You send in an email or a tweet
With your current
Total weight
No pictures of your girth
Because I ain't trying to get sick over here
Just the facts and figures
Just the stats, and then let us know
Just the stats
That's the name of this contest
Just the stats comma fats
And if you're the fattest
If you're the fattest one I will give you a
Free code to download MBMBAM
The app experience
Don't eat that iphone though
And fats domino stop
Applying
You are dead
Yahoo answers user I look so good without you
Can we not have one where it's like are you
MBMBAM's sexiest listener
No that's not required
Yahoo
Answers user
I look so good without you
Asks
Is there, oh jesus
Is there was a disease and it killed everyone
On this planet except you
And some other person who was ugly
It didn't kill
You two because you were both immune to it
Kind of like in the movie I Am Legend
Except opposite
Would you kill yourself or would you
Continue living and have a sexual relationship
With that one ugly person
Oh my god is this person asking
Would you rather kill yourself than
Fucking ugly person
That is exactly what they're asking
Would you rather bring humanity
To a screeching halt
Yeah
Speaking of
Confidence that's gotta be like the worst hit
Like two people left you look
At them and just say well that ends this
Chapter of humanity I suppose
Dead
Make sure you say something to him before
Cause I want him to live with that
That's how humanity should go out
With a sad person too ugly to have sex with
Not with a bang
But with a suicide
Or a double
Hey
Why don't you just kill that other person
I mean doesn't that solve
Your problem
If you
Don't want to have sex with this ugly person
Because you're the last person on earth
Who won't have sex with him don't kill yourself
Why does that even make sense
Why do you have to kill yourself
Yeah
Or just junk on him
Whatever
Did the disease also destroy all the bags
In the world
Come on
Take care of this
Okay don't kill yourself
Please for all of us just start
Although you know what I was gonna say
They should not bring humanity to a halt
Think about it half a go kids
Nobody wants that
The whole human race is like
That gene will never come out of the pool
The ugly gene will never
Me oh my father yeah
I'm 1 16th ugly
My great great grandmother
Was ugly
Hey my bim bam
I'd really like to have one of my questions
Answered on the show but my life isn't interesting enough
That I have any questions
You're doing it wrong dude
Can you guys help me out
To come up with a question to ask you
Alright
I'm so glad you asked
This is a little bit before we get into this
This is a little bit like
Could god make a rock so big that even he couldn't lift a thing
Right like this is pretty spacey
Should we come up with a question
That we couldn't answer
We may wink this out of existence
But we do need to address
Some things
That have been happening in our lives
In the life of the show
We're so happy that people have been sending in questions
I was
Like from episode 1
We started getting more than enough questions
That we needed to put an episode together
And that's awesome
That's really great
But they've started to take
A turn
What kind of turn
Towards
The creepy
And I'm not saying all of them
If your question is not on the show
It's not because it was creepy
I don't know
How to address this
Because I don't want to sound ungrateful
Stop asking us about poop
That's a good first step
If that is even in there
Even as a concept
Just edit it out
Not good
Not a good question
Because we probably won't read that on the show
I can't even say that
Because my mic traffic
Is rerouted through China
They censor anything scatological
That I talk about
So that's pretty whack
Speaking of whack
Maybe don't ask creepy questions
About like
Jango
Or joing
Or jingo
That probably won't get read either
Or Kimbo slice
And none of that
Don't ask any of those things
Just ask
Just ask a straight up question
True from your own life
Not made up
Because we know if you're making things up
It's pretty obvious
You send in made up things and they're funny
And we appreciate the humor
And it's so awesome that you want to share that
Funny story with us
But we're not going to read it on the show
Probably
But I would like to see
If you can't come up with a question
Or if you've had a question before
And you followed our advice
I would like to know how that worked out for you
We can maybe read some of those
I would remind you
Never follow our advice
But if you do
We are not liable
The best thing we can tell you
Is to ask for advice
About something
Don't ask a question
Like what's your favorite
Type of hot dog
But ask for advice
Because it's an advice show
Or do what that one guy did
And send us pictures of his girlfriend
That works too
Or tell us how fat you are
So either ask for advice
Tell us how fat you are
Or send us emails about how much you like Griffin
Just the stats
Please
I have a two year old son who is awesome
And lately everybody thinks that
Catherine
I have a two year old kid who is dumb
Boring
Do something fun, stupid
I have another one
Ever since I was a little girl
I only wanted one child and I'm not sure if I
Really want another child or I miss having a baby
Because my son is getting older
What to do?
That's true
I think it would be pretty lonely
Growing up an only child
I think you probably have three kids
I think that's about the right number
And three boys
Three beautiful bouncing baby boys
Two year old is pretty good
Let's have another one though
Catherine
I want you
One
You're asking the wrong
You're doing it wrong
You shouldn't ask us if you should have a child
But if you do
And I'm going to wholeheartedly insist that you do now
You have to name it something
Show related because it's very
Existence is thanks
To my brother, my brother
We basically are going to have a son
The three of us are going to have a son
Pretty soon
We're going to be your child's godparents
We're it's pod father
Holy shit
That's got to be trademarked somewhere
Just DM it
Copyright
What I want you to do
Is when you get ready
For the baby making times
However that works
Play this episode
Put a song in the background
Because we want our son to have a
Strong confident voice in his life
That he can
He knows that he can turn to whenever he needs anything
Except for money
Yeah
And make sure you play our show on headphones
On your belly like I see on TV sometimes
With Mozart and stuff
Baby Einstein tapes
We should make baby Einstein tapes
That'd be great
But it's cool instead of smart
Justin Travis Griffin the third
I love it what about Batman
See I was thinking Preston
Preston
Hi I'm Preston Bim Bam Stevenson
It's a pleasure
And I want to be the next president of the United States
That's what I hear in my head when I hear that
I appreciate your support
Third term
Who are these three guys hanging from my coattails
Those are my pod fathers
I'm going to
Find them lush cabinet positions
In a lush cabinet
Oh this is nice this velvet
I want to hear Griffin's last question
But a couple things
First if you want to ask
A question of the show
All the methods you can do that on are
At mbnbam.com
We love it when
People tweet about quotes or how fat they are
Just make sure
You use that mbnbam hashtag
If you
Want to buy something there's a
Buy stuff link there where you can
Buy our My Brother My Brother Me
App experience it's two dollars
You can listen to all the shows and ask us
Questions and there's some special
Features and
You can also
You can still
Get T-shirts
The pre-orders are over
But we have some extra supply
So those are available on the site
And those are going to start shipping out
Hopefully this week
And they're going to be shipped in the order
That they were ordered
So if you got on it early
Then they should be there thank you
You guys were so super supportive
With the T-shirts and
The app and everything and we really
Seriously cannot tell you enough
How much we appreciate it you guys have been
Super super cool
About it and make sure when you
Get your T-shirt I want to
See pictures of everybody
Wearing T-shirts and like
Maybe we can make a page on the site
Where people can just
And not just wearing the T-shirt I would like to see it
In provocative places like
Places where perhaps
A Hey Jeffrey T-shirt isn't appropriate
Yeah like a funeral
Yeah especially a funeral
Nothing turns a funeral into a funeral
Like a Hey Jeffrey T-shirt
And nothing
Turns a funeral into a funnel
Like a funnel
And uh
If you know someone who's good at making websites
I think we could use a new one
So let us know
I'm looking at our website right now
It looks like an ad for the New York Times
But so all that
We should just adopt an Ethiopian family to make us a website
Make that website
As quick as you want but do make it
And make sure you subscribe to the show
And rate the show
Tell a friend
We have over 400 ratings now which is just
It's mind boggling
You guys boggle my mind on a regular basis
My mind is boggled
Boggleded
Boggling as what?
Zach Stelz on Twitter
He introduced his boss to the show
So
I'm sorry about getting you fired
But we do appreciate you spreading the word
Thank you
Hit me
I've been excited to read this question
I've been excited the whole time
This question comes to us from
I think it's Sechal
S-E-A-C-H-E-L
Not a real name
But here we go
What's the difference between
Anorexic and Balsamic?
Laughing
Oh Christ
I'm Justin McElroy
I'm Travis McElroy
I'm Griffin McElroy
This has been my brother my brother and me
Kiss your dad square on the lips
You will never know me
Music