If you change your mind, I'm the first in line Honey, I'm still free, take a chance on me
If you need me, let me know, I'm gonna be around If you got no place to go when you're feeling down
If you're all alone, when the pretty birds have flown
You've done it, you've succeeded, you've engaged in the right series of clicks and types and taps that make the
My Brother, My Brother and Me Advice Show for the Modern Era come out of your speakers or headphones or cans with string
I am, of course, Justin McElroy, I am the oldest McElroy brother
I am Travis McElroy and I am the middle-est McElroy brother
You can't get more middle than Travis
I'm Griffin McElroy and I'm the adopted McElroy brother
I was gonna bring it up this episode if you didn't
So, real brother, thank you for joining me again
No problem
Adopted brother, you didn't have much of a choice
Right, you'd put me back in the cellar
Back to the cellar with you, dum-dum
Words hurt, words hurt
Words do hurt
Our first question comes to us from FormSpring
If you need advice, you can find out how to get it at the end of the program
Dear MBMBAM, have you ever fallen in love with a girl for her taste in music?
A girl started making me mix CDs that were surprising and addictingly good
And now I am in love, but maybe just because of the mix
I ask, is there anything wrong with this?
There ain't nothing wrong with a music girlfriend
Not in the short term, my man
Yeah, that ain't gonna last long, but you can get some sweet burn CDs from them
Most of my collegiate musical taste came from a girlfriend that I had my freshman year of college
That burned me like four MP3 CDs, not even audio CDs
We're talking like Googles and Googles of music that I still listen to to this day
Wait, Googles?
Google Bits
It's not gonna last long unless the song that unites the two of you is Crazy Game of Poker
Because man, that song never ends
Once again, this is one of those questions where if you're in high school, yeah, no, that's perfectly fine
If you're 45, it's time to get your ass together, man
Yeah
I don't think there's anything wrong with judging a person based on their musical taste
I think that says a lot about a person
I think everybody has that quality
For me, it's TV shows and movies, and I think for other people it's like video games and music and books and magazines
There's always gonna be that one thing that sparks our interest
Just build off of that
For me, it's Pogs
I find a lady with a fine collection of Pogs and maybe some really heavy alloy Slammers
Just some really nice Slammers
Look at the Slammers on her
Wow, look at her Slammers
Is that a Digimon on there? Nice
So in closing, it's a fine reason to start a relationship and a terrible reason to continue one
There it is
That's great
Another one from FormSpring
If you work someplace that lets you interact with many different people, customers, and you're immediately attracted to one of them, is it cool to tell him or her you think they're attractive?
No
What's up with those Slammers, girl?
I like those Slammers I see across the register
I'm gonna have to go with Travis on this one, no
There's no way to avoid being that dude
Even if you're the nicest guy in the world, there's no way when you're wearing khakis and your work shirt to not sound creepy
Are you gonna say you're attractive? Because that's probably creepy
But if you're saying it with body language and stuff
You just need this, Alpo? Do you want me to put it in your bag?
You're attractive
I like your face
I'm attracted to you
Your body, your face is setting off chemical reactions inside of my body that find you very desirable
My aesthetic sense is inflamed
It's one of those things where if you're just paying a compliment, great, it ain't going anywhere
But you might make them feel better
Maybe you can use that to get ahead in your business, right?
Like if you're a real estate agent, maybe show a little bit of the cleave and then what's up?
Yeah, what's up?
Okay, confession time
I once asked a girl out when I was working a waiter job and I asked her out via Facebook
We went out once and it was awful
It was quite terrible
Sounds bad
Yeah, so I personally don't recommend it
Also, I felt like the creepiest creepo ever
You should have
Yeah, and I did, even as I did it, I was trying to justify it and you can't
I'm surprised the girl showed up and didn't just call Chris Hansen because it's creepy time
Because she was 12 years old
She was also 12
This is also like so much of our advice
It's highly contextual dependent upon whether or not you yourself are very physically attractive
Oh yeah, no, if you're banging, forget it
Yeah, if you're super attractive, super handsome dude or a super bodacious lady with just real nice slammers
You are always going to be on the right path by telling people that you find them attractive
It's always acceptable if you're very, very physically attractive
Sweet, sweet slammers
Just the sweetest
Hi brothers
Hi
Hi, I have a problem
I can't start studying for a test until the day before
What should I do to start earlier?
You've come to the wrong place, my friend
How about this, hey bitch, just start earlier
Just do the thing
Do the thing you asked how to do
Let's do that
You understand the concept of earlier, so pick a time before the time you normally do it and do it then
Don't do it now, do it yesterday
If you do it now, it's too late, do it before
Now that being said, I do the same thing or I did the same thing because I retained the knowledge better in a block before the test rather than trying to study all week
Bullshit
I couldn't hold it in my head that long
No, I sort of got it
The only thing I think you can do which proved to be kind of useful for me was to get like a, I don't want to say study group
Because that's not the right vernacular, but like a shared pain group who will guilt you if you don't study
Yeah, the hardest class I had growing up was theater history and I actually had a study group for that one
And I felt like pretty lame about it
That's why I should have a study group, what is it, 1930?
But that worked out well for me
So if you get somebody who will say, like if you make a study appointment with somebody like a few days before, say hey we're going to study on Tuesday, let's just study
Then you will keep that appointment
Sure
In theory
Got to get accountability is what that's called
Yeah
Got to be accountable
Got to get that
Yahoo Answers user Rock just says
Hey Rock
That's spelled R-A-Q by the way
Whoa
I'm figuring that's how it prefers to be pronounced
Hey, need a film, not anything like The Lake House or that sort
Desperate for something to watch, anything for a 15 year old girl?
But not in the wheelhouse of The Lake House
So the only parameters set on this choice
Okay
Might I suggest The Lake House?
No, wait, fuck, shit
You choked, you choked McElroy, you choked
Not The Lake House, anything but The Lake House
Maybe something that, maybe Walk in the Clouds?
Maybe
That's got Keanu
I'm thinking of, I'm trying to think of other Keanu Reeves time travel based rom coms
Oh, Bill and Ted's Excellent Love Affair
Bill and Ted's most tender engagement
Travel through time, kissing George Carlin
This question is troubling to me because of the addendum
I'm desperate for something different to watch
Which makes me think, this is a 15 year old girl who her entire life
The only film she's ever watched is The Lake House
I'm ready for something new
I would say the Jurassic Park films, that would probably be a good place to start
Have you tried Titanic?
You've never seen any movies, I don't know where to start with you
Have you tried anything else?
Not that she hasn't seen any movies
She done seen The Lake House
Don't even try to quote Lake House to her
She knows all the lines, all the classic, classic lines
Like, I've got a time traveling mailbox
I live in a house by the lake
That really is the worst movie ever
You've watched it?
Yeah, I watched it
Oh, that's good
I'm sorry
I hate you
Another one from FormSpring
I fall in love with every girl that pays attention to me, is this normal?
If you're fat
Fair
I mean, right?
I don't know, I get it
If you've been single for long enough, I don't think that's such a ridiculous feature
It was actually something I just learned in the last year
To not view every female that I meet as a potential love interest
Right now?
Yeah, just like a year ago
Sometimes you can just meet and be friends with a girl
And you don't have to be romantically involved
It's really freeing
Yeah, you can't do that
But I see what you're getting at
Maybe you've never seen a film called When Harry Met Sally
Or The Lake House
That's all I've seen
That might be a good one
Go see When Harry Met Sally
Billy Crystals
You say Billy Crystals?
I don't think you should
I don't think you should fall in love with every girl that pays attention to you anymore
That's my advice
Because it's not healthy
No, it's not healthy
It's a losers game
You're a worthwhile person
You have great taste in podcasts
You don't need to fall in love with every girl that pays attention to you
And also look at it this way
If you fall in love with every girl that pays attention to you
You will be less desirable to women
Because they don't want that dude
They want someone who is funny and aloof
And not desperately trying to get the attention of every woman that pays attention to him
So, you know, play it cool, hotshot
Play it cool
I've got a bad problem of falling in love with every girl that's pretty on my TV box
Every girl I see on my TV box that I think is pretty
Just instant infatuation
Like Lauren Bacall
Flo, Flo from the Instagram
Don't get me started
Flo, those progressive commercials
She's my favorite
She is a cutie
And you know she's got the N for insurance
She can hook you up
I mean, C.E. Wilson
I mean, I guess he's a good enough looking man
But I would hop onto the Flo wagon
You would with very little hesitation be a Flo rider
Oh
Wow, from downtown
My wife and I are expecting first child in a month
She wants some songs that would be good to listen to in the delivery room
Can you give me some great tracks for this special occasion?
That's from Thomas via Gmail
No, I think we could come up with something, Thomas
Oh man, Zees
I actually, I read this question earlier
And I came up with a really great solution
And I think for the longer portion
The more drawn out portion
Like from when she actually gets posted up in the room
And starts squishing out the baby
You put on something soothing
Something mellow
Something like Iron and Wine's double sided LP around the well
Just something to bring the mood down
And then
Right when she starts crowning
Thunderstruck by ACDC
Wow
See, I was going along the same idea
India, Nazareth, Hair of the Dog
Now you're messing with a son of a bitch
I think that's the best way for a baby to enter the world
How did that go again?
I don't want to do that again
I don't think he can do better than Thunderstruck
Like if you guys want to try and come at me with something else
But Thunderstruck would be the most trial
How about with Arms Wide Open by Creed?
Fuck you with that
It's about bringing a baby into the world, it's perfect
Get out of here with that, get off the show
Fuck you with that
The obvious answer by the way
For the special moment of childbirth
Is Black Hole Sun
Oh man
What about
What kid wouldn't want to make a triumphant entrance
To Hurricane 2000
Obviously
Hurricane 2000 is the way to go
Is that the
What am I thinking
I was thinking of the orchestral version
Of Rock You Like a Hurricane
That is in fact Hurricane 2000
That's what you're talking about?
That would be pretty good I guess
It would be perfect
Shake it at the knees
And then she would really be shaking at the knees
And a baby would come out
Thomas whatever you pick
Make sure you sing it to her
She'll really appreciate it
She'll really love it
Make sure it's with Arms Wide Open too
She'll dig it
Formspring asks, my girlfriend gets a little upset
That I don't tend to hug her at night
In bed, I explained I just need
My own space to get to sleep but I don't think it
Made her feel better, how can I keep my
Own bed space and avoid hurting her feelings
Um
I
I think that
You should go
With the, it depends on how quickly
She falls asleep, if she falls asleep really
See my wife likes to cuddle in bed
But I don't like to touch anything
I'm sleeping, so I'll like
Justin has a hover chamber
He just gets in and he just shuts down
For the night
I snuggle her until she falls asleep
And then I dog pound her out of that side of the bed
Check out my other side of the bed
And if I'm lucky
I'll have hit a real cool spot on the pillow
Got a real cool spot going
Cause I've been relocated for so long
What I like to do is just straight up
Cuddle, cuddle, cuddle and then say
Hey I'm going to sleep now, and then roll over
So she gets the cuddles and then
It's your turn, and it's your time
For sleeping
I've never been married so I don't know what it's like to sleep
In the same bed as a woman
That's my good boy
Onward Christian soldiers, onward
Um
Christian, what?
Yahoo
Yahoo answers user Mousseau
Which may be
The evil twin brother of Justin Rousseau
Yeah, or
The children's singer Mitchell Mousseau from the hit show
Hannah Montana
You know they're the same person, right?
Yeah, who? Hannah Montana and
Miley Cyrus or Justin Rousseau and Mousseau?
Mousseau Rousseau
I think it's Justin Rousseau and Hannah Montana
Yeah, well
Okay, go ahead
Which is a better name for a character?
Here's another fun little naming game
I'm torn between
Jaden and Jacob
Either way, his name is shortened
To J. My character
Is 15 years old and is growing up
In England. He comes from a
Middle class background yet smokes weed
Is a teenage Casanova
And basically a rebel without a cause
Get out of here
Which name would suit him better and why?
The only reason I didn't go for Jacob, which was
My first choice, was because of the
Werewolf character from the Twilight series
But my book is nothing like Twilight
Nothing
Oh
Basically
This guy's a rebel without a cause
More or less
Basically, more or less
Just don't get in his way
Mister, because you don't like Jason Jaden
When he's angry
Boy, golly
I like any character that's defined as
He's from a middle class background
But he smokes weed every day
As though those two things are mutually exclusive
Yeah, he's middle class
But you know, he'll still smoke some weed
He's the narcotic of the proletarians
What do you want him to smoke in middle class?
Is a middle class white guy
Who will
Wear some khakis, whatever
Not a big deal
He's a free thinker
I think your book sounds shitty
I wouldn't
I wouldn't read it, I don't see what the concern
Is with what the character's name is
But, to answer your question, Jaden
But, Jaden, obviously Jaden
The world has too many
Jasons already
Jacobes
Jason
Jadakiss
Desiree
Gotta be bad, gotta be bold
Who's that one guy
Who sang with his shirt off
In a black and white video
R&B
Right side Fred? What are you talking about?
You know
Not Seal
He had his shirt off in the Desiree video?
No, he's like
He's sort of like Desiree
You gotta give me a song or I can't sing
Kinda like Jadakiss
He's an R&B singer
Okay, that's a genre
DeCantrus, maybe
It'll come to me
I wanna say something like a pony
Is his name
Jadakiss, Ludacris
Something like that
Ludacris is a thing, he's a guy
DeAngelo
Got it
How is that like a pony?
Like Capote
DeAngelo Capote
Popular district attorney in Boston
Can we keep going?
My wife and I, this comes to us from Christian
That's the only way I can think to pronounce that
For a man
Christian from Gmail
My wife and I are going to New York
For a week in June, would like some advice on
What should we do or not do
What was
Keep going
I can do it
I keep waiting for it to arrive
What should we
Should we not do, what must we do
See, eat, buy while we are there
Keep in mind, it's our first trip
To the US, so everything is
Brand spanking new to us
Can't imagine
I mean if it's
I think if it's
Your first trip to the US
There are more staple US activities
That you need to partake in before like New York
Activities, right?
First things first, buy shoes
We got them here
Lousy with them
Also throw some money in the garbage
It's what we do, we don't care
Get real fat
Buy a new like
Very consumptive
Automobile
And like just drive it into a building
Get one of those
Room scoot 2011's
They are really fast and they will just burn
That oil, if you want a place to go
To eat, try
Max Brenner chocolate by the bald
Man, there they have
It's not only delicious and New Yorky
But they have
A chocolate marshmallow pizza that really
Sums up a lot of American values
Welcome to America
Here's your complimentary diabetes
Yeah, I got
This lousy t-shirt and diabetes
I would say just go to the nearest
Walmart or Sam's Club
And buy a big box
Of Jimmy Dean's breakfast
Corn dogs
And then just eat those the entire time you're
Within the borders of our nation
Sorry, no Walmart New York
What?
No Walmart in New York
In all of the city there's not a single
Walmart
They would have to leave the city, they would have to take a taxi cab
Well maybe you could like
Maybe you could get one like under the counter at a Whole Foods
Probably yeah
They deal in like shady
Like so non Whole Foods
There, you gotta pay a premium
Talk to Jerry, the guy that sweeps up
He answers to the name
Sweepin' Jerry
He's got a beat on a breakfast corn dog
Travis, what show
Do they see a show?
God, I wish I knew any
Shows on Broadway right now
What show gets the T-Sax seal of approval?
What about The Addams Family?
That name's always a delight
Is Cats still on Broadway?
It is, but now they changed
They changed the name to Miss Saigon
Oh, okay, but still there's
Cats in it, right?
I feel like there is something on Broadway
Right now that I heard about
And was like, oh that sounds so dope
But I can't
Like it's like a show about like a musician
Or something
Oh yeah, um, D'Angelo
That was it
Wicked
The Addams Family
You're Googling, you make me sick
You know what, actually go see Blue Man Group, it's awesome
What?
That shit's incredible
What if they're shirtless and it's black and white
And they're singing R&B songs, maybe
And also, it's called D'Angelo the Musical
Um
So
Max writes to us from
Gmail, he's kind of a wordy
chap, he says
I've taken a real shine to a girl
Every 20 year old who writes our program
Is a 70 year old man
I just wanted to get that out
I've taken a real shine to a girl
I fancy a young lady
I like the
Nevermind, her bustle
A delight
She has the best Lindy Hop in the Tri-County area
Um
So anyway, I've taken a real shine to a girl I know
And after thinking about whether I have a chance or not
I'm feeling inspired by your advice on the show
Have decided to give it a go
Oh, there's your first mistake
After some friendly banter, she asked if I was doing anything later
Yes, and we soon arranged
To meet later in the evening
Yeah
You're welcome
Tell your kids about us
I wish more people would write and let us know or name them after us
More accurately
Thing is, I'm not 100% certain this is a date
Don't get me wrong, by all accounts
This seems like one when you read it
Read it back, indeed
But this is one of those girls who has a naturally
flirtatious demeanor
Meaning it could just be a friendly meetup
Here comes the real problem
I'm going to try to keep this meeting on the down low
So I can ascertain the truth of the matter
And not have it announced to our social circle
That I'm trying to court this girl
Well, Max, I know your fucking first problem, buddy
Maybe
Does your social circle listen to our podcast?
Because this is a bad start
Probably not, let's be realistic
Yeah
If not, then you've got an even bigger problem
And that's that you haven't
Shared this with your loved ones
I think
And maybe this is just me
I don't know how the young people are today
I don't know the
Their various social
Codes, signals
They send to each other
It's all online now
Is it all?
See, I was afraid of that
I think that if you
Make an appointment to do something
It's a date
With a lady and a guy
Just by themselves, it's a date
Like, if you
If she invites along other friends
Or suggests that you invite
Along other people, it's not a date
But if she's saying, let's just do this, you and me
You gotta assume it's a date
It's on her if it's not a date
Do not spend the entire date trying to figure out if it's a date or not
Or you will fuck it up
You will fuck it up, bro
You will probably be better off
If you act like it's not a date
Because that will
That will keep the confidence high
I don't feel like pressure like
Should I hold her hand? Should I kiss her?
Should I hold her kiss?
Jayda Kiss
Jayda Kiss, D'Angelo
All the questions that seep into a young man's mind
Should I take her to see the lake house?
Should I take her to see the lake house again?
That's the only movie she's ever seen
What other movies are there?
I take a much more backwards
Approach to my social engagements
Where at the end of any social
Engagement I partake in
I try and kiss the other party
And if they take it
Then I will know in retrospect that it was a date
And if they fight me off
Then I know
The truth
It was really awkward when Griffin got his taxes done
Well, I don't know because my H&R Block
Representative
She was fantastic
The weirdest was when he was baptized
And he's had them all over the world
As far as your
Friends finding out
You know, don't worry about it
They'll all grow up and if they're
Dicks, don't worry about it
It'll be cool
Just don't adhere to any labels, man
You know what I'm saying?
It doesn't matter if it's a quote-unquote
Date or not, or if it's just a friendly
Hangout, if it turns into love
Yeah, it's by less pressure if you don't
If it's not a date, then you can
Just hang out, and you know what?
Dude, seriously, if you don't
Hang out with her, treat it like it's a friendship
And if you don't like spending time
With her in that context, then you
Probably don't want to do it again anyway
And honestly, if you like spending time with her
If you don't act like it's a date
You can probably preserve the friendship easier
If it doesn't work out
Actually, that's a great point, because we get asked a lot about
Friendzone, and I was friend
No one that actually likes you
Romantically puts you in the friendzone
So there's no concern of like
I became too good of friends with this person
And now they don't want to date me
They didn't want to date you before
And they just wanted to be friends with you
And hey, this goes for him
And Max, and everybody
Let us know how this stuff works out
If you follow our advice
Not that we recommend you do that
Or anything else we've ever told you to do
Anything else we've ever told you to do
Yahoo questions user
Simmons, aka
That Guy
Asks, in all caps
Help my little baby sister
She drank beer
Hi, one of my little baby sisters
Who is 11 months old just drank some beer
She didn't drink a lot, and she doesn't seem affected by it
But my mom is freaking out and yelling at all of us
But I think she is fine, and my mom doesn't think so
Can anyone help? And no bullshit
Serious answers only
Take her keys away
First and foremost
Don't let her drive
This is another
One of those times where we have to remind you
Of the right time
To call poison control
And the right time to ask Yahoo answers
What you should do about your situation
Because it's not now
Babies think they can party
Babies don't got shit
These babies come up here
They think that they can roll with the big dogs
Trying to stab
I don't think humans get livers
Until they're like 3
You gotta earn that shit
Where's that beer going?
I think we're missing some important
What beer?
Oh that's another
That's a big beer
What did you let her have first?
Did you let her have some highlife?
If it's like a heady dogfish stout
Then that baby's donezo
That baby's out
My baby sister just slammed a Rasputin
Oh no
What if she had a PBR?
You got a hipster baby on your hands now
Hope you can find really small
Horn rimmed glasses
Plaid shirts
Tiny fixy tricycle
These jeans don't come any smaller
I'm sorry
You'll have to go to the My Buddy aisle
To find smaller jeans
For tight tight hipster babies
Tight tight hipster jeans
At the Gymboree
But seriously
Go to a hospital I think
Have her drink a glass of water
And an ibuprofen
And a glass of water in the morning
And she'll be fine
Also film that shit and put it on YouTube
Did you guys hear about
Josh
His problem
He wrote to us gmail
Our answer
Just found out
My ex cheated on me with her current boyfriend
When we were still together
What's the best way to set a person aflame?
I think you gotta play in one of the hits
Of D'Angelo
And just watch their heart light up
Right? Does that mean literal?
Yeah I was gonna say literally
Fire
But
Fire and some sort of flammable oils
They gotta be asleep
That's so important
Or unconscious in some way
Yeah you can't just like start
You will never work
You will be shocked at how quickly a motivated man
Is gonna fire
Josh let me drop something on you
That Jerry Springer dropped on me when I was 12
A bottle of beer
That is one of
The wise Jerry's final thoughts was
If someone will cheat on
Someone to be with you
Then they will cheat on you to be with someone else
So drop that knowledge on her new boyfriend
Like listen dude
I don't know what makes you think
She wouldn't cheat on you she cheated on me
Hey bye
And then dip
That's possible
Maybe you just didn't love her hard enough
I know that's kind of
I know that's
That's a harsh reality but
Did you love her as hard as you possibly could?
You know what you just said she's your ex
Who cares man
Let it go move on
Griffin you made a great point too
No girl cheats on someone
Or nobody cheats on someone they're happy with
You know what I mean?
Unless they get drunk at their office party
Or the someone is profoundly physically attracted
Also that
And that's another thing I'm just going to heads up real quick
Listeners
We appreciate questions and we appreciate
Input and we appreciate you listening
Questions about
How to get
People with boyfriends and girlfriends
To sleep with you
Not really our expertise
Or something we're going to address
Not cool
Not cool just be cool that's the number one
Advice of my big bam
And
Just don't hate
I'm just going to give you an in general answer to those questions
Question my friend has a
Girlfriend I want to sleep with what do I do?
Answer realize he's not
Really your friend
You guys maybe aren't as close as
You thought
Joseph has a conundrum
There's a girl he works with
Who he met while she was
Reading about the new Pokemon game
That got the conversation
Started now I'm at a loss
For what to do next should I just go
Forward ask her out I'm really
Bad at the asking out part what should
I do what should I ask her out
To dinner or something
Else maybe Digimon
Hold on Gertrude
Just go ahead
I think maybe you could arrange some sort
Of series of romantic Pokemon
Battles right
You know what I'm saying maybe kind of
Sexy Pokemon battles like that could be
The way that you ask her out like oh if my
My Charizard topples your Venusaur
How do you feel about a little
Squirtle and of course you will because
Her Venusaur will be weak to your Charizard's fire
Attacks
That's all I can
Do that's all I can summon up
I can't do anymore
I think that
Ask her about your Pokeballs
Oh Jesus
You could
You could just ask her if you
You two want to meet up the next day we could do an anonymous
Meeting I figure
You could try that
Ask her how her collection of cats is doing
I'm trying to make fun of this guy
But honestly
I feel like his email is pretty much just
Sort of
Got it out there
I mean I don't want to make fun of him
We just said that
It's a good reason to have a relationship with
Somebody if you both dig Pokemon
We can poke fun all we want
Dude met a girl
What's up beautiful
Keep the human race going
Joseph you had the courage
To email a podcast
To ask him how to ask out a girl
Who your only contact with her
Is Pokemon related
I don't think you'll have any problem mustering up
The courage to ask her out and do something
Your balls are huge dude
Your pokeballs
Your penis are ginormous
You can see your pokeballs from space
It doesn't matter what you do
It doesn't matter what you ask her out
To do
As long as you have fun
As long as it is interesting
Be interested in her
The date is not important
The experience is important
Be interested in her Pokemon
That's what she wants to talk about the whole time
But you guys are making fun
Dude if you've got that N
If that's your N
It's unconventional
But you gotta fight tooth and nail
For love
And you have the best
Nerd point argument ever
Well I disagree
Because I met a girl
And you will win every nerd argument like that
Joseph if I could just
Give you one other piece of advice before we move on
Hold on to this one real tight
Just really
Trust me on this one
Don't let her go
Just
We don't know how many more times
This opportunity is going to present itself
By which we mean none
So just really hold on to this one okay
For me
Just hold on tight
Trust me
Make it work
Gordo
That's a great name
Gordo asks on gmail
I am super whipped
By my girlfriend and generally despise my life
My brother and friends say
I'm more whipped than even the most whipped guy
On TV
No that's a good metric
Haven't you seen the new reality show
The Most Whipped Guy
I would break up with her but I feel
Bad about it and I'm locked into a few
Trips that include her
What do I do
Stop planning trips
Why do you have more than one trip planned
Step one
Start dropping subtle hints
Asking about refundability of certain trip deposits
Babe you know that trip we had planned
In 2015 I returned it
Stop planning trips
We got Bonnaroo in June
And then the cruise in September
But so help me God
October rolls around
Guys
Listen man trust me on this one
Trust me
If you get to a point where you think
I want to break up with somebody
Get in a car
Find them and do it right then
Because there's not a second of your life
You're not going to spend worrying about it until then
And as soon as you do it you will be
You will feel so much better
And you are not doing them any favors by waiting
Yep don't go on the trips
Because then like okay
Let's say you got a romantic cabin
Trip planned for this weekend right
You're going to go on that cabin trip next weekend
You say I think we should break up
Oh man that cabin trip
That you just went on is completely
Invalidated like it never happened
Even worse
You're going to say nice things on that cabin trip
You're not going to sit on the opposite side
You're going to say like baby I love you
And then the next week break up with her
That's going to make it messy dude
And the thing is a lot of people shy away from breakups
Because like oh it's going to be messy
Every breakup is messy it gets better
The sooner you do it
It starts healing immediately afterwards
So the longer you put it off
The worse it's going to be
I know it sucks man I know it sucks
But you got to do it
Don't waste any more time you're wasting your life
And also your money
Stop planning trips
Stop planning trips Aaron from
Gmail says how do I comment on my wife's
Terrible new haircut without lying
Here let me feed this one for you Aaron
You ready
Get close
Lie
Glad I could help
Rob on
Gmail says I'm having a
Baby girl in June my first
We have a first name
Picked out but haven't chosen a middle
What do you think of the middle name Danger
For a girl my wife says it's white trash
But I don't know any white trash people with the middle name
Danger Your wife doesn't know shit
Yeah sorry Rob
But that doesn't
Those two things shouldn't associate
With each other at all
I generally have a baby naming
Rule and that is that naming your
Baby is not an opportunity for self
Expression
Because your kid has to live with it for the rest of their life
That being said
Danger as a middle name is
Badass
I say do it
You are raising the sort of person
Where
That's going to shape
Their life right
They're going to have to introduce themselves to
People that's going to come up
They're going to associate with people who
Think it's cool that their middle name is Danger
And that's a cool crowd
That's the kind of people you want
It'll be great and like her wedding
Her wedding day where there will be a lot of
People in attendance who don't know her middle name
And the preacher will be like do you
Eliza Danger McCutcheons
Take so and so
And everyone in the audience will be like Danger
Sweet
Yeah
I like it I'm a big fan
If she ever becomes like an international super
Spy it's right there
Danger is my middle name
She can actually say I love it
Right but that joke she's going to hate
That joke no unless she becomes
An adventurer
But even then like
The danger is my middle name thing like people are
Going to say that to her at parties and she will
Get sick of it after like the second time
That might get a little old actually
I'm saying that the word itself
The concept of danger
As a moniker is so strong
Yeah what about
Adventure I like that one
Excitement Punctuality
Monkey Shines
Monkey Shines is my middle name
What's the best way to
This is from Maverick
89 What's the best way
To remember stuff you've forgotten
This question is so paradoxical
I've been thinking about it all day
And I can't
I forgot to think about it
No come on
First creed
Now this
A2 Travy
Listen it's been an awful week
I think you just need to sit down
You gotta sit down in the dark
You just gotta turn on the AC
Low as it goes
High as it goes?
Make the temperature
As close to zero as you can get it
Okay
Ice down?
Cover your body in ice and oils
Icy oil
Think as hard as you possibly can
About some old shit
That happened to you
Back there back in the day
Cause you got shit back there that happened
To you with you
You have memories in there
Cobwebs
They are cobwebs surrounded
And you gotta get back there with the oils and just get them out
Just dust them out
So what you gotta do is you gotta pop some ginkgo
Dust them off
Drink a shasta
Get in the dark and just sit and get them out
Watch some old movies
Watch a movie that was created
In the year that you were born
And just think
Like the lake house? Were you born in 1997?
Like the lake house?
Think deep
That movie came out in like 2005 dog
Sorry dog we're back
I forgot
No but for real ginkgo it up
The best way to do it
If you're talking about something
And reset like I was gonna say something
And I can't remember it
Retrace what you were talking about
Or just stop thinking about it
The more you try to think about it
The more you're going to think about thinking about it
And not actually remember it
As humans we have a short term memory and a long term memory
And getting things to transition from
Short term to long term memory is a process
Didn't you hear
The part with the ginkgo
And the ice didn't you think that that pretty well covered it?
I answered this question pretty
Decisive. I feel like he's probably
Already remembered it. He's probably stopped listening already
Uh huh
Maybe he was trying to remember to unsubscribe
I don't think you can blame him
I know I can't
Dude it's coke
Asks us via twitter
Big news
After three years with my girlfriend
I feel it's time to make the leap
And ask for her hand any suggestions to make it memorable
Alright guys let's do it
First of all congratulations
Let's do it
Susan or Marie
Oh god it's our first
Okay okay
I know I'm really nervous
Susan or Marie or Ellen
Or Tammy
Let's just say baby
Hey baby
Sweet baby
Dude it's coke's been with you for three years now
Three long years girl
Over one thousand days of pure
Bliss
525,600 times three
You got
You went on some dates you had some good times
Met each other met each other's parents and friends
You all get along really well
He's been true to you
He's been there for you
He's got a really really important question
To ask
Do it dude it's coke
Yeah
Alright
Wait let's do the second one
It's like a choose your own adventure
Reaction
Right
She says no
Dude it's coke that's rough man
That's tough that's tough buddy
Hey listen there's so many other fish left in the sea
Yeah don't even worry about it
Don't even worry about it
Because that's not gonna work out
It's over
You had your shot and you blew it
You blew it
But if you did it and it worked congratulations
Yay
I'm sure she said yes
I'm sure she did because those kids are so so in love
Unless she didn't now if she didn't
She didn't
That is too bad
But congratulations or not
Congratulations or fuck you
Fuck you fuck that bitch
She never knew you she didn't deserve you
Dude it's coke
She doesn't know you like we do
Fuck her
Or congratulations
We hope we get invited to the wedding
Hey thanks for inviting us
Before hand I want to thank you
In advance for inviting us to the wedding
Let's shut this bitch down
Or
Fuck her
Okay I want Griffin to
Tell us his last
Super important question but first
I want to remind you of all the different ways
You can seek out our wisdom
For your very own
You can visit mbmbam.com
That's a great place to start
In case you forget about any of these
Methods
All kinds of flash games fun for the kids
Social networking
Yeah mp3s data
Jpegs and photos
Smiley faces
Smiley faces hidden can you find it
Easter eggs
You can
Hit us up on twitter either do
At mbmbam or
We like pound sign mbmbam
We see a lot of people
I see a lot of people quoting lines from the show
With that tag on twitter
That makes me really happy
It means we're reaching people for once
Reaching out
We're reaching into them and we're changing their minds
Inside out
There's a form spring
Of course there's a link to that on mbmbam.com
Sorry the lost wasn't
The finale wasn't as good as you'd hoped
Or disappointed to
Unless it was awesome
Yay
But
Oh and please subscribe and just
Get a friend maybe today maybe tomorrow
Say
Listen I've got a show a hit show
Hot show that you've just
Got to listen to with me and then
Hold their hand go on the journey of a lifetime
And if you are on facebook
Look for the
Mbmbam appreciation
Group it's really great
Everyone on there is wonderful we try to release
As much news on there as we can
So check that out for
Late breaking up to the minute
Mbmbam news
And email
At us also that's a good one
That's the best one is mbmbam
At gmail.com
That's a good way to do it
Last question of the day
This one comes from
Yahoo answers user James
Who asks I think
I have pepsi stuck in my lungs
What should I do
I'm Justin McElroy
I'm Travis McElroy
I'm Griffin McElroy
And this has been my brother
My brother and me
You will never know me
You