The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on the wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
Hell yeah!
What up?
What's up?
Who brought the cheer wine?
Who brought the...
Yeah!
Nice.
Good looking out.
How's Florida?
Holy shit!
This guy...
Did everybody hear that?
I hope you all feel bad about yourself.
This guy drove 20...
30 hours to be here today.
Do you want to start the show, Justin?
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I...
Hold on a second.
I didn't...
You know what?
I hadn't started recording yet.
This time, for sure.
Should we start?
Should we walk out again?
Yeah, we can.
Well, we can.
We can.
Yeah, we can.
Welcome to My Brother, My Brother, Me, and My Show for the Moderna Era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
Sweet, sweet baby Griffin McElroy.
Let me just jack into the Matrix real quick.
So, thank you all for coming to our comedy advice podcast.
You're here in New York.
This is our first time doing My Brother, My Brother, Me here in...
in New York City.
Here are the big Snapple.
I came over that earlier, it's good, right?
Oh, my god, he is not joking.
He was.
I was so excited about it,
and I told everyone in our group.
He was word shopping that
on the street a couple hours ago.
And by word shopping I mean he said it once
and nobody laughed or responded to it in any way.
Dog pound, I swear to god, he says,
this is my, this is the dog pound.
I should have said it was like the Greek chorus thing.
Excellent joke.
We were walking and we had not heard the beginning of the conversation because we got split up by the intersection.
And we catch up with him and he says, hey guys, big snapper.
Just so you know, the beginning of the conversation was, there's so much to do and see here in the big snapper.
So I didn't miss. No, well, I felt like you didn't really get it.
This is a randy audience, can I say that?
You guys are a little randy.
You guys are very productive.
And what's funny is I know you're not drunk because you all stood outside.
There's a bar, you guys could have chilled in.
And what I love is that you waited in line outside where it's like, I don't know, it's outside so that's not ideal.
And the reason that you were waiting in line from what we were told was because you wanted to get the best seats that you possibly could.
Which is great because it means you're like, your fans, and that's obviously very flattering.
But it also means that you're very polite and you understand how lines work.
And you don't throw yourself in a crowd and fist fight each other.
You must have been surprised when you got in here and realized there wasn't a single seat you couldn't spit on us from.
There were also just three dudes sitting at the table.
So I don't know what you were afraid you wouldn't see.
They were afraid they missed our electric light show.
Lasers. Can we activate our...
Can we cue the show for them?
Yeah.
Hey audience at home.
I should have bought a ticket.
You didn't get a ticket because you waited a minute and a half.
Again, you guys are crazy. Thank you very, very much.
Let's start doing questions.
Oh, by the way.
Oh man.
Jinx.
Now that we can't talk, listen to me.
This is a shitty show.
Bitch, you just talked.
We may, if we have time, we may do a couple of questions for people here.
So think if we have a good one.
Not like a bad one because we will get a freaking problem.
Nothing about wanting to have sex with your friend's girlfriend.
Or dog.
Or car.
Or garbage compactor.
I don't know why you'd want to have sex with garbage compactor.
Trash free.
Okay, great.
So these first couple of questions are from people that are hypothetically here.
So feel free to raise your hand.
I won't be able to see you, but sure.
I'm from the Midwest and since moving to New York,
I've heard that Dime Mountain Dew is a broke ass
or trashy soft drink.
Is this true?
Am I drinking a soda that will make me look trashy?
That's from John Wagner. John, are you here?
I'm here.
I'm from the Dog Tale.
John Wagner.
Hold on, let me figure this out because it's like what a dog tale is.
He can't think if you laugh.
Which explains a lot, John.
Is that like a Midwest?
I mean, I know, Justin, it's your, like,
I know you're big on Pepsi Max now.
Yeah, I weigh into Pepsi Max.
I was into Dime Mountain Dew for a while.
When I was, this was like actually caught me by surprise.
Because where we grew up,
what I had associated Mountain Dew with
was what the copious amounts of advertising I'd seen associated with,
which is like extreme sports.
So I think if you're doing Mountain Dew, you're doing the Dew.
You're probably shredding or carving, maybe.
Wind jamming.
My friend, Michael Beth, I met him from college and he was from Ohio.
Let's hear it for Ohio!
Dayton, more specifically.
Who has any feelings about Dayton positive or negative?
And we were drinking Mountain Dew and we offered him one and he said,
Oh no, my mother says...
That's what he sounds like?
Yeah, it's not a joke.
Justin's not doing his, like, jokes.
He sounds like Kemo Phillips having a stroke.
Oh no, my mother says that Mountain Dew is for briars.
That story's so much funnier if you know Michael Beck, which nobody here does.
Let's hear it for Michael Beck!
Briars was another term that I was not familiar with,
but apparently it means hill people.
I heard a theory online that if you spill Mountain Dew or Diet Mountain Dew on the sidewalk,
the puddle that it forms, no matter how you spill it,
or the weather effects that it might have on the spill,
it will splash down in the perfect shape of the state of West Virginia.
It's true. Look online. Google search that.
Every time. Perfect. Two panhandles.
The West Coast.
It's a coast. It's on a river.
Sure.
You want to know my geography more?
Well, so my other question is the other side of that.
Is there a soda you could drink that makes you look like the classiest fellow?
Is there a soda?
Yeah.
Like if you're drinking Diet Cheer wine and someone goes,
How sophisticated.
I feel like, what about...
Jones? Jones sodas?
That's something that...
That's pretty good.
I'm pretty good.
I drinked it.
No, you're right.
That's what I know too.
They were like small batch root beers? Is that a thing?
Yeah.
Oh.
Micro brew root beers?
Get out.
Did I make that?
I thought I created that in my mind's eye.
No.
Do you guys want to ask him a question?
Oh, do you?
Yeah.
I'm going to give you regular questions only.
I have three choices.
This Yahoo answer was sent in by Himmel member and level 8 Yahoo Shaman,
Drew Davenport.
Thank you, Drew.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Bulls Cubs Fan who asks,
Is a loveseat called a loveseat because people have sex on it?
But I love how that question is.
It would imply that they couldn't come up with a name
and they like field tested it.
I put two people on.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
All right.
Loveseat it is.
That's the fucks over for sure.
I don't think we can sell those at the big Sandy Superstore.
Our branding expert wasn't even out of the room.
Our brand Shaman Skylar hadn't even left the room yet
before you started having sex on it.
Did they know each other before this?
No, the power of the sofa, sir.
Etymologic or entomologic, one of those two, strictly speaking.
Etymomically.
It has to have something to do with it, right?
Etymomically speaking.
You can only fit two people on there.
Sorry?
You can only fit two people on it.
Two regular people?
Yeah.
One big person, three little people.
Cheat the chart.
Yeah, a million borrowers.
What are we doing?
I've been watching a lot of my 600 pound life
and I don't want you to say they aren't people
because you cannot fit two normal loveseats.
That's fair, great.
And you wouldn't want to
because they'd initially start having sex
and go, thank you, check please.
Or you'd rather not.
Oh, boy.
I don't think that would be a comfortable platform
for that experience.
Well, do you think that it started off as like they
first said, hey, two people, which of these
would you choose to have sex on?
And it was like a Goldilocks kind of thing?
Like they tried it in a recliner and they're like,
oh, no, no, no, no.
And then they did it on a couch.
Like, how can I even reach them?
They're so far away.
They were trying to have sex.
I don't even know what to do with it.
And then they got on a loveseat and said, yes.
This is it.
They originally were trying to have sex on the couch.
Oh, this is going to be a fucking great reference.
Fuck it, everybody.
From the Gallagher live stage show.
But then they found John Lacherio's
and started having sex.
We can't have sex here.
Gallagher is out there.
Gallagher has touched this.
I don't want to have sex on the couch.
And Gallagher's over there masturbating.
They all pictured it, didn't they?
That sentence is out there.
That's why everybody in the first year
has those plastic wraps.
Is Gallagher here tonight?
Oh, Gallagher 2 is.
No big Gallagher 2 fans?
All right, next question.
I recently decided to move in with a friend of mine
and all seems to be going well so far.
My issue comes from when we signed the lease.
I had come to the lease signing prepared
to pay for my half of the deposit,
only to find that my roommate had decided
to pay the entire amount.
My question now is,
what do I do with the money
I would have spent on the deposit?
Am I required to spend it on stuff for the apartment?
And if so, what should I spend it on?
And that's from Suddenly Affluent in Astoria.
Are you here?
Right there.
All right.
I mean, you're a thief.
I've never rented a New York apartment,
but I imagine the deposit is like $14,000.
But I mean, you got away with it.
Until now?
Until like 30 seconds ago.
Perfect crime.
It was the perfect crime
and then it was the shittiest crime.
Well, here's the catch.
Your roommate will get that deposit back hypothetically
and you will not get money back for whatever you are.
So you need to think less about
what you're going to spend your stolen money on
and more about like,
you can do all kinds of wack shit in this apartment.
You need to start kicking holes in the wall,
burn the carpet, whatever you need to do.
You no longer have a horse in this race.
Whatever the condition is, is what it is.
Oh, you can hang a bunch of shelves?
Repaint the wall and mix sawdust into the paint
and get a nice textured look.
Welcome to Property Brothers.
They're fucking shit up.
You didn't want to sell this again, did you?
We're going to put a really nice reclaimed ivy up here.
Really support it.
You know, really fuck this place up.
Really, really fuck it up.
They'll never get that up.
You didn't pay the deposit on that.
Oh, you stole it. Great. Cool.
No, you're fine. Yeah, perfect.
We are going to ruin this.
We're going to get bathtub on the ceiling.
Yeah.
Just cause.
Why not?
Fuck it.
Could that help?
Try it.
Try to yaboo.
Really, you're not going to attempt to help that gentleman.
I mean, I wouldn't...
Here's the thing.
You have entered into an emotional battlefield.
The next few months to years, but let's be honest,
months of your life are going to be about the power struggle
between you and this person.
You cannot see the victory this early.
Here's what you need to do.
He's not going to take a check.
He's not going to take a stack of cash
if he wants to out line around.
What you've got to do is slowly repay this debt.
Which I mean, anytime you see an open pocket.
If you see his...
He leaves his jorts out.
Whatever.
Jorts is not going to fit.
A lot of money.
No, no, no.
Just like a jorts full.
You slip one dollar in.
He'll never notice.
I'm like, huh.
A dollar.
Cool, I forgot.
And then with the 800,000th dollar,
which is what I'm assuming your deposit is,
you have to present it like a pain in the feet.
I think we're through here.
That's a great plan to pay back your fee.
Your fee-fee.
And it's also a great plan to slowly drive your roommate.
Yeah, if you want to gas light your roommate real bad,
do that and move the furniture one inch out of the way.
Are we talking singles only?
Because that's like the whole apartment.
How about just quarters?
And you put them random places.
Like underneath his shoe, inside his shoe.
Something where he's like, what the fuck?
What are these people doing?
Can we talk about, we didn't address this,
but it's sort of germane.
It happened to us earlier this morning,
and it was so crazy that we didn't talk about it,
but we were getting on the elevator at our hotel.
There's a dude waiting on the elevator
who had dropped a $50 bill on the floor.
And like I pointed out, like, hey, you dropped $50.
That's the craziest thing ever, right?
Like I wanted to chide him.
Like, that's $50.
What kind of person are you that you can drop $50?
That was only the third time I've ever seen one of those
in my life.
I had one once, and I like duct taped it to my thigh.
He should have felt the weight change from his fall down.
Oh, something's different.
Hold on.
My boys.
I've been carrying like a plastic case for like baseball cards
or something like that.
Also, if you drop a $50 bill, and someone is like,
hey, you dropped your $50 bill.
You have to give a piece of it at least.
Don't you expect a little bit like a...
I seriously thought, I thought John Keane was going to jump out
and be like, you did it right.
Good.
You picked the right answer.
Why did you do that?
Explain your bravery.
Next step on Upworthy, you won't believe that this man...
One man dropped $50, you won't believe this other man's response.
You won't believe this little boy's response.
You dropped your money.
His only child doesn't swipe it.
How about Yahoo?
Yeah.
Let's see.
It got the response.
Positive reinforcement concept.
This was sent in by Evan Weston.
Thank you, Evan.
It's by Yahoo Answers.
This is the fucking worst website.
It's been suspended.
But the question remains.
They asked posthumously,
how do I make the garbage man fall in love with me?
I'm in love with him.
I wait every Monday morning and the first Friday of every month.
That's kind of a fucked up trash collection schedule.
The first Friday is for the baby things.
That's ball collect.
That makes sense.
You've seen him use those big strong arms to pick up the garbage.
Like that.
Go on.
No matter how much garbage I put in there,
he still picks it up with ease.
I had thrown away 20 bricks.
Wasn't a problem.
That fool got it.
How do I win his heart?
You could start by not throwing away so much heavy shit.
Yeah.
You could maybe stop making every day for this man a test of skill.
Why don't we just bury all the trash in your yard
and put an empty garbage can out there?
He doesn't pick it up.
He picks it up.
It's empty.
He looks up.
Is that you, Diane?
You're like, that's me.
Happy birthday.
Do you want to move in together?
I have a buried pile of trash in my yard.
Could you throw away awesome shit?
Not expensive shit that he's going to keep.
Not a bribe.
But something where he literally goes,
man, this person's awesome.
Yeah, you have to find out his facts.
That does assume that your garbage man is coming to you going,
well, hold on before I throw this away.
Let me build a character profile.
Let's make sure there's no awesome shit in here.
Just count pasta.
No, thank you.
You threw away the entirety of X-Files on DVD.
What a cool lady.
With apparently money deferred.
These four are newly found distains for the X-Files.
A book called How to Seduce a Garbage Man
and give him everything non-sexually.
Crazy.
How have I not heard of this book?
You could hide in the trash can.
You could.
You hear the truck on by and poof.
What's up?
And then you're wearing some sexy lingerie.
In the trash can.
You know what's special for you?
I'm garbage.
You got an Oscar of the Grouches.
I'm what you know.
I want to be a part of the world.
Look at this stuff.
Isn't it neat?
The trash can actor broke both of my...
What's the word again?
Legs.
We're not going to top that joke for the rest of the day.
You did warn me.
For like 30 minutes.
I thought we agreed in the pre-creditor
we were going to save the little mermaid garbage man.
How about another question from a normie?
Okay, let's see.
I'm going to save that one.
Let's go.
Okay.
This may be my favorite question we've ever received.
Sorry, everybody else here...
All the questions is dump.
When ordering a pizza online the other day,
I accidentally typed in the wrong apartment number.
By the time I noticed my mistake and called the pizza place,
it was too late.
The people...
Son of a bitch.
The people in the wrong apartment took the free pizza
rather than admitting it wasn't theirs.
I know where these pizza thieves live.
What are my options?
And that's from Trustless in California.
Big thanks first off to Justin
for grabbing the crunchiest food on the table.
You could have gone banana and nobody would have known
and you went with kettle cooked potato chips.
What the fuck are these?
What is a chocoroon?
Wait a minute.
Time out on this question.
What is a chocoroon?
Sweet and crispy.
Hold on a second.
We need to take a quick break.
Welcome to the Mavro Brothers Eat Snacks.
Can we take chocoroons to the Money Zone?
Yeah, let's go to the Money Zone.
Wait, you're going to wait and eat them together?
No.
Oh, okay.
Chocoroons wait for no man.
Pretty good.
It's way better than regular mushrooms.
Regular mushrooms are not chocolatey or crispy.
Okay, great.
But I'm at the store and this has been the Money Zone.
So back to chocoroons.
So someone stole this piece of pizza.
Guys, we literally can't snack the entire show.
Yeah, that's going to keep you.
I'm 48 pounds overweight.
This is what's been stopping me the entire time.
Travis said I'm going to hit you with a one-two punch.
If only someone had moved the snacks one inch out of my reach.
Travis will push it out of reach and I'll do cookie points.
And then that will be Bradley Cooper.
Griffin is trying to suggest that I lost cookie points.
If you don't know, cookie points is official currency.
I earn for eating salad or vegetables.
That you can exchange like arcade tickets.
Or cookies.
Not cookies he gives me, but the right ability to eat cookies.
And Griffin tried to tell me today that just because I got a muffin.
Which is a tall cookie.
Well, he said a muffin is a tall cookie.
A chocolate chip muffin that you try to get.
Yeah, it's like taking a cookie and making it grow.
We've been off topic for 15 minutes.
All right, pizza thief.
Pizza thief, pizza thief.
Should you confront the person?
Do you know how many pizzas you'd have to give me to confront anybody about anything?
I saw a story on Dayline about people who were using Find My Phone.
The app on your phone.
That you can find your phone with it.
And people will get their shit stole.
And then will find their phone.
And by which I mean the person who stole their phone.
Who would then kill them.
Sometimes.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
The person finding their phone kills the person who took their phone.
Or the person?
No.
What he's saying is like someone steals my shit.
All of a sudden I'm going to deputize myself.
Now I'm the equalizer.
I'm going to go track down that fool and settle the score citizens arrest style.
Pardon me, sir.
You wronged me earlier.
I demand satisfaction.
Please lie down on the ground until the authorities are...
Now what is that you have there?
Is that a gun?
Interesting.
But you're implying that we would be afraid of confronting this pizza thief as the pizza thief.
Rather than going to prison for stealing your pizza would kill you.
A pizza costs $5 at Little Caesars.
Do you think a person ordered a $5 hot and ready to be brought to their home?
What kind of life are you living?
Listen, I don't want nothing fancy, but I also do need it raw.
I'm a humble man.
I'm saying a phone costs way more than a hot and ready.
So why would you confront a person for pizza?
Just get another pizza.
How about you just start ordering pizzas for that apartment with a note saying,
I think you need this more than I do.
And just really shame them about like clearly you're on some hard time.
The old guilt pizza.
Do you know what the best type of pizza on earth is?
Pepperoni's in shame.
No.
It's Fritza, which is free pizza.
And you need to just appreciate the fact that you are giving these people a wonderful and beautiful pizza.
That you can't give yourself.
That's a great point.
You could pay for a pizza with money that someone else gave you.
It would never be as delicious.
Even if you're not taking a net loss is what I'm saying.
Pay it forward and pay it forward the movie.
Which we reference a lot, but it's a fucking incredible movie.
It's a movie we will see at some point.
I promise you we'll actually watch it.
I saw it in theaters.
Caleb Joel Osment buys three people, three pizzas.
And then it gets stabbed in the stomach and dies.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, really, yeah.
Does the second part actually happen?
The pizza part?
Why would that be a movie?
They just stab a little kid?
Yep.
Sorry, it was other little kids.
It wasn't like an adult stabbing a little kid.
But yeah, he definitely gets stabbed in the stomach.
Why?
He was paying it forward and shit.
Listen, some people don't want that.
Some people are like, pay it backward.
How about you pay off the people that did shit for you?
Yeah.
You owe them money?
He tried to say, oh my god, are we going to fucking go over the entire thought of pizza?
Everybody talk amongst yourselves.
I don't know if I got bored for Justin Roeper.
So here's what happened.
He was trying to stop these bullies from picking on his friend.
And it was the one he put off until the end.
So he rode his bike and said, I'm going to get you.
But then he had a knife and they stabbed him in the stomach.
And Kevin Spacey was there.
He watched the whole thing and didn't do any.
Cool job, K-Pax.
I don't know how you return from that in this movie.
It's the end of the movie, Justin.
Fuck me.
It's not like they end it.
He gets stabbed and they're like, well, that sucks, Bailey.
What happened is, as Haley was dying, he grabbed Kevin Spacey's shirt and said, pay it forward.
And then Kevin Spacey stabbed the three bullies.
He went, one, two, three, done.
And now Haley, you pay it.
Ah, fuck.
I should have taken you to the hospital.
I'm the worst dad ever.
I want to say something to you.
I have six podcasts to record today.
I'm legitimately bummed out about this movie.
I saw it in theaters when I was like 11.
That explains a lot.
Can we get like another, a whole other...
Whole other subject.
Is there another...
Who wants to...
Have the first person say, I'm going to pay this forward.
I'm going to not tell anybody to watch this.
I'm going to tell nobody this is in the theater.
I'll pay it forward.
He was very antagonistic.
It was one of those things where he gets stabbed and you're like, oh, it's a kid.
I get it.
Fucking great.
This is the Haley Joel thing that starts the pay it forward movement, right?
Am I missing something about that?
Pay it forward movement.
Oh, we have to move on.
We have to move it forward.
Hey everybody, we want to take a quick break from the live action to provide you with this important...
It's not live though, is it?
Well, I mean, it was live when we made it.
Now it's not live anymore.
Now it's dead as fuck.
It's dead as disco, Griffin, but we still wanted to take a moment for the Money Zone to tell you about Simple.
Simple is the way banking should be.
Take everything you know about banking and flush it down the fucking toilet.
Like a bill info turd.
Simple doesn't even use money.
What does it use?
Cookie points?
It uses cookie points.
It's the internet's premier cookie point transaction facility.
Well, they don't actually use money for some stuff.
You don't have to have a minimum balance.
There's no monthly fee.
There's no overdraft charges.
And you can use over 55,000 ATMs around the globe for free.
You can deposit your checks also by taking a picture of them.
I like that.
But I'm bad with money.
Can Simple yell at me when I try to spend too much money on dumb shit?
Hey, dummy.
I want to help you reach your goals.
It's like tough love.
You tell how much you want to save and it'll tell you how much you can spend on fun shit.
And you'll still have money to pay for the bills.
And save your money.
Set one up for your max fun contribution, it says here.
So you can just put that aside.
And maybe set that number to 1,000.
Maybe jack that up because you're so Simple rich.
Because you did Simple good.
You can pay your bills super fast.
Is this a fake one that's going to take all the money that I have from me?
I know why you would think that.
But you're wrong.
They're an actual real ass company.
And your account's FDIC insured.
And they don't sell your data.
And it's all very good.
Now, the Simple.com is popping off so hard that they have like a wait list to get in it.
To get onto it.
But you can skip that.
Sorry, we're full.
We only got room for chicks.
I know the McElroy brothers.
So I can get in for free.
Oh, come on in then.
Simple.com slash my brother.
Let me do my bit.
Let me do my bouncer bit.
Okay, finish the bouncer bit.
I thought it was done.
Come on in then.
Simple.com slash my brother.
Okay, let's talk about Squarespace.
Yes, two different people listened to this and said, yeah, let's give them money to talk about us.
Squarespace is the all-in-one platform that makes it fast and easy to create your own professional website or online portfolio.
Listen, you've heard us talk about Squarespace a lot.
They've been chopping and screwing it.
Improving it.
They got new designs, new features, even better support.
They have beautiful designs for you to start with if you're a dummy and don't know how to website.
If you're not a dummy and you do know how to website, you can take those designs and chop and screw them even more.
To create a bespoke website of your own bespoking.
This sounds amazing, Griffin.
It is fucking amazing.
It's expensive though, right?
It's not expensive.
It costs dollars a month.
Eight dollars a month.
And you get a free domain name if you sign up for a year with that.
So do it.
They have responsive design.
It'll work on all your products.
You can start without a credit card.
You can just do a free trial.
Go to squarespace.com and use the offer code MYBROTHER.
That's all one word.
MYBROTHER.
And you can get 10% off your first purchase.
That's Squarespace.
Check it out, you dummy.
I got a personal message here.
To Lisa from Don.
Don says May 26th is our third or fourth wedding anniversary.
Pretty close.
Pretty good job.
And May 31st is Lisa's 28th birthday.
Happy birthday and happy anniversary from your sweet, sweet husband.
Your pup, Jonas.
Your kitty, Blueberry.
And your favorite trio of podcasting brothers.
Travis, a sad lib would really make her day.
Sorry, Travis is dead.
That's why he's not here.
He's not dead. Don't say that.
Travis will never die.
He's got the secret diet that keeps you alive forever.
Happy birthday, Lisa.
Sorry we couldn't Travis you.
But I don't know where that fool is.
Have you heard from him today?
Nah.
I got a message to Henry and Allie from...
Should have read this ahead of time.
Tilda Swinton's pussy and associates.
Is that a callback?
I hope we haven't talked about that.
Salutations.
Yael's wedding was the blast of blast.
You two are simply the best two people that we know.
And we are so happy for you.
Now go and get to work on growing your cat harem.
Because buddy told us you wanted friends.
Here's hoping the goofball reading this
pronounce your names goofily.
It's Henry and Allie.
How we can fuck up Henry and Allie.
I fucked up the grammar of that sentence.
I said how we can fuck up.
So even I fucked that up I can't fuck up that name.
Henry.
Sorry. Henry.
Anyway guys, good job.
Good job getting married.
Big thanks to everybody who came out to the live shows too.
We're going to spread them out probably a little bit.
Is the first one.
They all went super well.
I feel like we met everybody at all three shows.
And you were all super fucking cool.
We'll have to do it again real soon.
Because I'm turning the corner on New York City.
I actually think it's a nice place to be.
As opposed to just like a trap that you fly into
and then you can't fly out of.
The Bermuda Triangle.
It's the Bermuda Triangle, yes.
Of cities. But actually it's pretty tight.
They got real good Korean food there.
Oh boy.
That's a story for another time.
Anyway, thanks for listening.
We'll get back to the live show now.
This Yahoo answer was...
Oh, I'm going to fuck this name right up.
You want to try this one?
You never are in this position of having to try it.
How do I know?
Ivica Fulnovic.
Better than nothing.
It's asked by Yahoo answers user
Grand Duchess Anast.
Who asked...
Have you ever heard of the
McDizzle at McDonald's?
I have heard of it and only one of my friends
have heard of it. Do you know?
I love the conversational Yahoo is the best.
Hey, did you guys know about this?
Yeah, that's just typed on screen.
This...
This fucking Yahoo Knights mystery
sent me down such
a rabbit hole.
Because there are
secret orders online
who assure you
that there exists a McDonald's secret menu.
Much like In-N-Out.
Much like Peteri's and so many
other chain fast food restaurants.
Is the argument, is the conceit
here that like, among the
absolute baseline
level training that a McDonald's employee receives
there is another level that
they have to come in on Saturday
to learn the secret menu know-it-all?
We're not talking about if you can't get a pasta
we're talking about taking their garbage food
and making it into other garbage.
Let's start with for instance...
Make it worse.
Was that Tim Gunn
or Jean-Luc Picard?
I couldn't tell you.
We'll start with the poor man's Big Mac.
And this is a secret menu...
What's the rich man's Big Mac?
Burn.
Take that, Ollie.
Oh man.
The beginning sentence of that
is my favorite.
Who doesn't love Big Mac?
A lot of people actually...
But not everyone loves its price.
Yeah. How much?
35 cents.
So if you want to get something
close to Big Mac without paying the full price
what you can do is order a McDouble
but remove the ketchup and pickles.
Instead, ask for extra onions, lettuce
and a Big Mac sauce.
It tastes almost the same because of the absence
of the sesame seed buns and a slice of cheese.
You can get
at least three of these secret
secret budget Big Mac
for the price of a Big Mac.
I want you all to picture the face
of the McDonald's employee when you go
I want a McDonald's but hold on.
Before you start making a McDouble.
I want a McDouble.
But hold on.
Here's the thing. I'm going to chop it and screw it up.
I'm talking after onions.
I'm just going to hand you
this pre-made McDouble.
You take this and you leave.
And I go back.
They may not
be on to the game until
you say and um
Big Mac with sauce.
It's like um
an extra one of those
and give me those and
Big Mac sauce.
Maybe you just have
I mean if you have them.
I heard it's just Dallas, Mildred and Jackson.
How about
oh this is fucking the worst.
This one can't be
This one can't be something that you just say.
It has to be
you're a piece of shit.
And then you fucking
sloppy handed Guy Fieri
at the sad McDonald's table
like
This is the
McBland sea and air burger.
Captain Planet may have been a thing in the 90s
but this burger is like the powers
of Captain Planet.
This burger is like the powers of
Captain Planet combined.
I don't think diarrhea
was one of the elements of a
Imagine eating a hamburger
and the chicken, sure.
And the filet of fish, sure. All in once.
Fuck you.
So yeah.
Epic burger is epic. There's a picture.
It's the
Oh God.
Anyone like to come up and see the picture?
No.
Jesus Christ.
Let's talk about the McCrape recipe.
McDonald's has crepes?
Kind of.
I'm not sure you're pronouncing
McCrape properly.
And then we went for some French breakfast.
Why did you go to McDonald's then?
I went to McDonald's but I want something
with an international flair.
I considered both a breakfast and a dessert.
And a thing, apparently. That exists.
This secret menu item will allow you
to eat crepe McDonald's style.
Just like you've always wanted to.
You guys have done such a great job
with chicken and hamburgers.
What I was wondering is...
Maybe a crepe?
Just or Mr. McDonald's hot cakes
because they're extremely delicious.
I didn't make that up. That's on here.
I'm not sharing the treats.
I'm writing it to you right now.
That's the person.
Then buy a yogurt parfait.
Simply put the yogurt inside the pancake
and wrap it up like a crepe.
Top the pancake with fruit, granola,
and optional syrup.
That's it. You have your own homemade
slightly-eaten McCrape.
You laugh but right now there's a guy
at Taco Bell like...
Here's the thing.
That's not a crepe.
That makes it a fucking pancake with shit inside.
That's a sloppy boy.
That does not change it from a pancake to a crepe.
It's just like a crepe.
No.
It looks like dump.
It really does look like puke.
In a pancake.
Welcome to our show.
We talk about pictures you can't see.
No, we're painting work pictures.
It looks like if you jammed
oats and a hand grenade
inside a pajama.
It's what it looks like.
How's that?
But now you know what it is.
We can go on.
There's a Mc10-35.
Half breakfast, half lunch items.
Just keep that in mind
next time. Just say I want a Big McChicken.
It's a triple down basically.
Now wait. I have a question for you.
How do you do onus and not
address the McNizzle?
Oh, it doesn't exist.
I think it's not real.
You guys want to take some audience questions?
Yeah, we can start that.
Who has a question that's good?
Justin, do you want to point them out
so the whole onus is on you?
Do you want to point out the people?
Sir, right here. Come on down.
Come on down.
I apologize you
aren't going to get the best view of this show
but we'll get you back.
What's your answer?
I'm Marco.
Marco, is this a good question?
No, I don't think it's a bummer question.
Oh, hold on.
There was a second half of it.
I don't think it's a bummer question.
Last time we did a live show we had people come up
and be like, oh, no, it's great, it's great, it's great.
Girlfriend just laughed at me and...
All right, Marco.
All right, so I'm the oldest of four
and I've always gotten along fine with my siblings.
I don't have a whole lot in common with them.
They're more like super into sports.
Yeah.
But now we're all getting to be grownups
and I feel like
there are so many families that have
so much tight sibling bonding.
How do I get to be friends with my siblings?
It's easy.
You've got to find financial incentives.
Start a podcast so you can pay the bills.
I mean, before we had the podcast
it was sports for us.
All sports, 24-step.
So you have three brothers?
One sister, two brothers.
Are all three of them into sports?
Yeah, she's like a business school
marketing kind of person.
Just kind of like pop culture.
Which one's your favorite?
Which one's my best?
You can be honest.
She sounds like the best.
Your brothers are into sports.
Okay, so it sounds like I've figured out the problem, Marco.
You're the odd dog.
You're the odd man out.
You've got to realign everything
you think is worthwhile and valuable.
You've got to stop liking the things you like
and like the things you hate.
But if you can teach yourself to do that
you have given yourself the ability
to like everything in the world.
Love me.
Should we cancel the show now?
Was that it?
Was that everything?
You could get a really specific sports knowledge.
I think that's a good...
You pick one team...
You have a really great highlight.
If you get deep into a sports
well that they have no knowledge of
they will just assume you have a base level
of sports knowledge.
You can build off that.
The onus then becomes on them.
They're in the highlight, just like you.
That's a great plan until the first time
you try to watch a football game with them
and they're like touchdown!
So basically, Justin, your advice sounds like
what you should do is instead of
alienating his brothers and sister
because he's not in the sports
he should alienate them by being into a sport
they know nothing about.
The numbers aren't in your favor right now.
In this family game
you're losing 3-1.
Maybe you pick a specific sportsman
to get super into.
And you try to inject him
into every sports conversation.
Yeah, Jordan's great.
He's no Flick Rickleson.
Flick Rickleson, you know her?
This man can hook a ball at a wall
and another man will catch it.
How does highlight work?
I just know the ball travels extremely fast.
Some are scoops and then concussions.
Yeah, it's a very dangerous sport.
So my advice would be that
the desire to want to be close to them
and get along with them seems to me
like it would override everything else.
And something like setting out and saying
I'm going to make this work because
it is important to me, I'm going to make it a priority
is really all you need to do.
Because everything else is just icing.
But the relationships between you
and your brothers and your sister
is something that if you say this is a priority
and I'm going to make this work
and I'm going to stay close to them
and become close to them, everything else is done.
Some relationships take more work.
Some of them are natural effects,
like you just click with people.
But if it's your family,
then maybe you have to force it a little bit.
I mean, really, yes, I hate these two.
But you find the things...
Interests don't have to be what you have in common.
The common desire is wanting to get along.
The common desire is wanting to be close.
And then you build off of that and say,
hey, I will go with you to see a football game
and you come with me to see a weird live show
where three dudes get up and talk about grenades and vagina.
Talk about you.
It'll be great.
Does that help?
Yeah. Thanks, Mark.
Anybody else?
Want to help?
I saw the hand go first right there.
Yes, stand up.
Yes, yes, perfect.
Come on down.
Oh, boy.
Oh, hello.
Hey, everybody.
It's your family friend, Laura Frye.
You don't know Laura,
but hey, everybody, it's Laura.
Hello, Laura.
Laura, how can we help?
Is it sad or about poop or...?
Okay.
So we are headed to the beach
in a few weeks
and we have a great friend who we love
but who's going with us.
Happens to be one of those friends, though,
that every story you say,
he possibly has one that tosses in.
I mean, constantly.
So how do we spend nine hours
and not jump out of the car?
Can you mouth his name to us
if we know who he is so we just don't...
Like, it won't come up.
Oh, nobody from home.
Nobody from H now.
Can you top...
Can you re-top?
Oh, yes, you can.
Cool story.
That made me remember another one
that's even better
than the one you told me just then.
Like, maybe...
And if he...
If he does not realize
that he is being
inceptioned by the, like,
third or fourth time...
Cool thing, Greg.
You know what? It's so funny that you said that
again after the thing I said after the thing you said.
Oh, no, shit!
Tell your first story again!
Like, that reminds me of a story!
Drop your original one!
Yes!
But then he's going to do the same thing
and then you will both die the whole day.
What about...
Turn on some tunes.
Turn on some...
Tell the most boring stories you can
think of. Just really lob them
like a slow ball, but on top of that, like,
one time I ate a sandwich, like, nailed it.
You got it.
Don't put yourself
in this situation.
Do you have a car? Do you have a luggage rack?
Can you put some peanut butter
in his mouth?
Is there gonna be a lot of
peanut butter?
How much peanut butter does it take?
How much peanut butter does it take
a man to eat nine hours?
What's it, the cubic volume of a man's mouth?
It's gonna look...
By the end of the road trip, it's gonna look
a little bit like Dumbledore in your backseat.
I warn you.
I don't remember what it was like.
Did that help?
So much.
Is there anyone here?
Do you want to write?
Sorry?
Anyone in?
This guy who was sent in by Derek Engel.
Thank you, Derek.
It is by...
Brandon Lambkin, you asked.
Don't put your full name on the line.
Is it okay to trim
my dog's pubic hair?
Guys,
can we be delicate
in the representation of an owl or a bee?
Can we just help, please?
I just got a dog
for my fianc, and it is about
five to six months old.
Dogs get pubes at five to six months old?
A little intimidating.
Yeah.
When she rolls over, you can see
extremely long pubic hair.
Is it okay for me to trim it,
or will it affect the dog?
It'll affect the dog, probably.
It will affect the dog's gait,
I bet.
And their general mood probs.
Chaz, you worked at a kennel for a while,
and I know that your specialty was
to trim your ears.
Okay, I was going to give them a fair warning.
A spoiler warning, because it's going to
spoil your day.
I squeeze dog buttholes.
I was known for it.
Fastest hands in the West.
There's a gland...
I don't know why dogs...
Hold on.
Time out.
There's a gland back there
that makes stinky.
Why do they need that in their life?
Hey, you know how many awesome things
I gave dogs?
Check this out.
We're going to balance it all out.
Put a thing in their butthole,
people are going to squeeze.
Here's my question about dog pubes.
I guess my question is...
Talking about dog pubes now after that
is weirdly refreshing.
Is this person's concern
if they don't trim these pubes?
It's entirely aesthetic.
Okay, great.
I just don't want people to judge my dog's
super long pubic hair.
Have you seen Steve's dog's pubic hair?
Jesus.
They want to trim that shit.
Got stuck on the wrong nose.
I guess my question is...
Where does that region
end and begin?
Is there a definitive...
That's tummy hair.
Tummy hair stops here.
Look at that bush!
I think you have to put a bikini
on the dog.
I guess the real question is,
do you bleach their asses off?
Travis!
We were all thinking him.
There's not a single person here.
They will be asked to leave.
Raise your hand.
The smile this guy was giving us
when he put his hand...
Goddamn it.
It's burning right in the air.
Is there anybody else
whose look we can see
and make fun of?
You must have a weird look.
Why would hair grow
faster than the hair on the rest of the body?
Is there a breed where it's
just like a bushy breed?
Just like Chihuahua.
You gotta maintain that shit
before it gets out of hand.
Going up here, we're really trainable.
I'm Iranian, smart,
but kind of standoffish.
And like the Yorkshire Terrier,
huge bush.
There's just no going into it.
Who here loves talking about dog bush?
That's okay.
Do we have another audience question?
Dog down!
Let's say it right there.
Come on down.
Everybody give him some applause.
He hasn't done anything
in this room.
Dead air is like weird.
What is your name sir?
My name is Ryan.
My younger brother
is about to leave for college.
I moved home since then.
How do I deal with being
basically the only child again
for the first time since I was five?
Is there a wall between your bedrooms?
Take it out.
Look who's here!
King Ryan!
Ryan's gonna do
a little reworking
on the house.
He's gonna take that wall,
clean the fuck out.
Ryan, if I might suggest,
you could also just totally regress
and be like, I'm the only child now.
Take care of baby Ryan.
Oh, take care of me?
I want ice cream.
Ice cream, daddy ice cream.
Buy me a dinosaur copy.
Baby, I want all the toys
on Toy Store.
Baby, you gotta love me.
Wait for the show dinosaur.
Yeah, let's hear it for dinosaur.
The show is on ABC Family.
Should we talk about
the plot of dinosaur?
I mean, the bit where we talked
about the plot of pay-for-wear
was such a joint hit.
Are you sad, Ryan?
Just in general?
I mean, what's your day-to-day
happiness look like?
I mean, that's your brother leaving.
Does it make you sad?
Yeah.
I mean,
what would you say
your actual question was?
Let's pretend that some people
might not have been paying
super close attention.
Because they were thinking
about a bit they were gonna do
with you taking the wall down.
And they didn't actually hear the question
that you needed help with.
This is kind of a thought experiment
that we do so far on the show.
So what would you say
your actual question was?
You know, what are some tips
for being the only...
The only child?
Could you pretend like your brother had died
and you guys didn't talk about
the horrible accident?
Oh, yeah.
What was that sound?
Travis hitting the nail on the head
with a hammer.
Pretend your brother died.
He's dead now.
Great comedy show, everybody.
What are you doing?
Ironically, the idea of my brother
dying is bringing me some relief.
Oh, yikes.
Oh, man.
But the other side of that is
when you pretend like he died
but then he comes home from college
and isn't dying.
It's basically a deposit you're making
on a future miracle.
Miracles are really just the reversal
of lies you started believing.
God, you are dropping some
Mahatma shit over here.
It's getting real in here.
I think all of that helped.
Yeah, you're welcome.
I'm pretty confident
you're gonna make it.
Thank you, Ryan.
We're done?
Thank you so much, first off,
to the People's Improved Theater
for having us here.
Holy shit, they've been incredible.
We talked about this before
and no fucking idea what we're doing
in this department.
They've done everything.
Most of the people here
were people that missed out on tickets
to the second two shows.
We're doing more?
Yeah.
It's gonna be really exhausting
but we did it for you
so I was thinking
maybe a hand for us.
Because you guys were standing outside
like weirdos,
you probably might have missed
our new merch table.
I bring this up not for us
but for you.
I don't want you...
We don't know how to sell this online.
We don't know how the internet works.
I'll start with the coolest thing.
It's so small,
nobody can describe it.
It's a sweet-ass patch
to be a fraternal order of brothers
with an awesome horse in front of the moon.
We got button packs
and these brand new beautiful tote bags.
They pack your bags and move way tote bag.
We've got some really cool
bumper stickers and everything.
More importantly, even if you don't grab anything
on your way out, grab one of these postcards
and if you use the coupon code...
I won't say it out loud
but use the coupon code.
Does everyone see the coupon code?
Grab the postcard on your way out
and it'll give you a discount
on your order online.
Make sure you grab that
and hang out in the bar,
where I was here.
We'll come out and say hi.
For like 30 seconds and then we have to do another show.
Yeah, whee!
That's your fault, remember.
I hate to interrupt you
live, Justin, but you forgot
to mention to thank Simple.
It's me.
Captain Kangaroo.
Oh, interesting. Special guest.
Special relevant guest,
Captain Kangaroo. Sorry about it, Chief.
But thanks to Simple rebuilding
banking from the ground up the way it should be.
Putting people before policies
and helping you find
clarity in your finances.
I'm having a stroke, buddy.
You can skip the waitlist at Simple.com
slash my brother, Captain Kangaroo.
Back to you, J-Man.
I want to thank
Sawbones for opening
for us.
Thank you, guys.
I learned a lot about my body
during that episode. Yeah, me too.
I'm all warts under
my shirt.
If I took my shirt off,
I'm bristling with
warts.
I'm bristling with anticipation for that.
Big thanks to John Roderick.
Special thanks to John Roderick.
Fuck! I missed it.
This final
answer was sent in by, I just wrote Drew.
I'm assuming this is Drew Davenport. Thank you, Drew.
It's by Yonkomancer's user,
Ciso Altairzio,
who asks,
Who invented cranberries?
I am Druster
Macklemore. I'm Druster Macklemore.
This has been my brother, our brother,
Druster Macklemore. Thank you, Druster.