The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother, and Me, an advice show for the
modern era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother, Travis
McElroy. And I am your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy. I tried to do a normal one.
I tried to think, like, how's a normal person just say the introduction to, like, a normal,
happy person. I thought about, like, I'm unhappy, just like, sure, it doesn't need to be weird just
because I feel weird about doing it. Just like, how do you say your name? Yeah, I thought about,
like, what if I did, like, a howl in the middle of mine? See, it doesn't need to be that every
single fucking time. Yeah, or it doesn't need to be that. We're near 500. We can't keep, we can't
keep escalating. Introducing the program. My name's Justin. I'm a person. I got two brothers.
We do this show. Just because I feel weird about introducing a show doesn't mean I have to make it
weird while I'm doing it. It's hard to get comfortable in my own skin. What with this weird
hair everywhere, this new hair that everybody else is so excited about, but I'm so, so scared
about this hair. I think as long as you say it- Pubes and all? Yes. No, yeah. I think as long as
you say it as a statement of fact rather than, I'm Travis McElroy, right? Rather than, I'm Travis
McElroy, don't make it sound like a question. Statement. I'm Travis McElroy. I'm Griffin
McElroy. I'm Griffin McElroy, and I do hate my pubic hair. Griffin hates his pubes. I want to
tell you guys a story. We often get into the email like a weird thing happened to me in the bathroom.
What do I do? Am I good? Mostly. That's like 28% of the questions we get. Yes. I would like to share
my own, and I want to preface by saying it's not blue. This is not, it's not a blue story. It's
brown. Okay. Okay, Griffin. Justin, did you hear? Thank you. Play the noise. When dad and I flew
into the Los Angeles airport for the Dungeons and Dragons live stream- A lot of weird bathroom users
in there. Well, this was in the LAX bathroom. There was a line, men's room line, and I was
nearing the front of the line. The person in front of me stepped to use the stall, and I hope to God,
I presume an employee of the airport in a vest, I believe a turtleneck, and they had a laminated
badge, stepped up, stepped in front of me, faced me, and said, number one or number two. Okay, so
hold on. They had a turtleneck on? Yes. Was it like a uniform? Was it like LAX uniform? You have to
wear a turtleneck like a Steve Jobs? Oh God, I hope so. Because the other option is just a
passerby said either A, I'm going to help direct traffic, or B, I'm a big old bathroom pervert.
It's one of those two. And looked me in the eye, another human, another human being looked me in
my human eyes and said, number one or number two. It could be both. It could be both a
bathroom pervert and an employee. It seems like a great job. I thought you were saying it can be
number, both number one and number two, as it always is for me. I can't have one without the
other. And so I said, number one, like without thinking, because I was so terrified. And it was
number one. It was number one. And then this person simply directed me, as I said, number one,
a urinal became open, and they directed me towards the urinal. And all I could think is like,
that's what I would have done. What purpose? Why did you ask me? But then you look to the
left and you saw an old, old man just having a shit in the urinal. And that's what you knew.
I think what they were trying to solve for is a problem that happens in men's rooms all across
this great land. And if you traditionally go to a bathroom that only has toilets and no urinals,
you wouldn't be aware of this. When you go in, sometimes there's a bifurcation of the line.
So there's urinals available, but no toilets available. And you're just kind of haunting.
Oh, okay.
It's going to be like that. It's going down like that. And you have to like wave
other people onto the urinals. Like, go ahead. Yeah, that's no, I'm just going to go ahead.
I'm going to wait for one of the little closets here.
While I understand that, I still stand by that there is a better way to ask that question
than number one or number two.
I mean, I will, y'all have given this person way too much credit. This is a profoundly
discriminatory, not inclusive thing, right? Like not everybody goes number one in a urinal.
So fucking chill out, partner. Also, the other thing is, Travis, you should have just said like,
I always forget which one they are and I have to make shitties.
So can you tell me which one?
I need to make dirt.
I'm making a dirty mess. So can you tell me which one is it?
I always forget.
Which one do I make dirt in?
I already made pissies on the plane and now I need to make shitties.
Can you tell me which one it is?
If somebody said number one or number two to me, you know what number I'd give them?
38. That's my age of the years that I have. That's my number of years.
Yeah.
And I'm just going to go wherever I feel like going.
We've got a big man with a big swirly gray mustache says,
I'm a kindred spirit. I also make 38.
I also need to go 38. And let me ask you, how do you get it out of your belly button?
How do you polish the tool afterwards?
He steps into a stall and just tendrils start shooting out of it.
Like the birthing scene in Men in Black.
You hear steam like whistling through some kind of steampunk device.
Trav, you brought up the Dungeons and Dragons thing.
I know you caught some FaceTime with some famos.
I did.
And I just want to know if you had any interactions.
Did you get that Lillard stink on you?
I did. He was nice. He was a very nice person, that Matthew Lillard.
I had a lot of fun playing the Dungeons and or Dragons with everyone.
I don't give a shit about that.
Let me tell you about Joe Manganiello.
I want to hear about famos or nothing.
Yes. I'm going to tell you about Joe Manganiello.
A mountain of a person.
Perhaps the largest, just square footage wise, largest human being I have ever been beside.
Yep. The fridge is what we call him.
At one point, he stood in front of me and blocked out the sun.
Listen, I'm not the biggest person in the world.
I'm 5'10", but I'm a fairly broad 5'10".
And I felt like a tiny child in his presence.
Like, I think he could have juggled me.
How many of his big D20s just turned into ash in his hand when he just crushed it with so many bones?
I watched him try to eat a peanut butter cracker and it just turned to crumbs in his hand.
And then he said, I wrecked it.
And he started punching through buildings.
Yeah.
He's a dad figure.
Dad showed me a picture of him with him and I said, oh, two dads.
There's my two dads that I have.
My dad and my real dad, my bio dad.
My big bone crushing fridge dad.
My big strong dad and my regular dad.
Enough of this Hollywood bullshit.
Thank you.
Whoa.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Wait, really?
Yeah, I am going to go to the bathroom.
Number one and number two.
Number one, Justin.
Okay.
This has been so fun, but I'll just be right back.
Okay, I visited my grandmother over the weekend and we started to watch a show together.
We watched two episodes before I left and promised to text about the episodes as we
watched them.
Problem is, from the third episode on, there have been many sex scenes, some of which are
relevant to the plot.
How can I binge a show and talk about it with my grandma when folks are blatantly getting
it on?
That's from Chaste in Chicago.
And folks, if you don't start sending in fucking relevant information in these questions, I'm
losing my mind right now.
How on earth would you think we don't need to know what the show is, right?
What if it's mad about you?
And I'm supposed to talk about Paul Reiser and Helen Hunt.
I've got all this great Reiser material, Reiser shine, etc.
Yes.
And I can't fucking do any of it because I don't know what show you're watching.
Yeah, there's a lot of porking and mad about you.
I'm going to email them.
I'm going to email them right now.
And let's find out if we get an answer by the end of the show if it is mad about you.
Just send a, just send mad about you?
Question mark?
Twas it?
Twas it mad about you?
Um, first of all, don't be so close minded.
Your mom's mom or dad's mom probably, I mean, they porked at some point and that's why you're
here, right?
In a roundabout way, their porking led to your parents porking, which led to you.
Even if your parents happen to be adopted by this grandparent, I can't guarantee they
porked at some point.
They probably porked.
Yeah, they probably did pork.
That's a good thing to say.
That's one good thing is like, I'm glad you did this probably.
You know what I mean?
Like, I'm glad that you probably, I'm glad you probably did this because otherwise I
wouldn't be sharing this moment with you.
Maybe like when you get to that sexy and like, text your grandma and say like, I really like
this episode, but I was confused by that one scene where they seem to be just slamming
their bodies into each other.
What's that about?
They were really slapping shanks and I'm not quite sure what the purpose of that was, grandma.
So tell me now.
What was even happening there?
What's that?
What is that?
Did that hurt them?
They seem to be in pain of some sort.
I couldn't place it.
Are they okay?
They seem to be laying down in bed, but very exhausted.
So please tell me why it was.
Did they run?
Are they okay?
What happened?
Is it a sickness?
Justin, are you done drafting the email?
Yeah, the email has been sent.
All right.
And now we wait.
Chased in Chicago.
Option two, you text your grandma and be like, I really like this episode, especially the
part where they fucked.
Or you could just-
No, that's nothing.
That's not helpful.
Yeah, sometimes you just say stuff that's not helpful.
And it's a joke of how bad helpful it is.
Then what would you do?
I mean, unless it was like, you know, Skinamax.
I bet there was stuff that happened in the episode that was not slapping shanks.
But then you would worry, like if you said, like, I thought the car chase was really good
and all that negotiation scene was so tense.
And then grandma writes back, like, what'd you think about the fucking?
Then you are probably in the clear.
And this question doesn't matter anymore, Travis.
I would argue that that is best case scenario.
Okay, then what if it's a little more subtle and it's just like, what do you think about
the rest of it?
And then a winky face of a-
And then a winky face and maybe like an eggplant.
An emoji of two ham shanks that are moving in together.
They're slapping together one might say.
Oh, I thought you like maybe got like an apartment together.
Maybe like, what about this?
Oopsie snack time.
Saying something like that to your grandma when the sex starts.
Like, oops, oops-a-daisy snack time.
I don't know if you're syncing up your watch, are you?
Yeah, I don't know if you're live texting it.
That was what I imagined.
Why else would you text?
Text about the episodes as we watch them.
So wait a minute.
I'm just going to get a bunch of fuck.
I'll be middle of my day and my grandma is going to be like, oh man, I'll tell you what,
the rock has really got these ballers around his finger, huh?
Anyway, I can't believe he went to this-
Wait, did you get the answer back?
Is it ballers?
Did you get the answer back?
No, I don't know.
It's just a guess.
It seems the right.
It's, it felt good in the moment.
Yeah, grandma's like ballers.
I sure hope that R-E and E hug it out.
I'm betting it's either ballers or entourage.
That's my bet.
You think it might be entourage?
It's definitely ballers.
It feels like it's probably ballers.
Okay.
A show that may only exist.
I feel like ballers, okay, I feel this way about a lot of entertainment programming,
but I feel this way definitely about ballers where it's like a fake, it's like a facade.
Yeah, and if I walked in through the front, like on a sound stage,
if I walked in through the front door of ballers,
it would just be two by four supports and paint, paint claws and everything.
Like there's no actual show in there.
Like you're not actually, like they only shoot enough to do like the montage
of please don't cancel your HBO because Game of Thrones ended.
We got lots of other things.
It's like at some point, like somebody said to Dwayne The Rock Johnson,
like, hey, we're good friends, right?
Will you come see my community theater production of Cats or something?
And Dwayne The Rock Johnson said, I can't, I'm in a new show that I need to film.
And they're like, oh, what's the show about?
It's like, it's called Ballers.
And it's a real show.
It's definitely a real show.
And then they're like, well, I can't wait to see previews for it.
He was like, oh, and then he had to go to someone and said,
please help me make previews, but we can't say what day or time it's on.
We don't want people to watch it.
And so it only exists in preview form.
Okay, so just a quick update.
I am looking at a Vulture recap of season one, episode three of Ballers,
which would be the inciting episode.
It's called Move the Chains.
And here's just a little excerpt from their recap.
Thanks to this episode, I practically see Reggie's whole arc
mapped out for the rest of the season.
While he claims to be looking out for his boy Vernon,
even telling Spencer he's mostly pissed that he wasn't consulted
about the ideas that he had for his friend and his brand,
we later learned that that's all bullshit.
And then more stuff, more stuff, more stuff, next paragraph.
But enough about Reggie.
Let's get to Ricky smashing Alonzo's mom.
So it seems like maybe this is Ballers.
It could be Ballers.
Because I think episode three is the episode,
if I remember correctly, let me go through my notes.
This is the one where Ricky does smash Alonzo's mom.
So it could be Ballers.
Can you just text your grandma about the artistry, right?
I'm really believing this.
This is appropriate.
I love the lighting, you know, like that kind of thing.
Oh, it seems like they hired an intimacy director.
This seems very realistic.
Is that a dog?
Yeah.
How do you think I'm feeding my family?
Podcasts?
It's like a fight choreographer, Griffin,
but instead of the two ham shanks punching each other,
you choreographed the two ham shanks.
Stop, stop, stop.
You guys know more about movies and drama and theater
and the arts than I do because you went to college
for some of that stuff.
Yes.
Is this a real joke you're telling me
or is this dry olive garden pasta?
No, this is a real thing.
Intimacy director is hired to choreograph love scenes
and really any kind of physical intimacy.
Love scenes!
Yes, love scenes, Griffin.
Not just physical love, but perhaps other kinds of love
so that everyone on set feels comfortable and it's realistic.
I think that that's important, right?
Making sure everybody feels comfortable.
I just am imagining something to be like,
you guys know what Porkin's all about.
I think that's the opposite of them making everyone
feel comfortable, Griffin.
The reason Griffin had a hard time believing
that intimacy coordinator is a real thing
is because Rob Schneider did not make a movie
where he stars as a-
Right?
I mean, because of the absence of the Rob Schneider movie,
like the Pork Doctor or whatever the fuck he'd call it.
I mean, it would be the Sexspert, which is unfortunate
because that'd be our brand.
It sucks for Travis especially.
Drunk through the mud.
But that's why he had a hard time believing it
because it's not a Rob Schneider movie already.
I just, now that you've explained why,
it makes a lot of sense.
I think it's an important role.
But my brain immediately went to,
so you guys ever done kissing?
Kissing.
How about a Yahoo?
Yeah, I'd love that, Griff.
Thank you.
I have a miniature one here.
It's not gonna be a good jump have for discussion,
but when I read it, I laughed for like a minute straight.
It made me very happy.
Jack sent this one on Thinks Jack.
It's Yahoo Answers user, Greta, with all caps.
Greta, who's a very recent member.
Greta asks, I have a TV that talk, but no picture?
Huh?
I have a TV that talk, but no picture.
My TV talks.
My TV does talk, but it doesn't produce picture.
It talks the sound of the show.
The thing is, I think it's easy to assume
that you're hearing the sounds from TV,
but Griffin, well, that's the TV just talks.
Okay, let's get into this, yeah.
I've been watching The Americans and Keri Russell
sometimes speak American on that show.
Sometimes they'll speak English,
sometimes they'll speak Russian,
but you're saying that it's the TV.
Uh-huh, and it's just like, hello, Greta.
It could be the TV.
We don't know for sure.
And you like TV, because here's the thing,
my Amazon Alexa talks to me sometimes.
What if this just went a step further
and was just like, hey, Greta, and you're like,
hey, TV, please turn on picture.
And the TV was like, no.
And you're like, what?
The screen's all fucked up,
but they're in the big throne room,
and the dragon seems very angry,
and you know what?
I do want actually my spin on the Game of Thrones finale
because it could be a softened sort of blow.
Would you enjoy that, Greta?
Uh, no, TV, I think I'd just rather watch it.
Could you show it to me?
This part's dirty.
Your mom told me to not let you see the dirty parts.
So this part's dirty.
It's totally fine.
My mom left, but before she did,
she said, and tell TV it's okay to see the dirty parts.
So Greta's watching.
It's really dirty, though.
Greta's watching Ballers episode three
and fucking Denny's walking up towards Alonso's mom
and starts to pull his pants down.
The screen just cuts to black,
and Greta's like, what the fuck?
And then Greta's like,
uh, he pulled his pants right back up.
He pulled them right back up.
And then he took her up for ice cream.
Took her to Wendy's.
They got a Frosty together.
He took her home.
He pulled his pants up and said, I gotta get to church.
And then that was the end of the scene.
Do you have a real Yahoo?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Here's one that was sent in by Jeremy S.
Important science question.
We're very good at these.
Thanks, Jeremy.
It's Yahoo Answers user, Lana, who does ask,
what happens if you eat pudding mix
and then drink a bunch of milk?
Does it turn to pudding in your stomach?
Well, not if you don't shake around a bunch.
You gotta shake around a whole bunch.
Come on.
Get one of those old timey shaky belts that they have
on like funny TV shows about like how whack old stuff was
and give it to jiggle and jiggle and jiggle year round.
And then, I guess you'll die.
It's not, yeah, you'll probably, no, you'll be fine.
I mean, first off, I bet it would taste pretty good
in that same way that like that dirty way
where if you get a big chunk of chocolate milk mix,
you know what I mean?
Oh, you like that?
Yeah, it's good.
I like that.
I think that that's good.
I don't like it.
Really, okay.
It's powdery.
Yeah, okay.
I like the marshmallows.
In chocolate milk mix?
Yeah, sometimes they have marshmallows in them.
Do they?
Seems like maybe you've never had chocolate milk mix, Griffin.
I thought you said hot chocolate.
You did not think he said that.
He didn't think I said that.
He twice, he repeated himself.
I shoot chocolate milk all the fucking time.
Child.
Uh-huh.
When was the last time you had chocolate milk?
Now.
From a mix.
Right.
Oh, you're having it now, you said.
I'm having it right now.
Shit, listen.
You're loving it.
Wait, what is happening?
This is sonically, this is sonically the worst part of my life.
I don't care for this at all.
This one afternoon, this one May afternoon when I was 38
was sonically the worst thing that ever happened.
Oh, that's weird.
I thought you liked chocolate milk mix because that's the sound it makes.
That's weird that you fucking said that.
I've read the instructions for pudding a lot.
I've made my fair share of pudding, not to brag.
I made my fair share of pudding.
But you prefer British pudding, the proper the Queen's pudding.
A delicious pud.
Listen, I love a pud and I love to make a pud.
No, actually, judging by the leftovers I have every Christmas,
empirically, we don't all love a pudding.
Some people would prefer to leave the pudding where it is
and maybe at the store bought key lime pie.
I bought two anyway.
I don't want to get hung up on a lot of Christmas angst,
but not once have I seen in the directions
and also include a bunch of fucking stomach acid
and bile into the into the equation.
That's not part of the recipe.
Just because you have two of the components
doesn't mean we're not going to wang it with some extra ones.
I also would say, while I appreciate the scientific nature of this question,
you're missing out on the enjoyment of the pudding.
Like if this did work, you wouldn't mix it together in your tummy
and then like say like, mmm.
It would not become pudding.
Now I have pudding.
Right.
It wouldn't become pudding at the point at which it is important
that it is pudding, which is just, if not more so,
prior to going in your mouth.
Have you had pudding today?
Not yet.
But give me a second and then I will have had pudding.
Let me throw myself down this set of stairs
and then I will have had pudding.
Let me shake up my tummy.
Right.
Roll me down this meadow, this buttercup covered hill
and perhaps at the bottom of it, I will have had pudding today.
Put me in this big barrel and roll me over the falls
and then there will have been pudding the whole time.
Put me in coach.
I'm ready to make pudding today.
There are very few foods where the flavor or texture of it
isn't designed for the mouth.
You guys ever think about that?
Wait, what?
There are very few foods
where the flavor isn't designed for the mouth.
Where the flavor and texture of it
is designed to be enjoyed once it's in your belly.
Like that's the peak of it.
All right.
Yeah, there's booze.
Yeah, that's one of them.
But I wouldn't say that's a food.
And I think if you do think that's a food, that sucks.
But I would say any carbonated beverage
where once again a beverage isn't a food, I get that.
But where you're almost guaranteed to make burpees.
You guys are really throwing up some real fucking air balls
right now, some real bricks.
Yeah, you fill a person with milk,
you fill a person with pudding mix,
you shake them around, they're full of pudding.
You know who I bet wishes that worked?
Bears.
Bears and sharks.
What are you eating, dude?
Well, it's a guy, but it's also fudgy gushers.
It's a guy.
It is a guy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is a pudding boy.
Did you guys not have pudding in yours?
Careful, Kevin, I know what to do.
Stand perfectly still.
No, Kevin, here's what you do.
All right, so you're gonna take
all this jello pudding mix.
You're gonna eat it up good.
Trust me, Kevin, it's the only way.
It'll really drive me off or whatever.
Oh, I hate what you're doing.
And then the milk, Kevin.
All the milk, all the milk, all the milk.
Keep going.
Now shake it.
Now do I stand perfectly still?
No, Kevin, quite the opposite.
You're gonna shake it like a Polaroid picture, Kevin.
Just jiggle and jiggle.
Sorry, Kevin.
Can I go?
Yeah, Dylan, you can go.
I'm out of pudding mix.
Yeah, this is the only pudding mix I need.
Munch, munch, munch.
Yeah, and then the boy gets eaten.
I wanted to jump over that part
because it makes me sad.
That part's sad, but at the last second
the bear doesn't do it
because he remembers he has diabetes.
Oh, the last one that he remembers.
Oh, no.
Do you want a yahoo?
Well, let's do another question real quick.
That'll be our third yahoo.
It seems a little bit unnecessary.
We'll do six yahoo's in a row.
Let's do another question then.
Here's a quick question.
Whenever I get my hair washed at a salon,
I close my eyes because I don't want to make eye contact with the stylist.
Oh, perfectly normal.
I'm worried the stylist will think I'm some perv
if I close my eyes,
but I'm also worried it'll be worse if I look.
Oh, man.
That's the same reason.
Is that weird? Am I creepy?
If you walked into a salon
and saw someone with their eyes closed getting a haircut,
what would you do?
That's from Eyes Wide Shut in Shanghai.
Cool.
I don't think we've ever had a question from Shanghai before.
That's neat.
I think, and I don't know,
maybe I'm in the wrong here,
but I think it's way weirder
to be sitting there
because you have two options if you keep your eyes open.
You can go straight ahead,
which is, after a long period of time,
weird,
to track what they're doing with your eyes,
which is even weirder.
All right.
Hey, everybody.
Eye contact. Unbroken eye contact.
That's no good.
There's only another way.
Everybody, on a monthly basis,
you have to come to me
and sit down in front of me,
supplicating yourself to me,
while I touch your hair for a half hour.
In this situation,
there are infinite,
imaginable vectors
through which things can become uncomfortable.
I think that's fair to say.
This scenario,
getting the haircut,
it can be very uncomfortable,
which is why, for me,
I have had the same hairstylist now for a few years.
It's one of the longer streaks I've had with a hairstylist.
She does a great job cutting my hair,
but the reason I decided to stay
is because I had found comfort there.
I had found a routine that was comfortable.
It's a huge selling point.
So I don't think we...
I don't think this is...
This is not, like, a travesty, right?
Like, this person closes their eyes when they get a haircut.
I'm sure that your hairstylist has seen weirder things
because it's an inherently strange
human flaw
that these weird,
sticky, itchy things
keep coming out of our heads
and other parts of our body
and I wish they just would stop for, like, a minute
so I could get a handle on it.
I think you've just made...
This is, I think, a fun thing
that you could do to break the ice
with a new hairstylist
is you sit down and, you know,
there's a little bit of tension, you know,
because it's new and you don't want to talk about...
The first time they cut hair, scream in pain.
Oh! That's interesting.
And then you're both gonna have a good laugh about that
because they're gonna jump
or you say, like,
and I have a minute, and then you say an individual goodbye
to each hair they've just cut.
They make the second cut, you do it again.
You repeat that over and over again.
What if you have a bunch of little
bones sticking out of your scalp
mixed in with your hair?
Oh, that's fun.
Just to mix it up like you're
King Koopa from the Super Mario Brothers movie.
I like that.
Maybe you have a few Double Dare flags in there.
Cool.
And so as they're digging around, they find one,
and you're like, you're on a space ship.
Maybe as they cut it shorter and shorter,
you've written a message on your scalp
that says, like, too short.
Too short.
Start over. Try again.
Maybe one thing you could do
would be to,
as the haircut progresses,
continually compare yourself
to other celebrities.
Like, oh, nice.
Just like Eddie from the Munsters.
Or, oh, nice.
Patrick from Spongebob.
Just continually, he doesn't have hair,
so that wasn't ideal, but you get the idea.
That's really great.
Just like Lance Henderson
in Aliens.
I think giving the hairstylist
an activity to do while they're cutting,
as we are suggesting universally here,
giving them something to occupy themselves,
like a child on a road trip,
is definitely the right way to go.
So you can just close your eyes
and have a good anxiety nap.
Mm-hmm.
Here's all I'm saying.
I used to talk a lot on this show
about social anxiety, right?
Before you've gone, cool!
Yay!
Now, no.
Now, I think,
I don't think of people
who have social anxiety
and don't know what to say.
I don't think those people exist anymore.
You know how I label them now?
Ooh.
If you have memorized...
Hear me out.
If you've memorized 50 riddles,
you'll never be
in a conversation or social situation
where you don't know the perfect
thing to say, because it's probably
a riddle.
One of your 50 riddles, yeah.
One of the 50 riddles you know,
one of them is probably somewhat applicable
to the situation.
There's no such thing as comfortable
socially. There's people who are comfortable
socially and people who haven't memorized
50 riddles. So then...
Because if you've memorized 50 riddles,
that is going to be the perfect icebreaker.
It's fun. What a fun brain
teaser. While I'm cutting hair,
I get to like, you know,
try to unravel
your mysteries.
Right. I think it would be great
to memorize some riddles. And then...
An added benefit, if you find somebody
who has memorized the exact same
50 riddles as you, you marry
them. That's another option.
That's how you know. Or if you see your
hairstylist for long enough,
when they finally solve that 50th
riddle, you can take their
hands and look at them and say,
thank you.
And then you transform into a wind
serpent and you
fly out of the salon.
And you never go back there. But then you're
back a month later. With 50 more
hot new riddles. And you also
bring their ant back from the dead.
Yes. But only if they get the
riddles right. Don't get
the dead ant back if you get
49 of them. You know what I mean?
Ant stays dead. For each
one you'll miss, another
ant's gonna go.
Because that's the wind serpent's curse.
And you should have known that before you agreed to take
me on as a client at this
Super Cuts.
You work at Super Cuts?
You should. That's day
one in the orientation. You work at Super
Cuts, you're gonna lose a few ants
to some cursed wind serpents. That's just
in the manual, man. That's what they always
say. You can't work at Super Cuts without
losing a few ants to a wind serpent.
Listen. And it's terrible curse.
Unless we wanna get a second
job at Super Cuts, we're gonna need to head to the
money zone. Okay.
Cause we won't be making a podcast
in like a week.
Hasbro. They've got a new hybrid
mattress. It combines the pressure relief
of their award-winning foam with
the durable yet gentle springs.
Oh boy. When you lay on this
it's like you're sleeping on a giant's palm
and that giant has moisturized
consistently but not too much.
Right? You know
that's a perfect metaphor or simile or whatever.
Yeah, not a wet giant. Not a wet giant.
Not a wet giant. Just a perfectly
balanced, moisturized giant.
And this new innovation
offers the best of both worlds.
Luxurious comfort and resilient
support just like a moisturized giant.
And even with springs, these
mattresses still come magically in a box
that simply arrives on your doorstep just like
a giant's hand. And you can be sure
of your purchase with Kasseri's 100 night
risk-free sleep on a trial
just like a giant's hand. So basically
these mattresses are
as much like a giant's hand in the real
world as you will find anywhere.
And you can get $100
towards select giant hands
by visiting Kasper.com
slash Brother and using Brother at
checkout to buy one of these giant's hands to sleep
on. That's Kasper.com
slash Brother and using Brother at checkout
$100 off select
giant's hands. Terms and conditions
apply. You guys know about stamps?
These things are like very, very, very
small, sticky hands.
When you put them on a letter, it lets
the post office know that this letter's
good to go, baby, and they will take it
where you need it to go. But only if you use the
right small, sticky hand
like you might find on a rat in a sewer.
Okay.
Every stamp that you get from stamps.com is like a
rat's hand from the sewer. And you put it on
your letters and it's great. Stamps.com
is a very wonderful time
saving tool for your small business. We own
several of those. Stamps.com
eliminates trips to the
rat hand store, which is what I call the post office.
And it saves you money with discounts
you can't even get at the rat hand store.
So rat hands dot com
brings all the amazing services
of the US rat hand store
right to your computer. Whether
you're a small office sending invoices
or an online seller shipping out products
or even a warehouse sending thousands of
packages a day. Stamps.com
can handle it all with ease. You just use your
computer to print official US postage
24-7 for any letter, any package,
any class of mail, anywhere you want to send.
With stamps.com you get five cents
off every first class rat hand
and up to forty percent off
priority mail. So right now our
listeners can get a special offer that includes a
four week trial plus
free postage and a digital scale without
any long term commitment. Just go to
stamps.com. Click on the microphone
at the top of the page and type in my brother.
That's rat hands, that's stamps,
that's rat hands dot biz or
stamps dot com enter my brother. Probably
just stamps dot com though
not the other one. It was a joke
and a pretty freaking one if I had to say it
by myself.
Welcome.
Thank you. No problem. These are real
podcast listeners, not actors.
What do you look for in a
podcast? Reliability is big
for me. Power. I'd say
comfort. What do you think of this?
Oh.
That's Jordan Jesse Go. Jordan Jesse
Go? They came out of the floor?
And down from the
ceiling? That can't be safe.
I'm upset.
Can we go now? Soon.
Jordan Jesse Go.
A real podcast.
Now he's back good.
Not forgotten.
More theremin like.
Now there's just a bug in the studio.
Yes let me get that.
I want to munch. Bugs.
I want to munch.
Squad.
First off, it was dead to me on
Netflix.
Cool.
Cool. I'll just say cool back.
Oh, okay.
I don't
know. Okay, so
this is a weird situation
where
I heard about this
when it was first making the rounds
and
I, it was
like such a munch squad that
I had somehow assumed
that it had, like I had
already done it. Like once I'd heard about it
it just seemed like oh, certainly I've
already done this.
Certainly I've already done this.
But
I haven't.
And so it's Garfield Eats.
Is this
the concept of
the orange cat we all love?
The orange cat is in it.
And it's just the concept
that he does consume food for
calories and power?
Yes, he's
in it. He's in this
one, okay? And it's Garfield Eats.
Introducing, it
says here in the subject line, the
world's first Garfield
mobile app restaurant.
Wait, what is Love Me
Feed Me at Garfield Eats?
It's the world's first
Garfield mobile app
restaurant. So that means that when they
decided to do it
they had to see, has
anybody else done a Garfield mobile
app restaurant? I can't believe
they beat the rush. And the answer is no.
I know. They were the first ones to
pioneer this at Garfield Eats.
Did you say Love Me Feed Me?
Love Me
Feed Me at Garfield Eats. Does it say
that? It's the subject
of the, it's the headline
of the press release. The headline of the press release
says,
like Frankenstein would say,
Love Me Feed Me
Frankenstein Eats? Or like
Audrey 2 from Little
Shop of Horrors might say. Another option.
You all are
getting, it's not that you
can't see the forest for the trees, there's like
a big sign outside that's like
trees ahead and you stopped there.
Like you need to come with me, okay?
Garfield is, this is how this
press release fucking starts, okay?
Garfield is the most read comic strip
in the world. You know that Garfield
Eats. Holy
shit. I do know that. That's the
first. Garfield is the most
read comic strip in the world. M
dash. You know that Garfield
Eats. I remember that about him. A lot.
A lot. Oh.
That's a whole sentence. A lot.
The fabulous funny that
inspired. The what?
Certainly they meant to say feline.
Certainly they meant to say feline, but they don't.
They say the fabulous funny
that inspired books,
movies, and TV
shows. Feed the fabulous
funny. Love him.
The fabulous funny is about
to mark its 40th
year. This is like how John refers
to Garfield if they were like old Victorian
lovers. Oh my fabulous
fun. It's about to mark
his 40th year on the comics
pages. So it's apropos
that Garfield Eats
a new innovative mobile
app for entertainment and ordering
food will make its debut
in the world. What the fuck
do you think apropos means?
What do you think apropos means?
That 40 years of Garfield
being on comic pages
is apropos to do a whole restaurant
about it. Garfield
Eats is a new food experience brought to
you by the world's first
intergaging app.
What? What? What? Stop. You're the
Garfield restaurant. You don't get to make up
that word. That also once
again sounds like some of the most steampunk
shit I've ever heard.
It is gonna fucking. We must
apply force to the intergage if we want
to power our steam zeppelin.
I don't want to do anything else other than this press
release. This is the first sentence
of the second paragraph
of this six paragraph long press release.
It's the world's first intergaging
app and it is
an entertaining and
engaging app.
Fuck. It's a
it's entertaining
and engaging. It's
both entertaining. This is entertaining
me but not engaging me.
It's an entertaining
and engaging app that replaces
the quick service restaurant with
the quick mobile restaurant.
OK. Not a QSR.
A QMR. The app
immerses the user in
a complete
Garfield experience.
Holy. Wait.
How much longer do we have in this episode
because I'm starting to feel like this may be
it. Now Justin
before you continue on with any details
they're just kind of. Oh I'd love to take a break Jeff.
Hold on let me pull over the car.
They're just throwing out that word complete
with a lot of bravado huh.
Because to me a complete
Garfield experience does involve like
a costume and maybe a
giant house that makes me feel like the
perspective of a tiny kitty. Maybe
even a box of dirt I'm supposed to
shit in. Yeah. Unless I can
experience this app through the Oculus Rift.
I don't think this is a complete
Garfield experience. I'd love
that to be true but I don't think that
that's accurate. It's a quick
mobile restaurant. The app immerses
the user in a
complete Garfield
experience offering
cartoons and
augmented reality. Holy
shit. Whoa.
Whoa.
Cartoons
and augmented reality
and food.
Cause it's a restaurant.
It is one. Remember
how it's a restaurant. Yeah.
Cause it still is
and it's got that too cause it's
intergaging. Yeah. Garfield eats
by the way is stylized. No space
eats is all caps.
So that's powerful. Fucking cool.
It's very fucking
cool. It's like a it's a very
punk rock of spelling Garfield eats.
So
on the menu
delicious
healthy farm
two plates and
here they have in parentheses F2P.
This is a free to play
AR Garfield
experience.
You can fucking have this
fucking fresh kale that just came
from a half mile away while you put on
your Google Glass and
have Odie's big powerful
feet step on and crush you baby.
Now
we should warn you there are microtransactions.
Let me finish the clause.
On the menu
delicious healthy
farm to plate lasagna
of course and
pizza shaped like
Garfield and baked
in a wood fire oven.
Ordered through the
app and delivered quickly to anyone
in Dubai.
Justin you just
I have never been so quickly deflated.
I know
I know.
I can't fucking believe you.
What you just did
what you just did was treasonous.
It was treason.
Ordered through the app and is delivered quickly
to anyone in Dubai. Also
this is a sentence.
Also because
Garfield loves his coffee.
Enter the Garfuccino.
Made with 100 percent
Arabica
coffee from Italy.
It's an international
affair.
The word Garfuccino
is the grossest thing
I've ever heard. Like if you
told me that was a euphemism for
vomit I would be like oh man
I gotta go Garf.
I'm gonna Garfuccino all over this place.
I've got a running list
of substances I would
least like to drown in.
And Garfuccino has just
rocketed up the list.
Especially when you consider that
one of my favorite like
abomination words duncuccino
is such a great word
that I love saying.
Yeah they were so close. Garfield eats
co-founders. Oh no!
Are they okay? Oh man!
That's too bad. Sorry
Garfield eats co-founders Nathan
Mosery and Pascal Heider
were born well after Garfield's
rise to fame but both
were fans of the cartoon growing up.
What the fuck could that possibly
matter?
So they're legit. These aren't your
bandwagon Garfield. No they know
they're gonna get the brand right. Knowing
Garfield's penchant for Italian food
they thought Garfield would be the perfect pitchman
for their brand of scooter pizza
I guess. I don't know
that he's a fan of Italian. We never see like
we never see scenes
of him like at a fancy restaurant
enjoying like
bolognese or something
like he's. You're gonna lose this
because his favorite food is lasagna.
No I know that but his favorite food is lasagna.
That doesn't mean like
he's a fan of Italian. It just means he really likes
lasagna. Yeah.
Their vision is to make the ordering
of food fun and easy
utilizing modern technology.
You can use voice recognition
to order.
Here's the thing. How
frequently do you have to
order from the Garfield Eats app
before you're like I don't have the time
to type this every time I want
lasagna. I'm gonna need
to start speaking and just rolling the dice.
If I could have a button like one might get from
Amazon then I would have that
with just a picture of a Garfield
shaped pizza on it that I can push.
No I sold my phone.
I got an Amazon Dash button for Garfield
scooter pizza. And you know what really sucks about that
is when I'm watching my
television stories and one of the
characters on the show says boy
I'd love to have a scooter deliver me a
Garfield shaped pizza in Dubai
which happens in most of my shows.
Yeah that happens eight
time in Ballers episode four.
That's a false positive.
That sucks and maybe I don't want a Garfield.
Of course I am always gonna want a Garfield shaped
pizza. That shit's hilarious.
By the way if you're wondering
I looked it up. Garfield shaped pizza
is like the outline of
his face which looks
to be an impossible
shape to roll a pizza
out into. So every
one of these motherfuckers must
be like hand shaped
into his face.
Nice.
So
okay so Garfield Eats will adhere to
and I'm sure this is everyone's concern
adhere to strict F2P
guidelines on supply
sourcing guaranteeing no GMOs
that doesn't matter. No preservatives
no artificial colors. That's Garfield modified
organisms.
Yeah
he hasn't fucking licked anything.
No artificial
colors and no fertilizers.
I mean I should hope not.
That would be a weird topping as these
things go.
They'll also use rechargeable
electric scooters to deliver
the food in rebox packaging that
can be repurposed. Okay.
Anything can be repurposed. What's the Venn diagram
of people out there
who are so excited about
like is there is that
how big is the overlap between like
yes listen of course of course
I want to eat a Garfield
shaped pizza or maybe even Garfield
shaped lasagna I'm not sure
but only if
it is sustainably
sourced and eco friendly.
Farm to table.
F2P.
Free to play no loot boxes no
pay to win.
Here's something that's just a whole
you guys
know what a nut graph is? Sure.
Griffin you probably know that from journalism.
It's the paragraph in a press release
that's so good that you can't
not have a cum.
Nut graph is the
thing that you like if you're a reporter you like
Dave it's like anytime you need to talk about
this thing like you can
put this in right there.
So the nut graph
for Garfield and this is a paragraph
I'm assuming is in everything Garfield related
from here to eternity.
Nearly 40 years ago
on June 19th 1978
Garfield was born on the
comics pages. The master
mind of cartoonist Jim Davis
that's not what that means.
Garfield is a humorous strip. Or wait let's
change the possibility.
Wait Jim Davis not exist?
Jim Davis was the fictional
creation of the orange lasagna cat Garfield.
Whoa. Garfield is
a humorous strip and you know what
humorous is just about right
huh? That really gets it doesn't say
riotous or funny.
It says it's humorous. It's definitely
not sad most of the
time. It's this unsad
strip except sometimes
it's very sad though I will say that.
It is very sad.
Garfield is a humorous strip centered on
the lives of a lazy
cynical orange cat who loves
lasagna, pizza, coffee
and his remote control. His owner
the long suffering John Arbuckle
and Odie a sweet but dumb
dog. So
can you give me
here's the thing Travis here's the thing
this is five paragraphs in.
I'm excited about this
idea I cannot wait to find out who
this Garfield character is.
Who the fuck is Garfield?
This is so good I love all of it
F2P lasagna for sure.
Who the fuck is Garfield?
I cannot wait to find out about this lasagna cat.
I'm on pins and needles
about who Garfield is.
That's the one thing
my checkbook is out. I'm loving
it but who's Garfield?
It actually ends on an even higher note.
Garfield's creator Jim Davis
said he was delighted with the concept
here's a quote. In forty years
no one has ever come to me with a better
thought out plan to deliver great food
in a fun and engaging way. Holy shit
Really?
So Jim Davis
in Jim Davis's life one component
of it is people frequently
come to him with plans to deliver
great food in a fun and engaging way.
No no no none of you. He can't even
look at his Twitter DMs anymore.
It's just fucking. So here's the thing Jim
it's called the Gar Ferrari. No.
It's Garfield shaped Ferrari and you bring
it and kids love it. Listen when I created
Garfield like a half
a century ago I did so
with the dream of one day
turning it into an F2P
home delivery food
intergaging experience
and you have not found it yet sir.
So you take this garbage
and you bury it in a box of dirt where it belongs.
So you can go to GarfieldEats.com
and
find out more
about that. I'm very disappointed
because I wanted to get the Garfield Eats
app on my phone. I think it's only in the UAE
but if you search Garfield on the
app store here's what you get. Garfield Rush
Garfield My
Big Fat Diet. My Talking
Garfield. Garfield
Survival of the Fattest.
Garfield Snack Time
Garfield Go. Garfield Food
Truck. Garfield Daily.
Garfield Walk.
This is all the Garfield apps that
there are. So there's a lot of that. Wowzy
bowzies my boy. This website
GarfieldEats.com is a
good one of the websites.
This website Justin. This website
it's a good website. In
this website you've seen lots of websites
folks because the internet's been around for a bit.
In this website they do have a picture
and it's half just Garfield's
face but then the other half
is what looks like an asparagus
and broccoli pizza. So it's almost
like he is a I'm gonna say Pizzamorf
which is a new series from Scholastic
that I'm very excited about in which famous
cartoon cats do turn into pizza.
This website is so fucking good Justin
I'm losing my mind.
I think very
we've been looking we've talked behind the scenes
a lot about trying to find that perfect
excuse to do a Dubai live show
and maybe this is it.
Maybe this is maybe
it's not we don't
go to the live show and happen to eat some Garfield
shaped pizza. We go eat
some Garfield shaped pizza and happen to do
a Dubai live show. There is
on the website
because they did it in
Canada too. It is in Canada so it is
Well we're never going to Canada. Let's admit
that. Canada?
What's that? There's a video
on
the website that has 371
views. It was released
May 2nd so this is off the presses.
It is on the Garfield Eats website
and is a 3 minute and
44 second long video
of Jim Davis talking
about Garfield eating while
he holds the stuffed Garfield and
cartoons of Garfield.
That's a video that you can go see at
GarfieldEats.com if you want to scoop that up.
Griffin if you want to
edit in like 10 seconds of the
audio from that I think we'd be cleared to it
just to like get a little bit
of that heat. Okay don't tell Jim.
Garfield Eats.
I think that's been pretty well established.
His lifelong love affair with pasta
and pizza is legendary.
In fact if Garfield could dream
up the perfect restaurant it
would feature lasagna and pizza.
Well Garfield's dream has come
true and it's in the form of
a new innovative concept
restaurant.
Garfield Eats.
Take care of the cat
and the cat will take care of you.
And I'm on the website now there is a little
chat box where you do want to talk to customer service
so I did ping them hoping to ask like are you
planning to spread to the states anytime soon.
So I said hello and then the bot responded
oh it's you. Thanks for chatting us up.
One of our friends will be
one of your friends will be happy to reply to you
in a few seconds. Give us your name and number
and we'll call you back and I panicked.
Hard pass. I panicked I said my name is Derek
and then customer service
immediately responded
we are experiencing large volumes
of chat messages.
I'm sure yeah. Please leave your mobile number
or find our social media page called Garfield Eats
app for updates offers and more calls anytime
by clicking the call us icon for every order
you will get free pause
to unlock
guys
I will get free pause to unlock
goopons
and Garfield exclusive series.
I don't think you meant to do that.
Guys I don't think this is groupons
misspelled because why would they give out
groupons. I think this is
Garfield coupons
is an experience that they
have a currency that they have titled
goopons.
There is a fucking. OK
guys this is going to sound like a joke
but it's not a joke. So this
Reeboks thing you can and
it's not Reeboks how it sounds
in your brain when I say the words
it's R E hyphen B O
X right Reeboks is a thing
where you can reuse
the packaging
that your food comes in and
they have videos for how to do it
on
the website and there's a video
that is 20 seconds long that
says how to transform your
Garfield cup your Garfield
eats cup into a pencil holder.
Wow. And here are the instructions
the instructions are this number one
uses a pencil holder
that boy
that's it. Oh boy.
You've made me very happy Garfield eats.
Thank you Garfield eats
please come to West Virginia. I will start
a fucking
I will start a
branch here. I will buy a scooter
I will just you can franchise here
please please I'll do
anything.
This has been our program
my brother my brother and me an advice show for the
modern era. We hope you've enjoyed
how long we talked about Garfield eats
if you live in Canada
and you don't get Garfield eats
you're a criminal.
So I
want to thank John Roderick and
long winter sees for a theme song it's a departure off
the album putting the days to bed you can find a link to that
well shit I always do that
you can find that I mean you find it
anywhere you can find that album on Spotify
you can find that album on Amazon you can
find it on cool album stop fart
you can find it wherever you get your albums. I don't
know because I'm not watching you
and also thanks to maximum fun
for having us on the network. They have a bunch of great
shows like stop podcasting yourself
and beef and dairy network and
can I pet your dog and a whole
bunch more all good shows.
We have other stuff at McElroy dot family
including some
still some tickets to some live shows coming up including
a tour we're about to do in Nashville and
Indianapolis that's coming up in just a couple weeks. So if you
live there come see us. We're doing my
man and Taz here in the middle of June so
you can find links to that at McElroy dot family
and you'll find all our other shows and video shit there
too while you're there also
you will see other shows
we're doing for the adventure zone
graphic novel book two coming out
I believe it comes out July
what 16th 17th
one of those two days
and we're doing a book tour like we did
last year for it. We're going to be
in New York New York City
at the Town Hall Theater Justin
Griffin and Carrie are going to be there
and on the same night July 16th
dad and I will be in Portland
Oregon at Revolution Hall
and then on the 17th Griffin
and Justin will be in Austin Texas
at the Paramount Theater and dad and I
will be in Los Angeles California
at the Ace Theater and then on July
19th we
me dad Justin Griffin
and Carrie will all be
at San Diego Comic Con at the
Balboa Theater you can get all those tickets as
well at McElroy dot
family and speaking of
the book even if you can't make it
go to theadventurezonecomic.com
and you can preorder book two
now the adventure zone
book two Murder on the
Rockport Limited it's really
really good and you're going to love it I hope you
like it you will you
will there's no hope about it Griffin it's
even better than the first one and
well it's great
you're going to love it Angus is in it
and Angus is great everybody's got
different tastes they're
going to love it Griffin okay
so everybody likes different stuff
that's just a fact here's a
final yahoo and this one was sent in
by oh also merch
is there check out our merch McElroy
merch dot com Merritt Palmer sent this one
in thanks Merritt it's yahoo answers user they're anonymous
so I'm calling
Garfuccino asks
if you cared at
all
what episode of the
Flintstones do you think I should watch
my name is Justin
McElroy I'm Griffin
McElroy you're my brother my brother may you kiss your
dad's ground lips
maximum fun dot org
comedy and culture artist
owned listener supported
this
is NASA I see
a flat earth but we should lie to everybody
about it and say it's around ten
four maximum fun brings you
the latest podcast an expose
on the flat earth
I want to take advantage of
humankind and make them believe a lie
so that they will trust us with the government it's
all an elaborate lie and when you get on a plane
they purposely fly you farther
than you need to go it's disgusting
it needs to be stopped and if you
listen to Ono Ross and Carrie we will tell you
the truth behind the lies
just kidding
we won't do that we will just tell
you the truth behind the truth because what we
do is we look at extraordinary claims
that's right we've gone under cover
with alternative medical treatments
fringe religious groups fringe
science claims spiritual
paranormal we're there to check
it out and let you know what happens is the
Queen Mary haunted I don't know find
out we show up we make
friends we learn what happens when
you ask questions and we tell you all
about it and we get all that funky stuff
done to us it's Ono Ross
and Carrie at MaximumFun.org