If you change your mind on the first in line Honey, I'm still free, take your chance on me
If you need me, let me know, I'm gonna be around If you got no place to go when you're feeling down
If you're all alone when the pretty birds have flown
If you need me, let me know, I'm still free, take your chance on me
If you got no place to go when the pretty birds have flown
I wish you guys would have told me this before I took all the epic act
Oh, I'm Justin McRoy by the way
I'm Travis McRoy
I'm Griffin McRoy
Hey, can you guys hear me over there?
Can you hear me all the way out on the east coast?
Griffin's rocking it Midwest style these days, he's moved to...
I'm up in that bread basket dog
I finally got his piece of the pie
Yeah, I did, it's so nice out here
Yeah
No
No, scary
Can I come back please?
Have you seen any gangs?
It's so hot all the time, the gangs and wild dogs just right across the street
I don't like it here anymore
Oh man, okay, so here we go
This is the first question, it's from FormSpring
My university flatmates have gone home for the summer
What are you, where are you from?
Flatmates?
However, I have a summer placement
What can I do to stop becoming too bored or going slightly crazy?
I don't understand half of the words in this question
I don't speak the same language as you
A summer placement, flatmates?
I think that means they have summer classes
I know what you can do to help pass the time
Get an English dictionary and memorize it
So you call things the right names
Or maybe just move to Merca
Move to Merca
This would be the best day to do it
Yeah
America's birthday
Greatest day
How old is old lady liberty?
60, 70 years old, who can keep track?
I believe you mean 70 years young
70 years young
You know, being bored
I remember those days
I remember when I would worry about being bored
Who has time to be bored anymore?
Are you sleeping enough?
Set yourself up some kind of random project
This summer I am going to read 16 books
I am going to build a cabinet
Open a lemonade stand
A lemonade stand for grown-ups
Only Mike's Hard Lemonade
Yeah, what's up?
That'd be good
That's got to be legal
Refreshing
I like your house's suggestion
Say by the end of this summer you are going to kick ass at photography
Or kung fu or something
And use your time that way
Or street side bartending
Or just treasure these days because soon you won't be bored
Ever again
Soon you'll be dead
It's the best time to go exploring too
Go exploring?
Yeah, if you are in a college town and everyone is left for the summer
You can go to all kinds of places
Or you can just go on a rampage
Just go on a looting rampage because nobody is there
Yeah, say by the end of this summer I am going to break into 16 houses
Goals are so important
Goal setting is so important
So I got a problem
Oh no
I am in a situation
I love this girl
I work with her
Also I am a random person on forum spring
But she has a boyfriend
That is a problem
She has told me she likes it
Let me start at the beginning because I feel like we have gotten confused
I am in a situation
I love this girl I work with but she has a boyfriend
She has told me she likes me and wants to date me
But she doesn't want to lose what she has with her current boyfriend
But I really want to date her
What?
What should I do?
That is the most ridiculous thing I have ever heard
Okay, so alright
She is with
Okay, you love girl A
Girl A is dating girl B
Or boy
Guy B
Wait
Lesbian apocalypse
It is coming so quickly
Is it a girl?
I don't know
So
Dude
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude
I have a bigger problem with this question
And it is that he starts with I love this girl I work with
Yikes
Yeah, dude
You are rushing
Here is the thing
If she is with this guy
And she also wants to be with you
Then they are hopefully going to self-destruct
But you need to tell her that if she wants to be with you
You are better than that
She needs to drop the proverbial zero
And get with the proverbial hero
But don't let her string you along like this
If she wants to be with you she needs to dump that dude
I know it sucks
I know he is going to cry and sit in her shitty mixtape for a week
Sorry
But it sounds like she is setting up
If she wants a little booty on the side
If she is making the statement
Yeah, I want to be with you
But I don't want to lose what I have with my current boyfriend
A, that is a really shitty thing to say
B, what she is setting up is
But we can still hang out
Is that what you want to be, FormSpring?
You want to be a side booty?
You know, I knew a guy with a side booty once
It is really tragic, I shouldn't joke about it
It is a serious medical problem
What is that stain on the side of your pants?
I am sorry, I have a side booty
And I have no control over it
Because my destiny is not wired properly
I absorbed one tenth of a twin
And I just got one of his butt cheeks
So he has
Wait, let's jump back
So he has two butts
One on the back, one on the side
It is more of a one and a half situation
Yeah, the one on the side doesn't count as much
It is like a side butt, but it is only like half a butt
Because you don't have room for a full butt on the side of your body
God, biology 101 Travis
I am sorry, I wasn't paying attention that day
They can fix that with a pretty simple outpatient procedure
Ask your doctor wife about it
Jacob via Gmail asks, recently at a camp out with a couple of friends in my backyard
In the Canadian woods, I got really close to a girl
My friend has been chasing for a while
And ended up hooking up with her without anyone else noticing
I like that verbiage
Should I tell my butt or keep it a secret?
Tell your butt
Jacob
What can I say, nice ninja hooking up first of all
Jacob has the ability to turn invisible like a chameleon whenever he is fully aroused
Jacob, I think that this story is so cool that you just need to write it out
Because you don't want to taint it by telling your friend
I think you need to keep this a secret in your heart when things are down
Just think about that time that you covertly snuck into a girl
And hooked up with her
Here is my question, did she notice?
Because you have a sincere problem
I think you should go ahead and tell him
Because if you were that stealth about it, then he probably won't believe you
And he'll just turn it into a joke and he'll diffuse the whole situation
Yeah, I would never tell anybody
Yeah, keep it to yourself
And keep up the discreet lovemaking
Because that's a skill that you're going to exercise more often than you might think
This is one situation where I kind of wish this guy would start an advice podcast
Where he could ask him about his secret lovemaking
I was in the middle of a group of friends, but I really wanted to bone down on this girl
What should I wear?
One of my friends was like, did you feel a breeze?
And the other one said no, but I made love for an hour
And you were unaware
This is the guy who set up the popcorn dick trick
Cut a hole in the bottom of the popcorn
I like this guy
What's up with that language?
I can't say popcorn?
It's America's birthday, could we maybe keep it down a little?
Yahoo Answers user Jessica asks, can I hit American men?
She expounds, hi, I am Jessica from France
And this fall I will be going to college in the US
I just wondered, if dirty American boy tries to hit on me
Can I slap him hard in the mouth with clenched fists so his yellow teeth breaks?
Only French man can touch this, will this get me in trouble?
No, I think that's fine
Yeah, I don't know much about the law
I mean, if you make his yellow teeth breaks
Then he could make you pay for it, the operation
Listen, on this, America's birthday, I feel like I have to be the one to say
Jessica, you would be lucky, lucky to have some American penis, go on
Again with the language
I said penis this time, how is that not better?
It's like weirder, it's grosser
Is it grosser?
It's grosser degrees
You're making me more and more uncomfortable
I'm going to eat some American wieners later
But those are called freedom franks because we can't say French dogs anymore
So they're freedom franks
Like we all used to
If he comes to the US and hits an American man in the mouth, I'll go to war with France
It'll be my own private campaign
Your own private campaign
Do you think Tristan would come help you out with that?
Tristan's going to come and he's going to fuck Jessica up
Right now I can picture Tristan listening to this podcast and hearing that question
And just start smearing on war paint and tying a bandana around his head
Well, now it's time to go get Jessica too
He's going to hog tie Jessica and use Jessica to beat Osama to death
It's going to be totally awesome
I think Jacob just had sex with me
Wow, I did not see that coming
There's a joke in there somewhere
No, I'm seeing something coming
No, go on
On America's birthday, Travis
I work with many interesting people
This is not true of me, this is Dan from Gmail
It is true of me, I'm just not the one talking
It's not my question
One in particular has a disturbing mustache that looks like he would drive an ice cream truck and have a basement full of children
How do I nicely inform him that his mustache is a sad and failed attempt at having facial hair?
Oh, the pedo stache, that's tough
I don't understand, so he's a part time ice cream truck driver and a part time day care attendee?
Dead children
Or maybe the children are manufacturing the ice cream for him
He has a slave labor thing going on in his basement
I don't think we should jump to pedo conclusions
Let's give this guy the benefit of the doubt
You think that he's worried because the guy that he works with is interesting but looks like he might run a small business
And also employ local children and be infusing cash into the economy, that's what you think
That's what he's worried about
The American economy
Happy birthday America
Thank you America
Thank you America for everything
Such a good country
I think this would be such an awkward conversation that what you need to do is sneak into his house when he's asleep
Shave it off when he's not paying attention
And then just say, what happened the next day?
If I might suggest, get Jacob's help
Yeah, get Jacob's help, he's really good with stealth
I can't grow hair in the area underneath the corners of my mouth
Which makes it hard to go with a full goatee
And sort of ends up with a half van dyke, half pedo stash
It's a no-tee
And I sympathize with this guy
Because it's every man's right to have facial hair
Only some people are better at it than others
Travis has a full luscious beard that you could hide skittles and jolly ranchers in
To recall for later snacking
But I can't get that going
Dan, if I might suggest, start posting pictures in your cubicle of men with these pedo stashes
Like Jeffrey Dahmer
Guys like this, until eventually this guy
Now, this will reflect poorly on you
So you need to be ready for that
But I think that's the only way to do it without just saying
Hey creep stash, how's your creep stash?
The best way to deal with a creep stash is say
At any opportunity, say, God, your mustache looks so good
And like really let him know
And then say, you know what, I love your stash
And if he's into it, if he's feeling you
Okay, if he's not feeling it, he's like, oh man
This guy is hitting on me for my stash, I'm gonna shave it
If he is into it, then say, God, you know what though
As much as I love your stash, you look so good with like
A little beard, just a little beard coming down off of it
And then he'll grow it
What if you had a mustache, but it was made of skin
Like a skin stash
There wasn't any hair there
And it was just skin that blended with your other skin
That would look so good if you had a skin stash
That would look so, so good
So, I hope that helps
Brendan from Gmail says, I was walking with probably best friend
She has made it clear that I am in her friend's circle
Although the way she said it also said that to who is not
Okay, nope
Nope
Sorry Brendan, maybe get that stuff right
I can't do this with you
Tyler from Gmail writes, my friend and I live in LA
We love it
Whatever he talks about going to any place outside the city
He refers to it as going down to whateversburg
Regardless of the town's location, north or south of Los Angeles
Does he also say that regardless of the name of the area you're going to
Going down to whateversburg
That tells me nothing
There's no information in that sentence
You say that every time we go anywhere
Likewise, if we're heading into the city from some place north
He says heading up to LA
So to recap, he thinks that if you're going to a bigger city
Then you call it going up to that place
Even though the larger city may be located more southern on the actual globe
Even on the same latitude
He listened to the show and his name is Mark
Please tell me he's wrong so I can have this one trivial but incontrovertible moment
Of being right to lord over him for all of time
Help me Mo Bim Bam, you're my only hope
Tyler from Gmail
Okay, let me think about this
Tyler, I'm sorry but I feel what Mark is spitting
I understand it because it has nothing to do with geography
He's talking about moving up and down the socio-economic ladder
So if you move from Shitsville to LA
That is an upward move on the ladder
So you're moving on up to LA
What is this ladder that there are places below Los Angeles
I'm figuratively speaking
If we're talking about this soul crushing ladder
LA is the bottom rung
Because it's the most oppressive city on the planet
Now you don't mean that, Las Vegas still exists
Los Angeles, you're a fine city
You need to get a little smaller
And make it so the traffic isn't so bad
And then we'll talk again
And make everybody less hateful
I think people are nice to me there
Do you think it's because you're white?
That probably, maybe, I don't know
Everyone there is very friendly I think in Los Angeles
To get back to Tyler's actual question
I have to agree with your friend Mark
I think that up and down are interchangeable
And have nothing to do with actual location
Would you prefer if he was like
I'm going to head up north on California 1
For 364 miles until I reach my destination
Which is LAX
I always use the right words
Is that you, Wood?
Like directionally?
I always say I'm heading
I don't say I'm going to Cincinnati
I say I'm headed north-northwest
You don't do that
Yeah I do, sure
As the crow flies
You know what I would like to hear
Those ones that are on the same plane
The same latitude
Say I'm heading left to someplace
I'm going up north, down south
Left, right
I'm going right
Yahoo Answers user Steph P. asks
Is it possible to bend air, water, fire, and earth
Like in Avatar?
If so, please help me learn how to
Subquestion
Like in the show Avatar
Yes, the answer, of course
It's also possible to bend sadness
And you've got that down
She's the last of the sadness benders
You've bent my mouth into a frown
A disapproving frown
Steph P. the frown bender
I can't wait to see M. Night Shyamalan
Ruin that franchise
Don't say that
I hope it's so good
It's not
It's got like a 6%
Have you seen Last Airbender?
That shit rules
Shyamalan
Shyamalian
forms
Chameleonare
Chameleonare asks
What are your guys' stance on the changing of last names
When people get married?
My current girlfriend just told me
That if we ever got married
She would be keeping her last name
She claims it's a sexist tradition
Should I be offended?
Just say
You know what else is a sexist tradition
It would be paying for dinner
So pony up
Say that
And then she'd be like
Well, we always do that
You'd be like
God, I'm sorry
I'm such an asshole
Can you forgive me?
I mean
Is it a sexist tradition?
I don't know
Is it everything?
Isn't everything?
What?
Isn't every tradition inherently sexist?
Like you bring a Christmas tree in
That's just a phallus
It's just one
A big green leafy
Just a big green leafy phallus
See, that's the words we use, Travis
Phallus
Phallus is less creepy
That's the least creepy one
That's scientific
Yeah
That's hospital talk
I think wiener is pretty scientific
Oh my god
He's saying it again
I mean
Her preference is the most important thing, right?
So if
I don't think she's the sort of lady who is independent
About not changing her name
Until two guys
Three guys who are brothers
And record a podcast
Tell her differently
So I think you're just going to have to ride this one out
That said
If you were going to do a compromise
You see my wife's name
She took her last name and made it her middle name
And then took my last name
So we'd have
I think it's nice that married couples have the same last names
Because I think it's
Yeah
I think beyond being
Whether or not it's a sexist tradition
I think that it is nice for them to
Have
If they're starting a family
Then they want to be the whatevers
Sure
I think this issue really boils down ultimately
To what the last name in question is
I guess if it's
If it's like
J.P. Gargle Stinch
Like
I can understand you not wanting
But if it's like Hogan
If your last name's Hogan
Like what woman wouldn't want to have that as their last name
Right
And I think you should also explain to her
That she should be prepared
That for the rest of your lives together
You will always be introduced separately
And everything will be addressed to you separately
And there will always be that confusion of
It would be awkward
Like this is Mrs. Gargle Stouch
And her husband
Tom Danger
Like well Mrs. Gargle Stouch what didn't you
Never mind
And she can't be Mrs.
She can't be Mrs.
Can you be Mrs. if you don't take their last name
I think so
I think Mrs. just indicates that you're married
I'm pretty sure it's pronounced Mizz-rizz
Mizz-rizz
Mizz
Yeah
Mizz-mires
Mizz-rizz
Formspring asks
I just started seeing this guy and I feel uncomfortable
Whenever he tries to take my shirt off
I like him a lot but I'm not a skinny girl
And I feel like he won't like what he sees underneath
Do men even care or do they just want boobs
Good news
Listen the doctor just came out of the room
You've been sitting there in the waiting room
With bated breath waiting for something
And Dr. Travis has good news for you
Men like boobs
There you go
It doesn't matter to me
What if these are not two connected thoughts
We're assuming that she means she's a little bit chunky style underneath
And that's why she's worried what he'll see
Maybe she's got like a really tragic
Maybe she's got like a giant tattoo of Ray Romano or something
Maybe she's got a side butt but it's on her torso
Oh my god a torso side butt and you're embarrassed that he'll see it
Listen if he loves you he's gonna have to deal with the fact that you have half a butt on the side of your body
And a tattoo of Ray Romano
I understand you were attached to it
Maybe have it surgically lowered so it'll just look like you have great childbearing hips
Why would having a tattoo of Ray Romano lower make it look like you have great childbearing hips
I'm really confused
It's about perspective
It's hard to explain
If he loves you it won't matter and if he doesn't love you don't give it up
There it is man
Lock it up, lock it down
Words never spoken
Protect that carnal treasure
That's right that's your flower
Does anyone here find Michael Cera really attractive
Sorry that was a yahoo question
You need to prep this shit like that Griffin
I didn't want to dedicate too much time to it so I just dropped it like it was hot
I don't know why but I really really like him
I just think it's his amazing personality lol
Go creepo you're the only one
No I think he's cute
He's a cute little guy
The thing is he's 50
It's getting a little old, a little tired
He needs to bust out of his shell a little bit
Ye three brothers
My best friend is a bit of a dick
Again with this talk
He takes the piss out of it
He takes the piss out of everything I say and bitches about me constantly
How could I put him in his place
Okay welcome back to fucking class 1000
A continuing series on my brother my brother news called are you my friend
Class 1 was of course if you want to really have sex with your best friend's girlfriend really bad
That's not your friend
You're not friends that's not what that means
Class 2 if your best friend makes fun of everything you say and bitches about you
He's not your friend
Find a new friend
What kind of confidence issues do you have
Where this guy is picking on you all the time and makes fun of you and bitches about you
You're like that's my best bud
That's my bro
A lifetime bro forever
He has my best interest in mind
I know that he pees all over me and sets my stuff on fire and kicks me in the face
But god I love him
Hey Tony you're a pussy
Thanks Mike
That's my best friend
How many more boxes do you think we have to move to your apartment
I'll tell you when you move enough boxes gay
That's my best friend
That's my man
Who's that man abusing you
Do you want me to call the cops now we're bros
We're best friends
That said
Hey Jerry I fucked your dad
Oh Mike
Thanks
Why'd you do that
How about you just tell him to stop being a dick
Stop being a dick
Just slug him once
And see how the tenure of the relationship changes
I bet it'll be drastic
Real good for that friendship
You guys are so chipper and gleeful
You're never down
How do you do this
This dovetails
This dovetails with another question that's from Matt
The theory of you seem to be great terms as adults
Were you always good friends or does that
Amicable nature of family just
Naturally reveal itself after you no longer
Have to share a living space
Yep
These questions are tied in because
You don't know us
We're animals, we're monsters
This show
Is our ticket
To the big time, to the big money
And we know that we're the only three people
We know that will be on it with us
So we
We act chipper
But usually we're hateful
And misanthrope
This question reminds me of people who are like
That Matt Lauer seems so nice
Well that's his job
That's what he gets paid to do
Our job is to make it seem like we like each other
And that we're chipper
They're lying by the way
We're chipper and gleeful because we
Enjoy talking to each other
I'll tell you straight up
Stone Cold
This is from Matt
Matt I'll tell you something
Man you only get one go around
You only get one spin
On this crazy globe
Why waste a moment of it
Not one more moment of it being
Anything but chipper and gleeful
I have a great reason to be chipper and gleeful
It's because I woke up today
You know what I have a new thing that I've been trying
To do for like the last year, year and a half, two years
And whenever I start to get frustrated
About something or upset about something I stop
And I think is this really worth getting
Upset about and the answer is always
No, you know in
Two minutes it's gonna be over anyways
Might as well ride
The happy wave
If that doesn't work just go buy
Something
That's what I do
I'll go back to my original point and
Make that something just a little bit
Of speed
Just a little bit of
Upper, maybe just one rock
Just one rock of rock cocaine
But it's important that you promise yourself
Great speed powder, just the one
Maybe just a little
Bit of nose whiskey
We'll turn that frown upside down
As a woman what is
The best way to seduce a man?
Say hi, I can't answer that
As a man the best way to seduce a man
Goes a little something
Like this
Then it's
On, just like that I don't know
That's all you need, just make that noise
And the guy's like you're down
Then you're like I'm down, clearly I'm down
As a woman, what seduction
What do you mean, there's no seduction
There's no, I mean this is
A crazy concept
Men are stupid, just
Penises attached to brains, I'm sorry Griffin
And it
Takes very little
What's the best way to seduce a dude guys?
I think maybe a little bit of
I think maybe a little bit of clarity
Will come out of
This related yahoo question
Which comes to us from Mr. H
Who asks, exactly how
Can I get horny?
I don't
I don't get it
I look at something sexual and dirty
And then what, do I have to have a specific
Mindset to get fully horny?
I tried saying over and over
In my head, oh god I want that so
Badly, or something like that
That didn't help
Am I supposed to get a big emotional feeling when I
Get horny? Is it like my heartbeat
Changes during horniness?
What aspect of the
Dirty thought is supposed to make me horny?
I looked at something that made me
Horny, but it only worked for a few seconds
And then it went away
And sometimes it doesn't work at all
What do I have to do to keep the feeling?
This is once again something a psychopath
Says
Signed Kyle H5
Someone give me a real answer
Nothing like, you'll know when it happens
That's the most
Upsetting thing I've ever heard
Clearly dating
Clearly these two are
She doesn't know how to seduce a man, and he does not
Understand horny
He doesn't understand how to be seduced
That question
By the way, came to us from
Tyler, who sent it in
Thank you Tyler
That's a good one, good looking out money
Good looking out money
I think this might have been
Sent to us by Beesbow, or some other
Extraterrestrial force that doesn't understand
How horny impulses work
I think just
Scientifically speaking, if you ever said
To yourself, oh I'm down
To bone, then you're probably horny right then
You don't need to, there's no
Horny fairy that comes down and says to you
You are on
You are on and ready for game
Dear horny fairy, please send me
A boner, it's all I want
Just one please
Send me a bone
Give just one boner to
Me
My advice to both of these people, the young people
And the former string person
In my experience
It's all about the atmosphere
And just
You know
And by which I mean, is there a dude
Present and is there a girl present?
Atmosphere completed
Yeah, and then just start kissing
Did you try to start kissing?
That's always a good start
Why do you have to jump right to
Having sex?
You have to take your clothes off and kiss
Nothing makes me hornier than a good
Conversation
Which is really awkward when talking
To Griffin
Is it awkward?
Help
I need to get my girlfriend back, any advice
Brothers? This comes from Form Spring
How bad was the
Prank that she pulled on you that you want to get revenge for?
Is that what he means?
Do you want to get back at her for a prank she pulled?
Either that or she was kidnapped
I think she's been taken by Colombian drug runners
At which point, call Kiefer Sunderland
Yeah, he'll sort that out
Here's what I would do, I would wait until you know
She's going to walk into her room, then you get a bucket
You fill the bucket with water, then you put the water bucket
Half on the door jamb
And half on the door
And then when she opens the door
It all tumbles onto her
She'll get
She'll get moist from the water in the bucket
That's what you're saying
This works both ways, if she broke up
With you, if she pulled a prank on you
Then you point at her after the water bucket
Falls on her and you
Laugh, if she dumped you
Then you point at her and say
Well no one will have you now
I'm the best you're going to do
And the best you're going to do, Weddy
Take a picture of her
Film it and put it on YouTube and say
Be a little fool of yourself and then walk away
That's going viral
I'll see you this evening
For dinner, we have dinner at Giovanni's
A reservation
I'll see you there, have you guys seen the bucket ex
Oh she's so foolish
No one would ever date her
I'd say I guess I just put
Hooking up with me back on your bucket
List and then walk out
That's real good, that's a good one
That's real good
For real though, you don't need her
You're too good for her
You listen to a great podcast like this
Unless it's like a
Justifiable reason that she broke up with you
Like you need to quit doing
Speed
Or pranks
Listen, it was funny the first time
You have done the bucket thing
26 times and it is
Old
Until you get a tattoo that says I'm the trickster supreme
I'm not going to stop pulling pranks
Trickster supreme with an
XXX
I want to hear Griffin's last question but first I want to tell you
All the different ways that you can seek help from
Our show, there is
Of course an email address
M-B-M-B-A-M at gmail.com
There's form spring
It's form spring
Something
I think it's like form spring dot me
You really need to nail
Down that web address
I don't know that one so just go to
M-B-M-B-A-M dot com and all these methods
Are on there, we love seeing
Retweeted quotes
We have a search so we always see those
And
Those always bring us a lot of joy
If you could grab a friend
The next time you listen to the show
Or burn a CD for them
It would be
Great too, just put a couple Eps on it
And say hey listen to this
I know you will like this
Enjoy this
I'll tell you a campaign I'm going to try and get started
I was looking at our stats the other day
Our statistics and almost half of the people
That listen to our show download it through the web
You got to get on that iTunes
It's so efficient
It's such an efficient way of getting the show
You just put it in
And then you hit the subscribe button
And then you get it automatically every week
It's just waiting there for you
And if I might suggest subscribe
And then just download it independently
Seven times
Just get it as many times as you can
But tell a friend
I was talking with my buddy Slice
Who was telling me all the different
Ways he's come up with to share the show
And I think that's about it
And I'm ready
Travis if you are
To hear our last question
Our one to grow on
Comes to us from Yahoo Answers user Rick
Who asks, I just got out of jail
When is NWA
World Championship Wrestling on?
I'm Justin McElroy
I'm Travis McElroy
And this has been my brother, my brother
And me
You'll never know me
Yeah