Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Sing it.
Do what Justin's doing.
But I don't know what song you're doing.
You were doing you.
He's just, he's making holiday notes.
I'm doing old legs on the news.
Okay.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Hey, everybody, it's Griffin McElroy from My Brother,
My Brother, Me Brothers.
And this is our annual candlelight special
live in Huntington, West Virginia.
Thank you to everybody who came out.
Apologies to the ones that couldn't make it.
We had a really great time.
You're about to hear us open up the show
with some beautiful carolers from Heart in the Park.
It didn't come out super good in the final mix,
but it was fun if you were there.
So share this episode with your family.
There's no, there's no swears in this episode.
There were a couple of swears in the live environment,
but we went ahead and nipped those in the bud.
So go ahead and share this with Pee-Paw, Poop-Paw,
Pump-Paw, and Pumper, your dog, Pumper.
And joyous candle nights.
That was just a nightmare.
The McElroy brothers are not experts.
And their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert,
but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only
so the babies out there will know how cool they are
when they see it.
What's up, you cool babies?
Hello.
Intimate.
Joyous candle nights.
My name is Justin McElroy, and I'm your oldest brother.
Welcome, my brother, my brother, main advice show
for the modern era.
Feliz Navi candle nights.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm the sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy,
and I want to apologize for, after all that stuff we planned,
my introduction to you was I screamed the word intimate
into my microphone, thereby unraveling the scarf
of intimacy that we worked so hard to unravel.
Griffin makes an excellent point, because what we've done
is we planned carolers, we made a video,
we had a whole thing, there was a grinch,
and what we did is we planned right up until the start
of my brother, my brother and me,
and then we didn't plan anything after that.
Oh, I planned something.
It's right here in this bottle.
I mean, I'm...
You have a can in your hands.
You planned poorly.
Oh, all right.
No, this, actually, this can is part of my new
keep it cool...
my new keep it cool live show lifestyle.
Let me tell you what folks about it.
It's called Wait to Make Some Room.
Here's how it works.
So let's say you do three shows as part of candle nights.
How is this tree back?
I bought that at the dollar store.
What's up, house left?
It's called Wait to Make Some Room.
So here's how it works.
It's called what?
It's called Wait to Make Some Room.
So let's say...
Is that Simlish?
Is that the Sims language?
No, it's Wait till you make a some room.
Here's how it works.
Let's say you do three shows.
You have a certain level of drunk
that you need to be for each one.
The first one, none.
It's perfect.
It's called Things So Much.
Artistic creation that is a symbiosis of art and commerce.
It's perfect.
So you don't have to be drunk for that.
Saw bones, drunk enough that I have to forget
that I married way above my class.
It's a certain level.
But then, okay, so Wait to Make Some Room.
Here's how it works.
You pour the liquor into the can of soda,
but here's the thing.
Before you can pour the liquor in,
you gotta wait to make some room.
So you gotta...
You have a one in, one out.
Get out of here, regular liquid.
You're pacing yourself.
You're saying, whoa, whoa, 10-year bullet bourbon.
I'm gonna enjoy some more of you.
And I do want to be clear here.
He's got 10-year-age bullet bourbon,
which he is going to pour into Diet Dr. Batman.
That's fine.
Hey, eat a big'n, okay?
How much was that bottle?
Can I say that?
Is this candlelight appropriate?
Yeah, big'n is fine.
That bottle, it's not important.
It's the candlelight.
So this is an advice show for the modern era.
This is an episode where we're not gonna swear at all,
we should point out, which is...
We are gonna try really hard not to swear at all.
Hi, Justin.
And suddenly our production quality jumps up to 10.
I was really worried when they started
because I couldn't see Griffin super good.
But then Jelson flipped that tiny plastic switch
on that tiny plastic street lamp
and suddenly all became clear.
I had to explain it to the people at home
who knew what we were talking about.
This has been, fellas, I don't know how you feel about it,
kind of a swearing day.
Like if I made it to the end of this day
under normal circumstances, it would be 9 p.m.
I would put on my sweatshorts and I'd be like...
Sworts.
Shorts, I guess you could say.
Sure.
And then I would just like kick up the ottoman
and I'd be like, time to do some swearing.
Let's start with my favorite ones.
And then I'd say my...
I wish I could tell you what my favorite ones,
but I can't because it's Candle Nights
and that's not what we're going for here.
That's not what Candle Nights is about.
I don't know what it is about, but I know it's not that.
We'll find it by the end of the episode.
Going back, listening to old Candle Nights episodes,
I've realized they're beautiful
and we've pitched this holiday in the perfect way,
but none of us have had a moral revelation.
Except maybe Justin at the end of Candle Nights 2014
when three ghosts visited and were like,
hey, drink less on stage.
Only they didn't get around to you until like January 16th.
You know what's funny?
We'd ruin Candle Nights by swearing the show,
but there's a lot of Christmas things that would be a lot better
if they had swearing in them.
I was thinking about this today
when I was watching Emmett Otter's Junk Band Christmas.
How much money would you give
to see one of those little otters just be like,
mother grabber.
Like, but not, but they'd say the bad thing.
The bad one.
Should we do some...
What if Scrooge...
Oh, there's more. Okay.
What if Scrooge is just like, they're like,
can we have some money, Scrooge?
And he was like, son of a...
And then he said the rest of it.
The next word that comes in that usually at the end of it.
This is an advice show.
Don't laugh.
My family is doing a gift exchange this year
and my sister-in-law, as of last March, is buying a present.
A cast iron skillet.
Spoilers, come on.
For my wife.
Save that for the end of the question.
You don't know how to build suspense.
By the way, I know you've been wondering.
It's a cast iron skillet.
My wife's Christmas list did not specify
the type of cast iron skillet that she would like.
Rookie mistake.
But knowing her, I have reason to think
she would prefer a different type
than the one that was purchased.
Brief sidebar.
What character traits?
I know that she hates Mondays and loves chocolate.
So she wants a Dutch oven.
Not a cast iron skillet.
It could be.
You could have a cast iron Dutch oven skillet.
That's what you have an issue with.
Not that somebody wants a cast iron skillet.
Just not that cast iron skillet.
If you can't figure it out on your own,
it doesn't mean anything.
It doesn't mean anything.
You know I only like ceramic handles.
That's one of the things about me is I love ceramic handles.
I said ceramic handles three times
because I worried it would sound like ceramic candles,
and that doesn't make any sense.
A sincere concern.
Thank God you cleared that up.
Welcome, by the way.
Welcome behind the veil.
But I have reason to think that my sister-in-law
would prefer a different type than the one that was purchased.
I'm not about to ask my sister-in-law to return it
and get a different one.
But is it okay for us to return it
and get a different one ourselves
once the present has been opened
and thank yous have been given, et cetera?
It might not be an issue for most people,
but since my sister-in-law is relatively new to the family,
I don't want to do anything that might accidentally insult her.
And I know this is getting long, but hang in there with me.
There's a twist.
And she will know if we do this because my brother, her husband...
He's an octopus.
Why would she be an octopus?
It's just a better twist than the twisted.
Go ahead.
My brother... You've ruined the tension.
This isn't you.
Build it back up. Start at the beginning.
It was a dark and stormy night.
Call me Ishmael.
What's up with cast iron skillets?
It was the best of times.
It was the worst of skillets.
Okay.
Pick it up.
Let's take it from...
And she will know.
Reset to one.
Let's take it from the exact word I stopped at.
She will know if we do this because my brother, her husband,
and I share an Amazon account.
What do you think, brothers?
Should I return the present and restrain the relationship
or should I leave well enough alone?
And that's from sauteing in South Bend.
Can I just say...
Are you here sauteing in South Bend?
Are you?
No.
I'm deeply in love with the audience reaction.
Very much.
You guys reacted like a Spanish soap opera.
Ooh.
Die off me.
Whoa.
Because that's what I wanted you to do and you did.
You did.
I think it's busted how everybody thinks all commerce...
Why is everyone laughing?
Did I swear?
I think it's busted how everybody thinks all commerce
has to go through Amazon.
I think they're laughing because you said busted
like a character on Ghost Rider.
Hey, gang.
What's Ghost Rider spelling on the wall?
We've got to bust this...
Anyway.
Take it from me, Sheldon Turnipseed,
the actual name of a person on Ghost Rider,
Sheldon Turnipseed.
I forget what I was going to say, fellas.
I think it's...
Made some room.
I think it's bad and wrong.
You poured it into a cup.
That's a cheating version of making room.
I think it's...
No, I'm going to go with the original.
I think it's busted how everybody thinks all
monetary transactions have to go through Amazon
and you got to do a street return.
Just take this new cast iron skillet thing
into Pullman Square Plaza and just carry it around
saying like, who wants this skillet?
No.
Your problem is no one wants...
And correct me if I'm wrong here, audience.
No one wants a new cast iron skillet.
Right.
Like, what's the fun of that?
You need it preceded.
You want that stank fake thing.
You want your great-grandmother's old
busted skillet.
Travis Patrick!
Oh, no!
No, you can say that on TV.
No, three strikes.
Three strikes.
That's one.
You can say that on TV.
Three strikes.
Your old donkey skillet.
You want a skillet so old that something in it
at one point had a racist slang name, right?
Sorry, grandma, did you...
Do you mean bacon?
Sorry, wait, grandma.
Did you mean to say bacon just then
instead of the thing that you did say?
Because that's not what we call it ever.
This is polite society.
Could you take it to like Cluckers or something
and have them just like...
DJ Cluckers.
You mean Roosters.
It's not...
No, we don't want to get sued.
Anybody here eat at Roosters since you've been here?
Yeah, what's up?
It's like half our audience.
How did that happen?
Jason, don't raise your hand.
Of course you've eaten at Roosters.
They got a lot of TVs, right?
You were saying?
Yeah.
T-Fried TV.
We'll talk about hunting stuff later.
Go ahead.
Take the pan to Roosters.
Say, can you just dunk this?
Give it a speedy crusting.
Maybe one of the chefs puts it down his shirt
for a workday and you get that natural...
That increases the price by 25 American dollars.
You got to put some sweat equity into it.
Literal, literal sweat equity.
Quick poll.
Quick poll of this table.
Griffin, Justin.
Yeah.
How much would you pay for a cast iron skillet?
Do not answer audience.
Why can't they?
You're being really rude.
Because...
I want you to answer.
There's hundreds of people here.
You just pull...
I'm going to pull them in a second.
Okay, raise your hand.
This is going on.
Okay, let's do this.
Raise your hand if you pay $10
and then we'll just go up in value.
No, why would we do this?
And put it down.
Sia, okay, I see like one...
Bad start.
Bad long game.
Okay, 20.
Let's just get to the joke.
If there's a joke, God help me, please just say it.
No, my point was is that I think that in this day and age,
if you went up to someone and said,
I will sell you this cast iron skillet for $25,
they would be like, yeah.
On the street, homie?
What's your fear?
That you're getting a knockoff cast iron skillet?
That it's not name brand?
Hey, why is Paula Deen spelled with four E's?
I like how her face is printed on it, for sure.
This is a Paolo Deen.
That can't be right.
This is one Pablo Deen.
It doesn't even make sense.
Hey, does anybody want a Yahoo answer
from the Yahoo Answers website or service?
If you're unfamiliar,
we take questions from the Yahoo Answers service
and try to answer them before everybody on earth did it.
Fallon.
I know he's here.
If you're here.
If you're here, Fallon.
Eyes on you, buddy.
No, no, don't boo.
He's adorable.
He's a great guy.
All right, let's do the thing.
Send in by level 9,000.
Yeah, Drew, Drew, Drew Davenport, thank you.
Sure you're here?
He's usually here.
No, that would be amazing.
No, that's too far for him to come here.
We'll find him out next year.
At the top of the Yahoo page,
there's a little promotion that says,
get double points throughout December on Answers.
Is it time for me?
Is this the time to strike and become an active member?
I take so much from Yahoo Answers.
Is it time to put them back into the ecosystem?
Give.
I worry that you'll draw too much attention to yourself.
That's a good point.
I don't want to poison the well.
This one's asked by a Yahoo Answers user.
It's anonymous and for good reason.
We'll call him Purvis Asks.
What?
It's a name.
Purvis Asks.
Why am I attracted to the weight gain belly scene
from the movie The Santa Clause?
I'm so happy.
How's your candle lights?
Mine's good so far.
I'm a straight male.
Always have been.
There's no doubt to that.
Maybe slight confusion.
Wait, okay, maybe slightly what?
I'm a straight male.
Always have been.
There's no doubt about that.
Maybe slight confusion.
Just like Oni.
There's a backspace key on your keyboard.
There's no doubt.
There is.
Too late now.
You know what?
Don't read that last sentence.
I want that stricken from the Yahoo record.
Now that I think about it, I'm dated exclusively men.
I didn't see where that would be confusing.
Yeah, I can see why this would be confusing.
I'm attracted to the whole weight gain fetish thing
among women and only women.
Nothing crazy like serious gaining,
but a little bit of chub around girls' stomachs
that create a little gut is attractive to me,
and I didn't read this part,
and I'm uncomfortable on the stage now.
The next part's too gross to read.
When I say gross, all right, the humiliation factor
and seeing the girls act or whatever
and hearing dialogue or monologue gets me aroused a good bit.
All right, let the record show there were no bad words
in what Griffin just said.
But I would say mature concepts.
Challenging ideas.
Mostly just the idea of being aroused during a monologue.
You didn't specify the topic either.
My question.
Can we take our robes off yet?
I need to warp.
Pretty hot.
Cool.
My question is why for that particular scene only
do I get a similar feeling?
If memory serves in the Santa Claus with any,
there are several scenes where Tim Allen.
No, there is one specific where I believe he turns,
I'm sorry, profile, and in the mirror watches
like buttons pop off his shirt as he like.
Oh, slow down.
Oh, mommy.
Again, again.
If you'll remember the scene,
he then turns full onto the camera
and does this for 15 minutes.
So you can understand where.
As he just gets bigger and bigger.
Bigger and bigger.
Sorry, one second.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Did everybody get that on Twitter?
I'll do it one more time.
Why?
Why is any of this?
Yeah.
Justin is putting this on Twitter.
Get your cameras out.
That's because it's ethically bad.
It's ethically bad for them to do that thing you said.
So Tim Allen, I think what you've got here is a,
you've got a lot of ideas that we're growing up.
A lot of cross wires.
A lot of cross wires, right?
Everybody loves Santa.
Ho, ho, ho.
Green giant.
Well, stole that.
One of them stole it.
And everybody loves Santa.
Kids grow up loving Santa.
And then Tim Allen.
Need I say more?
I hoped that you guys would say something else.
America's sexiest comic.
America's sexiest comic slash novelist.
Oh my God, why am I here?
Changed my life.
It's why I'm a Zen Buddhist.
I wish that was not true.
Have you seen, yikes.
Have you seen.
Whoa, sorry, pump of the brakes.
I just found out Travis got his religious theology
from Tim Allen.
Sorry, the show is canceled.
We're only talking about this now.
I believe I was 14 and his views really unlocked
something within me.
The first annual Allen Nights.
Where's Travis?
The show has come to a halt until you tell us more.
Well, there's a metaphor running through the book
of him trying to find the perfect hood ornament.
The perfect chainsaw.
And what's great about it and I feel truly moving
is he finds what he thinks to be the perfect hood ornament
like we all have.
And then when he sees it the next morning in a clearer light
he realizes it's not as beautiful as it was
on the show floor.
And he realizes that what is truly important in life
is his wife and kids.
And not a hood ornament.
Okay, good.
And I think.
You read that and in the other hand.
I was 14.
Yes.
In the other hand you were holding a big bag full
of hood ornaments and you were like,
what am I becoming?
No.
Why did I sort through so many of these?
We are not talking about the matter at hand
which is this person's Tim Allen chub chub.
His double trouble chubble bubble.
And I guess we're just not gonna.
I would say this.
If it is confusing for you, my 35 years on this planet
have proven one thing and one thing only
and that is not that hard to not see a Santa Claus movie.
I was going to say, how often is this coming up
that you're like in the middle of, I don't know,
getting your license renewed at the DMV
and you look up.
Oh no, no.
Excuse me.
Can you change your channel please?
That guy got too worked up.
Yeah, and specifically not that scene, right?
Like it's not the whole movie.
It's just the part where he gets large and in charge, right?
I got another question.
I've bought a book for a friend.
What time did we start by the way?
It's been like four minutes.
Go ahead.
Okay.
I bought a book for a friend as a gift
this impending Candle Nights festivities.
While waiting for the approaching holiday,
I've been hearing amazing reviews
and have been seeing it on a number of years best list.
How morally reprehensible, sorry.
How morally reprehensible is it to read a book
prior to gifting?
That's from Dishonorable in Davidson.
Hey, all the information's used up again.
There's only love left in this copy of Eat, Pray, Love.
This is garbage.
Use of all the story.
Wait, why?
No, don't contextualize it.
The idea of if you said anything,
like I bought a sweater for my friend and I wore it first,
no one would be like, that's fine.
You can wear it again.
No, no.
It's a present you bought for someone
and you're not allowed to read it beforehand.
What's the alternative?
Go get it yourself.
It's $6.99, it's a book.
And that's, hey, hey everybody,
if you're wondering why it seems a little hot this winter,
it's because old climate change Trav
is trying to just like waste,
a lot of wastefulness, I think.
In my book, in my America.
Two more words about that, Paris Accord.
What?
Trying to get it fixed up.
A little hot out there today.
Dad has his head in his hands right now.
That's not a joke.
It seems a little steamy out there in my America.
I don't know.
Maybe everybody should like,
there's a picture of me reading a book.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Maybe you bought a book and they cut a tree down
to make that book and they paved paradise
and put up a parking lot.
We got libraries for a reason.
Go to the library and get it pre-loved too.
Congratulations, Mr. McElroy.
He's your library card.
We're excited to have you.
Thanks.
I need books that nobody's touched.
I need your new shipments.
Well, you have like a new Highlights magazine.
I guess if that's it.
Here's some books about how bad climate change is.
Nobody's touched those.
Apparently.
Let's change some minds.
I'm sorry, I spilled on the thing.
We got another Yahoo?
Yeah, sure.
Hit me.
How about this one?
This one, oh man, there's so many good ones.
Thank you to everybody who sent these in.
This one was sent in by Don Ames.
Thank you, Don.
It's by Yahoo Answers user.
Sorry, something has gone wrong.
I'm going to try refreshing the page.
Do you have a Wi-Fi?
I'm on that.
Those fat pipes.
Thank you, big Sandy.
Sandy is the IT person here.
Fun bit of trivia for people who live here.
When we tell people we were doing the show, the Big Sandy,
everybody was like, whoa.
And then we had to tell them it's like, no, not where the He-Man
live stunt show would be.
Also, it's 1992.
Yeah, not where they do World of Wheels and have all the trucks
and tractors come in, but like over here where they do.
In the prom crypt.
This actually might be the room I had my prom in.
Oh, yeah.
No, this place is a regular like teen boner storage facility.
There are prom boner ghosts all over this place.
Oh, I just walked into a cold spot.
I once saw American hero and West Virginia native Chuck Yeager,
first man to break the sound barrier.
What's up, Chuck?
All right.
I didn't make it, but you want to talk about cool intros.
I want to tell Chuck Yeager, come onto this stage in sweats.
Is my wife in this room?
Am I lying, Sydney?
Come on the stage in sweats and say, I got this video about me.
We're going to watch that first.
10 minutes.
What, Chuck?
Did you just start with a video about yourself that you started?
He introed a video about himself.
Sydney, am I lying?
She says, no, I'm not lying.
No, for those of you at home, no, he is not lying.
Also, for those of you at home, no, we literally
did that exact same thing when we introed our show, kind of.
OK, but wait.
Hold on, wait.
No, no, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
It's fine because we're not wearing sweatpants.
Oh, dang.
The difference is we were singing in Christmas pageants
and he was breaking the sound barrier.
So I feel like an a-hole.
OK, go ahead.
And now a 10 minute video of Chuck Yeager.
I wish.
He's a hero.
He's got to be so much better than our stupid show.
I don't know.
Fascinating life, that guy.
Chuck Yeager asks.
Wouldn't it be great if he was like a 10 minute video of me
knitting my true fashion?
Chuck Yeager asks, who stole my Christmas goose?
Who stole my Christmas goose?
I built a fence around him and it was 12 feet high.
Just now.
Picture it now.
Yeah, my reading comprehension is just now kicking.
That's a high A fence.
I built a fence around him and it was 12 feet high
so he couldn't jump out.
And I know he didn't run away, but he did.
But he know, but he know there.
And I can't find him anywhere.
Who stole my Christmas goose?
It was the Hanukkah Fox.
The Hanukkah Fox snapped the neck of your Christmas goose
with his powerful jaws.
That's it.
That's the shortest sentence in the English language
that has all of the letters in it.
The Hanukkah Fox snapped the Christmas goose's neck.
Well, that was good.
Listen, a goose is not a VTOL bird.
It cannot just like, whoop, up and go.
It needs a running start.
If this is a small enough pen, then we have a locked room
mystery on our hands now.
When you first read this, I was literally picturing a fence
just wide enough for the goose to be at it.
Like the goose wouldn't even have room to turn around.
We're talking about the barrel of a goose gun.
Yes.
But then I saw it 12 feet high, the circumference of a foot,
tops, I don't know, the diameter of a bird.
You built a goose silo for your one goose.
This would all be a lot funnier if this wasn't how most
of the chickens we eat are raised.
Jiminy creaminy.
What's up?
And you know what we feed them?
Fossil fuels.
Think about it.
A lot of agendas.
Wake up.
Wake up, it's a hotter one out there.
We're boiling our geese alive.
This is my new character.
Guy laughing at a thing that isn't that funny.
Who stole the Christmas goose?
Sorry.
Justin, you made a lot of jokes, but no firm denial.
It was me.
I stole the Christmas goose.
I thought the goose stole it.
It's going to be okay.
Yeah, I know.
It seems like quite the turn, but we got to end for it.
Don't worry.
We're not like J.J. Abrams.
We got an actual outro for this thing.
What the?
What is going on?
No, no, no, no, no.
Shut up.
It was a lost joke.
It wasn't like a Star Wars thing.
It was not topical.
Don't worry.
Don't get it twisted.
Here's a true story.
I ate goose for the first time two years ago.
My mother-in-law made it for Christmas.
And it tasted fine, but I realized that it is very hard to add a new animal to the list
of animals you eat.
Like, it's just like it moves them from one column into another column.
Like, welcome.
I'm eating you now.
Welcome to the things I eat.
Welcome to the Justin Tummy Club.
Welcome to the Tummy Club.
Put it back in.
Now when I see you flocking through the sky, I think, mm-hmm.
Yep.
Why don't you flock on down here?
When you do that, does it push another one out?
I added goose, and now I can't have fish anymore.
No.
No, that's the bad thing.
Eventually, it just becomes me, like, mad eater lad.
Just like, I'll eat the mic.
I don't care.
So it's kind of like a weird version of the most dangerous game where you just have to
keep eating until you've eaten the most dangerous animal, and then you have to eat man.
The most delicious game.
And, like, Justin's great-great-great-great-grandchildren will be like, all right, capybara, you're the
last one.
Come on, it's on.
The most elusive game, capybara.
Come on, capybara.
Well, no, they're the cutest game.
Why would you want to eat one of those?
But then you eat them, and you're like, I caught them all.
I've had it all.
Capybara, dolphin, bulbasaur, all of it.
Time to turn in my tummy decks.
All right.
This is moral.
Science says that you're an animal, but I don't believe it.
But there's only one way to settle this.
Come on in.
The tummy's fine.
Plankton, I'm just, I'm gonna hate this.
But I gotta know.
I can eat a billion of you at once.
Think of the possibilities.
Hey, hope everybody's having a real good time at this live show we recorded.
Before we thank any of our sponsors, I want to say a huge thank you to Heart, the theater
group that provided our carolers for us during the show.
You didn't come in so great through the final mix.
It was one of those, you had to be, one of those Patton and McElroy, you had to be there
moments.
But every summer they do theater in Huntington, and if you can get by, I think you're really
gonna enjoy it.
I love it.
Two thumbs up.
I love theater.
I love Heart.
I love Huntington.
Last year they did a play that our nanny wrote.
I want to say a big thank you also to Zip Recruiter.
When you're short staffed, there's no time to deal with dozens of different job sites.
With ziprecruiter.com, you can post to 100 plus job sites with one single click and be
instantly matched to candidates from over six million resumes.
I'm so hung over.
I'm just realizing I'm so hung over from last squats.
Look at me.
We're all together right now.
Day after candle lights, day one, when we did our live show.
This is day zero.
It's day zero, and now we're all together, and my brothers are watching me do my post
hangover squats.
Watch me now.
Squat.
That's one.
Two.
Reps.
You keep squatting.
Travis.
You are doing an excellent plie.
Zip Recruiter has been used by over 400 businesses, and you can try it, right?
400,000.
Well, it is also over 400.
Okay, you are right, but the copy does say 400,000.
Go to ziprecruiter.com slash my brother.
That's ziprecruiter.com slash my brother.
No, Travis, you do it.
Go.
Burn it.
Okay.
Well, we also are sponsored this week by Harry's.
You've heard us talk about Harry's before, but in case you haven't, Harry's Razors offer
high quality shaves.
It's better for your face and your wallet.
Maybe you've gone to like, I don't know, a Walgreens CVS, and you're like, I need to
get some razor blades.
And the dude's like, all right, well, first you have to find me, and he hides in like
the snack aisle, and then you gotta find him, and he unlocks the thing, and then he's like,
these razor blades are gonna be $100.
I haven't shaved in a long time.
Okay, great.
And so Harry's, in fact, is much cheaper, but way better.
You can get a starter set for just $15, and that includes a razor, foaming shave gel,
or shave cream, and three razor blades, plus free shipping.
But if you go to harrys.com, you can get $5 off the starter set with the code MYBROTHER,
all one word.
Start shaving better today.
Got a quick text.
I got a message for Ian also.
It wasn't in the text.
Hey, it's Ian.
I'm texting you.
I got a message for Fiona.
All right, so let me try again.
I strike that, reverse it.
Hey, it's Fiona.
I was reading the phone upside down.
I got a message for Ian.
The text says, wishing you the most magical birthday, wiggling to that nice blonde girl,
and making prostitutes.
Remember, someone is going to die today.
What is this?
It's not candle nights is what it isn't.
I'm sure they didn't mean for this to go up on our candle nights.
Travis is taking his shirt off.
I love you guys so much.
That's all right.
Yeah, happy birthday, Ian, and a happy candle nights, and a happy wiggling, I suppose.
Wiggling, happy wiggling.
Travis, we got another message.
Hit me, dude.
This message is for Just Fisher Parentheses Done, and it's from Johnny Lev.
To the best, best man there is, congrats on finally squeezing that baby out.
Now that the whole preggo thing is over, and you're free of responsibility, you can spend
all your time planning my bachelor party.
Good work.
You're the best.
Does this get me out of babysitting?
It does, Johnny.
Congratulations, and joyous candle nights to everybody.
Thanks again to everybody who came out to our show.
We hope you had a lot of fun.
We know we did.
Let's get back into it.
So one of the things heading into candle nights we discussed on the show was that we didn't
know all that much about Hanukkah.
As represented by the decorations on stage, we tried, and we failed.
There's just none for sale.
Dollar General, not a huge Hanukkah selection.
That's a regional problem, and not really our problem.
We tried.
I've seen one delightful person here in a Hanukkah sweatshirt, and I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Oh, it lights up.
How glorious.
How wonderful.
So I wanted to take a minute.
I constructed a report.
It wasn't even mine.
Honestly, it wasn't even mine.
I took it, I copied and pasted it from the internet, but it did have a lot of words that
I didn't understand, so I had to translate them, and I would like to read it for you
now.
It's titled, Hanukkah, colon, history.
Unlike many Jewish holidays, Hanukkah, also known as the festival of Lutah, is not mentioned
in the Bible.
The historical events upon which the celebration is based are recorded in Maccabees 1 and 2,
two books contained within a later collection of writings known as the Poopkins.
Although Hanukkah is considered a minor Jewish festival, today it ranks, along with squeegee
and squelch, as one of the most beloved Jewish family holidays.
In the year 168 BCE, the hungover Syrian tyrant, Don Cheadle, sent his soldiers to Jerusalem.
The Syrians desecrated the pizza roll.
Will you guys just raise your hands if it gets anti-Semitic, like a little, like when
you're anti-Semitic...
Not you in the back.
Cheadle also abolished taters, outlawing the observance of Shabbat and the festivals,
as well as booty-touching. Altars and idols were set up for the worship of Greek gods,
and he offered Jews two options, conversion or Nantucket.
On the 25th day of the Hebrew month of croissants, in 168 BCE, the pizza roll was renamed for
the Greek god Tim Curry.
A resistance movement led by a priestly family known as Jingles, or Maccabees, developed
against the cruelty of Cheadle.
The head of the family was Bodacious, an elderly man.
I'm actually learning a lot from this.
His son, Hamilton, became the chief strategist.
That's not one that's added in.
That's just a word I can't say.
Yeah, just try to say strategist, but it makes it up.
Oh, I didn't say it. Never mind. I'm an idiot.
And military leader of the resistance, though outnumbered, Hamilton Jingles and his fighters
miraculously won two major battles, routing the Syrians sloppily.
Hanukkah, which means moist, is the festival...
A lot of hands on that one. That one had an impact on the audience.
...is the festival that commemorates the purification and undulation of the Temple.
Following, and this, not a word, changed.
Following the defilement caused by the Greeks during their occupation of the Holy Place.
Today, the holiday reminds Jews to rededicate themselves to stand against forces that would
destroy Judaism and to keep alive the flame of Jewish religion, culture, and people.
No, you really are just going full blown Wikipedia right now.
So that it may be passed on to the next generation.
The end.
According to the legend, when the Maccabees entered the Temple and began to reclaim it
from the Greeks, they immediately re-lit their nur-tamin, which translates to...
Yes, boo louder. Feed me. Feed me. Feed me that energy.
...which translates to lugubrious milquetoast, which burned constantly in the Temple and
has a parallel in our synagogues to this day.
In the Temple, they found a single jar of calamari...
There's whaling. There's actual whaling.
...which was sufficient for only one day.
The gallivant, who was sent to secure additional calamari, took eight days to gavort, and
miraculously, the single jar of oil continued to hogwash until his return.
I am feeding on it.
The rabbis of the Talmud attributed the eight days of Hanukkah to the miracle of this single
jar of calamari.
The end.
I'm gonna say something a little contentious here.
I don't take it out of context, ever.
But if it means that that hadn't just happened, then I wish Hanukkah had never been invented.
That's how... I gotta hand raise on that. I guess that's fair.
If you could save us from that, I think it would be worth it.
I thought that was informative and insightful.
You did go on a weirdly, like, educational run there.
Like a Christmas special from the mid-80s. I wanted there to be one moment where everyone
went, huh, and then came back to hating it.
And then Screech still does run in after they learn a lesson about drugs.
And here's Screech right now.
I'm sorry about booing you.
That's all right.
This past Thanksgiving, my partner and I celebrated Thanksgiving at my parent's parent...
I'm sorry, partner's parent's house.
The parents live locally, but since we wanted to spend Friday with them as well...
You stuttered through a phrase that I really enjoy.
My partner's parents...
After that.
I celebrated Thanksgiving at my partner's parents...
Just do the whole thing.
This past Thanksgiving, my partner and I celebrated Thanksgiving at my partner's parent's house.
The parents live locally, but since we wanted to spend Friday with them as well, and since
we don't have our own car, we thought it might be best to just sleep over Thursday night.
Thursday night is highlighted here on Travis's iPad in case he wants to make an appointment for them.
However, maybe just stop by, see how things are going.
However, we were informed by the parents that it is expected that we would not share a bed.
My partner and I have been together for nine months.
We're both well into adulthood.
We have completely lost this audience.
And the...
Yeah, because it's like not funny.
I was...
Oh.
Sad libs is a bad bit.
Nobody likes it.
So say we all.
My partner and I have been together for nine months.
We're both well into adulthood.
Parents like me are progressive in most every other way.
My partner and I are, of course, classy enough to not get busy on the family room futon during our stay.
But we're not married and have no plans for it.
So I'm not sure when circumstances would change the parents' mind about this.
And the problem is certain to rear its ugly head again.
Brothers, how can I convince them to let us sleep how we are most comfortable?
Seeking the solace of shared slumber in Cincinnati.
What if your partner's parents are just saving this for a gift?
So maybe not like 2019 under the candle night's bush.
What's that?
Oh, it's an envelope.
Oh, no, it's probably a gift card at a Home Depot.
Boo!
But then you open it up.
It's not.
It's a little letter from your partner's parents.
And it just says, go for it.
Connect 4, do it!
What if it just says, we know and we're cool?
Because you have to assume at that point, 2019, three years, four years from now, they know they're doing it.
I like more of a demand.
Go for it!
Do it!
No.
What's worse?
Like what?
That's worse, right?
Definitely that's worse than saying like, go for it.
You're cool.
I want to say that I do like...
Aren't you excited to be able to sleep like with the room as cold as you want and the fan on?
Because I'd be like a little excited about that.
Like, oh, I'm just gonna make it like 40 degrees in here.
And my question is, if the debate is whether or not you can sleep on the family room futon together,
if you're not allowed to sleep together, where do you end up if the family room futon is the best option?
You're in the garage.
Like what's the other option that you get secluded to?
You're in the dog bed.
You have to sleep with the parents.
Meredith and Joey, I had a bad dream.
That you guys are closed minded.
Jeremy, we've laid some blankets on the floor and now you'll listen to us do it.
Yeah, we just...
No, no, no, no.
This is how two adults make love.
Take notes.
Still no bad words.
Just remember, no bad words.
We're very progressive.
We just want to make sure you know what you're doing in there.
With it.
Watch Meredith and Joey for a second.
Sorry?
You probably thought that was an affectation.
Oh, that's her names with W's.
We're very progressive parents.
Well, now they're just...
Yeah, that's doesn't mean.
Do you guys want...
How about we do one final yahoo and then we...
Not the final yahoo.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We'll do another yahoo.
Okay.
And then we'll turn it to the audience and do some audience questions.
We'll just...
Don't line up or anything.
We'll just yell at you when you put your hands up and call you forward.
Does everybody know the rule about questions at live shows?
It's printed on the microphone.
We brought no bummers with us, by the way.
You can see it right there.
And also no cursing.
Yeah, no cursing.
Yeah.
I swan to John.
You guys are going to think it's funny.
I'm going to immortalize myself by ruining candle nights.
No, I mean you will.
Yeah, it'll work.
For this room, but you don't make it on the recording or any podcast recording from now
to the end of time.
We got the juice to make that happen.
You want to be on Marin?
No dice.
We'll find somebody who knows that guy and say, hey, they're off limits.
I just want to send in...
I just want to finish my plug.
Thank you, Ear Trumpet Labs.
They made that for us.
Yeah, thank you.
Beautiful microphones.
No bummers.
Sent in by Zoe Kinski climbing that ladder.
Zoe Kinski.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Passenger Wow Widow, which...
Sorry?
Oh, it's okay.
World of Warcraft Widow is saying, okay.
Wow.
It's either ways, but it's better than like, wow, I'm a widow.
Wow, you're a widow.
Wow.
Yeah, there's a little Christopher Walken in there.
That's the only word I can do.
If Dwight was here, he's got a pretty good walking, but my only walking is wow.
Wow.
All right.
Passenger Wow Widow asks, if I am a super good girl, will Santa bring me Robert Downey
Jr. for Christmas?
What I love about this question is the thought of Santa showing up at Robert Downey Jr.'s
house like, it's time.
The bargain we made when I put you in Iron Man.
Time to pay the piper who is Santa.
And you know, I would like to think of RDJ the dude would go, I get it.
You?
I get it.
RDJ.
Sorry?
Okay.
RDJ.
Your personal friend and mentor.
I'm pretty Hollywood at this point.
Yeah, sure.
Then he would go, you're right.
You're right.
And just walk into the bag.
No, this is on me.
I've lived a good life.
Could it be a?
Tell Mark Ruffalo I said I love you.
Could it be a Robert Downey Jr.?
Hi, I'm Bob Downey the second.
And I want to thank you for having me to your boudoir.
I hope to show you some challenging yet comfortable lovemaking positions.
Shall we begin with the smooches?
Shall we begin with some heavy petty?
I hear it's somebody's special day here.
I heard you've been a very good girl.
This beats the heck out of the tile store.
Wow, I'm really excited to be the Bob Downey in your boudoir.
Sorry, I don't know any other words for it other than boudoir.
I meant to learn some, but I didn't.
It's a busy season at the tile store.
I was in a bicycle accident and I lost some words.
Luckily not bicycle or accident, because can you imagine?
How would I even describe my situation?
I was in a two-wheeled mobile accident.
You know pedal pedals?
I did a bad on one of them.
On a pedal pedal I did a bad and boom, ouchie.
I'm Bob Downey the second.
I have a head contusion.
Bob Downey the second, I'm glad you're here.
You're better than Robert Downey Jr.
You've explained this to me 18 times, Bob Downey the second.
Sorry, I had this bicycle, uh-oh.
I think there's a sliding scale for how good you have to be
and how bad Robert Downey Jr. has to be.
Because it's like you can be as good as you want,
but unless Robert Downey Jr. has failed Santa in some way,
I don't think he can close on that deal.
I don't know, I didn't like Iron Man 2 very much.
So now he has to be someone's servant?
Yeah, I guess so.
That's a pretty high standard now that I think about it.
I don't want to be held to that standard.
We all have off days.
Questions from the audience?
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's start on this side.
You want it too much.
You weren't the first hand up.
Yes, with the finger pointing at themself, yes.
Hi, hello, hey, hey.
Not you, Michael Sullivan,
stage manager for our live extravaganza.
We'll do you later.
Hello, sir, what is your name?
My name's Jordan.
Do you understand the rule?
No bummers.
How can we help?
I travel a lot for work,
and I have to be in a place for a long period of time
on a project.
Can you speak just right up in here?
Like an old timey radio show.
Pretend you're doing an ad for Ajax.
You can just lean down.
You don't have to do a weird squatty thing.
You bend at the waist, right?
I don't want to assume.
Can you stop kibitzing for a second?
Sure can.
I have to travel for work and be in a place
for a long period of time.
I'm living in a corporate apartment in New York City.
I'm single, and I can't really decorate.
I'll buy the rights to your TV show right now.
How ready are you to mingle?
How zany is your neighbor?
The mingling is like mid-level ready to mingle.
I am single and somewhat ready to mingle.
So as I am ready,
like I need to...
Right now it's like filled with like Pier 1 imports,
like gross furniture and stuff,
because I didn't furnish it.
So, but I also can't put anything permanent in
because I'm leaving in March.
So how do I put together an apartment that feels like me
without spending any money
and also...
So let me understand.
You can't spend any money on nothing permanent,
but it has to really scream Jordan.
Yes.
That's exactly it.
Can you write over the wall,
to the door,
on the outside of the door,
Jordan's place.
Well, I did that, so that's done.
Done.
Darn.
Ooh, that was close.
Can you...
Can you turn on the furniture upside down,
just like Jordan lives here,
he's a real free spirit.
You know Jordan.
He's a real free spirit.
He doesn't like to sit on things.
You know those noonie and noonie from that funny SNL skit?
He's like those people.
Cool.
Yeah, Jordan,
you're kind of tying our hands,
because normally I just say,
go out and just buy the most expensive rug.
Right.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop, everybody, stop.
Wait, wait, wait, shut up, shut up.
Unless...
Okay, now there will be some investment in this,
but you need to get a storage unit,
move all the furniture into that unit,
and then get nothing else in your unit.
And then when people come in,
you look at them in the eye,
and you say, think about me,
picture the furniture.
Oh, my God.
He is the pan.
Yeah, and then, yeah, bang-a-rang.
Oh, there you are, Jordan.
Knowing what you know about me,
inflatable furniture.
You're doing it, and then the furniture will appear.
Yeah, bang-a-rang, you did it.
It's a futon made of dogs.
What?
I'm going to have a seat on it.
Oh, God, I broke my tailbone.
That's so Jordan.
I feel so unsafe in Jordan's place.
Jordan's always breaking tailbones.
Okay, can you make them
draw a picture and then decorate
the apartment with the pictures that they drew?
Like, this is what others have seen.
What will you see?
I'll be back in three hours.
I hope we didn't have anything pressing to do.
Did we help you, Jordan?
That was so good. Thank you so much.
Thank you, Jordan.
I picked the last one.
Travis, you pick the middle.
Yes, you should.
Yes, mustache.
That was fun.
That's a jaunty hello.
Well, hello.
Oh, boy.
I see what we're doing here.
What is your name?
My name is Bobby.
Bobby, do you understand the rule?
No, gosh-darn-bummers.
There you go, good.
I travel in town for the holidays
every year, and over the past couple of years
my family's been moving Christmas
back
gradually. Now, because I'm traveling
in, I can't necessarily get
off work for the 18th.
Oh, whoa.
How do I stop Christmas from sliding into September?
Okay.
I must stop Christmas from coming for now.
Have you already experienced
Christmas, Bobby?
It's been a little while.
Okay. Like this year, 2015,
has your Christmas come and gone yet?
Oh, I missed it.
Oh, you missed it. Cool.
Oh, wait, hold on.
I've got this. Do you know what's great here, Bobby?
Whenever you roll up is Christmas.
Yeah.
You didn't miss Christmas. They did
Christmas early.
That's what we learned from the Grinch who stole Christmas, actually.
If it's not the exchanging of gifts,
it's the people around you.
I would legitimately say, like,
I don't think you did have Christmas
because Bobby wasn't here.
Check the pictures.
Do you see Bobby?
Let's go to the videotape.
Yeah, I'm seeing no Bobby here.
Yeah, no Bobby. I don't think
you had Christmas because it's about the people.
I've only known you for 110 seconds,
but I just know you are
Christmas.
I'm not convinced you're not a bunch
of presents stacked up in jeans
and a shirt.
Well, you don't have to...
I'm not looking at your naked
boxes.
Well, now I am.
He was unwrapping me with his eyes.
Can you imagine
anything more... I think you do a protest
Christmas on December the 25th.
Can you imagine anything more rad than
Bobby sitting on the floor,
little Santa hat, pile of presents in front of
the tree by himself, just like,
Well, this one's the sandwich maker.
Thank you to whoever
got this for me.
If anyone would like to join me, I'll be in the living room
while his family's in the kitchen.
I don't know where we went wrong.
It's New Year's Eve already.
Over here, we're a week
ahead.
Oh, wait till they lap you, and then it's
Christmas again.
The
stupid thing is they should be pushing it later
because they can get all the decorations that
like 50% off.
Hence our entire like
scene right now.
Bobby, does that help?
Very much so.
Justin, pick somebody from the right.
My turn. If you're a
non-dude,
can you raise your hand?
I want to get a non-dude. There you go.
Right here. Come on up.
The mic is so far away.
This Christmas...
Alright, let's give him a big round of applause.
Hello,
and what is your name? Hello, my name's
Nathania. Hi, Nathania.
Is that with an N? Nathania? Yes, it is.
Okay, welcome. And do you know the
rule? Yes, I do. No bummers.
Okay. Okay. How can we help?
So, my husband, he's the best.
Okay. Alright!
Sounds like you don't need any help.
Yeah, sounds like you're fine. I don't.
He's awesome. I've been
waiting for the results of that contest
all day.
And to find out like this, Nathania?
Yeah, I know.
This how you do me?
Steve Harvey should
come out and announce the results, right guys?
Tabagal!
And the best husband is
Griffin McElroy. No, wait a minute.
I'm like on
news alerts, like, what just happened?
So I can reference that. Freshest ref.
Freshest ref award goes to
Griffin. No, wait, it went to Travis.
Steve Harvey, not again!
Nathania, how can we
help?
So, he
knows what he likes.
And it's hard to get
him gifts. Sure.
So I don't want any advice
on what gifts to give him. Good.
I want to know, how
can we, myself
and his family, make him
like whatever gifts we give him?
Nathania,
is your husband here right now?
He is. He brought me here.
This is my Christmas present.
Oh, man, he won. Nice.
That's hard to beat. He's the best.
Mr. Nathania?
Can I give you...
Did you raise your hand? Yes.
Sorry, what? No, we're singing with
Mr. Nathania. Yeah, it's not that important.
You're not at the microphone.
I'm gonna
tell you a lesson that I learned
when I was about eight years old.
And that is that gifts
given to you are
not for you.
They are for the person who gave them
to you so that you can be thankful
for all the love that they showed you
in that gift. And if you look up from the gift
and go, you're
the worst.
I learned that
at eight. I doubt very much he does that.
But there is
some nuance to the situation that Travis does not.
That is impossible.
But this is the lie in what you
just said is that if you
really love somebody and you cannot
tell instantly
that they don't like something,
right away, everybody...
Oh, it's a lie we tell each other.
It's a lie we tell each other like, oh, you hated that
and I know you hated that, but that's not what this
is about. I get it. Yeah, you have to
go to your grave like, no, absolutely not.
I loved it, and it was the best coffee maker
I ever got in my entire life. I never used it.
It was great.
Get a present-receiving
catchphrase.
What? No, listen.
It's something I've been
doing for years, and you guys probably haven't noticed.
I'm kind of part of the kimono right now, but...
Don't look!
Get a
present-receiving catchphrase.
So every time you get a present, no matter what it is,
it doesn't matter. This is a
gift-agnostic
idiom, and don't steal mine because
I need it, but just be like,
oh, tight!
That makes so much sense
now.
But everybody has one
of those, right?
Mine is like,
I'll open it.
That's a whole
run!
I do it every
gift. Mine is just this.
Ooh, Travis like!
We all really don't like Travis.
Christmas is a real horror show.
We don't use Travis
gifts anymore. Not even
invited. Nathaniel,
can you tape a 20 to
it somewhere?
Just tape a 20.
Who doesn't like that? Yeah. Just hand
him a 20. Just hand him a 20. Tape to
like, whatever thing. And ask for five dollars
back. Or a fake
price tag on
it. That's a big
high price.
Like one million dollars.
Wait, Griffin, I'm worried that this side
of the audience didn't see it. Could you do that one more time?
Like a high price. Like one million dollars.
You can purchase the GIF outside
after the show. Don't worry, folks.
Yeah, we got DVDs.
Nathaniel, does that help? Absolutely.
Great. Thank you.
She's good at lying if she didn't like
what she got.
Let's go
for one more from the back.
From the way back. Flashy Hanukkah shirt.
Flashy Hanukkah shirt, yes. You earned it.
And I don't mean like
ostentatious Hanukkah shirt.
No, it's literally, it is
illuminated. Hello.
Hello.
Did somebody just boo me?
No. They said hello in a very
Germanic manner. They said hello the opposite
of booing you. They did a hello from downtown.
Hello. What is your name?
My name is Shaylin. Hi, Shaylin.
Hey, Shaylin. Hi. Can you scoot over to the
just close the door? Perfect. There we go.
Let her rip. Okay. Hi.
Go for it. I was wondering
if I was to decorate my home
for Candle Nights next year,
what color scheme
would you say is the official
color scheme of Candle Nights?
Whew.
No, this is a good question.
And it's honestly,
it's honestly as
one of the three dads
of Candle Nights.
It's one of the reasons
why the holiday
hasn't caught on as much as
we would want it to.
Because the problem is
the color of Candle Nights
is fire.
And you hear,
you just heard me say that and your brain
thought like, oh, red. No, you
misunderstand.
It's
fire.
To do a house up
like that is...
Arson.
I mean, it's arson.
Everything you see in front of you is
rigged to explode when the show's over.
It's going to be quite
the... Don't stick around.
Don't stick around. Get out.
I think that what we just did
was illegal.
No, there's nothing flammable.
Just claiming fire in a big stuff building.
But fine. No, that was a joke. Clearly
it's parody fair use. Listen.
That's how fair use works.
It's tricky because inside
you get some candles, whatever.
Outside, what do you do?
Outside of a controlled burn?
Outside of like
sick like butane
fountains? Is that even a thing?
You could also, I was going to say
like project fire onto your house
but I feel like that might go poorly.
They have a name for that, Travis.
It's somebody whose house is
about to be gone.
You can't project fire onto your house.
Oh, you meant a picture. Okay, got it.
Got it. Not literal fire.
I'm with you now.
But still, the point
stands, if somebody has a fire hologram
on their house, your neighbor's not going to
drive by and be like, oh, sick.
I will say, they won't this year
but maybe soon. They'll be like, oh,
candle lights. Nice.
That's all the holidays together.
A controlled burn on the front facade
of your house. Get an
expert. Oh, get an expert to get this
controlled burn going. But just have
it spell out, it's cool.
This is cool.
This is cool is fine. Don't call the police,
Dave.
Again.
Unless this, if this doesn't,
if this stops spelling out
this is cool.
Call the police or the fire
people. Unless this is also on fire,
Dave.
Then please tell me, Dave.
I'm so scared.
His house says it's all
Oh, no, no, no.
That's not a word.
Stop being words. Get them.
Get the fire.
Is this a call about the house that's part way
on fire? Yeah, we've heard about it. No, you don't understand.
No, no, no. The worm has turned.
It got worse.
Does that
help? That helps a lot.
Cool. Don't do any of that stuff.
Thank you.
Yeah, I think that's
going to do it. Okay, listen.
All kidding aside,
the fact that so many of you
folks who raise your hand if you're not
from West Virginia at all.
Oh, my God. No.
Anybody not from America?
Curiosity. All right.
All right. All right. Cool, cool, cool.
Thank you so much for coming
to Candle Nights. Did you have a good time?
We
sort of like
tweet nice stuff to that effect.
Tweet hashtag Candle Nights.
Hashtag Candle Nights like I had a great time so we can keep doing it.
Not that like
the man is going to keep us from doing it.
It's pretty much just us and Chase.
And you can't shut us down, Obama.
Thank you. By the way, thank you.
Huge, huge, huge thank you.
There's so many people I have to thank, but
Chase Henderson put on this show.
He's the promoter of our show, Chase Henderson.
All of Chase's volunteers
who helped out. Thank you so, so much.
Thank you to Michael Sullivan,
who was our stage manager. He did a great job.
Thank you to
Dwight
Slappy. Am I saying that right? Dwight.
Great.
Dwight Slappy from Things I Bought Sheets.
Thank you to Sydney Smurl McElroy.
Is it McElroy? McElroy?
McElroy from Sawbones.
I would also like to say thank you to
Theresa McElroy. And to Rachel McElroy.
Let me put you back on this.
And Clem McElroy and Carol McElroy
who did all of the beautiful decorations
that you see on stage.
Thank you to Jason
and Tyler Eldridge for being our
for being the Druids who stole Dwight away.
Thank you to Boyd Smith for being the Grinch.
Okay, that's all. Oh wait, one more.
Thank you to Josh and the folks at Billions for helping us set up.
Yes, and all the Carolers.
And the Carolers who named Dad.
Dad!
And thank you to Riley. Riley Smurl.
Riley Smurl, thank you so much.
I just want to like, I referenced this at the beginning
about how this was a swearing day.
It got really thorny there
like right before we had to come here.
My baby, about
literally exactly the time
we were supposed to leave, my baby threw up
and had a temperature of 101.
So it was like, whoa. She's fine now.
She's fine now.
I got a video of her playing Ring Around the Rosie.
Like, she's good. But it was like, it was pretty intense there.
So, thank you to
we have another hand to Sydney
who didn't really want to come, but did anyway.
Because she loves you.
And Charlie, if you're listening
to this in the future,
we're cool.
You're fine. You made it.
My point was it got really thorny
and I got so stressed out because we got here
and everything was running behind and I was like really worried
that it was going to be terrible.
But like all of our friends and family came together to help us
put this on. It was real inspirational.
It was a genuine Candle Nights miracle.
Thank you all so much.
And thank you to you, the people who
like, if you came and stood in line
I understood it was raining. I'm sorry about that.
And if you came a long way
to come see us, that's awesome.
We're going to be
over at a bar called
The Lantern for a little bit.
Big fans here.
Some lantern heads in the house.
It's a 4th and 8th, right?
4th Avenue and 8th Street. Is that right?
Yes. Thank you, Sullivan.
So we'll be over there.
It's a fun place.
And is that going to do it for us too, though?
I think so. You want that final yahoo?
We're going to do a final yahoo.
Yeah.
Yeah, final yahoo and then...
Then we've got a special Candle Nights carol.
There's not a lot of Candle Nights carols.
There is one.
And we're going to perform that for you.
But we do have a final yahoo for you.
Calm down.
This one was sent in by Zoe Kinski,
climbing that ladder, Zoe Kinski.
Sorry, something's going wrong.
Oh, no, this one was Chuck Yeager too.
Chuck Yeager asks again.
Man, he's active on yahoo.
Did you think Mrs. Doubtfire
was hot when you were a kid,
or was that just me?
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name has been Justin
Tyler McElroy.
And I'm going to be
Justin Tyler McElroy.
My name has been and will always be
Travis Patrick McElroy.
I'm Griffin Andrew McElroy.
This is a Candle Nights song.
Strummin' my sixth string.
No.
You already goofed on it.
The words are on the screen. Read them.
Okay.
I followed him.
Wait, where are you starting?
Where are you picking up?
From the beginning of the song!
Okay, go ahead.
Go ahead.
I would have been fine.
I would have figured it out.
I'm a frigging professional.
No, no, no!
He didn't finish it.
I didn't finish it.
Let me know when you're ready.
Oh, my god!
Livin' on sponge cake.
Watchin' the sun bake.
All of the tourists
covered with oil.
If you were in the show,
come on up!
I'm in my sixth straight.
Come on, Dad.
Riley.
I'm on my front porch swing.
Smell of the shrimp, they're beginning to boil.
There's Sidney and Dwight Slappy.
Wasted away again in Margaritaville.
A druid.
Searching for my lost shaker of salt.
Salt, salt, yes, sir.
Some people claim that there's a wolf on the plain,
but I don't, it's nobody's fault.
Let's do the chorus one more time.
We're gonna drop the guitar,
and I just wanna hear everybody.
Let's share this moment together.
You ready?
No, that's cool, I get it.
Five, six, five, six, seven, eight.
Wasted away again in Margaritaville.
Let me hear you.
Come on, everybody, it's Candle Nights.
Searching for my lost shaker of salt.
Salt, salt, salt.
It's a thing.
Some people claim that there's a wolf on the plain,
but I don't, it's nobody's fault.
Wait, one more time, one more time.
Come on, one more time.
Wasted away again in Margaritaville.
I wanna hear you out there, Bill.
I wanna hear everybody, come on.
Searching for my lost shaker of salt.
We actually sound like a drunk Jimmy Poppins concert
right now.
Some people claim that there's a woman
on the plain, but I don't, it's nobody's fault.
Joyous Candle Nights, everybody, goodnight.
Hey, good girls, do you wanna just say you got water?