The McElroy brothers are not experts,
and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert,
but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Hey, it's my gig, okay?
It's all I have.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only,
so the babies out there will know how cool they are
for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
It feels like life, oh, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, oh, it's better, it's better with you.
This is true, oh, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, oh, it's better with you.
Let me tell you something,
if you've never experienced that before,
and then you go two years without it,
oh, it starts to hurt.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, it starts to hurt, you start to crave it.
Hello, and welcome, my brother, my brother,
me an advice show for the modern era.
They did have to recast me during the break,
but I'll be playing Justin McElroy, the oldest brother.
Sorry, McElroy, it says here, McElroy.
I'll be playing Travis, big dog.
McElroy.
Oh, no, oh, no, I don't think so, folks.
How many more live shows can we pack into 2021
before that dies off?
I just checked, is it?
None, okay, apparently it's just this one.
And I'm Griffin McElroy.
And I also want to say a special thanks
to the old prospector who came and introduced us
at the start of the show.
Thank you, old prospector.
Yeah, that's funny, I guess.
Griff, what's the matter, buddy?
What's wrong, bud?
You should be happy we're back doing live shows.
Yeah, I was back doing shows.
Oh, yeah, I'm stoked, I'm stoked, everyone.
Did something happen?
Yeah, what's up?
Hold on, let me try, let me try again.
This is sincere, can we get a second read?
Yeah, I'll take it, we'll get this in post.
Okay, we'll get it clean.
Can we get it clean, please, everyone?
Hey, what's, what's up?
It's fine, let's just do this, we can do it.
No, hey, this is a labor, Griffin.
Clearly something's up.
Do you need to talk in private?
Yeah.
John Cena whipped your ass?
Sorry, oh, I forgot the mics were on.
I'm so sorry, Griffin.
What, wait, wait, Griffin, is he telling the truth?
Or is this some twisted game of telephone?
Certainly.
No.
TV and films John Cena didn't whip your ass?
Not children's prank show host John Cena.
It's fine, it was this afternoon
and I'm doing much better now.
What happened?
Well.
Tell me the true story about John Cena whipped your ass.
Up and down.
Oh, up and down, you didn't say.
Not side to side?
No, he got me there too, he got me there too.
Poor thing.
It was just like, it really wasn't a big deal,
but it was right after lunch and I was going
to the restroom.
You just finished your Crestless PB&J.
Yeah, and it was just after lunch
and you know, for the bathroom, that's like rush hour.
Yeah.
And so I just like showed up to a bathroom
and there was only one stall open,
but John Cena kind of walked in there at the same time.
Yeah.
And he was like, excuse me, excuse me.
I'm glad you took a second run at that.
Excuse me.
Much more Cena-esque.
No, you guys can joke about this.
But I was like, oh hey, great stuff that you do.
I'll be real quick.
And then he started, like what surprised me
was how quickly he started just yelling.
He was like, I should go first,
I was the one who did wrestling.
And then I was like, I understand that,
but I'm actually here with,
but he already was whipping my ass at that point.
Hey, Griffin, I'm sorry.
Yeah, no, go ahead and ask.
Whatever you want to know.
Did the ass whipping ramp up slowly?
No, it was like, it was so,
everything about this was so fast.
He like, before I knew it,
and I was already like, oh yeah, okay, you can.
And like a few more stalls opened up,
but he was like pretty focused in on that point.
Yeah.
That's kind of his whole thing.
Yeah, no, he has sort of explosive strength.
And then he was like, he was like picking me up
and he was like trying to put me in the sink.
And he was like,
Like head first, like a swirly?
No, like he was sitting me in it.
And then he was like pushing me down
and he was like, I'm gonna make you go in the sink hole.
Yeah.
And you're sure it was John Cena?
It was him, for sure.
You weren't mistaking it with another large man?
We are never going to be invited
to this convention again.
100%.
We've done three.
I know John Cena just stood up in the crowd and walked out.
John, it was a joke.
We've done three events today.
And in every one, the majority of discussion
has been about John Cena.
It's only been able to talk about all day.
Before he whipped my ass inside and out
and tried pushing me down the sink.
Wait, inside and out is new.
And he was yelling.
That's a new interaction.
That's a new piece of information.
Guys, I'm not kidding.
You're running like a hand puppet.
It was like 10 minutes of him trying to push me down
what he kept calling the sink hole.
And I was like, do you mean the drain?
Was he whipping your ass during that?
Was it separate?
We're gonna get a letter.
We're gonna get a letter from someone.
So did he whip your ass
and then try to put you in the sink hole?
Please ask the McElroy brothers not to talk about me anymore.
He should have thought, I mean, it is my fault.
I should have let him go first.
I guess part of it.
Did you try going in the sink hole to defuse it?
I didn't, I did.
God, it took so long.
I started to get uncomfortable for him.
And I was like, I'll try to go in the sink hole.
How did it end?
Where did you leave him?
I ran, I mean, I stayed in the sink
until he left the room.
And then when I was outside, I grabbed a security person.
And I was like, hey, and I pointed at him.
I pointed at him and I was like, he just,
and then he started yelling like again.
And he was like, he kept yelling, I'm invisible today.
Wait, now hold up.
We don't even have time to unpack that.
This is an advice show.
We do advice here.
No, wait, I do have to ask one more question.
Did you try to fight back at all?
Did you try to take a swing at him or anything?
I did a couple of times, but then like,
I kind of got invested in trying to fit in the sink hole.
Would have been a great story.
It was collaborative art at that point.
And Mario makes it look so easy.
I know.
So this is an advice show.
We take your questions and turn them alchemy-like
into wisdom.
And I realize now that I should have begun
because it's never been more appropriate
by saying we're so happy to be re-emerging
with our proud Chilean miners.
We return here to the Emerald City,
Seatown, Jet City, the Queen City until 1982
when they officially changed it to Emerald City.
Wait, no, what?
The Queen City's Cincinnati.
That's right, they changed it.
They were scared.
Yeah, take that.
That Cincinnati was gonna cross the country and-
And beat them up.
Like John Cena beating up Griffin McElroy.
Who, by the way, John's people, if you're listening,
was the one who told that story.
Yeah, not us.
Not us.
It's very easy to confuse our three voices,
but Griffin definitely told the story
about how John Cena-
I told that story.
John wrote it with his actions.
I, Justin McElroy, am still extremely hireable
for any work that you may have.
What the fuck are we hireable for at this point?
I mean, they're making another Trolls, so-
That is true.
Hey, weirdly, because I'm sure,
I just want to give you guys a scoop on this.
No one has, let me check with Amanda.
No, okay.
They're playing coy.
They're playing coy on this one.
They haven't reached out yet about that one,
but I'm assuming they'll eventually ask us
to be in the movie.
A much larger part, I have to assume.
I have to assume.
Yeah, a five-headed tall Troll.
That will still not incorporate our dad.
No.
I don't know if you guys know this,
but a lot has changed in the last three years.
In these trying times.
In these trying times, a lot has changed.
I would say that in many ways, I think we've matured.
Like a third of the audience just realized
you were setting up a bit.
The show has become, I would say, much classier.
Oh God.
Okay, that one.
Much more artistic.
Paul, I'm gonna need another White Claw, my man.
And so I'd like to start this show off
with a little high-class segment.
I like to call it Work of Fart.
Just say it.
Yeah.
Kidding aside, thanks, Paul.
Thank you, Paul.
Should we play?
Kidding aside, before we move on,
would it be possible for us to listen
to the Work of Fart jingle in absolute silence
so you guys can appreciate
what a fucking low-grade fart sound?
Okay, wait, let's all be quiet.
Play it again, Paul.
["Work of Fart"]
Okay.
So there are, there's, yeah.
Sounds like a fucking key chain.
It sounds like a key chain you press a button on.
It sounds like a fucking yak back from like 1994.
It was a free use sound effect.
I don't know what to tell you.
We're not gonna spend money on this podcast?
We're not gonna spend money on Work of Fart?
Are you kidding me?
How am I gonna explain that to an accountant of any kind?
Now, I see a charge here for $1.79.
What is that for?
I'm paying for a fart?
It had to be a good fart so my brothers liked a bit.
No, that part, I think that is actually a federal crime
to lie to your accountant, so I don't think.
So here's how it works.
I have some-
Now really listen,
because the rules are pretty complicated.
I have some classics here of different kinds,
and I will list the description
and all my brothers have to do
is give me the title of that classic.
For example, if I sat a genius detective
who uses deductive reasoning
and is also very confident in his penis.
The Sherlock Holmes.
Yeah, exactly.
Thank you, Griffin.
Yeah, I fucking hate how good I am.
Justin, I think you're gonna win this one.
Okay.
You're not, but it's because Griffin,
Griffin and I have kind of the same twisted
Southwark style sense of humor.
Okay.
So this first one, I framed kind of like a trailer
description while I'm here.
Oh, cool.
That ought to fix it.
This orphan waif having been tossed aside
by numerous people is back and ready for action.
He's angry and he wants more revenge.
This has nothing to do with using the bathroom.
Well, what's the word for angry?
Oh, Oliver Pissed?
That's us. There it is.
Tied.
That's a tie point.
Are you ready?
Yeah, and don't give us a double hint.
That felt cheap to me.
Yeah.
Humphrey Bogart has to help.
Humphrey Beaufort.
Nope.
I said it wouldn't be that.
God, it's like you've never played
a word of fart before.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
Humphrey Bogart has to help his ex-girlfriend
escape a Moroccan city
if only he can stop masturbating.
Casablanca.
Yes!
Wow.
And Travis, may I say,
just to doff my cap to you, sir,
the easy one was Asablanca
and you didn't walk down that route.
Not as good.
Not as good as Casablanca.
Yeah, that's real good.
Yeah, we can all agree.
After being framed for a crime he didn't commit
and sent to a terrible French prison,
Edmond Dantes is back,
posing as a rich gentleman,
attempting to get his revenge on his enemies
by shoving his hand as far as-
Santa Monica Stowe.
Yes!
Wow.
Next!
Next one!
What's the score?
It's two-two, right?
Well, here's the weird,
that was all I had.
Damn it.
You son of a gun!
Come up with another one right now.
Come up with another one fresh.
Just fresh, right off the dome.
Okay, great.
Ariel is dying to join Prince Eric.
The Little Spermaid?
In a land filled with flatulence,
in this I Want song.
Fart of Your World.
Yes!
A rare work of fart victory
for Justin McElroy.
Wow, this is huge, huge.
This is-
It's weird.
That's weird I like this bit now.
That's weird.
This is doubly humiliating
because I didn't have to say The Little Spermaid.
Or Asa Blanca.
Yeah.
I see your true colors shining through.
So as I was saying,
this is an advice show.
And we're gonna help some people right now.
Here we go.
I'm in the middle of creating a delicious bowl of chili.
One of its ingredients being a bottle of lager beer.
Lager beer.
Okay.
I've effed up and forgot to get this ingredient.
But there's good news.
My neighbor is having a birthday celebration
which he invited me to stop by for.
In fact, I already did drop by
to drop off a few baked goods as a birthday gift
before returning to my apartment to do chores.
One of which was making this chili that brings us to now.
Would it be weird for me to-
Yep.
Would it be weird for me to go and grab a beer
from this celebration and then walk back to my apartment?
It seems like it would look like a dick move
or at least just weird, but I was invited.
I did provide snacks and I wanna make this chili.
Which honestly, friend, you should have listed first
because that's what's driving you.
What's my move?
That's from Chili Maker in Chapel Hill.
What I love, I think we need to change
the way people ask these questions
because I think it should be like,
is this a higher level weird than normal,
weird human behavior?
Yeah, everybody's a baseline weird.
Our baseline for that's pretty fucked up, gang.
Yeah, because we've all done this, not this thing.
Not this thing.
Yeah.
No, never, this.
But we've done a thing that you've told the story
like three years later and seen the look
on someone else's face and gone,
oh, this isn't as charming as I thought.
I thought this was kind of roguish.
Okay, I think this may be a helpful way of framing it.
If you throw a party and someone comes
and they have a kick-ass time,
but then they leave to go do chores,
and then they come-
Next door.
Next door, and then they come back in
an hour and a half later and they grab a beer
and then they leave with the beer
as if to say, I got thirsty next door,
and then they drink that beer.
You would think, pretty inconsiderate friend.
Does the same hold true if they walk in
and grab a beer and say, don't worry,
this is for my chili.
Is it the same, is it-
What if you say like, I'll be back with some chili soon.
That's one thing.
You gotta return with some, like a sampling of the chili,
but you're not making enough for a party.
No way.
So you're gonna have a small solo cup full of chili.
This is for the after party of just you and me, Derek.
Yeah, a chili fest style sample cup with styrofoam.
I actually think it's the one ingredient
that it is better if you walked in and said,
this is for chili.
Cause if you walked in your neighbor's house
and went through their cupboard
and grabbed like just a bag of dry beans
or like looked through their refrigerator
for a pound of ground beef or something,
you said, sorry, just need this for chili real quick.
But if you grab a beer and said, I need this for chili,
I think there's enough going on that someone will go, okay.
And then only think about-
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
In this circumstance, what you have set up
is the situation where somebody's gonna be like,
hey, where are you going with that beer?
It's like, well, you know, it's a party.
So I'm just getting a beer.
Well, no, the nice thing is because you live next door,
you can go ahead and crack it open right there.
Pretend to drink and make like a glug, glug, glug, glug.
Love that beer flavor.
I'm going to hate to waste this.
I look so fizzy in my nose.
And hate to waste this on chili.
You guys feel me?
I'm gonna go drink this next door
so I can really savor it.
Savor this.
And if you smell chili later,
then I made another drunken oops.
I got so tagged off of this Corona.
Excuse me, I should have picked any other beer.
Yeah.
You know what's funny is I actually,
in my pantry, I do have about half of a six pack of Corona
that I do specifically keep around
for chili-based sort of experiences.
I can't imagine it's for drinking.
No, not anymore.
Not today.
That's a tough break, guys.
Hey, tough break to my friends over at the Corona Foundation.
Does it change it at all?
If someone walks into your party, grabs a beer,
and says, this is for chili, and leaves,
there will still be people at that party
who's like, who's that asshole?
But-
They're probably already doing that though.
To be fair, people love judging people.
Absolutely, but would the same be true
if I walked in shirtless with a cape on
and grabbed a beer and yelled like, this is for chili?
And then laugh, people would be like,
who the fuck was that guy?
Well, grab that and a lamp yelling this is for chili.
These are both going in, baby.
This one's for me.
I'm trying some stuff.
It's been a weird year.
This one's for chili and this one's for dad.
Let's go.
Wait, which one was which in that example?
I'm gonna eat this fucking lamp.
Woo!
You can just do what I do
and just run in, just like, oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
And then do it while you're still doing that.
Nobody's gonna stop and question you.
They'll be like, it seemed like an emergency.
Especially if you say like, quick, where's the beer?
I have a beer emergency.
How about another question?
Please.
My sister is getting her nipples tattooed.
You're starting Chicago Bulls.
She has many tattoos already.
And I like to be supportive and encouraging
when she gets new ones.
How do I appropriately compliment her new nipple tats
without being weird?
I already follow her tattoo artists on Instagram.
So I know I'll be seeing at least some
slightly censored version of the artwork.
It should be a good regular day for you, I bet.
That's from Let's Nip It in the Bud.
That's fun.
Well, I thought, so when I picked this question,
I thought we could do a little scene work
because we are- Oh, good.
We're siblings and we all have tattoos and nipples.
And we're famously good at doing characters.
And I thought maybe we could do this like, you know,
and you can pick either one of your brothers
to compliment their nipples if you want to.
And like, just pretend-
Well, the tattoo that has been recently applied-
I mean, yes, obviously, it goes hand in hand.
Yeah, I guess.
It's never happened before in my life.
Oh, really?
Because our friend Barbara has a ham tattooed
on his nipple where the nipple is-
I've seen his ham nipple and it's exquisite.
But I don't think I've ever said word one
about the fact that either of you even have nipples.
Hey, can I say, I've noticed that?
And it's actually weird that you've gone this long
without acknowledging them.
It has been.
Hey guys, you have four nipples between the two of you.
But we won't say between who, you know what?
All right, now, Justin, say something about Griffin's nipples.
I'm remaining completely motionless
in the hopes that my brothers will forget I am here.
Perhaps the podcast will proceed without me
and move on to a different segment
in which I am more comfortable participating.
You guys.
Hoo, guys.
Where to start making jokes about your nipples.
That's our job, baby.
Ah, boy, I love these.
These guys, if you knew them like I knew them.
Woo, these nipples.
You gotta be proud of that.
What's your favorite part?
Oh, don't make him choose.
Gosh, where they look.
This just really shows that you're a Star Wars fan.
When you go to that length for a nipple tattoo.
It's actually a Stewie Griffin in a Darth Vader helmet.
Did you catch that?
I got that, yeah.
How did you integrate the nipple into that exactly?
It's his left and right eyes.
That is a big Stewie Griffin.
That's a real big.
It's a life-size.
That's why I had to go.
Can I be honest?
I said originally I just wanted a Darth Vader,
but because of sort of the wingspan,
it looked a little more sort of.
And a lot of it was just following
the natural contours of his body.
Right, yeah.
And it kind of actually looks
like a very tired, dark Stewie Griffin.
It was free-handed with a lot of it.
Travis actually did it.
I did it, it's so cool.
It was my first one and I really appreciate
the trust you put in me for my first tattoo.
It took a long time.
Yeah, it looks like it took a long time.
It was a labor of love.
It was like that.
I got that vibe.
Yeah, for sure.
So what do you think of my handiwork?
Why is it still me, do you think?
Why am I still the-
Why tattooed?
Griffin got the tattoo.
Yeah, why is it still me?
It feels like other people should have a turn.
Everyone is sort of feeling bad for-
Hey Griffin, what do you think about
what Justin thinks about your nipple tattoo?
Hurts my feelings a lot.
Justin, do you want to address that?
I think it's important to remember
that none of this happened.
You remember the part where he thought
it was just Darth Vader and not Stewie Griffin?
I did catch that.
We were supposed to have fun.
And then he asked how you integrated it
as if he couldn't see Stewie's eyes.
I was enjoying it at first.
The show, not this bit.
It sounds like you really hurt Griffin's feelings.
Is there anything you want to say?
Say it to me now.
I, you know, people grow.
Yeah, I actually heard that was going to be a problem
for the tattoo, the dimensions.
People change, one sec, one sec.
Let me, let me-
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Think about it.
Let me see them again.
I-
Great jokes, us from last week.
Hey, Griffin here.
And I'm here to tell you about our sponsors this week.
Like for instance, Brooklinen.
I don't know about y'all,
but the holidays done snuck up on me this year.
And I'm like, what am I going to gift everyone?
You know, a bunch of those sticky slime hands?
No, I did that last year, damn it.
Luckily there's Brooklinen,
which has a perfect presence for everyone on your list.
Brooklinen started with bedding.
You know this.
But now they offer all the essentials
to make every corner of your home next level comfy.
They got five-star sheets.
They got dreamy decor.
They got cozy loungewear.
They got a new line of slippers.
They have freaking candles, man.
Everything to turn your house into a cozy little cocoon.
That cozy loungewear is nothing to mess with.
When I slip mine on,
I feel like a luxurious little gentleman
on my way back from the spa that is in my basement.
That didn't make much sense,
but give the gift of comfort this holiday season
and order now to get items on time.
Go to Brooklinen.com and use promo code,
my brother, for $20 off with a minimum purchase of $100.
That's B-R-O-O-K-L-I-N-E-N.com
and enter code, my brother, for $20 off
with a minimum purchase of 100 bucks.
Brooklinen.com, promo code, my brother.
Squarespace was also kind enough to sponsor us this week.
Squarespace is the platform you use to make a website
that will beat every other website's ass
right into the ground.
They have the tools you need to showcase your work,
sell products and services of all kinds,
promote your physical or online business,
and more, and that's for you to fill in
with your filthy mind what that means.
They give you beautiful, customizable templates
created by world-class designers.
Everything's optimized for mobile right out of the box,
analytics that help you grow in real time.
They got free and secure hosting
and nothing to patch or upgrade ever.
Go to squarespace.com slash my brother for a free trial,
and when you're ready to launch,
use the offer code, my brother,
to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain.
And of course, I cannot forget about Bombas.
Bombas' mission is simple.
They make the most comfortable clothes ever,
and they match every item sold with an equal item donated.
So this holiday, when you gift Bombas to someone
on your list, you're also giving them to someone in need.
It's a give-give.
Bombas designed their socks, shirts, and underwear
to be the clothes you can't wait to put on every day.
Everything's soft and seamless and tagless
and feels good on the body parts that you have.
They're made from super soft materials like merino wool,
Pima cotton, and even cashmere,
which makes them the perfect cozy winter layers.
And they're also cozy gifts for everyone on your list
because they got these festive gift boxes
you don't even need to freaking wrap, man,
because you're already busy enough.
All you gotta do is give them.
So go to Bombas.com slash my brother
and get 20% off your first purchase.
That's B-O-M-B-A-S.com slash my brother
for 20% off Bombas.com slash my brother.
Gonna go quick with the announcements very fast.
We have a virtual Candle Nights special
coming up December 18th at 9 p.m. Eastern time.
You can get tickets at bit.ly slash Candle Nights 2021.
It's a virtual show.
It's lots of fun.
All the podcasts did segments for it.
We got lots of friends and family members
who did stuff for it and all the sales for that.
The tickets are $5 with an option to give more.
Go to Benefit Harmony House,
a wonderful organization in Huntington
that goes to support people experiencing homelessness.
We also have the Zone of Adventure and Balance series.
That's all up on the YouTube.com slash the McElroy family
and a bunch of new merch over at McElroymerch.com,
including the pin of the month, which is Steely Van,
sales for which benefit
the Asian Pacific Environmental Network.
There's a My Brother, My Brother,
and the Man Who Ruined My FYP sticker,
referencing Justin's incredible summoning
of the berries and cream.
There's a Zone of Adventure enamel pin.
There's so much stuff at McElroymerch.com.
Hey there, beautiful people.
I'm Trevelle Anderson.
And I'm Jared Hill.
We are the hosts of Fantai,
the show where we have complex and complicado conversations
about the gray areas in our lives,
the things that we really, really love sometimes,
but also have some problematic feelings about.
Yes, we get into it all.
You want to know our thoughts about Nicki Minaj
and all her foolishness?
We got you.
You want to know our thoughts about gentrification,
perhaps some positive question mark,
aspects of gentrification?
We get into that too.
Every single Thursday, you can check us out
at MaximumFun.org.
Listen, you know you want it, honey,
so come on and get it.
Period.
Here's another question.
Yeah, please.
The kid I tutor broke his hand
and wants me to paint his cast for him.
I'm not super artistically gifted,
but I don't want to let him down.
What could I paint on an eighth graders arm
to make him look cool,
but not super difficult to do?
That's from in way over her head in North Texas.
Why did, why did that kid ask you to paint?
Like why, what, maybe they only know one adult.
That's entirely possible.
That's sad, but fair.
Let's see.
I mean, this is a great question for us
because we definitely know what people of that generation
are super into and think is cool.
Eventually they're going to lose interest in Fortnite
and then I'll really be lost.
And that's it, yeah.
Wait, oh.
They seem to like pinatas and Minecraft.
Yeah.
Oh no, I'm hearing some no's.
Okay.
Well, put me in the casket, folks, legends.
I'm done.
Could you, instead of painting something
or doing a picture, do some lettering
to make it look like a Fortnite branded cast?
Oh, that's cool.
People like that brand that, is it Massive?
Is that it?
No, shit.
Supreme is definitely it.
A Supreme cast.
Pretty close though, I think we can all agree.
They practically rhyme, those two very similar words.
Oh, fuck, that was embarrassing.
I want to say something,
but I'm really trying to savor this for a second.
And then-
You used to be the young cool one.
Yeah, you were the young cool one.
Yeah, yeah.
We need a fourth one now.
We need another one who's young.
Dad, dad, what'd you, well, I mean, drugs.
Just write the word drugs on it real big.
You could write, ask me about drugs.
There you go.
Yeah, I know.
But that's a trick question,
because they'll be like, tell me about drugs.
And you'd be like, they're bad.
I have some literature for you.
You fell into my trap, yeah.
I keep them stuffed in my cask.
Sorry I broke your arm, love, John Cena.
That's good.
That's really not his style, though.
I don't want to talk about it again.
I feel like his lawyers might just now be losing interest.
I mean, maybe you could get, like,
maybe it's like, get it branded.
So it says like, hey, sorry about your arm,
but make sure to check out Matrix,
Reloaded, coming soon to H.E.O. Maxx.
That's not the name of the film.
Then what have I been waiting for?
Could you-
Draw a smaller cast.
All right, okay.
0.5% smaller.
So it's just kind of fuzzy at the edges.
I saw- That's dumb.
Did you guys see what they're doing with the Matrix?
What's the new Matrix?
Resurrections. Thank you.
Yeah, you're welcome.
So Paul Sabourin of Paul and Storm fame
and I went to go enjoy Ghostbusters Afterlife yesterday.
In a regular theater, Justin?
No, dipshit.
It was a 4DX experience.
Every time Slimer farted, my butt shook.
Now, Justin, I know for a fact-
Don't spoil the movie.
We talked about this.
Yeah, we talked about how we can't spoil the movie.
And whether some Slimers may or may not appear in the film-
And maybe you may or may not have lost a bet to Paul
regarding that fact.
I may have bet Paul a sum of money
that Slimer would be in the movie.
Without requiring Paul to match said bet.
Yeah.
So the best case scenario was
you left with the same amount of money you began
and got to see Slimer.
Yeah, exactly.
But the beginning of the movie,
they have these, they're like commercials for other movies.
And they did one for-
You've seen this, okay.
They had one for Matrix Resurrections.
Erections, yeah.
And before that-
You just said erections.
Thanks, Trev.
I actually think I said erections,
which is now the only way I'm gonna say that word.
Not that I say it a lot.
Erectos.
That gave me erection.
Hello, hello, what's all this then?
This is one of those erections I've heard about.
There you go.
So-
Apples and pears.
We were watching the commercial for the movie,
but before it,
it was, there was an ad that's like,
Denny's has entered the matrix.
And it's like, Denny's has glitch meals.
Featuring your favorite Matrix characters.
And it's like, I guess Matrix isn't cool anymore.
Cause that made me feel pretty old.
Cause I'm kind of excited about our new Matrix,
but if the only brand partner they had on board was Denny's
for this new Matrix flick, for their glitch meals.
I like that their branding was Uh-Oh Meals.
We made you glitch meals.
There's a glitch in the Matrix.
There's no way we'd give you this much bacon.
Is that pancake a square?
Must be a glitch meal.
And then it's cats.
There's black cats in it.
In the, in the commercial?
Or in the pancakes.
It's in the pancakes.
They're shaped like black cats.
And it's like, whoa, I know Kung Fu.
These Matrix jokes aren't landing.
One, not jokes.
Two, I feel like now that it's tied to Denny's,
maybe the shine is kind of off the proverbial apple
a little bit on Matrix.
Maybe Matrix isn't gonna,
against my box office prediction is,
Matrix is not gonna do as well as some people might hope.
Coming soon to HBO Max.
Check it out.
God, this is good shit.
Antlers.
It's like we never missed a day.
Antlers are super cool.
This is a statement of fact.
I would love to start incorporating different antlers
into my outfit rotation.
Problem is, you could guess for a thousand years.
And you would not guess the proper.
You could think the problem is clotheslines.
Problem is leaves blowing in the wind.
Problem is animals need them.
No, problem is I take-
Confused hunters.
Confused city hunters.
Problem, there's deer near my house
because I live in West Virginia on a hill.
And every, literally like every West Virginia guy
of a certain inclination and age,
when he sees them, he's like,
man, I'd love to come back up here with my bow.
And I usually have to ask him like,
do you mean to kill deer at my house?
I'd rather you not.
Thank you.
Also, they're not just carrying their bow with them.
Come on.
Come on, it's in the trunk.
Problem is I take public transit.
I told you.
Anything I wear is at risk of becoming an invitation
for fellow passengers to strike up a conversation with me.
Some risk higher than others.
Yeah, in this case, I would say
it would be their legal rights.
Even if it's just to say, excuse me, are those antlers?
Is there any way I can wear some dope antlers
that doesn't include strangers
butting into my podcast time?
That's from not as horny as I'd like to be.
I mean, no.
Yeah.
But that's not funny.
If someone says like, hey, what's up with those antlers?
You could just read.
You go, what?
What?
Not again!
Just pull the bus brake cord thing
that I don't know if it does.
It's been a while since I've been on a bus,
but I don't think it brings the bus to a crashing halt.
No, if anything, it just kind of-
No, it is.
Every passenger has the right to stop the bus
wherever they want to.
That would add to the bit though.
If you're like, what?
No!
Why isn't this working?
Not again!
I mean, you could have some small tasteful antlers
that maybe they don't notice.
Some fashion antlers.
Well, I just mean perhaps under a hat
and then someone comes on the bus
and you tip your hat to them.
Just for a brief wink of a moment,
they think, excuse me, are those antlers?
No, it must've been my imagination.
And now you've given them a story, my lads.
Yeah.
Oh, you're not gonna believe this story I have for you.
The wildest thing happening today.
I met Mr. Tumnus, I think.
At first I was like, why does that person have
like a wild Dr. Seuss Jamiroquai hat on?
And I was like at first,
like maybe they have antlers under there.
He called himself Mr. Tumbus.
And I thought that was a little on the nose.
I guess like why, if you want to keep it incognito,
there are many accessories that are not antlers
that I would recommend.
Like a flower or a hat.
Those are just two off the top of my head.
I bet I can list as many others given the opportunity.
Give it a shot.
Hot shot.
Regular shirt.
Okay, I wouldn't call a regular shirt an accessory.
It's on your ear, it's wrapped around your arm.
Like a, you know, like a.
That's not a regular shirt then.
It's a regular shirt that you've wrapped around your arm
like Bruce Springsteen.
No, I would say that that inherently makes it irregular.
Regular shirt, weird place.
Name some different places you can put shirts
where people will be like, I don't think so.
Could you, when they say, hey, what's up with those antlers?
You just look up at them and go.
And I'm going to say after that awesome joke
that I don't know what sound a deer makes.
It's also a good way to guarantee no one tries to talk to
you for the rest of the trip.
Yeah, unless they're like a secret crypto zoologist.
They're like, oh shit, actually, all right.
May I sidle on up next?
I never thought I'd meet a goat boy here on my own bus.
Especially one with deer antlers.
What a bold choice.
Traditionally goats have what we like to call horns.
You can wear a shirt that says,
ask me about my pocket watch.
And then when they ask you, you be like,
I don't know, watch.
What are you talking about?
They'll be so confused.
They're like, I was going to ask that guy
about his antlers, but nevermind.
He seems like a bit of a pill.
I'd hate for this to be another pocket watch situation.
Our show is funny and good and everyone's lucky to be here.
Okay.
So weird regular thing.
So a regular thing you're doing.
Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
Folks, it's a haunt.
This just came across.
Travis, thank you for seeing that.
This just came across my desk.
It's a haunted doll watch.
Sorry.
Honestly, guys, I'm as surprised as you are.
Haunted doll, Khloe Kardashian lookalike.
Wait, sorry, wait, what?
What?
Shh, shh.
Haunted doll, Khloe Kardashian lookalike, succubus entity,
sexual spirit, nympho, nymphomania.
Huh?
Just what it says on the eBay list.
And guys, I don't know what to tell you.
Haunted doll, Khloe Kardashian lookalike, succubus entity,
sexual spirit, nympho, nymphomania.
This doll resembles Khloe Kardashian
and is haunted by the spirit of Khloe, as she calls herself.
What are the odds?
How convenient.
Khloe was a huge fan of reality TV star and spent-
Huge fun?
I'm just reading the listing.
Was a huge fan of reality TV star
and spent thousands on cosmetic procedures to look like her.
You heard it.
Huge fan of reality TV star, period.
And spent-
Was the cosmetic work before or after the dollining?
If I could just read the next sentence-
That's dumb, Griffin,
because there's no way it costs thousands of dollars
to paint a doll.
I just want to say that she died
due to complications arising from plastic surgery.
Yeah.
Oh.
But not really, because it's fake.
Travis.
Her looks helped her become
a successful high-end escort in Las Vegas.
Khloe says it took a long time
to find the right vessel,
but she's happy with her choice
and finally feeling like her true self, a doll.
I guess.
She loves to be the center of attention.
When you give her all of your attention,
she will shower you with affection.
Is that good?
It isn't hard to get along with this spirit.
All she asks is that you are real with her.
Hey, Tony, cut the shit, okay?
Hey, hey.
It's me.
It's Khloe, man.
Be honest.
Oh, when you get her,
don't forget to give her a gift of something girly,
maybe something to do with fashion and beauty.
Doll is 16 inches tall, comes with a stand, smoke-free.
Smoke-free?
Oh, okay.
The household where the doll came from was smoke-free.
You're going to.
As I'm required by eBay's policy on the paranormal
to indicate that eBay forbids the sale of intangible items
in this listing is only for a tangible doll
with no promises for the attached.
Wait, why?
Why is this shot included?
Shh, shh.
So you can see the ass.
It's for entertainment purposes only.
But no, wait, friends.
I don't just have one doll for you.
I have two dolls for you.
I have another doll.
But wait.
This next doll is named Kim.
Thank you, Khloe.
Thank you for your service.
Oh, fuck no.
Oh, that, that's B.
I'm Khloe's friend.
Haunted doll, spirit vessel, negative entity,
dark presence.
I go everywhere Khloe goes.
I'm Khloe B.
Do you want a kiss?
This is, this is B.
Khloe and I have to be home by 10.
She can't stay.
This is B.
B's vessel is pretty.
An unusual vintage small bisque doll in good condition.
Bisque?
In good, I don't,
I'm not going to decode the doll stuff, Travis.
In good condition for its age.
This doll's full of soup.
But with some signs of age and where to be expected.
B is a dark and confused spirit.
She came to me recently in spirit form only
and was causing much disruption to my electricity.
Hence the lighting.
She's a lost spirit.
And to help her, I found this vessel for her to take over
as these do help spirits,
which cannot pass to the other realm,
to find some form of comfort or grounding.
Yeah.
Why is this the doll you put me in?
I'm sure that spirit is stoked.
I said no pictures.
We have communicated with B via Ouija and dowsing rods.
She was a farmer's wife.
You've been doing what?
She was a farmer's wife and advises that she died of quote,
poison.
Travis, can you confirm there is,
there are quotes on the word poison?
Correct.
When she was 43.
That does sound like the poster is like,
she's obviously lying.
Whilst we have not yet got to the bottom
of how she ingested poison,
we know her death was very unpleasant.
Yay.
Hey, how'd you die B?
Poison.
How?
No.
She says that she is buried quote, in the field.
And that she cannot sleep.
There's much work to be done with B
and many things to be discovered.
We'd like to find her new keeper,
someone who can work with her to find out her story.
She will disrupt electricity
by way of interfering with the picture on the TV.
House spirits love to do this.
That's a different doll.
And bulbs may go in usually quickly in succession,
which we all know if you've been watching.
She has eyes that will follow you around the room
and at times her presence can be quite overwhelming
and chilling.
Enhance.
Why do I see a reflection of myself asleep in her eyes?
Anyway, it says this has all been lies
and it makes him say it's a lie.
How much?
Paul, can you pull up the listing?
I don't have the, I don't know where it's at right now.
It's great.
It just jumped up significantly.
I would wager in the last five minutes.
Great, great British pounds.
Wait, raise your hand if you bit on this dog.
Oh my God, okay.
There are a couple.
Justin posted this listing.
I should, that would be a good grift.
Yeah, right?
I don't know where we're going.
And then they were arrested
on the weirdest insider trading charges ever.
She can be quite rude at times,
sometimes not talk or communicate at all
or just swear.
So she won't talk for you a few days
and then from your weird doll closet,
you'll just hear, shit, bastard.
I'm in the fucking field.
I'm not going to tell you how I was poisoned.
Get off my case.
That's my business.
Refresh it, refresh it, Justin.
We have to get it somebody big.
I can't refresh, I'm not controlling it.
Yay!
It's 69, folks, we did it.
Boy, that was a very great doll.
Throughout the pandemic,
I've really been trying to work on my physical fitness.
I'm also an avid golfer.
My fiance said she wanted me to take thirst pics
out on the golf course.
Fellas, how do I take sexy pictures on a golf course?
You've come to the right place.
Put your balls in the hole.
That, I'm going to,
there are like four different angles
on why that was a bad joke.
Which one will you be exploring first, Griffin?
Both the metaphor of that image.
First of all, okay,
if you put your balls in the cup hole,
the hole that you try to get the golf ball in,
it would be hard to see, I think, what you're doing.
Well, it's a look on your face that sells it.
They would just be like,
why is he laying down on the golf course?
But you would have a look on your face.
It's like, what, me worry?
Right.
I'm a bad little boy.
I'm a stinker kind of face.
Yeah, I'm a stinker.
But I also don't know that-
That's a thirst trap, right?
Yeah.
I also don't know if it's like,
even if it was very literal,
especially sexy to say,
I'm going to put my balls in the hole.
Oh my, promise?
You can do the thirst trap and then the sand trap.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Those are two words that sound alike.
So I said, I don't really have a follow up.
I just wanted to say that.
Could you lift a golf-
Can you guys do something?
Can you lift a golf cart over your fucking head?
Yeah.
That's the end of my joke.
Now I'm still going with balls in the hole.
All right.
Could you do a hole in one in a picture?
Is there such a thing as a thirst gif?
Yeah.
Maybe just like a nice,
like if you're playing at like sunset,
just a nice picture you smiling.
Maybe like a knowing smile.
Hey, I got a story to tell you when I get home.
I just got my balls out of the hole.
I want to give credit-
Where are my balls then?
I'll never tell.
I'm being forcibly removed from the golf course.
Can you guess why?
That's right, I've done it again.
We have to move cities.
I want to give-
I need you to take me to the emergency room
because I put the balls in the hole,
but someone played through.
I want to give quick credit to this question asker
because they must have thought for so long
before landing on throughout the pandemic,
I've really been trying to work on my physical fitness.
Do you know how many times there was a little like,
I'm fucking cut.
I look fucking good and everybody loves it.
Look at these fucking abs.
Fucking sexy and swollen, everybody loves it.
Help me, sad brothers.
Help me, doe siblings.
What can I do?
They actually wrote here,
and don't say put your balls in the hole.
It's like, don't tell us how to do our job.
Right.
Maybe you could just like pretend to hump the windmill.
That's fun.
Yeah, cause it's definitely a mini golf course.
Wait, there are other ones?
Yeah, they make these boring ass golf courses
where you have to hit the ball wicked hard
before you get to the fun stuff.
Major golf courses.
Major golf, yes.
Macro golf.
This is actually very awkward,
but can I run to the restroom real quick?
You guys got this?
Thank you.
Okay, I mean, there's another question.
Hey, Paul, could I have another beer?
Thank you, audience, for confirming that I can.
Hey, give it up for Paul.
And Paul, can you check on Justin?
He's been in the bathroom for a really long time
and I'm worried about him.
Can we say a big thanks to the Sheridan Grand Seattle?
A beautiful hotel that I love.
I've stayed here for a really long time.
I've stayed here a few times
and I hold it so near and dear in my heart
because it's the only hotel I ever stayed in
that's fucking across the street from a Cheesecake Factory.
Also, very exciting.
Let's give a big cheer for Rachel, our editor.
Yeah.
This is the first time that Rachel has been here
to actually help run the show
so we don't have to worry about it.
And it's huge.
Thank you, Rachel.
And to Amanda and Danielle
and to everybody who's helped us do this show this evening.
And my wife, Rachel.
And my wife, Teresa.
And our kids and our dad and Paul Soborin.
I don't think Justin's ever coming back.
I think that's entirely possible.
Oh, God.
Justin, I mean, Richard.
Richard, no, Richard.
Hi, everybody.
It's a good thing Richard isn't sharing a room
with anyone this week.
Yeah, Richard's flying solo.
Wow, some people smelled it even there
and they wave it away.
They wave a smell away.
It's like a fucking Gallagher show in here.
Oh, my God, I can taste it.
Through the mask.
I'm right next to Richard.
Hey, guys, it's so cool to be here.
They're already starting with the jokes, these cut-ups.
But it's like...
Hey, Richard, was there a point halfway
through spraying yourself 19 times
that you thought, this is too much?
No, there was a point where I thought, this is not enough.
I need 20 more sprays,
but I'm running out of music.
Yeah, so it's so cool to be here with you guys.
You made my beard taste like it, Richard.
I'd like to talk.
When I heard you guys were doing a live show,
I was like, yes.
I got to get there because I love comics.
Yeah.
You do?
Yeah, I'm like a total, total nerd about this stuff, man.
I love it.
Who's your favorite superhero?
Don't make me choose.
You can say, like, five or six.
Just anyone, yeah.
Red...
Villain?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You guys have him over here?
Your favorite superhero is Red Villain.
Red Falcon.
Falcon.
I misspoke, yeah.
Red Falcon.
I actually don't know if that's the one.
Okay, these guys know they're geeks and nerds.
They love it.
So what I want to do, right, because it's not winter yet,
normally I'm only allowed to come once a season,
which is like, I hope you don't like ratings, you know?
Yeah, man.
I wanted to talk about, like, some superhero fragrances.
Because I don't know if you know this, it's, like, not a joke,
but there's, like, there's a lot of them.
It's, like, a weird number.
If you Google later, not now, but these are, like, all real.
And I love them.
And they've been really good for me.
Fucking compliment machines, man.
Whoa, hey, Richard.
You get out there.
You spray them, people are like, yes.
Here's the first one I got.
I wanted to try on you guys.
No.
Try on us?
Yeah, it's just, like, yeah, this one is...
I do like that it came out of a capsule.
I do actually like that.
That's cool, right?
It's like a gamma rays.
Um...
You're fucking great, Richard.
This first one is for, this first one is Spider-Man.
Sorry?
This first one is Spider-Man.
Uh, this is, it says here, the web king is back
with his great original smell.
Notes of Vetiver Berry.
Can I see it?
The web king?
The web king is back.
Can I read where it says that?
The web king is back with his original smell.
The nose on this.
Can I read where it says that, Richard?
Do you guys know the nose on this one?
Is it Spider-Web?
Spider-Web?
No, it's, the nose, the Korean.
No, you're thinking of notes.
Right.
The nose, like that person who made the smell.
Oh, it's Andrew Garfield.
No, correct.
Wait.
Mixed message.
Grib?
Gribbert?
Gribbert!
Yeah, sorry, sorry.
I was, I just, I love.
The nose on Spider-Man.
Everyone knows, they all know it.
Don't get, don't give it to them.
Oh, yeah.
Hugo.
It's Spider-Man.
He did the scent himself.
I do want to take a close look at that.
Through the mask, he did it.
It's notes, I'll give, I'll do like one small smell.
No!
Because you guys know, all right,
we're going to pass on that.
But this one's Spider-Man, it's like notes of vetiver
and some wood and oak and Spider-Man's the nose
and he loves it and his wife Mary Jane loves it too.
They all love it.
Does it smell like Spider-Man?
I have to smell it.
Can I hold it in my hand?
Yeah, you can just smell it.
Give me quick, just quick thoughts.
Give me quick thoughts on that.
It's just that there's no branding on it.
Sample bottles.
Your TSA, if I can say this here,
I don't know if we're a mixed company,
your TSA won't even let me bring my seven ounce bottle
of Spider-Man cologne.
They take it out, they say, this is too big.
I say, I'll check it.
But I think that doesn't even spot back in my pocket.
They get very like, you know how this does.
Give it a quick smell.
No, it's just a Spider-Man cologne.
That's not bad.
Yeah, it's like got notes of vetiver and almonds.
Did you say notes of venom?
Next up is Superman.
Clark Kent is back, it says here.
Clark Kent is back.
Where was he?
Clark Kent is back from the dead
with a new smell that'll wake up the sexual animal in you.
What?
Why does it say this?
Known sexual animal, Clark Kent.
Clark Kent is back with a new-
Known boner machine, Clark Kent.
Do you guys know the nose on this one?
Is it Clark Kent?
No, it's Paul Lagartier.
You guys don't know this?
Paul Lagartier is the nose on this.
He put in notes of, let me hit, like-
Yeah, spray it right up your nose.
Oh, no!
No, he didn't!
Fresh.
Oh, God, it's bleeding.
It's like, how you doing over there, Richard?
It's like, it's challenging.
It is challenging.
Right?
It's like-
When you do it like that, Richard,
it's like everyone's wearing Superman cologne.
Yeah, where it's like-
It's kind of like-
How did he go?
Well, just like he wanted to.
It's got almond in it.
You can tell-
It sounds like melting brain.
There's some blood.
I want to move on to Iron Man.
Wait, just a kind of related question.
When Superman did get killed by Doomsday,
I think, in that comic series,
was there a following comic where people were like,
where's fucking Clark?
Has anyone seen Clark lately?
No, they covered it
because Supergirl pretended to be Clark Kent.
Okay, ask and answer.
Thank you, Travis.
Can I tell you about Iron Man?
I'd love to hear about Iron Man.
This is a robot that everyone's wild about.
He's a world's-
It says on here,
the world's richest robot is back.
Why is he always back?
It says the world's richest robot is back.
Yeah.
And everyone's favorite,
the nose on this is also Jean-Paul Leclete-Radier.
I swear to Christ,
you put some new syllables in there.
You put a steak on there, Richard.
This one is like-
I mean, like I smell this and I think money.
I think robots.
I think rich robots.
I think Iron Man smells-
Do you want to take a little whiff, Gribber?
Do you also, yeah.
Do you also think it smells like the last cologne
that you just sprayed up your nose?
Just get like a little-
Do you smell the spice though?
It's like a spicy Iron Man sort of rich robot, right?
It does kind of smell like motor oil, yeah.
They love this at my church, man.
They go crazy for it.
Oh yeah, how was your walk?
Stronger than everybody.
I noticed your necklace there.
Is that a religious symbol?
I did it for the geeks.
Like they love this.
It's never ending story.
What does it say on the back?
Right, this free with purchase.
Now my man Clint bought this for me on the show floor.
Thanks, Clint.
Well, you said like I had to leave my crucifix at home.
Clint, will you grab me a crucifix?
And what your man Clint came back with was-
Was the orange from Little Shop of Monsters.
What was it?
Never ending story.
Did you smell that, Gribber?
Did you spray it on you?
Did he, I didn't see him, guys.
Did he spray it on him?
Did he love it?
I did.
What was his reaction?
Do the face.
It was very non-plus.
Why is everyone wearing a mask?
What is happening?
You can't smell any fragrances.
I'm sorry.
Richard, sorry, come back.
What?
Still?
Yes.
Oh God.
That's so sad.
Anyway, there's lots of other great ones.
I got Black Manta.
Black Manta?
They made a Black Manta one?
Green Lantern.
But anyway, that's all the fragrances I got.
I feel like the three of us can just bring it home.
Let's like wrap it up.
Yeah, for sure.
Justin's dead white, man.
We don't even need him around.
Yeah, man.
You did drop one on the floor and if it broke open,
we would really never be invited back
to Washington State.
Wait, I have one.
No, no, no, I know that this one,
it wasn't, because you know what superhero this is?
What?
Unbreakable.
Richard, I know you're the guest here,
but do you want to take a swing at thanking the audience
and getting us some more?
Yeah, man, thanks you.
Thanks ABBA for the great music.
No, well, Richard.
Thanks to, I haven't listened for a bit, is it?
Yeah, no, no, no, I get that.
No, it's actually Montaigne now.
Oh, thanks Montaigne.
This is our first live show with that
as our righteous theme song.
Let me think.
Okay, me and Travis thanked most people
while Justin was being pretty killed.
Did we thank our dad?
Yes.
Thank you, Clint McElroy.
Sorry, I heard you goofing on John Cena.
You want to say anything about him,
like sorry or anything like that?
No, not until he says it first.
Fair, that's cool, yeah.
Can you, Justin asked me through a mirror
we use to talk to each other.
Awesome, fuck yeah.
We have a mirror we use to talk to each other?
Definitely.
Everybody knows this, they all know this.
I've actually heard, Richard, last time we met,
you had like a really small knapsack
that I could hear Justin screaming from.
Was that that?
Yeah, it's a huge mirror I keep with a small knapsack
and it's got Justin, we talk to each other
and it's just, that's all.
And then he just told me to ask you,
he said that you had, he'd sent a whip ass
final Yahoo for us.
Oh yeah.
From the final Yahoo answer, which is weird to me
because it doesn't work anymore
when I try to go to the site.
Yeah.
It's still in my RS.
Do you have your login?
What?
Have you like updated your password for Yahoo?
I, no, I do.
That might be it.
I do through a VPN.
Oh, good call.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've just actually left the tab open
for a while now.
Yeah, I connect through a VPN at Paul Reiser's house.
Cause I don't want my activity to be monitored.
So I hack into Paul Reiser's internet
and then I call my sites through there.
Wait, so you do it at Paul Reiser's house?
No, I hack into Paul Reiser's house.
And let me tell you, he is mad about that.
Griffin, I'm done with my Paul Reiser story.
You can finish show.
Oh, thanks to Jesus Christ, obviously.
Without his love, none of us would be here.
Huge big ups to JC.
My walk with him has never been stronger.
Please keep me in your heart and prayer.
Griffin, bring us home.
This final Yahoo was sent in by R.L. Stein.
Thank you, Dr. Goosebumps.
Please, that's just what they call him on the court.
It's from Yahoo Answers.
There's nothing I can say that would be as funny
as anything Richard Stank has done
since he crossed the threshold of this thing.
Just being myself, just read the one
that you have on the screen.
Sure, this one was, it's a Yahoo Answers user.
Don Sheena, Don, Don Sheena asks,
do you think there was a point where a manager
or someone said, should it be Gina?
Cause of the jeans.
Hurry, the people gotta go home.
Sure, Don Sheena asks.
My dad's the light guy, he says he wants to go home.
Whoa.
Hey, thank you, man.
Thank you for the ride over here, dad.
Love you, I'll see you soon.
Don Sheena, God, we've gone so long.
Don Sheena asks.
Yes.
Don Sheena asks, does, does, fuck.
Don Sheena asks.
Just read it.
Don Sheena, Don, Don Sheena asks, does,
does, does muscle milk, does muscle milk make,
does muscle milk make an invisibility potion flavor?
My name's Richard Stank.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been My Brother, My Brother,
make it your dad's square on the lips.
It's better with you.
My life, it's better, it's better with you.
Cause it's true, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, it's better with you.