The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it
Also, this show isn't for kids which I mentioned only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening
What's up, you cool, baby?
It's better it's better
Better it's better
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother and me and my show for the modren era
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. Hello booze and ghouls and
Non-boonary folk. I'm your middle this brother Travis were wolf wolf
McElroy, it's ah, it's ah, it's early August
No, let Griffin do his so I can ignore yours and this is Griffin and this and this is Griffin McElroy
There's a chill in the air
The leaves are turning
I had a silly dentist thing happen
From orange and brown and yellow
I can't I can't
There's a chill things are getting spooky
We're all already unhinged for time you cannot do this
I went to the home goods store to buy a picture frame and they had Halloween pillows for sale
Okay, so that's it that means that's the starting gun
The season has begun
They had ceramic pumpkins
It's it's actually gang it is July the 29th as we're required
Yeah, spooky season
When the ghosts come out to play
The ghosts won't be out Traff for three more entire earth months
The ghosts are on the beach
My local home goods had Salvatore Ferragamo Uomo fragrance on clearance
That don't make it fall. That's obviously an autumnal scent
Right
Don't make it fall
It's spooky season
It's absolutely not
I got one brother who is who's turned into a vampire skeleton only bones
And then I have and then I have another brother that's trying to backdoor Richard Stink in here in this in this Halloween
No, no, here's here's what you're fucking with
Yeah, this is why this is why
This is what's up Travis
This is why I sampled it. This is why I sampled it
Richard Stink comes out four times a year at the beginning of every season
And then my brother is telling me that it is the spooky season upon us
Then Richard Stink comes out
Now if he's gonna obey the Gregorian calendar of our ancestors, maybe you've heard of it, you know
That's up to Richard to decide
That same fucking calendar by the way that says that September 13th is summer
It's not
It's not, you joke, just like July 29th is spooky season
This is lose, lose, lose, lose, lose for me
Have you decided on your Halloween costumes?
Um
What will you be doing to celebrate Samhain?
I think we've let enough of this go I need to say something
Don't let a black cat cross your path
Fire skeleton only bones Travis can you just hold on for a second so Justin can say a thing
It's just like really important
Okay
I wanted to say if you all were listening to episode 566 of My Brother My Brother and Me
You may have heard me talk about some new Kraft Dinner flavor boosts
Oh my god
And I may have said something ill-advised at the end of that episode that I didn't really think through
Briefly this is what I said
If you're in Canada I need you to get as much that fucking Jesus you can just ruin my box
Ruin my box with KD okay? Hey ruin my box with KD
Get all that weird KD and ruin my box
So that's what I said and I kinda forgot I said it until this week
When I went to the post office and my friendly post office people were
I'll go ahead and say it not thrilled to see
How flavor blasted was your box?
They saw me and one of the dudes walked out of the room as soon as I walked in
And I walked to the other dude and I was like box 54 please and he's like oh yeah he's going to go get it
On site they know you on site
They had one of those don't let this shoplifter in photos on the wall
But it was like give this man his cheesy box as quick as you can
Get this cheese out of here
And these dudes start piling up boxes and all of them have that distinctive Canada post thing
And I will admit I did have a fleeting moment where I was like whoa a lot of fan mail this week
Guess the J man's back
It requires a certain amount of effort to send you macaroni and cheese flavor addition mix ins
That belies an amount of fandom that is staggering
I also imagine Justin that there were a lot of tariffs on the postage was probably high
Yeah so let's talk about that aspect of it for a second okay
Canada I'm just going to talk to Canada for a second Canada
Should we leave?
No no you guys can be here and you can listen because I want there to be a witness
Oh we're like ambassadors we have diplomatic community
Exactly
I asked you to send me all the weird KD and I was not specific enough I am sorry about that
You all sent me approximately by my count 83 different packets of flavor boosting
Are you kidding me?
83 different packets of flavor boosting
But Canada you sent me 109 boxes of mac and cheese
Now listen it's the same mac and cheese
Well well well hold on
KD and mac and cheese are the same product
But you don't know the consistency 100% I do
How do you know?
Nobody knows it but actually Travis I would say I Justin McElroy at this point in my life
Am uniquely positioned to say that these are the same products
But molecularly I'm saying that what you've got is Canadian cheese dust versus American cheese dust
You can't tell me it's the same cheese dust at a molecular level
You are an infant tickling yourself with a razor
You are speaking to the world's preeminent cheese dust scholar
You don't think I've had cheese dust in my life?
Travis
You don't think I've flavor blasted some nudes?
What?
Travis
But I also have been shipped
What I'm saying is I've been shipped 109 boxes of Canadian mac and cheese
And I've eaten enough
It's the same
Travis
You've only had these for about a week Justin
How much have you consumed with your human form?
Travis
Here's the thing though
This is not going to waste
We are sending around 100 boxes of Kraft Dinner to Harmony House
Travis
They're going to think you're an extreme couponer
Well the people who are experiencing homelessness currently want to flavor blast
That is up to them
They will get some packets no doubt
So the food will not go to waste
I did make a couple of these to go ahead and sample them
Travis
I'm curious about
Is it the cotton candy?
Travis
It is the cotton candy
I bet it fucks
Travis
We've had some different reactions
I bet Charlie loves it
Travis
I bet Sydney wanted to vomit
Yeah
Travis
Loved it?
Yeah, but it's great
Travis
It works in the same way as
Don't think of it as cotton candy and cheese
Travis
Because neither of those things are present
It's a new flavor in your ear
Travis
It's actually like Danish
Think of it more like
Travis
The flavor of
The flavor of Papa's beard is not very pricey
Travis
Yeah, they call it Papa's beard
That's why they call it cotton candy
Travis
Because it's like God's beard
That idea
If you can wrap your brain around that idea
It's sort of like that
Travis
Or like a cheese and apple pie that I learned about from pushing daisies
The only one that I know that only John Joy didn't like it
Travis
The fifth member of your family is where the differing opinion came in
I'm sorry, I forgot about your son, John Joy
Grown adult man who I believe is older than you
Travis
John Joy is a fellow West Virginia podcaster
Host of Professor Theo's Mystery Lab
Travis
You're going to love these stories
But he's a hater of this great mac and cheese product
Travis
He took one bite and this is his entire reaction
No
Travis
That's his review
He can't go into it with an open mind
Travis
The ghost pepper is a threat
There's three other spicy
And spicy with mac and cheese is pretty good
Even the butter chicken had a nice amount of spice
Travis
That sounds good to me
The one that was rough was poutine
Travis
Really?
It tastes so much like gravy
Travis
I use the mac and cheese
You guys know about how to make
I call it der bad mac and cheese
But you guys know about this, right?
Travis
I can't say that I do
I'm going to tell you this, give me one second
Travis
Are you googling a macaroni and a Kraft dinner recipe?
It is not my recipe
It's God's recipe
Travis
It's God's conduit
It's not my recipe
Travis
So I need a second
Can I guess whose it is?
Is it Guy Fieri?
Travis
No, it's not Guy Fieri
When it's called dirtbag something, he has trashcan nachos
Travis
I call it dirtbag
This method is actually by a guy named Brian Floyd
Travis
Thank you Brian
We should point out that it took Justin about 7 minutes to find this
Travis
Once you learn this method, you never need to refer to it again
Listen
You dump into a saucepan
The mac
The cheese
A cup of water
Some butter
And then you just cook on medium till done
Travis
Why is that dirty?
Better, faster, more delicious
Travis
A little bit of al dente in there
Yep, you've been wasting your time with your 6 cups of water
You're straining
All of it is a waste of time
You dump it all in the pan at once and then you wait a few minutes and mac and cheese
Travis
That's a great method and I don't want to belittle Dr. Floyd's work
Well
Travis
When you call something dirtbag, I thought you were going to crush up some Doritos in there
Make it with Mountain Dew or some shit
We're from West Virginia
You can't say dirtbag
And I'm supposed to think it just means a little bit lazy or simple
Travis
That you put milk in it also
It's great
Travis
Do you think that you could just
Make some artisanal cotton candy
Where you actually go to the state fair, get some cotton candy
Put that bad boy right in there
Travis
Yeah, maybe
Except I didn't even ask
Is there a color element to the cotton candy mix?
Travis
Oh, bud
Are you kidding me?
Travis
Let me see what color maul is
It looks like Kirby's fucking
Travis
It's wild
Yeah, it looks like Kirby's balls
Travis
Anyway, as you certainly gather, this is an advice show
Where we take your questions and turn them out into wisdom
And here we go
An aspect of my job involves collecting groundwater samples
Which need to be kept on ice
I usually buy ice a few times a month
From gas stations, liquor stores, etc
At the end of each month
I submit an expense report
With receipts for the ice to collect my cash
The other week it was incredibly hot
But when I went to a nearby gas station to buy ice
I walked past the ice cream chest
And grabbed a Minion popsicle
Normally, I would buy personal items
Separately, but the line
Was long and I panicked
Is it acceptable for me to submit the receipt
With the Minion popsicle on it
Or am I out $2.49
Travis
Wait, that's from Minion popsicle debacle
If it had been like
Some kind of drink, any kind of drink
Travis A pack of lifesavers
If it had been anything
But, fucking, the auditor
Scanning your receipts
Sees Minion popsicle
In all bold
And you can't say I needed it
Travis You all got it twisted
Yeah, you can
How? If they question you on it
Travis And they will
Travis They were out of ice
I needed anything else frozen
Travis So to preserve these scientific
Samples
Travis You jammed, there was like one
Little bit of space
With no ice, and you had to just slide
A popsicle right in there, they can never
Prove otherwise
Travis But then they can trap you like, oh, well how did it taste
You'd be like, it was a Minion popsicle dude, it was delicious
And they'd be like, got you
Damn it Travis It tasted like banana
Honestly, ironically
Maybe on purpose, it tasted like banana
It was great
Maybe you could say, well here's the weird thing
They wouldn't sell me the ice
Unless I bought the popsicle
It was a
Here's what you're saying
Yeah, it was a buy ice
Get popsicle free thing, not according to this receipt
Those motherfuckers Travis They fucking got me
Travis This is
Hey, Joan, this is how they get you, right?
Am I right? Joan pounded
Because we're in this thing together
No one's calling the police today
Right Joan? Pound it
Hey Joan, can you pound it real quick?
None of us have to go to, we're not going to
Debtors prison
When you go to Joan to get reimbursed
Joan's gonna look at the receipt and be like, I don't know
And then you're gonna pull out a second
Minion popsicle and say, do you wanna get your beat
Wet Joan?
Joan, I got a taste for you
Hey Joan, we can make this work, you and me
We're in this together, Minion popsicles
As much as we want
I never ate that Minion popsicle
Oh yeah Joan?
And then you just dump the popsicle part in the trash
And throw the stick at her, prove it
I got a text message here Joan
That looks like you told me to buy the popsicle for you
What? That's from your dad
Yeah, that's what I call you Joan
How could you bring your dad into it Joan?
How could you do this?
You made my dad an accessory
To your embezzlement?
How could you Joan?
There's not a job
On this planet
And I'm including this job
If any
Self-respecting human being can call
What we do that
Where if things aren't
At least a little bit
Shitty enough for you to feel
Okay about stealing a popsicle
From the man
You know what I mean?
I love this work, working with YouTube boys
And I know we gotta balance those books
Because we're family, and you don't fuck around with that
But if I do have the opportunity to steal
A minion's popsicle from
Our bottom dime
I would do it
Even though I love this
If I find out
That you've been getting
Minion popsicles on our dime
I'm afraid of you, I'm sorry
I'm so sorry, so sorry Griffin
Juice, how's the Fredo flavor boost
For the KD dinner?
I haven't tried that one yet
Just because it doesn't exist
Charlie's obsessed
With watching this dude on YouTube
Whose whole thing is perfect popsicles
Have you seen this guy?
He just goes around buying up all the minion popsicles
And all the SpongeBob popsicles
And he's trying to find perfect ones that actually look like the packaging
So it is his
Maybe you could be like
It was a collab
You're trying to sell Joan on it
Like you wanted to get into TikTok
Oh here's what you say, Joan
There was a hot bird outside
And the bird was overheated
That bird was looking at me
I came back out and I had a little water bottle
And it went, no! Minion!
And I was like
What?
And I had to buy a minion popsicle, Joan
Give me cold
Give me minion, minion
You get the
I think you have to report this
Because the
Worst case scenario
Is no one notices
And then the next time you're at the store
You think, well maybe I love two minion popsicles
Slippery, sticky, slow
And then you think
Maybe I'd like
Three minion popsicles
Fast forward six months
You're getting eight minion popsicles
And you're throwing half of them away
You just want to feel
Who knows where this stops, ten?
No
Not until you're fully the grew
Of popsicles
No
A full blown mini ice cream?
Ugh
Come on, man
Come on, here's what you do
You throw yourself at the mercy of the court
You go to the highest boss
You can find
You fall on your knees, you tear your shirt
You cry, you pull your hair out
And you confess in as
Dramatic terms as you can
And you beg for forgiveness
And I guarantee you
The next eight times
They're not going to check your receipts
No way
You can put anything on there
They don't want you to apologize to them anymore
It was really uncomfortable
I think I'm becoming more
And more
Dead set on you just looking them in the eyes
And saying, it's different ice
Yeah
It's just different ice
And in many ways better ice, really
It's boutique ice
It's gross ass water I had to get from
The mud
Excuse me, cause I thought that I could
You said buy ice
And this is ice
Part of my job is going to a liquor store
I bought a minion popsicle
Are you going to judge me for the minion popsicle?
Do you know how much worse this could be?
I could have bought 18 bottles of
Boons Farm, and I bought a minion
A $2.40
Jeff Bezos flew to
Outer space and I bought a $2.49
Popsicle and you're going to get mad at
Me, Joan? What is this?
Unbelievable
Be honest about it
But don't be embarrassed
No, just be honest
But not chagrined
Oh yeah, a sick kid wanted it
That's another good one
Yeah, that's always a great one that feels good to do
And joke about it
Hey, can we approach the wizard humbly
And supplicate ourselves
Before his throne? Yeah, I do
I was hoping to get some courage
No
What about, can I interest you in some
Snow power?
How about hubris?
No, you already have that
Graham Roebuck sent this one in, thank you Graham
This one was
Just updated June 1st of this year
So it's like, you know, it's going to mention
Covid, probably
It's called How to Appear to Have Snow Power
Oh, hey!
Snow power is a form of magic
A character who lives in snow encased environments
Might have, such as Elsa from Frozen
Name one more!
Name another!
The Ice King from
Ice Man
Does Ice Man from the X-Men live in a
Magical snow encased environment?
Nobody is an omega level mutant
I would say that this is like more
It's like less impressive if you
Live in a snow environment
And you have snow powers
And to be fair, WikiWizard
Elsa didn't live in a snow encased environment
It was summer
When she used her snow powers to create
The eternal blizzard
Come on
So here's how to convince people that you
Have snow powers
I think everybody gets it
One, wear gloves that have
Faux snow on them, that's easy
Glitter, small cotton ball puffs
White rolls of yarn
That doesn't seem convincing though
It's not the only fucking thing you do, Travis
Give me a minute
You can get black gloves for a dollar with snow
Already on them from dollar stores
What? I didn't know that they did that
America's the best country in the world
This is the best, you can get everything
Wear all blue and white
Yeah, that's ice and snow colors
You can't do orange or red or whatever
Also, when you make it snow, wearing a long
Sash on your sleeves will give it a great effect
If the sashes have glitter, even better
Or a simple necklace
With a sophisticated charm
A snowflake with a simple white beads would be nice
Pretty sophisticated
I would say that
I don't know if that's a sophisticated...
Anyway, this is where it gets really hot
By which I mean cold
Showing your snow powers, part two
One, act apart
Try to make somebody curious enough to watch you
Not sure what that means
Who said that? Me
If you were walking
Around a park
With your kid
And you saw somebody
Stride forward, wearing
Blue and white, with black gloves
With glitter on them, and some
Flowing things, and they began to
Sway and swirl their arms
You'd stop
You'd look
These next two sentences are so good
First of all
It said, use white glitter or similar items
To make it seem like snow
It might seem odd, but you could always play Christmas music
To set the tone if you wish
Jingle bells, jingle bells
You just threw glitter
On my fucking
Taco bell, I was gonna eat this
I did snow on it
So these two sentences
If using real snow, this is best done during wintertime
To make it more believable
The snow would melt in summer, excellent
That's excellent stuff
This one's dope, because I don't know what the fuck it means
When you're at
Your secret place
Start to play around in the snow
With your bare hands, if you can bare it
And throw it in the air
Do this for a few times, then look at your hands
Smile and get ready to do your trick
Oh my fuck
It's gotta be wintertime, because if you try to do this in summer
People will be like, um, excuse me
It's the hot season
And that's snow
I don't think so
You're gonna embarrass yourself
But more importantly, you gotta be in your secret place
When you're practicing this
Imagine
These two sentences, that sentence about the secret place
Is referring only
And especially to
Superman and the fortress of solitude
Yes, exactly
Make the snow appear to, quote, come out of your hands
If you have very large sleeves
You can try this neat trick
Get two small fans and secretly put them
Down your sleeves, get some of the faux snow
And put it on top of the fans, turn on the fans
Secretly and open your hands wide so that it goes through your fingers
And appears to come out of your hands
But hey, if you can't get the fans
Don't worry, just stuff some of the fake snow
In your sleeves and twirl around with your sleeves
Down, causing the snow to slip out of your sleeves
But this is not recommended because you'll look like
You're dripping wet afterwards
Slip snow out of your sleeves in moderation
But practice this for a few times
Before the real deal
In a private place
In your secret place
Practice shoving
White cotton that looks like snow
Up your sleeves and then just
Because you're not getting two fans
Up your sleeves, that's fucking ridiculous
So you're gonna do the other way
Where you just let it kind of
Impotently
Jizz out of your
Of your arms to the floor
And people are like, did you just do snow power?
And you say, I don't
I don't know, don't ask me about it
I'm still practicing, I gotta go to my secret place
This is stupid, this is supposed to be my secret place
I don't even know why I chose this power
I could have done fire power and there's a lot of things
You can light on fire
React while you're making snow
Always look like you're enjoying yourself
Laugh a lot and twirl around
Now, alternatively though
You could scream in horror at your own power
That now you wield without
Any kind of responsibility or understanding
That is how I think
It would really work in real life
If I suddenly started shooting
Snow and ice out of my hands
I don't think I'd be like
I think I'd be like, oh no
Why is it conceit that it's the first time it's ever happened to you though?
If you're convincing anyone
You're convincing yourself
True, that's the first step
If you're pretending to hide your snow powers
Do the following, after you run out of snow
Toss the snow on the ground in the air
Then seem to notice the person
Start to look worried, run up to the person and beg
Please don't tell anyone
And you're done
Oh
You're not quite done though
Because step four is try this out on your friends
Before doing it at a fancy dress or cosplay event
I like that trap
What would someone
Have to do
To display ice or snow powers to you
To me?
That would make you believe that they actually had
Ice or snow powers and weren't just faking it
Because I worry
That if we found out magic was real
Or if magic was real in this world
We would all be so skeptical
That no level of
Something would allow us to
Believe it was real
I would demonstrate for you to believe
If the air
Around this
This sorcerer
This warlock
Let's call Elsa what she is, a warlock
A dark ice patron
And legal with the devil
It might be Satan
If the air around them
Became superheated
As they did this
Thus sort of fulfilling
The law of thermodynamics
Then I might buy into this shit
But if somebody just starts throwing snow around
I'll be like, oh, where did the
Heat go? You know what I mean?
Because I got like a scientist
Way of looking at things sometimes
I always actually like that about you
Yeah, I love that too, very analytical
Yeah, yeah, yeah
A mind of sciences mind
So good questions on this one, but I want to just
Drill down on this one. Can I just say the weird thing is
If somebody had the ability
To make snow, but it only dribbled
Impotently from their sleeves
But that was how the power worked and it was actually magic
I would never believe them
And I would feel terrible
They'd be like, look what I can do
I'm like, that's just fucking, you had some snow
Stuff up your sleeve, I'm like, no, you don't
Understand, this is just how
It works. I think some effort
Would actually make me believe it a bit more if the
Snow just impotently dribbled out of their
Sleeve and they were going like
And I'd be like, whoa, damn, you're working really hard
To make that snow. That's crazy
You look really dehydrated, are you okay?
Yeah, I mean that water's gotta come from
Somewhere. Okay, I want to drill down on this question
Okay. How do I
Make it look like I've got more snow power?
Oh boy
This is always the fear
Isn't it? I mean, this is the danger that you run
Do something else. What?
Oh man
The community answered, try to keep some with
You at all times and while the person isn't looking
Put more in your sleeves to make it look like you
Have unlimited power
27 people found that helpful
60 people found that not helpful
Just loudly announce, now look
At my snow pockets and just start
Pulling snow out of your pockets
This is some snow that I made earlier with
Magic
Snow problem for
Me
That's the crowd clapping
At that pun. Yeah, it was good
You know what I think? I think we've earned
A trip to the money zone. Already? Just for that
Yeah, just with that. Shit, hold on, before
Wait, I gotta step on the brakes for a second because there's
A warning at the bottom here. I've never seen a
Warning on a wikiHow article before
And this is important, I want to cover us
Legally by reciting this
Warning. Don't
Make it obvious that you're faking. Be sure
To use good acting skills
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
Now, this is the kind of wikiHow that irritates
Me because now I have to go read one about
Good acting. I know, damn it
That's what Joaquin Phoenix did
That's it, when he got pooped on by
His buddy. When he really
Became the snoker
That's okay, we can go to the money zone on that
Yeah, now I think
Yeah, why so serious?
We are sponsored in part
This week by Squarespace
Stand out with a beautiful website
From Squarespace. I'm gonna
Read it word for word, but I'm gonna deliver it
Like you're delivering it to a friend who
Like, the advice is so obvious
You're so mad that they haven't figured it out
Themselves. Squarespace
Can help you create a beautiful
Website to showcase your
Work or sell products
And services of all kinds
Dump him, promote
Your physical online business
Deborah, you don't need him anymore
What? Squarespace gives
You beautiful customizable templates
Created by world class designers
And you're too good for him
He doesn't appreciate you
Everything is optimized for mobile
Right out of the box
He's a dead beat
He hasn't worked in three years
Analytics that help you grow in real
Time. Free and
Secure hosting, now let's
Party, cause there's nothing to patch
Or upgrade ever
So go to squarespace.com slash
My brother for a free trial
And when you're ready to launch use the offer code
My brother to save 10%
Off your first purchase
Of a website or domain
Now let's go to Slippery Joe's for
Some shots and we're gonna
Rebound
Okay, um
That's word for word
That was all in the copy
And it makes me wonder if like somebody at
Squarespace is like
Going through something
Like an ordeal right now
And that's you know what
I'm glad we could be here for them
This is Stitch Fix
They send you a box full of clothes
And the clothes is gonna look good
And it's gonna fit good
Pants is one of the things they have in the box sometimes
Jacket
Shoes
Belt
I got a tie!
Yeah, fucking ties
And you don't need to go to the store to buy them
You try the tie on and they're like
That tie on your
Neck? And then you get fucking
Sad and you
Run out of the mall
And you get hit by a car
In the parking lot
All because you got made fun of
For the tie not fitting the size of your
Neck? No way, Stitch Fix is here
To fix that. Don't ever get hit by a
Truck in the mall parking lot again
Cause they hand select these clothes for you
By expert stylists based on your unique
Size
Got a unique
No one's ever been able to find the perfect fit
Size, style, and budget!
And you get to try on the pieces at home before you buy them
You keep your favorites and send back the rest
You say fly back little birds, you're not ready for me
And you pay a $20 styling fee for
Each box which gets credited towards
The pieces that you keep. There's no hidden fees
No subscription. It's
Easy peasy. Get started today at
StitchFix.com slash my brother
And you'll get 25% off when you
Keep everything in your fix
At StitchFix.com slash my brother for 25%
Off when you keep everything in your fix
At StitchFix.com slash my brother
My victory is that I'm one year cancer free
But my tiny victory
Is that I took all
Of the cushions off the couch
Pounded them out, put them back
And it looks so great
So if you're like us and you want to celebrate the
Tiny achievements of ordinary people
Listen to Tiny Victories
It's on every Monday on Maximum
Fun
I want to munch
Squad
Got a Michael Giacchino vibe here
And I'm taking it
Listen, this is the most important
Munch Squad that I've ever done
And I'm trying, I want to
You know how before Walter Cronkite
Like you remember when he
Was about to watch them open the moon
Door and he was thinking like
I gotta say fucking something
You know what I mean?
And he said like everybody shut up, everybody shut up
Watch this, watch this fucking thing
I also
Wonder like if he was wondering
If the moon guy was going to say something
That he didn't want to talk over
You know what I mean?
This is like that moment
Popeye's launches
Nuggets
Calls for cease fire
In the chicken wars
Oh my god
Let's listen before we comment on this
And get too deep into it
Let's just listen to the
This is what they're going with
Remember what happened when we launched the chicken sandwich
These clips of them
Selling it
Chicken wars
But now we're ending the chicken wars
Now the chicken wars are over
We come in peace
So what they're saying is
We know we walked into a room
And kicked over the trash can
And then left the room and then came back later
And we're like you guys
Nobody cleaned this up yet
But now we're saying
The chicken wars
Have ended
I will say this is
I'm surprised some of you
But I don't know a lot about war
And how it works and stuff
But can you be
Can you start the war
And now it's done
And be like what
Fine
You can't, no Travis
You can't do that
You can't just say
We did a war
But now we're tired of the war
Because we're doing the different things
I've played Risk enough that I don't think you could
You can't invade some countries
On Risk and then be like
Okay I'm done now so don't like come back at me
Okay
The launch of our chicken sandwich was incredible
And we're humbled by the amount of love
And positive reviews
But at the same time many claim that it started
The chicken wars
Said CMO Bruno Cardinale
In a statement
Now it's time to say goodbye to the chicken wars
And celebrate our new nuggets
Because we come in peace
Eight piece to be exact
To prove it's serious about ending the chicken wars
The Popeye's Foundation
We'll pay a wear guild
To everyone we killed
The Popeye's Foundation
Purchased the cash equivalent
Of one million nuggets
From Popeye's restaurants
As well as competing brands
McDonald's, Wendy's, Chick-fil-A, and Burger King
The foundation will donate the funds
To Second Harvest Food Bank
Of Greater New Orleans
And customers may visit
The Popeye's Foundation website to donate
And Popeye's will match the contributions
Of up to $25,000
What they're saying here
And it's very tough to parse
But my understanding is
That they bought a million chicken nuggets
And took them to a shelter
Is that what happened here?
Could you read it again?
Because it does sound
It's so hard to follow
The Popeye's Foundation
Purchased the cash equivalent
Of one million nuggets
How is that money?
You bought money of nuggets?
What are you talking about?
Because the videos they have to
Accompany this just shows a single Popeye's
Employee going door to door
At McDonald's and Wendy's and all these other places
Just like, I'd like to buy all the chicken nuggets
You have
For some reason
I don't know, I'll think of it
I think that they're saying
The Popeye's Foundation
Is donating the equivalent
But to say we purchased the cash equivalent
Of nuggets
What could that mean?
I mean, what are they saying?
They bought the cash equivalent
Of a million nuggets
At different stores
And then donated the money
What are you saying?
Our hope is that today
Guests who finally try our new
Chicken nuggets will say to themselves
Popeye's did it again
Started another war
Started another fucking war
A cuter war
We would like to call for a ceasefire
By invading a different country now
Bruno
Continued, this is I think
Where things really start to
The rails
Those two things together
The product quality
And the strong marketing campaign he's referring to here
Those two things together
They're really the recipe for the success of our brand
And I'm very confident
We have those two ingredients here
This time with the nuggets
The product tastes
Amazing
The campaign, I think
It's very, very timely
Very relevant
It speaks to a cultural moment
An iconic moment
That happened in America
Two years ago
That cultural moment
And really delivering something that is relevant
That is unique to Popeye's
And really puts Popeye's in the
Center of the conversation
Hey, the war's over
Guys, we're bigger than this
But Popeye's did it
And we're in the middle of it, and we did it
And it's us, and the war's over
And we'll do it again
I think we all agree the war's over
And we fucking won
We have annexed cluckers
All cluckers are now Popeye's
Oh my god, the gall
The absolute wild thing about this though
Is that in like the late 80's
There were pizza wars
Which was like an iconic thing
And it feels like they want that
Again?
And it could be
And I don't fucking know anymore
I don't know anymore
Can I talk about something else real quick?
This is unrelated, but I did want to mention it
Long John Silvers has partnered with Gathered Foods
To debut
Plant-based
Seafood
And the ad for this
There's an ad for it
And it just says plant-based seafood is now a thing
Awesome
That's good
That's about as much earnestness as I want behind this announcement
Customers will be able to choose from two Long John Silvers classic menu items
Now with a plant-based twist
Good catch
Crab-free cakes
Which I would argue most cakes are
Yes
But not all cakes
Not all cakes
Are packed with 15 grams of plant-based protein per serving
Features lump crab meat tastes
Mmm
What an appetizing concept
Okay
This is what it literally says
It features lump crab meat tastes
And texture complemented with sweet peppers
Green onions, parsley, and a kick of spice
If a filet is what you're after
Good catch fish-free filets
Are crispy breaded
Tender flaky white fish texture
You're looking for
Are they skipping every third word
In this announcement
Our mission is to make the unique seafood experience from the coasts available to all
Says Christopher Caudill
So we're mushing up a bunch of beans
I guess
We're mushing up a bunch of beans
And frying them because our mission is to bring seafood
To the planet
We believe plant-based seafood
Furthers that mission by making Long John Silvers
Accessible to guests who are hungry
For more plant-based protein
Option
It's also a great addition for fans
Of our classic sustainably sourced
Wild caught fish who are curious
About a new take on their
Seafood favorites
We're excited to set sail with good catch
On this test
I'm really curious and listeners if you could
Tweet with the hashtag NBNBAM
After this episode goes out
If you're a vegan or a vegetarian
Or I mean maybe you just don't eat
Fish for sustainability
Or whatever reasons
How many of you have been longing
To go to Long John Silvers
But there just weren't options
You tried my Long John Silvers and you're just salivating
Oh if only I could
But there's no options
You just think about the fact that they'll sell you
A container of lard cast-offs
For 75 cents
Crunchy lard cast-offs
If only I could get those crunchins but I can't
Just want to get some
Crunchins have been vegan this whole time
I bet
How many of you hear this news and like
Before we even finished talking about it
There was just like a U-shaped puff of dust
As you ran to your car
A U-shaped puff of dust
As you ran to your car and then turned back around
And ran the other way away from your car
Creating the U
That is the U-shaped puff of dust that you have left
Oh yeah they're committed
They're in five restaurants
Yeah
Five different Long John Silvers
Have these
They're in California
So they're bringing the seafood
And coastal experience to California
Thank god
Give me that bean fish in the bread basket
You know what I mean?
Like where we need it
I would
And I'm not saying that this is true of everyone
But there's someone in
The bread basket, I say this living in Ohio
That would walk up to the counter and say like
I'll have the crab cakes and they'd be like
Do you want that or not?
And they'd be like what the fuck are you talking about?
I just want to see that play out
I just said crab cakes
What about crab free cakes?
I said I want the crab cakes
Yeah but with or without the crab
Fuck off!
You know what makes me so mad about this?
This fucking stupid segment
I would fucking
Annihilate some plant based chicken
Fish nuggets right now
I would annihilate them, so hungry for it now
Thinking about that great white fish texture
We love that
I love that here
Flaky
My partner and I have a habit of stealing interesting coffee mugs
Especially from people we dislike
Our crown jewel is a church mug
We stole from a landlord
Who took our deposit unnecessarily
A friend recently asked how we got so many weird mugs
How do we explain
Without seeming like petty kleptomaniacs
This is from mysterious
Mug mafiosos in Maryland
And I have bad news
You steal all the time
For not great reasons
Yeah
They got you
I think this is
If you can't stand in your truth
For this
And be like oh we stole these
Because it's funny
These are stolen
It gives us a little modicum of control back
Right
They took something from us so we took something from them
We know it's not great
But it's a thing the two of us do together
And we like
We like it
It doesn't hurt anybody except the person who we've stolen from
Are you guys at this point
With your mugs where it is a one in one out policy
It's had to become that
Yes
It's become that at our house
We have now two drawers
Filled with coffee mugs
We have a good drawer
And a bad drawer
A bad drawer of mugs we don't like
But can't get rid of
And then the good drawer of the mugs
This is what I was going to say
Because I
God help me
I have two shelves in a cabinet
And one shelf is full of mugs we use
And the other one are
Just in case mugs I get
Like in case I open a coffee shop
Suddenly
They're like
I suddenly had that corporate retreat
In my house
I got 40 people here from the local bank
Who decided to have a trust building exercise
In my living room
And I have to provide cappuccinos for everybody
Here's my thing also
These aren't even mugs I use
I haven't used a regular coffee mug for 10 years
I have two mugs that I use
On alternating days
I only use travel mugs
Even though I work out of the house
And that way my coffee stays hot and fresh
All day long
But then you have no rush to drink it
Do you do the same damn thing Griffin?
I love when it gets to be 2pm and I'm like
Hot coffee
It's still hot and good
I'm drinking one right now
Contigo Autoseal
Cheers
He hit the microphone with his cup
Oh boy
I just have a big mug with West Virginia on it
It looks like
And I am wearing overalls right now
I feel like a school art teacher
With this big mug
And it's kind of spotty and you feel like stoneware
I love it
Contigo Autoseal
Is it stoneware?
The Contigo Autoseal
Has a valve
That you press a button
That allows the free flow of coffee
This valve is spring loaded
This valve
This little release on the lid
Will flip up
So you can clean underneath it
I discovered this
Far too recently
Oh no
Why does the mug smell like that?
You had baked in coffee goodness
Why do you have wretched mugs?
I like the open mug
With no lid or
Thermal properties
Because then it encourages me to drain it
To drain it
I love that
My mug is
The brand of it is Zach
Oh I love Zach stuff
I have a big Zach cup that I use for all my
Iced beverages
But it's weird because it looks like
It's like
Not mine
It's like hey Zach
And I'm like damn it
Can I still drink it though?
I feel like we gave dad too hard a time
For talking so much about drinkware when we were kids
We didn't know how good we had it
To learn about drinkware from a man
Like a real man
Who drank all kinds of different things
Out of lots of different cups
He would talk to us about Tervis and we'd just kind of ignore him
And now I'm like won't someone talk to me about Tervis
Yeah I would love to
Hey I was sent a mug
By a fan
That had like a panther on it
And it said in big black letters
Be nice to me
I have diarrhea on it
And then
I would say
Six weeks later
I was sent
A mug by a fan
That also had a panther on it
That said be nice to me I have diarrhea
On it and it was the same
Mug and so two different people
Saw that
And said that reminds me of Griffin
So much I'm going to spend
You know $19.99 plus shipping
Or whatever to make sure
He has it so I do have two of those on it
Sometimes you only know one thing
About a person and it's like oh they love
Unicorns or whatever so you get them
The one thing people know about Griffin
Is he gets diarrhea a lot
Not a lot I haven't had it in a long time
In fact Travis I know for a fact you've had
Diarrhea more recently than me
Yes but not as often statistically speaking
Days out of our lives spent with
Diarrhea
In 2021 I haven't had it
At all
That's because you haven't been exposed
To the harsh spores
Of the world
And this is the truth isn't it
It's not my fault
It's the world Griffin doesn't have diarrhea
The world has diarrhea
It gives it to me when I'm not
I got a mask up Fauci's like it's cool
Or is it it's not and I'm like I don't care
I'm going to do it because the world's got diarrhea
But if you stay in your
World's got diarrhea
As long as you stay in your
Hormetically sealed home
No diarrhea can get to you
Exactly and also no chicken wings
No chicken wings
Guys I still I'm really like everything
We've said after finding out the chicken
Sandwich wars are over like I've got
Two sons
And knowing that they're not going to be drafted
They're not going to be conscripted
You know what I mean
They're not going to have to go overseas
It means the world to me
Yeah but now they're going to have to
They'll have to take up arms
In the plant based seafood wars
It's going to be a lot chiller though
That's going to be a lot of mostly like
Like there's going to be a lot of
Computer warfare there there's a lot
Yeah a lot of cyber one yeah exactly
At the end
This restaurant is by the way it said
And with the plant based seafood industry
Expected to grow to a staggering
1.3 billion
In the next 10 years Long John Silver's
And Good Catch are the leading edge of a long term
Movement I you know what I gotta
Say if you're going to open up five restaurants
I don't know if we're going to get there
If Long John Silver's only has five
Throw your fucking hat over the ring
Launch it in every restaurant
Even ones you don't own
Make a little kiosk
Where they can get it
My favorite fish place is this little
Hole in the wall called
Oxide Charlie's
In West Virginia you mean
Inside an O Charlie's
Oh boy
It's hey if you want the real catch
You know what I mean
The real catch
Is it like a VIP lounge inside
How do you get into it
Yeah it's just
It's a kitchen bun
Hey listen thanks so much for
Listening to our program
We hope you've had a fun time
It's brave
We got a new
We got some new merch at McElroyMerch.com
Travis you got
I'm very excited because the pin of the month
For August is work of fart
The proceeds of which
Will be benefiting One Tree Planted
Which is dedicated to making it easier
For individuals and businesses to give back to the environment
Create a healthier climate
Protect biodiversity and help reforestation
Efforts around the world
Plus you'll get a pin that says work of fart
On it
Who the fuck doesn't want that
Also very excited
We will be and when I say we
I basically mean like all the McElroys
Are coming to Emerald City Comic Con
That's December 2nd through 5th
All seven of us
That's Griffin, Rachel, Justin
Sydney, Travis, Theresa
And Clint will all be there
So keep an eye out there's more info
Coming soon about panels, signings, photo ops
And stuff
Travis and I are going to be at Dragon Con this year
We're excited to see everybody there
We have the Adventure Zone game
If you haven't played it yet
Two Gather Studios is celebrating a safe return
To the game table this summer with local retailer events
Giveaways and live streams
It has gameplay streams every Tuesday
Evening at 8pm eastern time
At twitch.tv slash
Two Gather
That's T-W-O Two Gather Studios
Hosted by at
Nometic
At Together Studio
On Twitter for weekly giveaways
Of swag from them and our publishers
For a second speaking of which
The Adventure Zone graphic novel
Crystal Kingdom is out now that's
The first four in the series are
All out now if you haven't gotten them
Go do so at a bookstore or
You can go to theadventurezonecomic.com
And as long as I'm saying links
I stream on Twitch
And it's pretty fun
Twitch.tv slash the Travis McElroy
Thank you to
Montaigne for this red theme song
My Life Is Better With You
It's close, it's close
It's all I can say
I thought you were saying I was close to getting the name of the song right
No, no, no, it's close
It's coming
The shadow of it has been cast
Over all the major metropolitan areas
Of the country
And that's all we're going to say about it
Y'all want to find a yahoo?
Yeah
Yeah, this one was sent in by Ricky
It says here Thick Ricky sent this one in
Thanks Thick Ricky
Yeah, and it's asked by yahoo answers user
It's asked by yahoo answers user
Papa John
It says Papa John
You're sure about that?
Yeah, it says Papa John
It's weird
Papa John Schlatter asked this
And he said
What happened?
My name is Justin McElroy
I'm Griffin McElroy
This has been my brother, my brother
This has been my brother, my brother Justin McElroy
It's better with you