The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother and Me, an advice show for the
modern era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother,
Travis McElroy. Thank you all for joining us. I'm your sweet baby brother and 30 under 30
media luminary, Griffin McElroy. Griffin, you brought us here to-
I want to thank you all for joining me here. I want to thank the press. I want to thank my-
We never use the press room here at My Brother, My Brother and Me HQ.
We've had one for years. This is our first proper press conference. I'm so glad that my family is
supporting me through this difficult time as I make these trying announcements to you.
And I ask for your patience, I ask for God. I ask for God's bliss and-
You ask for God? Just like give him to you? This is a press conference and I don't think
there's so much of a back and forth at the press conference until we get to the proper Q&A segment.
I was gonna say I'm pretty sure that's what a press conference is, but go on.
Well, okay. It's not so much a conversation. It's me talking about- I need God's help on this one
and my family. I love them and they love me and support me through this announcement that I have
to make these trying times is that I have decided today I think I'm just probably not going to end
up taking- have taken a shower. I think- I think by the clock will roll over and it's going to be
October 9th and on October 8th when I look back in my diary and I have the usual section in the diary
it says shower time. That won't exist. There won't be an entry for that and it's a difficult
decision that I've made and it's 7- it's 7 30 central time right now while we're recording this
and I could- I could ostensibly take one after the recording but then a night shower just doesn't
make any sense in my life right now. And have there been times today where I could have taken
a shower instead of playing Star of the Valley? The answer to that is of course yes, but it's just-
Are you ready to open it up to questions please?
I want to thank my family and God one more time because I think that's important because I'll
need both their help to get through this one I think and I- I- it's just- I've just- I- it's-
and it's not like I've been sitting around all day. I've been out in the hot sun. There's been
a little bit of sweat. I did go to the farmers market. I did go to an open house. There is a-
there's this- there's a- an aroma but I- it's just today's a stink boy day. No showers today for me
and thanks to God and family. Travis you- I believe you had a question. We'll open up the Q&A now.
I do have a question. Well first I want to say thank you so much for having us.
Well thank you and God.
And God and family and I also want to say it- it feels weird to go first episode to
375 episodes and still talking about your showering habits.
Or lack thereof. I hate to interrupt.
Yes thank you.
So here's my question. Do you normally shower every day?
That's an excellent question Travis. Yes I do. I honor my body with the wet room is what I call
it sometimes. The small- or the small wet room and I'll get in there and lather up with my soaps and
my oils and I do try to get clean every single day Travis because-
Every day.
Yeah I think it's- it's just a nice little bookend to either the morning or the afternoon as the case
may be. Probably not the evening because it is evening time and I will not be taking a shower
after the recording but yeah I do- I do typically try to keep my- my situation squeaky as- as- as
the case may be. Thank you very much for your question and God. Anybody else?
Excuse me Griffin.
Yeah Justin McElroy please.
Are you reaching this decision just now or did you have a moment where you were like I should
get in the shower and didn't? Did you cross a barrier at some point from which there was no
return?
So there was a moment yes Rachel took the baby and they did go to Target to shop for various sundries
and I did- I did stay home and I had the thought in my mind this would be a good opportunity for
me to go get in the small wet room uninterrupted by baby cries or any- any sort of other situation
that may need and so I made the decision in that moment that I was instead going to- I had a crop-
a big crop of cranberries come in on Stardew Valley and so I did decide that I'm just going
to sort of plop right down on the couch and I- I had the thought in my mind this is a lie
but I had the thought in my mind is I'll- I'll harvest these cranberries go sell them maybe pop
in the mine for a second give some gifts to my you know my beloveds and then I'll go get in the
shower but then I saw the- the Honda drive back into the part- into the driveway and I knew like
that that was never going to be a part of the plan and so I do want to apologize to my family
and the lord for that one because I knew-
I'm getting some reports that when your wife did return in the Honda the- upon entering the house
she said the stink is still here you swore it was- excuse me this is my question sorry I'm
reading this quote verbatim this quote is from God this quote God handed me this quote from your
bride and it says the stink the stink is still here you swore you would not be the stink man upon
my return and yet here the stink lies surrounding you like a tapestry lies and stink both drape you
like a uh it says here a dirty rug yeah I'm not sure that must be a little bit of um
illustrative sort of language and it hurt but it did hurt it hurt it hurt but I knew that the hurt
was my own and that I caused it and I forced it to happen I- I knew the moment she did walk in
and um her and the child the baby both looked at the gym shorts I had been wearing all day and sort
of looked upon them with disgust and I knew in that moment that uh mistakes had been made mistakes
have been made we can't go out there and perform 100 every single time sometimes Stardew Valley
just came out and I'm want to get my cranberries going um so another question sorry one question
over here over here let's get the let's get the follow-up from Justin and then we'll hop on over
to Travis and Justin are you uh at this point are you able to play Stardew Valley without a guide
because that kind of put me off when I was playing it the first time I mean I always felt like I was
yeah I know all the crop rotations and everything thank you I know the profit ladders and uh the
statistics and uh thank you very much I and it is because of that dedication to my craft that
kept me from the wet room Travis go ahead with your question please uh thank you very much
Travis McElroy Godtimes um just a quick question are you worried that this breaking of your small
wet room pattern will lead to further not using the small wet room in the future well and I'm so
glad that you've asked this Travis because I'm looking at my calendar tomorrow is Columbus Day
which is traditionally stink boy holiday where all the stink boys gather and celebrate not having
taken a shower that day now the thought of going two days in a row I would I think I would need to
consult a physician at that point because who knows what sort of bacterium have climbed up
into me just because I have stayed out of the wet room that they hate so bad but um I don't I don't
love the way I feel right now I will be completely honest I don't love the way I feel um but follow
up follow up sorry follow up question to that point sir then why not take a fucking shower
oh sorry I've been doing this press conference so long that my tongue got real dry um it's the it's
the it's it's the principle of the thing and I don't ask you to
understand or respect my decisions but I do expect you to respect them okay family and God uh uh
unrelated uh this weekend I was at Disney World and I saw an old man walking around
without shoes or socks and I just wanted you guys okay so I need you to I need why
don't you come up here why don't you come up here and we'll switch okay all right everybody
I thank you all the thank God thank family it's Justin McElroy uh I was at Epcot uh I think I was
near Norway and I saw an old man walking around um and he didn't have shoes on or socks and he
didn't seem shameful uh and he had a t-shirt on I think it was a big dog t-shirt and khaki shorts
and he had no socks or shoes at Disney World that's not what Walt wanted and that's not what
Mickey wants and I'm pretty sure about that um Walt envisioned his uh experimental prototype
City of Tomorrow I don't think or Epcot I don't think that he envisioned old men walking around
without shoes or socks now uh sorry Justin Justin quick question here from Griffin McElroy from
Disney yeah Griffin go ahead from Disney Adventures um it was did you follow this gentleman just to
make sure that he was removed from the park by a big burly security guard who was dressed up
like Pete from the Goofiverse yeah Pete came in and had a like comical handcuffs that were still
very much real and he was escorted into uh uh Spaceship Earth where I assume he will be kept
until his death um may I may I press conference status real quick you don't have a question
about the Disney or I don't okay well so you guys go ahead and I repeat he was an old man without
socks or shoes I can't believe you don't have anything for that I'm saying it no it's just
very well okay uh run it back okay Travis McElroy uh Goofy Goofy um no paper just Goofy um are you
sure that he was gets the news and he takes it back to Goofy and he tells it to Goofy one-on-one
and he has to talk real slow is it possible that this old shoeless man was some sort of new
character or cast member that you weren't aware of are you up to date on all of your Disney movies
uh I have a three-year-old so yes yes I've seen all of them I know all the movies now
okay so now my thing all right Justin get the fuck off this Justin get the fuck off the stage
thank you uh hello thank you very much I'm Travis McElroy you gotta thank God thank God and thank
you I want to uh thank God for giving me a ride here I'm predicting he doesn't have anything I
think this is just because he won a press conference no no I do Justin didn't thank God
and his family so his didn't count um I I have to apologize uh to everyone it is with shame
that I announce I took two showers today and I'm worried that cosmically I took Griffin's away from
him it's entirely possible it would explain my it would explain my I Griffin McElroy shower boy
time uh express I was I was at a hotel this morning and they didn't have hot water but I
needed to wash my hair so I'm just gonna set my head under it was horrible so when I got home
to my real home where there was hot water I took a second shower and even as I did it I thought
wow I'm enjoying this in a way that only Griffin McElroy normally enjoys his showers
and I can I be honest I luxuriated in it I did shampoo conditioner and body wash the trifecta
that you only do when you know you've got time uh and it was great it was amazing
Griffin McElroy shower boy express I just am curious about how you plan on repaying this
to me are we going to set up some sort of schedule where perhaps
I get to take two showers one day and you don't get to take any or what's what's the sort of way
to make this right with thank you so much for asking I would much rather do kind of an installment
plan where each of my showers for like two weeks is one minute shorter um and each of yours is one
minute longer maybe you don't get to use soap in one right exactly thank you um rather than just
skipping the whole thank you and god thanks god here's uh so this is an advice show uh uh and
here's the first question recently my husband and I bought our first house together congratulations
soon after we bought our house we met our next door neighbor whose name we will say is Rory
because that's hard to say can I all right I'll just go with that you can say Dennis if you want
I also just want to say I always love when people um include these fake names as though like saying
his actual name Jerry would totally give him away well I mean fandoms are capable of literally
anything and you know I love our listeners but anything's possible um uh as as they got uh that
shrimp heaven now kid had got elected mayor of his city it's true in any way capable of doing that
as we settled into our home I began doing yard work and used a big orange bucket thank you for
the aesthetic details they really helped to paint a picture a big orange bucket that I found in the
home to take pulled weeds to throw in the brush in the backyard after using this bucket a few times
I noticed that it has Rory or Dennis written across it I didn't make the connection at first
so I continued to use it until I finally click what you didn't make the connection that's not
a very difficult connection that's a good easy connection I feel like it's not fucking zodiac
killer it said Rory on it or Dennis did the former home homeowners steal this bucket am I stealing
this bucket do I return it to the owner do I hide it behind his shed do I buy my own orange bucket
and write my name across it and pretend this nightmare never happened help that's from the
real bucket thief it sounds like your conscience has already spoken just based on the title that
you've chosen for yourself there that you know this is bucket crime and you are continuing to
be party to it you're not the maybe the the perpetrator but you are an accomplice certainly
you are profiting from the bucket this is actually a really good question because you legally bought
everything in the house if they left it there that's your property you own it
I've always wanted a loaning scenario would happen because it would take I would need to
I would need a bucket pretty bad before I would break into my neighbor's look at him over there
using that beautiful orange bucket again one of these days when he's not looking it'll be
he could throw anything in there and carry it from place to place as a little effort I bet
he could even put liquids in there no way yeah yeah I asked him I said Dennis where did you get
that nice bucket and he told me to fuck off can you believe that Valerie he told me to fuck off
so I'm putting together a team I need someone who can do flips someone who can lift things
a guy who has pencils Valerie you're gonna seduce him and I don't listen I know I've had you seduce
a lot of neighbors for a lot of buckets but this one's different this is the last one last job
after this one we can retire um this is I I don't know my neighbors super well and I feel genuinely
guilty about that because I feel I on paper I like the idea of knowing all my neighbors and
getting together for backyard barbecues and bocce ball and what have you um and this seems like a
good opportunity to like go talk to your neighbor you know what I mean like I would never just like
go ring the doorbell and invite them to dinner although I'm sure they would be into that um
because of my considerable anxiety but if I had an like a reason to go talk to them I think I
would I think you should I think you should jump at it I think everybody could do better to like
know their neighbors a little bit better and this seems like a chance to do that and have a reason
for it I bought a house recently and we have a big uh like bay window in the living room and
there's this older gentleman who lives in the house across the street and he likes to spend his
time on nice days just sitting on a chair on his lawn and so I like to stand in front of my bay
window and look at him and saying old man look at my life and I uh laugh really hard every time I
do it but you don't go talk to him and see if no no no no no no no you are you are I should
advise you Travis you're in a window right now where you please don't be like me in every house
I've ever owned please learn your neighbor's names now and write them down somewhere because
you won't need them frequently enough to remember them and you are definitely going to get to a
window where it would be weird to ask them their name yeah like you are you're hurtling towards
that window from the day you buy the house are you ready that comes over my across the street
neighbor that comes over to use my phone sometimes uh-huh I I she told me her name once the first
time she borrowed the phone and I didn't know it's going to be a repeated thing so I didn't
remember it and now look at me we actually play with fire one step deeper where Teresa and I
within the walls of our own home refer to anyone who lives around us as neighbor Reno so I thought
I was like did you see what neighbor Reno was doing over there oh what was neighbor Reno doing
and one of these days I will talk to that person and I will call them neighbor Reno to their face
because I'm a monster who can't control themselves neighbor Reno's fun yeah that sounds like you're
on some Flanders shit I don't even I don't even have I have there's a old every day I drive to
daycare drop my son off not every day like four days a week and when I drive back it always times
out that I drive by an old man who lives near me he's always chomping an unlit cigar he's walking
his dog passing the same street every time we are kindred spirits we are always in the same place
don't know nothing about him except he likes to walk his dog on that street and chewing on that
cigar I'm gonna call him Jack from now on because he looks like a jack I so having just bought a
house this is our first permanent residence like house we've ever bought and it's amazing how your
psychology changes I took my dog out into the backyard to use the restroom her not me and
I will often use the small wet room and then put pajama pants back on and so like I was wearing
some Muppets pajama pants that Mary Small got me they're great and I made eye contact with
my neighbor who was like fully dressed because it was 2 30 in the afternoon and he was dressed like
you know a person an adult and I realized like oh I can't just move now I own this place I'm
trapped here forever and to you I'll always be that 12 year old adult who lives next door yeah
oh no and that that dookie is gonna stay there and you own that house and you gotta do something
about it if it's a rental or a lease you can leave and then in a year or so won't be your problem
didn't think about that I bet are you talking about dog dookie I cleaned it up so yeah I got
one for you sent him by uh zooey or zoe porter thank you it's from yahoo answers user what
I'll go do a rado oh this is br answers.yahoo.com okay it's it's yeah all right it's something
uh thank thank you sorry something's gone wrong ask this question I'm gonna call him
Raquel asks do you think that Mr Bean is sexy
hmm I read this and at first I thought maybe it's one of those dang trolls maybe we got a real
ogre in the mix a real shrek situation on our hands but then I pondered it and I don't know
where to land on the last thing I want to do is objectify Mr Bean or actor Rowan Atkinson
who plays Mr Bean but it's it's it's a it's an interesting sort of subject to tackle because
is Mr is Mr Bean sexy is I guess the core sort of question I'm struggling with he's successful
and success can be sexy right probably one of the best known British characters of all time
um funny a lot of people think that humor can be sexy or sexual makes you really horny when you
laugh at it and prudence and a good problem solver and I think there's a lot of qualities about Mr
Bean that is sexy and makes you horny if you really want to drill down it were there ever any
racier Mr Bean bit I'm not listen I'm not trying to get blue I'm not saying like a sexy I'm glad
you asked that Travis because there was the one in the swimming pool where he gets really scared
up on the diving board and crawls down for him but he's wearing a very tight fitting sort of
pair of trunks or bathing suit where you can see I guess a little bit of his butt and probably
if you look really hard on the 4k blu-rays a little bit of penile shape do you think he calls
him Mr Bean yeah yeah was there because I think there could have been a lot of humor I just see a
lot of uh like situations ripe for humor like Mr. Bean Mr. Bean shaves his balls right that's
funny no no no no no no sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry thank you Dustin yeah you did say Mr. Bean
so we are going to have to take a quick break my flexible friend I have to I have to shave my
balls Mr. Wayne if you'll excuse me that's not what Bane even sounded like that was Sean Connery
kind of a maybe oh that's the only way I can do Bane is that you kind of Bane Connery his take on
Bane um I want to just hop into the comments here and just pick some of those apart uh Ramos Jr. 107
says in his own way lol and I like that yeah to anybody he is confident I think in the way that
he does his stuff and confidence is well here's let me tell you what's messed up about this
question Griffin that I've just realized psychologically the only reason someone asked
this question is a they believe he is sexy and are looking for confirmation or they believe
he is sexy and are looking for confirmation or b someone has told them that Mr. Bean is sexy and
they disagree but in either case a human being has stated or felt that he is sexy answering the
question this isn't a question you think like I don't and no one I know does but maybe the internet
thinks otherwise you only ask this if you want confirmation I don't think and beauty's in the
eye of the holder especially when you're looking at being I want to dive down into this one from
he ie Rowan Atkinson is dressed as Blackadder Elizabethan version in that leather doublet and
that beard and then they say not af like apostrophe alf like maybe uh you're saying it with a bit of
an affectation but I'm glad that apostrophe is there or else this person would have said not alf
it's not he didn't play out he isn't not out just to be clear now you're not talking about alfar
it now I guess and what we need to dive into next and we still have the Mr. Bean question
on the table but if alf is sexy or not well this is how you build like a logical threat and if we
can establish that alf is sexy I think that will prove that Mr. Bean is sexy I know it's hard to
yes exactly thank you a equals bc equals alf
is Mr. Bean Justin you've been sort of quiet on the subject I'll tell you what alf is really good
at hmm nope oh god it's I was gonna make a joke about eating cats and I think you can see where
I was going but I'm not gonna say Travis you can park the car outside but everyone knows you drove
there I'm sorry sorry sorry Fred no that's the best metaphor I've ever heard for that kind of
thank you Justin rules rules are rules um here's another question moving on before he wants to
weigh in on the comedy I'll just say it I think yeah he's pretty sexy okay I think yes strong
silent type etc etc uh in the last city I lived there is what I and many others believe to be an
authentic bona fide Jimmy Buffett's margaritaville after visiting I never got the hype okay until I
saw a photo from an actual margaritaville thanks Justin and realized that ours isn't the real thing
instead it's just this fancy seaside bar and grill that has stolen the good name for their own uses
everyone I've talked to believes that this place is the real deal straight from the j man himself
what do I do how do I expose this establishment for their blatant fraud and that's from confused
in paradise okay so hmm the the fact that there were eight tees in Jimmy Buffett's margaritaville
should have been the first tip off um because that's not the real Jimmy Buffett uh it was Jimmy
Buffett's daiquiri town here's the thing don't you think if you looked at him playing said this
is a Jimmy Buffett's margaritaville right and they responded well you know that's hard it's hard to
say what is the Jimmy Buffett's margaritaville really what I that's a weird listen I don't think
James is particularly litigious but I think that he does try to keep the margaritaville thing pretty
close to the vest what with the chain of restaurants and the rum yeah it's like he's walking around
to everyone drinking a margarita and he's like no it smacks it out of hand that's mine you gotta
pay me five dollars but I do think in this one case you're probably right if you call it Jimmy
Buffett's right you just can't that's James's James wrote that for himself and he shared it
with us but not in this way you're this is I'll tell you what though I do have to call it a
question your determination here because like you didn't this is probably the the I assume
the biggest platform in which you will share this information and you withheld a lot of crucial
details that we could use to completely put them on fucking blast yeah right they would be they
would be currently being annihilated right now I would yelp them into non-existence please don't
please don't do that option please don't do that but like no don't do that at all listen we aren't
lawyers we aren't experts and I also don't want the burden of costing a number of people their jobs
on my conscience so like but you don't have to close it just call it something else you call it
something else Jimmy Buffett's would you care for a margarita sir I think Trav I'm not I'm
not I'm again no legal expert I think calling your restaurant Jimmy Buffett's fucking anything
yes oh I see what the problem can I hit you with a possible name Tony Keith's I love this pub and
restaurant he's not using that anymore is he what's that he's not using that anymore he might
even just give it to you well that's it now who is Tony Keith though is the real question
McDonald's what about a McBottles hi welcome to Burger King it's welcome to Burger King it's the
new good restaurant still frame flame broiled you're gonna love these these good burgers you can
have it whichever way have it whichever way you'd like it to be today our king isn't creepy
McBonald's I'm enjoying it I'm enjoying it ba ba ba ba do hmm okay Cindy's Cindy's
our our hamburger patties are octagons it's weird right it's weird we say welcome to the octagon
when you come in this is this is this is welcome to RC's opening up opening up a restaurant is the
most like risky thing you can do in the business world right like what's this like nine out of
every 10 like flop in the first year or so like well you have to think that your only goal when
you open a restaurant is you have to think in your head like you know how up till now people
have not known where to get food well now yeah let me step in why why run the risk of in addition
to like the pressures of the free food market um open yourself up to a cease and desist from
the historically chill island man jimmy buffett it doesn't it doesn't it does not make sense to me
unless unless this place was open first jimmy was a big fan oh shit my great great grandfather
james t buffett loved margaritas and villages and he combined those loves into jimmy buffett's
margarita and this no talent hack comes in and says hello my name is dennis lahoya and i'm going
to take it all now there's also a possibility that it's a fair use parody and we should always
keep that in mind too um that's a that's an option i think just keep just if jimmy's ever in town
just slide him a card just walk up to him this won't be a problem just walk up to him
slide him a note and just with an address or if you can meet him in a parking garage
that would actually be great too if you can arrange that is it is it not maybe it's totally
legal to open up a bar based on any song title and then it's because it's public it's public
domain is what that is and i took i took one sort of law class in college and it was mostly
like fair use law but i think if you call a bar like you ought to know or um you ought to know
be the worst name for a restaurant ever because it kind of implies like you ought to know what's
in here you ought to know what our food is i think if you open up a restaurant restaurant
and you call it despacito featuring daddy yankee then you're totally in the clear
but you have to put daddy yankee in quotes because it is a person's actual name
well now that is a restaurant i would go to despacito featuring daddy yankee and you have to
say it like that because of the quotes not a lot of people know this but if you ever look at
copyright documents it actually just says like we would really appreciate it if you didn't
but there's like no legal ramifications totally copyright it's just kind of like hey it would be
really cool if you didn't you know make a movie called mad max like we'd really appreciate it if
you like wouldn't we're gonna it's trademarked so please don't please but if you do there's
nothing we can do about it uh let's take a break right now and uh travel over to the money zone
to earn our money money we're gonna get money we're gonna talk about stuff and get money from
it great because that's our crafts our first sponsor is me undies and we told you all about
their underwear and it's extremely good underwear and everybody should have it but if underwear is
not your thing uh we are excited to announce that me undies socks are finally here me undies socks
are spun from premium materials they're dedicated to making the most comfortable pair of underwear
and now socks you will ever own i got a couple pairs of these socks and they are they fit real
nice they feel real nice they got a nice grip on them and um they are they have a sort of covert
hemline a lot of people will look and be like are you wearing socks you're like no they're just
barely there me undies so comfortable so fashionable so stylish have you guys ever
thought about the fact that socks are like the donut holes of underpants whoa that's deep because
you put your foot through the leg hole to put them on right and the sock stays on your foot and the
rest goes up around your thing so like if you sewed the sock to the leg hole you'd close it up
well that would not be very comfortable no but that's this is what i'm saying is
is the donut hole of underpants i've thought about it for the past 12 seconds and decided
what you just said was garbo nonsense you know what here's the thing though griffin you're gonna
be lying awake in your own mouth won't and yes i will the dat part will be true yes okay and then
it's gonna hit you if like oh that makes total sense because if the sock was sewn to the bottom
of the underpants i'd try to pull the underpants on but i couldn't get past my feet but if i pulled
hard enough but if it pulled hard enough the underpants would come with it sock would stay
on my foot boom sock underpants separated might be garbo nonsense i'll think about it though i
promise i'll put the effort in right now me and these has an exclusive offer just for our listeners
you can get 20 off your first order and free shipping plus they guaranteed you will love your
socks and undies or you get your money back to get your exclusive 20 off free shipping and 100
satisfaction guarantee go to me undies.com slash my brother that's me undies.com slash my brother
i should also say along with socks they've also just started doing bralettes um you know super
comfy bras and i was also in there looking they do hoodies too did you know that what yeah let
me get one of those hoodies man yeah especially if you head into the fall i'm gonna check that
shit out i still haven't gotten any of those sleep pants i need to get those lounge gotta get those
lounge pants they are life-changing uh who wants to tell us about our next sponsor i do i do i do
it's nature box we all want to eat better but when it comes to snacks sometimes it feels like the
whole world is delicious and a billion calories are boring and tasteless but it doesn't have to
be that way nature box has over 100 000 no sorry 100 snacks that's still a lot of snacks that's a
good amount of still a lot of snacks i shouldn't have i i should have gone they have 10 snacks
no way they have no snacks no wait oh wait hold on wait hold on can this be right it's just right
they've added 100 new snacks no this is i've got hold on i've got to send an email to check that
no it says it yeah just got confirmed 100 they just responded they seem a little stressed out
going from no product at all to 100 times that uh also not how that math works no come on you know
what i mean though you don't have to get fucking pedantic about it simple ingredients no artificial
colors flavors and sweeteners so you can feel good about what you're eating like salt and pepper
little loops or big island pineapple i know we always talk about the same ones with it you know
it's good to fruit starch i got to get those i got a new jammy jam they just sent me a box
and it had a pumpkin spice chocolate chip biscotti in it oh you know i'm dunking those in my coffee
with the hazelnut creamer all morning long whoa that sounds good i just got a french toast uh
kettle corn love that yeah uh if you want to try this and you should go to naturebox.com you choose
the snacks you want and naturebox will deliver them right to your door if you ever try one you
don't like impossible naturebox will replace it for free and right now naturebox is offering
our listeners 50 off your first order when you go to naturebox.com slash my brother that's
naturebox.com slash my brother for 50 off your first order go experience the naturebox um i got
a chunk of chocolate i got a new tagline okay sorry feel the crunch oh i like that
not all these snacks are crunchy though leave them out long enough okay think inside the
box have we done that one before no travis please read this jumbo okay i got a jumbo truck and here's
the thing this is the first time anyone's ever do it and i'm going to tell you right now folks
it's the last time i'm only going to allow this one message to slip past us and it goes a little
something like this this message is for Courtney Hall and Lin-Manuel Miranda and it's from Vicky
aka internet magpie thank you Courtney for all of the joy your writing on Pajima brings to my life
thank you Lin for all the joy and feels and car crying thank you both for unknowingly joining
forces to introduce me to MBMBAM great job to all Vicky you're great Vicky this is a very
good message and i like this idea just like dear Edgar Wright just saw uh Baby Driver good flick
you make some good flicks man i like it i don't know if you listen or not but keep it keep it
going actually that's gonna be my rule from now on the only way you can do this from now on is to
write to people who we know for sure does not listen to my brother yeah for sure definitely
we have to 100% know that that person not only doesn't listen but has never heard the name
McElroy before for sure uh actually yeah uh ad sales are the they're about to go back on sale
ooh the the Jumbotrons are gonna go out i'm looking right now to to try to uh to to get
this so hold on well while you got it i'll read the next one this is uh Jumbotron number two
from Ryan 2.0 Brown from Mark Beeve Ryan 2.0 note the same Ryan who sent you a shirt from his dojo
which increased your head butting power thank you oh did you get that because i also got one
maybe it was a different dojo shirt i got a different dojo shirt but it did make me head
butt way better like increased my head butt strength by like a hundred uh you have been
one of my closest friends i've been there for the birth of both your children you're a great human
and a wonderful father if you doubt it the brothers have now said it so it's an irrefutable fact
i'm glad to call you brother mark that's that's also lovely that's a very sincere and nice
message uh thank you mark for sharing that and for giving Ryan hopefully a good message we don't
know if Ryan listens but i i hope so well
stop podcasting yourself we don't even know anymore find it on maximumfun.org
or wherever you download your podcasts
justin you got that details uh jumbotrons from mmbam the zonecast wonderful pod and
greatest generation 2018 jumbotrons go on sale 2 pm eastern standard time or is it
yeah be eastern standard time at that point eastern standard time on november 1st be cool
seriously and also they sell out extremely quickly so please if you want to get a message on the show
make sure you're ready we also do them on uh shmanners by the way so if you want to do
personal yeah on any of our podcasts on max fun just hop on that's not actually accurate we don't
do them on top bones gotcha sucka sorry i don't know why never really talked about it how do you
want to talk about it now because you sound really you sound super i probably need some
help out with sydney you sound p.o'd no i just don't well now the energy is weird because you
sound super p.o'd dude i just i'm not i'm not super do you want to do you want to do a press
conference about it this always has helped us in the past oh oh gosh this has become a defense
mechanism justin i want to deflect
what a burger
can't make you laugh what a burger
up until now everyone has known what a burger as the place at the dallas airport where i saw
cardinals what a burger thing but there's a new thing in town what a burger is launching
the tree is a burger with creamy chili sauce this press this press release i like because a lot of
times in these press releases people are trying too hard and i feel like in this one they didn't
try very much at all and maybe they were just sort of writing it word by word not really knowing what
the next word would be chorizo a type of ground sausage that derives its bold taste profile and
deep red color from a fresh blend of spices is already a staple in many places and gaining in
popularity so already what a burger is on the defensive um they're saying chorizo is actually
good so calm down we're late to this category uh but trust us lots of other people do it i also
really like the first half of that sentence sounds straight off wikipedia like yeah here's
right but then the second half of the sentence kind of peters out like a kid who like copied
and pasted and like well i can't just leave that i have to add something to it and also i really
liked the book and also characters were good the dog represented uh industrial revolution
the sizzling chorizo gives the burger a bold taste while a blend of fire roasted poblano
peppers red peppers and onions give it a fresh bite what a burger combine these two ingredients
with the new creamy chili sauce two slices of monterey jack cheese and two fresh all beef
patties for a unique burger with the perfect balance of spice so those two paragraphs are
already in it right and then they go into rich's office and they're like rich help me i wrote two
paragraphs and i don't fucking know what else to say we can't just send out two paragraphs and
rich is like no problem i've got it quote mexican style chorizo makes this burger unique with this
deep red color we're still very hung up on the deep red color of chorizo that's very important
with its deep red color fresh blend of spices and bold flavorful profile says rich the whataburger
vice president of marketing and innovation the flavors on this burger blend nicely for a balance
for a balanced but savory taste we think our customers will really enjoy it now i want to take
two things i need to break off here he clarifies that it's savory okay you're not cinnabon there's
not a question in my mind of what the flavor profile is going to be on this burger you do not
need to clarify for me that it is a savory taste and then he says we think our customers will
really enjoy which i really appreciate the humility because he could have very easily said no
but no he said think listen we took our breast guess and here's what we know there's a bold red
color on this lots of other people are doing it spices and it's a fresh blend and a bite and
there's spices and a deep red color and we fucking we're out of ideas over here at whataburger so if
you listen other people are doing it just trust us about this if you have anything if you have any
if you have anything if you have any new ideas please let us know we are just hard i love that
in like the that statement there's so many different uh like uh so many uh synonyms for
blend and spices like the mix of flavors is great the blend of spices is great the morass of
tastations it's wonderful you're gonna love that it's just everything you can do be like we put a
bunch of like fucking flavors in it is that okay do you you're gonna eat it you won't even know if
you like it there's just so much flavor and then you'll be done please enjoy it we hope we we think
you will the chorizo burger is only available for a limited time and then in a parenthetical it says
no exact dates to share so they're really just taking whenever whenever the chorizo runs out
yeah whenever you guys stop liking it you can tell us we'll take it away we're so sorry we
bought 50 pounds of chorizo from somebody that promises people like it we're just gonna see what
happens i wait our sister's kid has invested in chorizo he's promised us you'll really like it
i these motherfuckers have i kid you not a bullet pointed list that i will spare you but a bullet
pointed list of everything that is on the burger and it covers exactly they they did it in prose
and then they wanted to break it down into like the real nitty gritty of exactly what's on this
motherfucker and that is available for a limited time they're also doing a spiced up chorizo
sausage what a burger late night and breakfast with the uh uh and then there's a taquito i just
slice of american cheese in it which does seem strange not how the taquito was intended but okay
i just like i would eat one of these i think it sounds good i'm a fan of chorizo but i will say
this blend of lots of meat and spicy sauce and spicy cheese like they may as well get like
fucking oscar de lohoya to come in and duct tape this to a boxing glove and just punch it directly
into my stomach because it will be that will essentially be the result of this event just get
like chuck laddell to come in and duct tape it to his foot and just kick it right into like my
fucking ribs because that'll basically be about where i'm at i'm sorry they have a list there's
four things in the taquito there's a soft flour tortilla scrambled eggs chorizo there's a colon
and it says fresh blend of spices sizzling bold flavorful deep red color you get this right it's
red fucking red one slice of american cheese listen the trees it's just deep red it's so
beautiful and none of us can bring ourselves to taste it but here's what we know about it just
from observing it deep red color and there seems to be a lot of fucking spices in there yeah i'm
gonna eat one of these i'm gonna eat one of these tomorrow yeah uh which means i'll talk to you guys
on thursday uh do you guys want to yahoo yeah please this one's sent in by hannah troxell
thank you hannah yahoo answers user aman a-y-m-e-n amen asks if i want to make a spa what will
really put it over the top and how can i beat other competitors try one more time if i want
to make a spa what will really put it over the top and how can i beat other competitors
hmm you go to the spa maybe you're getting a rub or uh oils applied to you or uh some sort of
exfoliating treatment or maybe you're in a mud situation for a while that's all standard operating
procedure this person wants to take their spa over the top and beat the shit out of their
competitors and travis has i've stalled for long enough go trap i've got it thank you every other
every other spa right every other spa thank you pampers yeah pampers here right they they treat
you like a little baby who needs a good rub down oh you need facial wrap right not this spa this
spa is fucking hardcore you got people yelling at you like you massage rocks yeah they like you
have to like slide down i don't know like sandpaper takes fully at your skin it's a really
it is not a relaxing experience at all when you said this spa rocks i wish you had stopped because
that painted such a beautiful picture in my mind of travis mcelroy's rock and roll spa
which is a great name for a business so much better than tony keese i love this public restaurant
um that i think we could have a lot of fun with it like maybe we just have like a lot of you know
heavy shredding taking place in the background while people assail you with sandpaper and
rolling pins but in a way that still feels good at the end of the day but you're you're also
listening to pantera here's what we're gonna call it we're gonna call it dick's last spa and resort
and it's gonna be that's very good by the way take a moment to let it sink in because it's like
really good and that's all that i had for that great great because dick's last spa and resort
do you understand now yeah i have another one i have another idea here this is my idea um take
a lap take a lap justin anyone who's ever been to a spa knows that there's always a moment where
they like leave you alone in a room or like set something down in front of you and you have a
moment where like what what am i supposed to do but you're afraid to ask but then after that comes
a nice relaxing experience but what if the whole spa was just built to confuse you into relaxation
okay okay and so like you walk into a room they hand you a plunger and say i'll be back when
you're ready and leave and the room is completely empty right and you're just left to figure and
they never come back you walk in there's a table there and the room is dark and they say i okay so
uh any trouble areas oh your neck and shoulders okay you work at a desk you seem tense all right
um so go ahead and lay down we'll get started uh go ahead and undress to my level of comfort
good luck goodbye they take you into a walk-in closet and say dress more to your level of
comfort and then leave and you're like is that two more jackets where where am i at with this
if we really are looking to improve the spa process i wish they would just say
get take off your all of the clothes and get on the table because the get it out
dress to dress to your level of comfort is is a very kind way of saying like
oh you're gonna do naked okay i got i got i got a massage when i was like 22 and they said that
and left the room and i was like i honestly had not even thought about that part of the equation
and huge anxiety and so i just thought like does that mean underwear it probably means
underwear it didn't mean underwear i guessed wrong i made an incorrect guess i think we have found
an easy way to to improve your spa is just directly clarify you should be like multiple
posted signage exactly how much you should undress this is the correct one card of each spa
like if you move into this room and you haven't redressed from the last room bad bad job robe
you're fine that's fine this is robe comfort here wait outside your competitors and as people leave
offer them a massage and if they let you then just start loudly and now it's like hey this
guy just left this spa and he's letting me massage he must not have done a very good job
because i i wouldn't want that so you stand outside el haji to try to relax some more and if you can
then then they must have been relaxed must have been very good like must not have been a very good
massage i got a massage about a month ago i was feeling extremely stressed out i thought i'm gonna
treat myself i went in i literally slept through the whole fucking thing like is that level of
pressure good yeah it's good gone out done out for an hour i slept through the whole thing and
so like i think that a good sort of new process would just be if they see you i'd snore so i they
definitely knew maybe a little pinch a little courtesy pinch right right in the you know the
armpit fat just get in there and just say like hey sorry you were snoring and i don't want you
to miss a thing because you paid a lot of money for this and it's supposed to be nice i have a
tendency um if anyone ever asked me like a question about how much pressure i could take i am a monster
and will say 10 when that's not true and so like i got this massage at the moment was like one to
10 and i was like 10 and it was it hurts so bad it hurts so much but if you say something it'll
drop i couldn't say three i couldn't say it and it was always like just as i was about to say like
no you know what no uncle uncle you win like she wouldn't move to another spot and so it's just like
by the end of that like half hour or whatever 60 minutes it was i was just i was in i my whole body
was a night i walked out of there like a fucking pretzel because i was so i was so stressed out
from my massage because i was um too terrible a person to say like oh you know actually let's go
to like the six like which i say now to you yeah and it's like the most normal thing speaking of
anxiety uh i got a couples massage with my wife one time uh years ago before we had children and
when we arrived for a massage there was a male masseuse and a woman masseuse and we were asked
in the moment to sort of pick who we want to do a quick draft and the fucking calculations that i
had to go through the kobayashi maru of that oh it's it's impossible there's nothing there's no
option for me there i like i'll rub myself and you both rub her i think is where i ended up to be
clear where you're saying that because like you don't want to come off as a homophobic but you
also homophobic but i also don't want to come off as like oh hello yeah absolutely and i don't want
to come off as like there's just no right answer i guess is what i'm saying there's no way this
ahead of time to look at a person and say i would like to pay you to touch me it's one thing if i
walk into a room and they're the only brother person there massage therapy is a legit very good
very helpful thing it's a very good contribution to society it's it's i i understand what you're
saying in what i'm saying is it's a challenge if i walk into a room and there's one other person
there i know where we stand but if i walk into room and pick someone from a lineup that person
knows i picked them over somebody else and that feels weird to me and also the other person is
like so not me all right cool i'm super good at this what we're touching on is it's a very intimate
thing i think in the massages is it i think because it's it's another person uh rubbing you
all all over and it shouldn't be sexualized and i'm not saying i'm not introducing sexuality into
it whatsoever i think it's a very intimate thing and this decision should not be in my hands it
should just be the situation that i find myself in yeah i'm perfectly happy either way perfect
i have to make the choice perfect spa over the top better than competitors you don't make that call
you show up the massage is one thousand dollars and but you don't get to pick and they tell you
just get nude and they pinch you if you fall asleep and then also they say go ahead and get
dressed naked and lie down and it'll be totally great and you lie down and you feel hands on your
back perfect amount of pressure every time and you're like whoa and you sort of get the inkling
that this was not the person that walked me into the room and then you feel sort of somebody get
leaning down close to you and then you hear let me sail let me sail let the orinoco flow and it
is inya they just have inya to do it and you get the live performance right there it's not coming
through it's not coming through any sort of loudspeaker situation it's really her and it's
only time and it's right there and it's that's why it's a thousand dollars okay here's all right
here's in the same thing pinch the dress signs but the massage is is a hundred thousand dollars
oh god and when you walk in this the first thing you do is they take a snip of your hair
and that's three months before and then when you walk in you lay down on the table and you feel
hands they're strong but familiar and you look up it's you they've cloned you and
and give it into a a sort of massage drone the year is 2178 yeah and they they've cloned you
and you start to say like i'm tenso and they're like i know i know i was tense there too three
months ago i remember now that is going i'm gonna go ahead and say this is a great premise for a
sci-fi novel but at the end of that session you do have to murder them with your own hands because
there can't be two of you walking around or it's gonna be a there's gonna be a lot of pivots is
what i was gonna say is there's gonna be oh well no i am justin and i i am justin and i paid one
hundred thousand dollars for the massage i'm going to go listen to the most beautiful classical music
composition okay so you're the drone then right okay all right i'm not going to go listen to
the most beautiful chopin piece i will go listen to jimmy buffett is his name and i love him and
all of his songs jimmy buffett island music i love jamie buffett you're so you're the drone
then and where's justin's body ah shoot we got another one so you know what you're just gonna
drive yourself home yes i have eaten the keys and i am prepared to operate a motor i'm prepared to
interface with the takoma all right so you're the drone then oh all right and you murdered them
somebody called somebody calling the fucking rub runner because we got ourselves another one nice
um i think the most relaxing thing you could do in a massage is like the person comes in and like
they ask you how much and you're like it's perfectly rude it's fine it's fine then during
the massage you lean down and you say it's a hundred thousand dollars and you feel them tense
up and the 30 seconds later you say but i'm gonna give you a discount it's gonna be 20 bucks that
would be the most relaxing moment of my life to suddenly find out relaxing yeah right like i can't
afford that i can't afford that i'm walking on sunshine it's not just that you say it's a hundred
thousand dollars and you instantly see where all the knots are when their body tenses up that's
where you carry good and it's in you telling you so like that's that's it's a it's not the
worst way to find out that you are now completely financially destitute uh folks that is gonna do
it for us this week thank you so i hope we didn't stigmatize massage in any way i can't stress
enough i love it and i'm not i i wasn't trying to say it's weird and sexual i'm saying is wonderful
i just don't like i never liked being the captain of a of a team in in sports either to like say
like you but not you but you i don't like it's an it's an into it's an intimate thing i think when
you struggle with anxiety and just like talking to somebody then it's this introduces a few
sort of things that are a little bit challenging to to get get to deal with but it's good uh it's
good if you uh have any fun stories in your massage therapist or we got anything wrong or
you just want to share i would love to start checking out a massage therapy more regularly
because i think it's fascinating uh i wanted to say we are going to be doing a we added a show
in chicago um it's going to be thursday november 16th at 7 p.m at the chicago theater um we don't
currently have a link to it on our tour page but traps is going to do that that i will do it before
this yeah before this comes out um so you can go to mcroyshows.com for tours and uh there are plenty
of good seats available for that one so uh we would love it if you would come out and hang with
us uh because uh that will be a fun show i think it's our first one of the the tour so we're gonna
be all fresh all fresh and ready for you uh but there's great seats available and all the tickets
are 35 bucks so come on out and if you already bought tickets uh to see us on the next day buy
them again the show yeah completely different um come on you've given people enough of a chance at
this point to buy tickets i think if you want to come we would love to uh to have you there so uh
come on out and see us we would love to see you i just want to say i had a great time in new york
comic con this past weekend if i had to see you great if i didn't i'm sorry maybe next time um
but i also want to say i had a great time hanging out with the folks that i'll be hanging out with
at the jonathan colton cruise this year and if you've never been like i've never been i think
you should maybe check it out and consider coming you can find out all the details jococruise.com
j-o-c-o cruise.com they were telling me about it this weekend and like i'm super psyched uh i hope
y'all can come hang out on a boat for a week and like freaking party don't ever just say that like
that freaking party cruise.com i want to thank john roderick in the long winters for the use
of our theme song it's a departure off the album putting the days to bed it's a very good album go
ahead and get it ready for winter because it's a good little winter album and a good fog and you
know what it's a good summer and spring album also and big thanks to maximum fun for having
us on the network you can go to maximumfund.org and check out all the great podcasts there shows
like lady to lady uh judge john hodgeman uh the greatest generation uh there's a new one called
heat rocks heat rocks uh that's that's really cool if you want especially if you're somebody
like me who's old and uh doesn't find out about uh new music anymore because you're old and you
don't encounter it uh heat rocks is a really fun show where oliver wang and morgan roads have a
guest on and just have them tell them what their their heat rock is just their their jam and then
they talk about that jam and play lots of other tunes and it's uh it's really cool so check check
that one out um also quick plug for my in-laws started a new podcast called still waiting for
guffman about community theater is a very good name for a podcast and you can find it on itunes
wherever fine podcasts are sold and if you like community theater i think you're gonna think
it's really cute and fun and and cute and fun so check it totally out and also you can go to
mcroyshows.com and check out all of our shit um do y'all want that that final yeah finally
yahoo was sent in by the delivery man seth carlson thank you seth it's yahoo answers user
yeah it's me who asks how do i join the japanese mafia also known as the jacuzzi my name is justin
mcroy i'm travis mcroy that made me so happy i couldn't even laugh this has been my brother
he kissed her dad's square on the lips i now just only want to talk about a honda mafia please
too late for the show over too late
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
i love it oh man every time well i hope that you're enjoying this podcast you're listening
to as much as we are pretending to but anyway why not listen to another podcast too it's called the
flop house and on our podcast uh we have recently watched a movie often a bad movie and we review
it on our podcast but mainly talk about other stuff and i don't know hang out it's all about
hanging out feeling like you're being with your best friends who are your best friends us three
dan mccoy emmy award-winning writer for the daily show stewart wellington owner of the best bar in
brooklyn hinterlands and elliot kaylen former emmy winning head writer for the daily show with john
stewart former head writer of mystery science theater 3000 the return uh so many things author
of the upcoming children's book all right that's enough the elliot's credits just go on and on
yeah but if you like the idea of listening to three funny guys talk about bad movies then
why not come over and listen to the flop house it's uh available at maximum fun.org
or wherever fine podcasts are found so get out of here