that's basically what wrestling is I know you don't watch it but hello
everybody and welcome my brother my brother me and advice show for the
modern era like the Chilean miners we've emerged we've emerged to join you Austin
yet again I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy I'm your middles brother Travis
McElroy and I'm your sweet baby brother 30 under 30 media luminary that can't
take it away Griffin McElroy
all right Austin we talked about this a lot and we just have one question for
you why are you missing Twin Peaks why are you here why are you here we have
none of you had shown up we could we could be watching Twin Peaks yeah I
would have been it would have been weird as we were watching the tickets sell for
this if it was just like still zero tickets sold well Twin Peaks is on that
night yeah we got that going for us I wanted them to buy the tickets but then
does not come I wanted their money when it rained really hard I was like so
we've been watching of course so we have some updates and plot points to just
fill you in on first first shot of course is Deputy Andy and he steps on
his own wiener and falls in a big garbage can I as as he does shot shot
number two and we will go shopper shot shot number two Kyle McLaughlin as
agent delcuber slow burns you say Doug Cooper Doug Cooper well it's his twin
brother oh sorry he just does a slow burn to the camera and just says fuck
and it's real real slow though and I know you're wondering like right after
the scene where Andy steps on his wiener and falls in a big garbage that's David
Lynch y'all that's how he did that's how he do shot three this time it's log man
hmm different now there's a man with the log I don't know it's just a big man
made of logs it's and he's got a psychic log girl and it's very different it's a
superhero thing David Lynch he's the master you gotta give him that shot for
Laura Palmer's back what and she's fine
I never explained I said to silence my phone and while I was doing that I got a
notification from my calorie counting app that was like hey you haven't logged
your dinner today and it made me realize that we had Lucy's fried chicken for
brunch and then we had fly right fried chicken for dinner we're gonna die yeah
so when I put that into the calorie app I'm gonna get like a notification that's
just like man you're not gonna try why do I have to be here so this is a this
is a weird question does anybody not listen to our show before okay cool and
you're weirdly excited so what we do on the shows we take questions from real
people just like yourselves and we turn them alchemy like into wisdom and we're
gonna start doing that well in a second after Travis interrupts apparently the
last third of the show we will also take questions from the audience yes but
there is one rule and that one rule is no bum sorry to the six of you who said
you hadn't heard the show earlier that must have been really scary for you yeah
the audience is gonna be less scary they promise so here's the first question
when my girlfriend wears a backpack she leaves it completely unzipped we live in
a city and I think someone will eventually just reach in and take
whatever is in there when I've addressed this with her she's responded with it's
easier to get things out when it's unzipped or don't tell me how to live
my best life how can I convince her to zip up her backpack or am I in the wrong
that's from debated in DC I've never are you here hey is she here and did she
bring a backpack all right all right she is here no backpack I've never
everybody I think who's listening to the show knows sort of my stance on taking
things but that said I was in a production of Oliver and you played I
played Oliver and I did he was I did I did pick a pocket or two it's a song I
remember that but I don't do that you give me a little bit of where is love
do you think is flawless cockney still it's really good that's really nice
Griffin but I don't do that shit in real life I just do it at babies are us and
stuff anyway but if I saw a backpack unzipped I couldn't help it just like I'd
assume it was one of those like bait cam things yeah but then an army vet saw
that her backpack was in there and you'll never believe oh shit John
Quinone steps out of the backpack like no tip to be fair to your girlfriend in
regards to the it's easier to get thing out of it that is true it's true
everyone yeah oh thank you oh it's like when you see those books outside of a
bookstore that are like for sale for like a dollar and it's like oh they want
you to take these yeah these are to be stolen there's no one standing outside
with those books those books are free if you bring them inside to pay for them
their reaction is all right maybe this is sort of a self-fulfilling prophecy
where if something is in there and she's willing to let it just sort of fall out
yeah I just sort of flop out of there because it's open she doesn't care if it
gets so yeah I had said life-changing tidying up
is it smart joy no put it in my back back then yeah okay I don't really play
Yu-Gi-Oh anymore I'll just put these cards in my backpack my dump bag oh how
is your girlfriend or person that is here I guess I could just address your
so much more I'm looking into darkness how are you wearing a backpack that
having it unzipped makes it easier for you to get in it oh yeah notice kangaroo
style or regular it's one strap okay so it's a it's like a cool message like
spin it around like a bass guitar yeah it's like a Yu-Gi-Oh holster at that
point you just have a bandolier of shit you don't care about what if this guy
who vetted zippers came back to life and you were the first person he saw
think about that think about my children really you didn't well I but you know
how the teeth kind of go wait has everybody forgotten does no one
remember how to damn you Charles velcro
do you guys want to Yahoo do you want to Yahoo yeah cool well this one is sent in
by level 9,000 Yaja Juju Davenport thank you drew oh it sounds like boo no it's a
true thing it's asked by Yahoo answers user anonymous we'll call them sea lion
oh there was a viral video of a sea lion grabbing a child and it popped up in this
Yahoo thing the child's okay the joke plays this sea lion who got a hold of a
computer and I want to hear that fucking story asks how do you stop obsessing and
overcome wanting a pie smashed in your face I get it been there I I fucking get
it yeah sure sometimes you're up late and you're
watching your Turner classic movies like you do and you see like a Stooges or
like a Marxist movie it's dumb and you see like a pie they were also that what
if Groucho every time was like pretend I said something smart about Marxism here
just doesn't know anything about it we'll get that in a post we do a lot of
ADR on our live shows oh shit and so you see them smash the pie and you just
think you get horny yeah no mine is like you you could fall asleep with that pie
like it would be very oh like when you're at the aquarium you see the fish
swimming around you like I just went dunk my head I just want to live it's
refreshing mr. limp it in there you know what I mean I thought it was gonna be a
horny thing for sure we can turn it into that should we make it a horny thing
from this way can we take a hold on it's not an audience it is actually about to
be can you the house that's on for a second I just want to see a quick show
of hands on whether or not this question specifically is a sex thing and please
raise your hand if you think that this person is asking about a sex that's
maybe as 50-50 split I'm as surprised as anybody keep your hands up dirty birds
okay I'm gonna say this though there's a weird okay when they sold you guys your
tickets was there a like question on the website that was like pie stuff and if
you said yes you had to go to the balcony cuz y'all's 100% over there if
you want to fuck pies you go in the skies okay you can turn the lights off
now I'm getting a run by how attractive they are I saw this hysterical movie
once where there was a pie and a young man
and his name I swear to God was stiffy and he did the damn thing to it and they
called it the pie movie or something so can you give me a beat my beat recount
well it opens with stiffy doing the damn thing and I imagine at that point most
of the people just left the theater because they thought it was gonna be a
fun Don McLean thing he did did he do the is that what the Don McLean songs
about I hope so you think people get their noses broken a lot that way with
the pie thing because it seems like you'd be so overzealous about like
finally I got to do this thing I'm always wanted to do that you would slam
it so hard you break that break the nose I mean with like a pecan pie yeah how
many people how many people do you think a year die from pie to the face more
more than you think more than you think how many people do you think died
because someone didn't think about whether to use a hot filling pie or like
a cold cream oh you gotta be careful you'll never get that out
even the song cherry pie is about horny pie stuff for is it a simile just about
pies it's a cherry pie smash it in my face in my mouth and eyes pretty good
pretty good it's hot stick is sweet gonna smash it with my feet oh no wait
you you've gone astray where now they should have another one called very
weird out hey listen I didn't mean to yuck any yums there if you're into
what's up copy with you I know there's no judgment here it must be a hard world
out there and I'm here for you okay but nobody else is here's another question I
work in a middle school and use a room that is shared by several other
employees sometimes I have to leave my materials in there but usually it's safe
however my favorite pin which has a quote on it from the hit Broadway
musical Hamilton Hamilton went missing I assumed a student had taken it or thrown
it away but later that week I saw my boss using my Hamilton pin how can I
give it back without seeming like a dick and that's from missing musical
merchandise kill him somebody says Wow whoa it's a super musical but and I'm
now worried that like tomorrow this boss is gonna end up dead for completely
unrelated reasons the charming boys on stage said not to kill anybody don't
kill him if you're a reporter that's the story okay everybody tweet that out are
you here a person who had their pencil on yes that was actually sorry that was
actually a wailing cry of sadness they're here and they're having their
soul ripped from their body by a mystical gem
so just did a fatality on somebody in our fucking audience I mean let me ask
you this well what Hamilton do he would write his way out with his own fucking
pin that he would go get back from this person you could do that you go to him
be like hey I I'm gonna write my way out but there's one thing all right don't
have a pen help me out oh I solved it go to them see the pen note the pen say to
them oh you into Hamilton then the trap is set yeah cuz then they'll have to be
like yeah so much that I got a pen and lie or to and if they do that then you
gotta ask for what lyrics favorite song like their favorite bit from it like uh
mr. president huff huff my shorts if you think I couldn't even do one like fake
bar of a yeah but what if it turns out they aren't also just a super big like
I mean odds are they're probably a pretty big a little niche number that
only this works but no if they're like yeah and they just do word-for-word
start to finish the whole musical it's like okay keep it you in here's a fun
here's a funny suggestion for a comedy podcast go to them and say that's my pen
I like it I paid money for that and I'd like it back it's mine I bought mine pin
and I'd like it back why don't you people ever try that before you come to
us it's just like maybe they did maybe they went the box like that's my beddy
wait no no I don't think so I have to go to write an email yeah you're like I'm
taking this to a higher court I'm assuming your boss is in here by the
way cuz we'd sort that shit out right quick yeah wait are you here and you're
somebody's boss and you might have stolen a Hamilton fan because it might
be about you here's another yahoo this one was
sent in by Zoe Kinski Zoe you here so I like a hundred people just yelled Zoe
where are you are you here yeah thank you Zoe for all of your years of hard
work Zoe said in like 300 awesome yahoo's and this is one of them thank
you Zoe it's from yahoo answers user Mary Lynn who asks should I add my dad
on Xbox that's the funny part for a while my dad has been asking me to add
him on Xbox I want to but my username is keeping me from adding him it's no wait
wait wait wait time out I know what it is um what are you thinking it is right
now cuz like I've seen some things on an Xbox user name so okay go ahead Griffin
it's kiss my ammo and personally I think it's too close to kiss my ass but they
put asterisks in I do love that sentence because they say it like they're
reviewing someone else's if you ask me it's too close to kiss my ass also I
like to putting a link in my youtube page in my bio for my friends to see but
I don't want my dad to view any of my videos because I cuss in a few of them
nice how about how fucking great my dad is Mike everybody this is Todd I'm back
again to tell you how fucking cool my dad is that's very touching time I'd
prefer to show you how to take down Oryx in two cycles and my dad's such a cool
bastard what just got a new iPhone 7 for my fucking awesome day piss yes he says
the best shit well Todd like like rate and subscribe and
remember don't show my dad I wish my dad would watch my youtube videos you're
really looking that level of support gift horse in the mouth because I would
love to have that level of support where my dad which watched my youtubes I try
to do it a lot like hey no it's like a food review quiz show we were getting
from sheets and he's like I don't get it yeah and I'm like yeah that no I watched
Jim Carrey movies then I talked about him sometimes not as big a response for
that thank you correct um gosh how do we help kiss my this is why I don't cuss in
any of my videos case my dad sees them you know the part about this that they
don't give information on that I really want is how they deflect their dad's
requests up till now yeah hey could you have me on xbox can you just fill your
channel of videos about how cool your dad is so he won't get to the other ones
with first words or by the time he does he's like I'll let these slide I really
appreciate all the nice things you said we're okay this one video that's like
Jeff comma my dad's so cool has 1.8 million views so I've made I've
personally made forty three hundred dollars off this video a thank you son
you can say piss as much as you want but just that one only piss Griffin you
getting any of the yahoos go ahead I bet now hold on I just want to know why
we don't usually do them back to back there's a thing maybe no no just go
ahead and tell me if you have any other yahoos I just I just was curious if you
had any other one I don't make up a sad lip on the spot no yeah okay Griffin go
ahead and give me a yahoo but this is a serious one it's really sorry I
interrupted the mic had static can we get somebody to look at that okay so
this is a really who is sad it's like a sad and welcome the Munch Squad it's a
podcast within a podcast
the headline of this USA Today story and I'm putting USA Today on blast on this
one too it's no you're not at Panera McDonald's introduces new artisanal
sandwiches whoa that is the most buckwild headline for so many different
okay try trying something new huh well fuck you fuck you McDonald's yeah no
you're not Panera what they're saying is that you could eat a sandwich at
McDonald's and be tricked into thinking you're at Panera which is like if that's
all I thought you said no you're not Panera you know you're not at Panera
okay I don't think you hit that at enough that's um hey if that's your
range that's a pretty wild range of thing I mean it's no Panera it's
McDonald's but it's no Panera and that would also imply that you walked in just
like blinders on did not look at any surroundings ordered sandwich hey and
they're like wait wait what a there's a big M is this my Panera folks here's a
story the Panera clown Pinero he's got the balloons for the children folks the
golden arches are going artisanal that's the head that's the lead from USA Today
McDonald's introduced three new sandwiches on May 1st and the menu
items are a big leap from the Big Mac nice nice pull it sir the sandwiches
pico guacamole sweet BBQ bacon and maple Dijon sorry is that one sandwich no
that would be good it's the first sandwich a fucking mess you could get it
with peak there's three varietals like that and they come with you can get with
buttermilk crispy chicken 100% beef quarter-pound patty or artisanal grilled
chicken or the trio marks the chain's nationwide launch of its signature
crafted recipes long you motherfuckers can put words like that together however
many ways you want no one's fooled no one is for artisanal market fret fuck
you like no one is full it's McDonald I saw another story where I was looking
for this one that said that McDonald's pledges to have fresh beef quarter
pounders by the middle of 2018 so we're just gonna spend a year kicking it your
old meat that you've alerted us to those motherfuckers said they're gonna
let us have cage-free eggs by I shit you not 2025 we gotta find them yeah we're
gonna have caged read a cage reacts before the heat death of the universe
that's our pledge to you signed Ronald McDonald fuck you guys quote from Chris
Kempinski he's the president of McDonald's USA signature establishes a
premium range on our menu showcasing high quality burger and chicken products
with more food forward ingredients what hey guys I got a new thing we should try
to think about first and that's food we by the way I should take a quick sidebar
I did get to try these in a test market in Columbus and what the fuck wait no
this is unprecedented we the quote continues from Chris we need to bring
more food news like this in order to appeal to millennial customers who are
seeking who are seeking new taste experiences these days okay there's pico
on one of these sandwiches sorry there's a pico element on one of these bad boys
that is a new experience of McDonald's salsa boy I love being born in the late
80s to early thousands it makes me want McDonald's salsa what the fuck's wrong
with me I can't buy a house but boy what's a McDonald's a salsa CBS
irrationally hates me but that's okay cuz I can numb that pain with my good
McDonald's salsa you know this is the end of the quote and it's I'm pretty
sure it's a threat you should expect us to step up our level of menu innovation
in the u.s. in the years ahead that's coming for you Justin McElroy yeah
that's a fun thing of like to think that I'm gonna spend the next few years
somewhere in my head like I wouldn't when McDonald's steps up their
innovation I'm ready for it because they did warn me that for the years ahead
they're gonna be dipping their toes in and this was a news story published in
USA Today yeah this is a drag this is all I'm quoting directly McDonald's move
is the Panera ization stop of the more down market chain no more for value and
convenience in creative flavor combinations hey USA Today thanks for
the elevator pitch on McDonald's go on and it's cheap too do you think that
that journalist walked into the editor's office and was like I've got an idea for
a story you'll never believe what McDonald's is up to
this is there more fast casual is a stolen market share from the fast food
segment said Jack Russo as senior analyst who covers McDonald's at
Deborah Jones cool job cool job when you see that's a competitor you think well
we can't completely transform who we are but we can steal some pages from their
playbook and then this guy goes into like why they why they can't make them
too good cuz it'd be expensive just like mom's kitchen that's too much money no
you get the weird pico de gallo can I do this other Yahoo yeah this is also
another Zoe Kinski join thank you Zoe
riding so high it's from Yahoo answers user sorry something's gone wrong
ah beans um Brian asks I need help looking cool while waiting at the bus
stop I've noticed that no matter how I stand or what I do there's no real way
to look cool in quotes at a bus stop and not come across as some loser with no
car how can I best convey a sense of coolness while waiting for the bus I've
got it well it's no jokes allowed now this is the solution when the bus shows
up you just go nah and leave pretty good not only is that cool cuz it is it's
awesome a serious what's that guy's deal but then you're back again the next day
will he get on this time pretty soon you're a local legend yeah guy who
never gets to work I wanted to go the other way with it which is just like
when it's pulling up you just be like oh there's my bus and they're like oh yeah
me too we're waiting at this bus stop and you say no no no you don't understand
that's my bus and you walk in you're like what's up people on my bus this is
my chain thing I'm allowed to pull it as much as I want are you enjoying my bus
did you fire off an air horn when the bus gets closed and then when the bus
stops just look at everybody there and say you're welcome they weren't gonna
stop and then they stopped for me maybe this is how sign dancers got started
okay and somebody was just like on a corner waiting for a bus and they're
like I don't look cool enough right now
and the fucking Little Caesars saw that was like hey hey you want $20 Raven I
didn't realize you'd trained I don't like to brag Julio Julio oh sorry no no
orange Julius I did was a side note you could you could sketch hell yes hell
yeah you could bus comes by I did you want to get on now I'm good shades and
then you when they're pulling away you grab the back of the bus flip your
skateboard out yeah get ready for the ride of your life just such a sex and
tailpipe you can't you can't hold on in such a way that it gives the bus driver
an opportunity like hey back there hey hey you hey chief hey chief could you
let go of my bus chief hey hey trying to drive here chief come on that's not the
way it works I'm going to see your sketching and raise
you teen wolfing you oh good team was a movie about it I hate this about her but
the young man who is also a like in throat that's a werewolf and it runs in
the family and at the end there's a wiener I know there's a wiener at the
end that's there's an extra and he gets his wiener out during the basketball
scenes I don't think that is what I do think that hey there's a wiener in team
you just said I don't think that only happens liar or idiot no it's there's a
wiener in team wall wait what Michael J Fox is a teen wolf and he's about to go
in for a dunk and you look in the background and there's like kids sitting
on the bleachers one of them's just like here's my wiener forever okay I said
don't like don't obviously don't do that like we've been we've all been extras at
some point or other and that's it goes against the whole extra code you don't
see zombies and walking dead just like
Bo Bridges is the dad in that flick right and he's a werewolf too is that
right holy shit guys come on just to be my IMDB here I'm pretty sure it's Bo
Bridges yeah thank you thank you I thought so and I want to make this
observation do you think Bo had a moment when they called him for that role and
thought like do you mean Jeff because my brother Jeff Bridges basically is
already a werewolf like who's a more of a werewolf in Hollywood right now than
Jeff Bridges I don't think Bo Bridges was in Teen Wolf I'm so sorry just whoever
yelled yes it's not your friend in the audience they James Hampton holy shit
the deepest cut thank you so much yeah I know you Google that cuz if you had
that information on your fingertips you would have blasted me with thank you
that's fine I'm googling too we're all googling hey everybody this is Griffin I
just want to pop in here and do a quick money zone sorry that Travis couldn't
make it he was on a plane and Justin couldn't make it cuz we already recorded
the money zone and then my computer crashed I lost it so now I'm doing a
by myself so handle that I want to tell you about our sponsors our first one is
nature box nature box you know at this point they send you snacks that actually
taste great and they're better for you they're made with high-quality
ingredients that are free from artificial colors flavors or sweeteners
so you can feel really great about snacking I enjoy all of the fruit star
gummies and the Big Island pineapple and all the figgy bars are all really great
I'm excited because nature box recently made their service even better because
now you can order as much as you want as often as you want with no minimum
purchase required and you can cancel any time it's simple you just go to nature
box calm and you check out all their snacks they got over a hundred to choose
from and they're always adding new ones and you pick the ones you want and then
you get them in this cool box and right now you can save even more nature box is
offering our fans 50% off your first order when you go to nature box comm
slash my brother that's nature box comm slash my brother and get 50% off your
first order one last time that Earl is nature box comm slash my brother I also
want to tell you about Indochino Indochino is a suit company and their
whole thing is if you put on a suit that wasn't tailored for you you're basically
putting on somebody's suit you go to a some other suit retailer and for all you
know those are we're taking off bodies in the ground they won't tell you that
at the store but I'll tell you that Indochino what they do is you go online
or you can visit one of their showrooms you pick whatever kind of fabric you
want for your suit and then you choose your customizations stuff like lapels or
pleats or jacket linings or whatever and then you submit your measurements and
you place your order and you wait for it to arrive in just a few weeks and you
get a well-tailored suit at an incredible price this week our
listeners can get any premium Indochino suit for just 379 bucks at Indochino
comm when entering my brother at checkout that's 50% off the regular
price for a made-to-measure premium suit and shipping is free that's Indochino
Indochino comm promo code my brother for any premium suit for just 379
bucks and free shipping got some Jumbotron messages this one is for
Travis mine not yours wait they're saying it's theirs not ours you get it
and it's from Elena who says Travis you are hard-working creative caring and
smart I'm so proud of your career as a chef and small business owner and I
can't wait to support you and whatever's next you've been my champion and
everything I've tried struggling nonprofit jobs accounting school and
race to Alaska craziness I love you let's get married on Saturday May 27th
that's this weekend congratulations on your upcoming wedding Travis and Leah
that's so exciting I have another Jumbotron message here and this one's
for Avi tall and it's from Rishi who says one year ago I did the meanest
thing that anyone has done on my bim-bam and made you famous I cannot surpass
myself but I can enshrine my victory like a mosquito trapped in amber I've
preserved your humiliation for the ages all are welcome to www.coldplaycrybaby.com
may the light of your burning shame forever illuminate our common
future this is absolutely brutal this is an orbital slam dunk from space just a
thermonuclear burn and I'm uncomfortable being the vehicle for it hey I want to
tell you some good news if you don't live in the u.s. as I don't know the
exact list of countries but I know the UK and Canada and I believe Australia
you can now pick up the bim-bam TV show it is up on iTunes in those regions you
can go to see so's landing page on iTunes or just search my brother my
brother me and then don't click the podcast just click the very next thing
and you can watch all six episodes of our TV show and I hope you really like
it and thank you for sort of demanding that this happened we had absolutely no
control over this happening but we are excited that so many more people will
get to listen to it or watch it that's right there's pictures I also want to
thank the paramount for having us this weekend and for everybody who came out
to the live shows in Austin we had a great time and it means a lot we're
gonna get back to the show now so have a good have a good time bye I'm this and
I'm Teresa and we host the weekly comedy podcast one bad mother we celebrate our
moments of parenting genius as well as our failures just like we're gonna have
hot dogs yeah I just like smashes that thing right on my chest and then I'm
just crying in the middle of like kids space while people are like literally
dancing with their children parenting can be sad and painfully funny at the
same time so join us each week as we admit that this is hard but we're
getting really good at it find us at maximum fun org or wherever you download
podcasts here's another question oh I like this question I'm currently
recovering from a wrist injury and have to wear a race did you hear I said what
you say sure get it I often get asked what happened and almost as often that
question is followed up with saying a variation of too much jerking off
we did it everybody we did it Mike Mike that's all right that's our Oscar my
honey pie it's finally paid off does it really fucking say that in the question
yeah people think it's funny it was funny I mean all due respect if you're
here it was funny but it's getting old which I understand what are some witty
responses to this annoyingly consistent joke and that's from
that's from no I didn't break my wrist for masturbation is the name are you
here cool what if the next time someone's like from jerking it you just
went yeah yeah it's a medical condition but we can talk about it if you want
please have you tried it it's all it's pretty good come take a journey with me
into my priapism we'll just discuss it at length and if you know what I mean oh
man I can't sorry if you had to sit next to that guy by the way quite listen
anything funny let us know okay the pie question it must have gotten pretty
rough um oh man I feel so fucking bad for the bad joke I did what do you say
what if he does that jerking what yeah make describe in detail what master
now what's Matt what a matter station you station mystic elation master case
what would that even do yeah why wait where the P comes out excuse me you must
be joking I was assumed since you can't tickle yourself that you could okay all
right all right there it is sounds weird to me but okay
important if true
that episode of Seinfeld suddenly makes so much more sense so they weren't
actually masters of any okay okay cuz I was wondering where the domain was so
imagine my well can we end of this show 20 minutes early okay no somebody else
of course not all right can I can I get I want to do the one I know I did tell
you one of the yahoo's and it was this was another level 9,000 Yajra drew
Davenport thank you true it is sadly germane yahoo answers user VA 2906 asks
what would it be like if humans were in a constant state of orgasm would it even
be possible to drive a car
somebody's yelling yes yes so I'm thinking you would actually probably
just establish that was your new baseline right like you would get you
eventually would you get used to it it's good to see you hey hey Frank you
ready go to sleep no are you hungry yeah this is a great point why did the car
question is so irrelevant it's like do you want to go to the movies and see
avatar not at all I'm good that's and that's what that bands all about that's
what ten roof rusted means what is it no it does it means I'm always orgasmic
wow that's some deep code they've got going on there you if we would have
never invented anything we wouldn't have invented the car certainly certainly not
no we wouldn't have invented it would have been like hey Carl I found out if
you rubbed some wood together it gets real hot I don't give a shit I'm good
I'm fine no it's cool we can make fire and cook our meat so we stop getting so
sick sounds like a lot of to me we all diet 17 it's fine that's fine it's 17
good ones okay wait what I've been this reverse mirror world when humans
orgasm was the only time they had like a moment's peace let's see it just be
like what a great sandwich and then somebody be like I just I have to do
this one before we get the audience questions I'm sorry I live by I live by
a locally run donut shop one morning there's a little bit long one but hang
in there one morning I went to get donuts from a boyfriend and my roommate
who I lovingly referred to as my boys when I placed my order the drive-thru
window I told the owner slash cashier I was getting donuts for my boys when she
asked me how old my boys were I I panicked and told her they were five and
seven years old my angels my sweet my little scamps we then proceeded to have
a detailed discussion about my assumed children no to whom I pointed names and
local elementary schools to make things worse I drive a two-seater smart car she
asked me how I managed to fit my kids in there to which I answered oh I have
another car that I use just for them special boy car this isn't my boy this
is my donut car I have a boy car for the boy times even worse she gave me a bag
of free donut holes for your little boys
bet those tasted good brothers how do I fix the situation in my guild about
eating those donut holes of shame that's from doughnut asked me about my kids in
Austin Texas
cheering for a city that has this person in it yeah you fucking champion how good
were those don't listen holes what they were really good yeah don't take in I
see you then don't a holes earned I've always said that hey you have to pack
your bags and move away yeah sorry we don't employ that one much but no no you
gotta move sorry or next time come in a different car bigger car with your
boyfriend and your roommate and introduce them as your boys don't blink
an eye yeah don't these are my boys Toddlin and Dugmer and there's whatever
you said there now you can probably use their real names I think maybe well
they're not little boy names oh yeah what names yeah I know I need to know
everything what names when you're on the spot did you give them just say the real
names my sweet ones my sweet boys Oliver and Tony they also take care of
protection racket for me the good news is she fucking knew you were lying for
sure they were pity holes yeah this poor sad person what do you say we do some
audience questions we're gonna call on folks I know we just put mics out but
don't it's not a TED talk please don't line up behind them I'll call out from
the left side okay I see somebody at the end pointing to
themselves yes you yes in the hoodie yes yes you've done it hi what's your
name hi Alexa I work remotely and we have lots of conference calls with
people that I don't interface with mm-hmm some of them are older and don't
use normal terminology and one of the women on my team refers to people who
are not very intelligent as who has
so refers to dumb people as who house yeah like this who ha okay I'm so
delighted right now is there a question are you just like my co-workers so cool
no I feel obligated to say something hey look in that deep dark truthful mirror
do you really feel obligated to say something because if you did wouldn't be
asking us yeah look at me right now you don't do you what would you say that's
a really delicate question yeah it is a really delicate request yeah I think
that we live in a world where sometimes joy can be hard to come by and if you
if you ruin this font of pure light for people you have to live with that for
all of your days is what I think this is an important person this means something
if you work with a person who says things like who has or erroneously uses
the term bust a nut which we've talked about before and you change them and
that you've taken something from me you know cuz I might run into that person at
Trader Joe's one day and literally bump into them and they're like hey watch out
you who are maybe so angry I'm gonna bust a nut and I'm like thank you does
that fix everything just right just ride the wave just enjoy it it's great keep a
tally every time it happens yeah record or secretly thank you all right let's
try this side of the room okay uh two two hands yes come on up to the
microphone not here go on back I guess hi hi hi what's your name hi Andrew so
my wife and I are here celebrating our five-year anniversary
what's your what's your wife's name Alexandria Alexandria hi hey so we got
married five years ago but we met in high school we've been together 11 and a
half years okay and years and so like I feel like I have to justify when I'm I'm
a younger person and so people are like oh that's so sweet you've been together
five years it's like well actually yeah we've been together 11 years because we
met yeah no it counts it's a big thing sure you know how can I kind of shorten
that say it's seven years yes what the difference that's a great point Justin
you just fucking let we're married a hundred years what yeah I've been
buttoned and I'm the oldest person on earth yeah or two Benjamin buttons
aren't you glad we found each other you didn't see that in the movie he didn't
even look for another Benjamin button he was like I found a non button this will
be sad at the end I bet
are you a button by the way your bedroom button you are you have to tell
legally it's a trap just say you've been together for 11 years I if you said that
I wouldn't be like well married or dating how long have you actually been
like you know in love like 10 years Jesus trash I'm just saying where do you
start the cow no no Travis has a good point was it like hollow and shitty for
a year or two there been a year in the middle where things were like and where
you're like don't count it as one of the years kind of one foot in one foot sort
of back in the cut a little bit where you can just kind of not really no no
so I think your king was bad yeah hey listen relationships are hard you've
kept on working for a long time longer than anybody rightfully should be able
to do that you should be proud of yourselves yes of you congratulations
thank you yes wear it with honor thank you yes I'm going to say glasses stripy
yes yes glasses stripy it's the most we've ever boiled down a human essence
I'm the new kid in town glasses stripy
my husband's family's from Arizona okay and we've been together not as much of
a response from that we've been together five years now and his mom refers to a
lot of things that's who has not not correctly so here cause cult she calls
kolaches kolach keys and San Jacinto San Jacinto okay and I've done those those
things in the last three days go on I really really want to correct her but he
says just let it go yeah I don't know if I should just let it go as she's my
mother yeah I think she's doing it on purpose
oh yeah our play thank you Travis that is of course the
correct answer yeah you're under psychic assault making words sound funny is
funny it's a thing that you do to entertain yourself she knows it's
collages she's the person who's been in the world for a number of years but she
says kolach keys cuz why not we're all gonna die someday so say shit wrong I
saw that word for the first time on a sign yesterday so maybe not everybody
is it college comes what now keep telling me I'm sure I'll get it right
here in a second I just call them what they are super banging pigs in a blanket
sounds good no listen there's nothing to be game here I mean there's like
literally nothing to begin just like let it slide cuz there you it is a no-win
scenario for you to try to correct this person just let it happen I know it's
painful but it's not your problem also nothing you have to worry about does
that and that was a neutral one I know I didn't help it was part of the course
okay sorry sorry we'll get a chance time I see somebody wearing a white short
sleeve shirt on the end on the oh wait there's two in the fight there's three
now fuck oh god they're multiplying he mean you might have oh yeah but the
blonde hair yes you've done now hey sorry that got really I didn't realize
how many people wearing white shirts that wanted to ask questions we're
sitting at the end of the aisle I would have thought don't worry okay what's your
name I'm Mads hi what's up okay so I work at a summer camp and I'm gonna be
actually I leave on Thursday for like three months oh sure goodbye yeah so
last summer I had to go by my last name it's kind of weird last name and a bunch
of the younger kids like the youngest kids we get are like six or seven or
whatever and they're like stay there for three nights and they all gave me a
really embarrassing nickname because some of like I had another girl on
staff who had the same first name as me so she got first name dibs for some
reason that sucks so all the little kids started calling me Rhino mom whoa what
goes with my last name I don't know it's stupid so I want to be cool this other
girl's not on staff this summer and how do I become how do I rename myself I
want to rebrand yeah how old are these kids again um they range from like six
and seven to like 18 yeah you can tell an 18 year old like don't call me Rhino
mom you're 18 you know empathy at this you wouldn't okay so you're you're cool
good good good good can I tell a quick sidebar real quick one time I was
filling out a job application to be a camp counselor cuz I thought I'd be
pretty good at it a bunch of laughter thanks you hurt my feeling I was filling
it out and I swear to God I hit a point in the application where it said this is
not your opportunity to experiment with growing facial hair and I said fuck this
and I threw it out yeah I don't know how you tell us gotta wear a t-shirt that
says nice to meet you I'm mad and like a rebranding get some marketing in there
yeah hashtag some sort of hashtags hashtags yes those are cute emojis yeah
all the staff members to call me either my first name or my last name so it's
really awkward yeah cuz they'll go like hey everybody to get people's attention
I'll be at the front it'll be like hey cuz no one knows what to say you know
what I think I've been trying this when someone does something or calls me
something I don't like just turn to them and go don't whoa shit yeah Travis
doesn't have a lot of friends but the ones that I do they call me Travis
Travis doesn't have any friends but he has a lot of campers who listen to every
fucking word he says you have to distinguish yourself with a hobby listen
get super good at basketball everyone will call you hoops it worked for me it
could work for you does that help hoops don't fix everything hoops let us do one
more all right thanks thank you all right this cat in the glasses and the
zip up yes stand up it's you you've done it you had another person pointing at
you which doubled your chances that's a strategy for next time keeping in mind
us he's tall too so yeah what's your name I'm Walker hi Walker so I just want
to know what that donut place was Oh fair enough what was that done a place
all right it's a good one all right now we're in it on that note finish thanks
we just yelped to end our show thank you to the paramount hold on I would I will
say if it was miss Johnson's I was gonna narc on you so fucking hard your head
would spin if miss Johnson's ever goes out of business because if you're kid
fraud I will I have a certain set of skills I will find you thank you
everybody go to miss Johnson's on airport after this show and patronize
the fuck out of that place okay all right thank you for listening to our
podcast my brother my brother may thank you to the paramount for having us thank
you paramount this is so I didn't appreciate the lights are on this is a
fucking beautiful building why are we here why are we allowed this is the
first place that we've done a show at that I think I've actually like seen a
bunch of shows at so this is pretty strange for yeah thank you to thank you
to max fun for having us the maximum fun network thank you to saw bones for a
very very good show opening up I was literally backstage eating those
delicious fly right sandwiches like no no no I would also like to say thank you
to our wives yes children so we could do this show thank you Rachel and thank you
Teresa Teresa and Cindy thank you all thank you thank you daddy thank you and
Carol for helping watch watch the babies backstage oh yeah yeah thank you Austin
Texas yeah I am the last time we were in Austin was in 2012 and we had a was
anybody at that show all right if you weren't it was fucking super weird we
had it was basically an empty building that we had to light ourselves we showed
up and nobody was there and there was anybody there and our wives had to sell
eggnog and cookies and well we gave them away actually it was yeah and we strung
up Christmas lights ourselves and there were 200 people and we did two shows
back-to-back and now we're here so I guess thank you to everyone and on earth
Griffin give me that fucking final yahoo this final fucking yahoo is sent in by
level 9,000 y'all true dude having poor thank you drew it's by yajoo answers
user says the Nikki Bella but I'm pretty sure it's not the Nikki Bella she's a
wrestler Nikki Bella asks did the owners of prego spaghetti sauce think of
pregnant women when they came up with anything prego cuz it's short for
pregnant my name is Justin McElroy I'm Travis
McElroy, I'm Griffin McElroy, this has been my brother and my brother, kiss your dad, square on the left!
the dead pilot Society podcast brings you hilarious comedy pilots that were
never made featuring actors like Aubrey Plaza Andy Richter Paul F Tompkins John
Hodgman Adam Scott Molly Shannon busy Phillips Tom Lennon Anna camp Lori
Metcalf Felicia Day Michael Ian Black Adam Savage Paul Shearer Ben Schwartz
Skyler Aston May Whitman Josh Molina Ben Feldman Nicole Byer Jason Ritter Sarah
Chalk Steve Agee Jane Levy Allison Tolman Danielle Nicolette Casey Wilson
Anna Ortiz Lorraine Newman June Diane Raphael Kiernan Shipka Ed Weeks Zach
Knighton Carrie Kenny Silver John Ross Bowie Jamie Denbow Janet Varney
and many more listen at Maximumfun.org iTunes or wherever you download podcasts
Maximumfun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported