Hi everybody, I'm Justin McElroy from my brother my brother and me hi
I'm Griffin McElroy from my brother my brother and me we didn't skip we didn't skip Travis
He working working probably we didn't actually ask him because we figured he's busy. He's always so busy
He's always a busy bee so we got it so caught he's fighting off colony collapse
We've got an unconventional
episode for you this week
Because I'm on the sunny shores of beautiful Tybee Island just outside of Savannah, Georgia
Laugh at the Sun. I'm on a three-day drunk
Cuz it's the weekend. I had no it's not just the weekend. It was
I'm having kind of a hard year
Rough one for Griffin. We're not going to talk about that. We're gonna talk about is that the greatest?
God in air quotes greatest mabim bam moments from the early years
We dipped back into the into the annals, and I went over with a fine-tooth comb and got one
Hilarious hour from our first 13 episodes now. I know what you're thinking weren't those episodes pretty bad
Weren't those episodes bad well. Here's your indication. I took 13 hours and convinced it to one worthwhile hour of material
Some some jewelers. I read this on the internet like that rough gems better than the ones that have been cut down
You know why why cuz cuz then cuz then they can cut it down and really make it their own well
That's what I've done
And I've boiled it down for you
So I hope you'll enjoy this look back at the early years of bim-bam their early weeks of
Bim-bam my brother my brother and me early weeks compilation one colon. It's better than nothing
And
Welcome
Welcome to our show the show is called my brother my brother and me
I'm Justin McElroy. I'm joined by my titular brothers
Great good start everybody
Travis and Griffin this is an advice show for the modern era
Mainly fashion
We take your questions every day every well not every day every week
And we every second real time every set. This is why it's a modern show. It's every
Party this call now now now now now
now
Speaking of questions this one comes from Yahoo
The question is what is the chord progression during the intro of the ABC series Greek?
Scrappy buns Jones
How many times a week should I shampoo my hair? I'm currently on a wash thrice
Shampoo every third wash cycle. Okay, we're gonna get just real talk here
Yeah, you just entered into our wheelhouse
This is it listen this is a matter of some debate for men of dry hair
Let me open up let me open up by saying I didn't know like
this is one of those many many things that I as a
22 year old adult should should know and and incorporate in my life, but I shampoo my hair every time I get
That's why you've got that hair like you have I shouldn't be you're having an awakening guys. It's our first awakening I
I feel like when I don't you're listening to awakenings with Justin Travis
I think I feel like I'm getting dirty like if I don't do it
I feel dirty is the natural oils that your scalp produces makes your hair look look
Think of it from like a caveman era your body biologically wants your hair to look better. It's trying to make your hair look better
It's doing what it can to help you and you like the 3d a rotation a day rotation. I am down now sometimes
What's the problem? You got to get in there on that third day with a real hard scrub or your Scouts gonna go to shit?
When my hair gets longer, and I know I'm running my hands through it a lot and getting that real gross
I'll do it two or two day rotation sir
Yeah, we've interviewed use a lot of products one day you and you got to get away from that feeling
There's one unsolved mystery here
Okay, so you guys obviously know more about this thing than I do but if you don't shampoo your hair
Then how are you supposed to put shampoo in your hair and let the suds run down and then just use those suds as soap
Great question
You're telling me that I shouldn't use soap is what I'm hearing except for every Wednesday and Saturday I
I think that this grooming section. I'm gonna has taken a weird turn where it's like more about
Just had a terrible good life. It's weird. It started out. It's about one thing. That's kind of depressing
I'm as clean as a motherfucker, but I do it in suspect ways
Yeah
Another thing you can do is um
Do you guys you guys remember when you were younger and you go like on a first date with somebody and you'd be in?
The movie theater and it would take you like the entire two hour
Movie to get up the courage to like hold their hand
And so the entire time like your hand is kind of slowly
Yeah, and it's all exciting and scary. What you can do is do that with the stranger sitting next to you
Right and have it like stretch it out for the entire like if you're flying east to west coast
It's like a unit six hour, right?
So just take six hours and very slowly just have this campaign of of just no finger by finger
Just move you'll be so distracted
You'll be so distracted so scared and like maybe maybe
Maybe
You know, maybe that large drill sergeant type sitting in 17 be made us be your special somebody
Right. Yeah, and if not, like even if you get shot down you just your your fights done
Take a chance. You know, I was reading my cosmo like I do
It's what I do and I found some great advice for the ladies
Little something ladies might like from an article tall called 30 things to do with a naked man
Mm-hmm, and this suggestion is find his g-spot
The hint is a guy's prostate the walnut sized gland under his bladder is the
ultimate magic button to push if you want to blow his mind in bed an ultimate magic button to
Analyze it partway through oral sex or intercourse rest two fingers against the swath of skin between his testicles
And they stay the fuck away
You mean taint
You mean it's a do you mean his taint right? It's an efficiency of language issue at this point. You mean his taste using cosmo
Um, please don't tell anyone to do that cosmo
My walnut is a temple and I don't want it doesn't need any insurrectionists
Nuh-uh
What's your walnut? How's everybody's wallet?
Situation today. It's like I it's feeling good the wallet wallets
Fine, I just remember when I went to Bonnaroo and I didn't shower for five days and I got walnut itis
Here's my question what actual situation would that be okay in my god, this is the whoa, whoa
What when I went to see a walnut all adjust about my walnut itis and he checked my walnut like still
Still questionable. Yeah, you know, it's weird about that story Griffin went five days without a shower still shampooed every day. Yeah
I had lots of aquafina which I could you know, hey women my shit up. I don't touch my walnut
Stay away from the walnut. Don't listen to cosmo
Take a chance. This one comes from Yahoo answers user Nikolai. He says or she says no, I think it might be he says
This is under the pregnancy and parenting baby names category
He says can I name my baby girl Justin after Justin Bieber?
Why don't you pick somebody more deserving?
Why don't you pick a more deserving Justin to name your child after someone who's gonna give that kid the sort of
Minute one publicity that a baby starting out in today's fast-paced Twitter based world needs
Maybe name your baby after like a Justin McElroy somebody who's gonna get the name out there
Gonna get that baby's get that baby promoted Justin McElroy Bieber Nikolai. I love it. What about what about Justin?
McElroy Bieber and I'll hyphenate my last name. He'll just have me back. I'm so sorry
I didn't know what I was doing. I'm so so sorry, please baby, baby, please please baby, please baby, baby
one more time
I'll tell you one time Justin. I'm sorry. You shouldn't have said it was it was just a tea. It was just
It was just a boat
It was just a boat at an amusement park and there was there was a calliope in the background
And I was had a belly full of cotton candy. I didn't know what I was doing
I'm sorry
There was there was no line and I just I saw it there in the in the reflection of the streetlamp
And I thought yes, yes
I'm a boat man, but man for life, and I left you I didn't go to see you show and
I'm sorry Biebs. I'm sorry. Why don't you name? Why don't you name your kid Viking Fury?
That would be the best see now I want to use that
Viking Fury
Yeah, this is my son Viking Fury. What's his last name?
Viking his first name is Viking. Sorry about your knee. Sorry about your kneecap. He does
He's two and he's got a little baby axe my first axe. What's up with that beard? He's got going
I don't know. I named him Viking Fury. It really stuck
It's red like a sunrise. Did he just kill that narwhal?
Yeah, he did. He's crazy
Stupid Viking Fury get over here. Somebody honey get the muzzle
Viking Fury is trying to eat mutton
His stomach can't digest he's only six weeks old
Oh mush up some mutton, sweetheart for Viking Fury
Take a chance, but she seems to enjoy going to movies dinner and spending a lot of time with me
But I was too timid to make her mine
I got it
I got a piece of advice from a man some unsolicited advice if you want to if you want to go out with this girl
Stop saying creepy shit like make her mine
Oh
So do you want to go see a movie or should I just make you into a skin suit
Mine possess you for me. I mean for life to own you to have you
I just want to own you and make you mine. I just want to own your body just your body. That's my property
I want to make how do you feel about man-sized jars?
I will poke holes in the top
Twig in there some leaves don't even worry about it. Don't worry about it, but you're mine now
As far as the signs you're looking for
This one comes from Yahoo
answers and I think it's great because
You guys are your professionals at this but the question is who is the founder of acting? I?
Would the subtitle is I would really like to know who is the founder of actor
Any answers, I think it's Aristotle I think Aristotle pretty sure it's Jim Varney
He was Ernest and the dad from Beverly Hillbillies and that coil dog high versatility
I think so. He was the coil dog. Yeah, he was a coil. He's everybody. I didn't know that
Cuz he's a fucking chameleon
It was a chameleon
Were there any answers to that one?
There was one from a guy named theater doc
did he say that what did he say something boring like a poet named Thespis and 534 BC became the first person to play a
part on stage
Barney revolutionized
Perfected it
It's like how the Chinese may have invented fireworks, but I guess the Chinese perfected fireworks. We perfected blowing our hands off
There you go, uh, this one also comes from form spring
Hey guys, just wondering what the word cute means
I hear women use the word in conversation all the time and I am more and more confused about its true meaning
given its multitude of uses
It means chubby
Sorry
But you got a great personality on the great personality
Sorry, they just substitute cute with non-threatening and that's exactly what it means. He's so cute means
He's so non-threatening and by non-threatening it means you you don't you don't know what she means when you she says cute
That's yeah, I'm threatening for you. There's a definition of non-threatening
Hey, hey, um, I got a little piece of advice for you prom king next time you're around
Someone who says cute flip a table just
A table see if they keep calling you cute that was that adorable was that so so cute and then just make love to them
Right there
They will they will not fight
They'll say can we flip the table back over and if they do fights if they do fight just just make them yours
Adam has a problem. I'm rude to us from Gmail
He says my friend doesn't seem to fully grasp the point of the would you rather game?
He puts this question such as would you rather be able to leap over tall buildings or have the ability to hear babies crying anywhere?
Let me just take a tea right here. It's a big tea sack right here and say
Um, that's a terrible power anywhere a newborn is distressed
Days would be like just cause it like from from dusk till dawn wake up to slumber not ever sleep sound of millions of babies
Read it keep reading the question because I like the second one better
Or would you rather be on fire or not be on fire? I
Want to read this guy, how can I teach
Play or is he a lost cause?
Adam I think man. I think you got a jettison that went into the Sun. Yeah
Yes, maybe he's just not allowed to play that game anymore. Maybe not that game maybe another one
Maybe he's really good at checkers be able to breathe
underwater or have Lyme disease
Would you rather
Find a crisp clean
$100 bill or watch an elderly loved one. We push on a flight of stairs
It
Is up to you the choice my friend is yours one for the ages a puzzler for ages
Would you rather have?
Okay a credit card credit card that you never had to pay back. Okay sounds good so far
Or no teeth
Well, okay, I have both they're just just the one one or the other by the other
I
Guess I could get those those metal teeth like the guy from James Bond. There you go. I
Can't I can't decide?
Everyone's favorite sound and the English language is the sound of their own name as a stone fact learn their name
Use it a lot
They're gonna warm up to you pretty quickly and then find out something they're interested in and and ask them about it
Okay, and if you if you don't know what they're interested in use the environment that you're in if you are at a party at
a show at a concert
Reference what is going on around you ask if they're having a good time
Jeffrey how did you get to this concert Jeffrey?
What would you say Jeffrey Jeffrey? What's your favorite Dave Matthews on Jeffrey Jeffrey?
How do you enjoy being the butler for the Fresh Prince of Bel Air Jeffrey Jeff Jeffrey Matthews band?
Yes, what did I do Jeffrey? I just got in Jeffrey Jeffrey. I didn't mean to say that Jeffrey
And then your best friends
Just like that say their name a lot and then at the first time you meet them say hey
Nice to meet you Jeffrey you want to go to a wine tasting with me Jeffrey?
Let's look at houses Jeffrey. It'll be like that movie sideways Jeffrey Jeffrey. Let's go to look at open houses Jeffrey
I bought us matching sweaters Jeffrey Jeffrey. Let's wear these matching sweaters Jeffrey for a wine tasting in the country
Jeffrey hug me Jeffrey come to my via for a weekend Jeffrey
They roll the double else
But as far as the timetable goes don't rush yourself because you don't want to do it when you're not ready and you're not prepared
You don't have the money, but you know, there's no reason to wait
You're not nobody do anything take the leap. Hey, did you ask Jeff? Did you ask Jeffrey if you needed a roommate?
Jeffrey Jeffrey Jeffrey wish to move in together Jeffrey. We've just met Jeffrey, but let's just free
It's a one-bedroom apartment. It's awfully spacious
Jeffrey Jeffrey
Jeffrey I've got a California king bed. I promise we won't touch Jeffrey
Jeffrey will you hold me during the thunderstorms Jeffrey?
Jeffrey it's hailing
Jeffrey the black clouds are rolling in Jeffrey Jeffrey. Let us buy a puppy together Jeffrey Jeffrey. We'll even have Jeffrey Jeffrey
Let's go shopping at the local market Jeffrey to draw Jeffrey
My seven-year-old and I spend a lot of time in the car listening to music while commuting across town to horse her school or mother's house
I'd like to expose her to more artists and songs that I consider insightful and enjoyable, but they use more profanity
At what point is it? Okay to say fuck it and listen and let your kid listen to whatever they want
Now fuck it. I think it's okay to say fuck it after you count to three
Justin could could you perhaps give me?
One two three and fuck it. It's like that just like that
You know what Tommy I think the bigger question is when did you forget what fuck it means?
Like at what like do you do realize that fuck?
It's not like I thought this over and now my response to the situation. My decision is fuck it
Fuck it means like fuck it
I take all the variables into account the only decision I could come to you is fuck it. Fuck it
That's my decision. I checked the bubble box that says fuck it. Thanks to it after weighing all my options
Fuck it
Joseph Joseph Jessup Jessop, Jesse
Final vote
All of them on that all of us like what about what about?
What about Joseph Joseph
Jessup Jessop Jesse the third mega mega
What about mega Jessup
Mega Jessup. Hey, who's that? Who's currently destroying our town? It is mega Jessup
To be fair just how he starts out and then he becomes mega Jessup
Don't make him angry
So I'm accompanying my wife to visit her parents in the coming weeks and while the visit is usually rather painless
The bed we are relegated to is very noisy
Being relative newlyweds. We still engage in the relations
If you know what I mean and was wondering what the etiquette on fooling around in this awkward situation might be Jeff
You ready for the pleasure
Mima mima is literally this this wall is stucco. This wall is completely stucco it anything we do
Listen I want to show you
that our relationship is still as fiery as
Fiery as it was when we started no, no Jeff. No
Jeff no, no, no
No, I'm married Jeff. No
Gross Jeff gross
Jeff is a grown-ass man with grown-ass urges
Just got to get himself sassified and Jeff noisy bed
Adjacent me ma or no Jeff needs to get Jeff needs to get his Jeff off
Jeff if you were if your urge
To get your Jeff off is not so strong
But you have to rent that you can't rent a room at the super 8 away from your meemaw
Then your urge to bed down. It's not so strong that it cannot be resisted
I'm saying learn how to bone down on the quiet by an inflatable mattress and lay that out because that completely
Obviates the whole squeaky bed issue
Maybe carry that around your bag and then lay that down and it makes sweet silent love upon it
Maybe you should maybe you should approach this uh, this problem head-on, right? Here's my plan
Go to your in-laws the day day one
Say listen, I appreciate you having us the bed
You've supplied us with is quite loud and we're afraid that our noise making will be a ruckus
so
What bed might be quieter that you could accommodate this with and also where can I put my oversized duffel bag with the words?
lube bags
Said I put that in did look like some spare room in me ma's abode. Can I put it me?
Was room will she be offended? I will need to access it a regular
Meemaw don't be coy, you know exactly what this oil is used for you old whore you old racist whore
Hey Jeff's me mom
Jake Yunzhi's magic incest Yeah
Moving on that's the username here via gmail
It's a great question. I think it's one might be divisive has a potential to be divisive peeing in the shower
Yeigh or nay honesty time don't say anything. I think we all just need to
We'll go one two, three
and then go so one two three and then you vote okay all right yeah one two two
three yes no yeah you're a traitor so Travis said no and Justin hey I like
it's the most natural thing in the world I want to throw an addendum in there the
way our bathrooms set up I can just open the curtain and the toilets right there
yeah I will do that from time to time because the convenience factor is the
sale that explains why our magazines are always soiled you're office you know
where's room I'm sorry I've ruined our reader readers digests so Justin you're
down with it why not cuz it's grown it's not gross it's basically like you're
peeing on your feet you're not being a feet okay I'm not saying like just
start spinning around and urinating wildly on every vertical surface in your
shower I'm saying fucking aim for the drain and be you're lying that's a good
motivational poster you're lying to yourselves because the two of you are
living in sin and you are embarrassed to admit to each other that you might have
stepped in the one another's urine from time to time that's all I'm saying you're
lying I want to do I want to see a poster where a dad puts his hand on his
son's shoulder and just says son aim for the drain we're not stepping in each
we don't take showers together that's not our style we're not down with magic
incest we take separate showers like grown adults grown ass men I'm gonna say
yeah I'll break thank you thank you yeah I mean this is a drain right there it's
practically a toilet you stand up in to get clean the shower is a toilet you
stand up in to get clean recently the buzz about not having elections in
2012 has gained a lot of momentum it seems to stem from several of Obama's
initiatives and other legislation being introduced that gives Obama some
frightening powers for example cyber legislation gives Obama sole power to
shut down the internet presidential term limits repeal of the 22nd amendment and
the controversial 16,000 armed IRS agents on radio and TV I have heard
several comments about the possibility that we will not have presidential
elections in 2012 when guests to the various show mentioned the elections
and possible turnovers in 2012 several hosts have remarked if we have
elections in 2012 now that Obama is a cyber God he can pretty much take that
out with a wave of his cyber hand if if President Obama President Barack Hussein
Obama shuts down the internet can we keep doing our show oh we can shout yeah
we'll just have to yell really loud so we'll do like live stage versions
yeah exclusively Obama has the power to single-handedly shut down the internet
he has a switch on the underside of the of the desk you can't stand up too quick
oops you can't where's my where's my gmail what is gmail there's that it's a
non-existent entity gmail never happened Craigslist sorry out
yeah shut it down Yahoo answers a font of constant comedy
it's gone now this question itself whoa so not only can he shut down the internet
he erases the internet from time he also has that cyber power you mean sole
power he has that sole power from the cyber legislation held in TechnoCon
there was a cyber bill in Techno Congress that gave him the power to go
back in time and stop events from happening Android of the house can you
pass the oil so I can the 22nd amendment hasn't been repealed it's been raised
derit it's been D D it's been unthought I just say we have just written the
greatest movie ever time-travel president yeah Yahoo answers user rock
just as that spelled our a queue by the way whoa I'm figuring that's how he
prefers it to be pronounced hey need a film not anything like the
lake house or that sort to watch anything for a 15 year old girl but not
all right not in the wheelhouse of the lake house the only parameters the one
criteria is choice okay might I suggest the lake house no wait fuck you choked
you choked back or what you choked not the lake house anything but the lake
house hmm what maybe something that maybe walk in the clouds maybe that's
not my good I'm thinking of I'm trying to think of other Keanu Reeves time
travel based rom-coms Oh Bill and Ted's excellent love affair
Bill is head's most tender engagement travel through time kiss and George
Carlin this question is troubling to me because of the the addendum I'm
desperate for something different to watch this is a 15 year old girl who her
entire life the only film she's ever watched is the lake house I'm ready for
something I would say the Jurassic Park films that would probably be a good
place to start have you tried Titanic well you've never seen any movies I
don't know where to start with you have you tried anything else it's not not
that she hasn't seen any movies she done seen the lake house don't even try to
quote lake house to her she knows all the lines all the classic classic lines
like how am I I've got a time-traveling mailbox and whoa my wife and I are
expecting first child in a month she wants some songs that would be good to
listen to in the delivery room can you give me some great tracks for this
special occasion that's from Thomas via Gmail no I think we could come up with
something I actually I read this question earlier and I came up with a
really great solution and I think for the the longer portion the more drawn-out
portion like from when she actually gets posted up in the room okay starts
squishing out the baby you put on something soothing right something
mellow something like iron and wines double-sided LP around the well just
something to bring the mood down to see that and then and then right when she
starts crowning thunderstruck by a CDC wow I don't mean you do better than
thunderstruck like if you guys want to try and come at me with something else
but thunderstruck would be come out with arms wide open by Creed fuck you with
that it's about bringing a baby in the world it's perfect get out of the show
fuck you with that boy we're having a lot of fun here aren't we we had a lot
of fun we had a lot of fun back in those early days the taxi on days of headset
mic recording I think I used a rock band Mike for like two of the episodes this
is what people want people want the fucking we got so many behind-the-scenes
requests when people wanted behind-the-scenes info is there any we can
bust out well in episode 10 which you'll hear a little later the audio quality be
better because we are all huddled around one microphone and Griffin and I were
just back from e3 and supremely supremely jet-lagged we almost didn't
record that episode because Justin you got fucking aggro crag I was upset I
didn't want to record you got full-on Shrek level grumpy why was Travis there
I that's a great question I can't recall I think he drove in specifically for the
record sesh was there a holiday is there a holiday around then anyway so you'll
hear us sounding like we're drunk in the last couple clips I was actually in
Washington DC recording it in a dude's basement because we were renting his
basement have you ever recorded the show drunk I don't know that I ever have no
maybe one or two but not three sheets the wind hey we want to why we why we
got you here we want to give a special hello to Eric Kelch from cat she says
happy very belated 29th butt day I guess she means birthday but she put button
there from your fiance I get it you're the best hoppy beer-loving nerdy large
buttock having puppy dad there is man I wish people would make us say things
like that just just put something normal like hey you're a bro you're a real bro
let's let's hang out together and slim Jim out she has hopefully Griffin will
sing a song about it can't love cat come on Griffin we're doing an old-timey
episode but with a Travis here I feel like I'm regaling you with like a
private it's a little intimate right check then sitting together just the two
bros the way it should be birthday Matt I mean Eric yeah speaking of intimate
moments if you'd like to spice up your lovemaking this is gonna be weird too
with just the two of us really Travis real quick just add him to the Skype
call so yes extreme machines calm is an adult superstore Griffin it's good for
fannies both because I can just say that and we can be done with the thing faster
because that means both butts and British vaginas oh British vaginas
extreme machines calm is a friend of the show they've been supporting us for so
long and you can support us and them in turn by heading over the site using the
coupon code sexabunga you're gonna save 20% which is fantastic they got bondage
items you want that you want fetish and erotic books they've got you covered
cock and ball toys I love though I love those like the little Amish game with
the stick and yeah yeah except you play it with your penis you can find all this
be hard to do all this and so much more extreme restraints calm and do they have
any like those creepy dolls without faces on there they have like they have
fannies they have removable you mean a fanny where their face should be um no
that sounds like a Silent Hill monster and I'm not crazy about that idea me
neither you know what I am crazy about Manny hearing some more of these great
bits some more hilarious bits this next one's my favorite you know when when we
got we got Sinatra in the studio and in 19 whenever he was around I remember he
came up to me during this during this session it was a hot day in in Cleveland
recording episode it's not true old blue I swung by I was like you know boys you
know it really helped this out a little treble a little treble yeah and he put
up he turned up that he potted up the treble in the mix and that's well we
didn't do any of that stuff when you're recording these because we were just
talking into bad microphones but hopefully the jokes will still hold
true thank you for joining us we'll be back with a regular episode next week
probably and we love you very much take a chance who's that who's that one guy
who's saying with his shirt off and black and white video R&B right said
Fred what are you talking about you know not seal got his shirt off in the
Desiree video now he's like he's sort of like Desiree you gotta give me a song
I can't kind of like Jada kiss you gotta give me a song right he's an R&B singer
okay that's a genre decantress maybe
it'll come to me I want to say something like a pony is his name some like a pony
Jada kiss ludic ludicrous some like that Chris's is a thing he's a guy that's
you're going to be Angelo how is it got it sweet how is that like a pony any
social engagement I partake in I try and kiss the other party and if you take it
then I will know in retrospect that it was a date and if they fight me off then
I know the truth it was really awkward and Griffin got his taxes done well I
don't know because my agent our block representative she was fantastic the
weirdest was when he was baptized he's had him all over the world Simmons aka
that guy asks in all caps help my little baby sister drank beer hi one of my
little baby sisters who is 11 months old just drink some beer she didn't drink a
lot and she doesn't seem affected by it but my mom is freaking out and yelling
at all of us but and but I think she is fine and my mom doesn't think so can
anyone help and no bullshit serious answers only take your keys away it's
in no shape to be driving this is another one of those times where we have
to remind you of the right time to call poison control and the right time to ask
Yahoo answers what you should do about your situation you know it's not now
babies think they can party they still got shit these babies come up here they
think that they can roll with the big dogs trying to stab they just I don't
even think I don't think humans get livers until they're like three yeah
shit where's that beer going in the inside of that baby's gully works I
think I think we're missing some important what beer like what's your
first another that's a big big what did you let her have first did you let her
have some high life if it's like a if it's like a heady dogfish stout and that
baby's dunzo my baby sister just slammed a Rasputin oh no it's what if she had a
PBR you got a hipster baby hands down hope you can find glasses plaid shirts
tiny fixie tricycle these jeans don't come any smaller sir I'm sorry you'll
have to go to the my buddy I'll find smaller jeans for tight tight hipster
babies tight tight hipster jeans at the jamboree I but seriously go to a
hospital I think you can chance dude it's coke asks us via Twitter
big news after three years with my girlfriend I feel it's time to make a
leap and ask for her hand any suggestions to make it memorable all
right guys let's do it first of all congratulations let's do it
Susan or Marie oh god it's our first okay okay I know I'm really nervous
okay okay me too Susan or Marie or Ellen or Tammy let's just say baby baby hey
baby hey baby sweet baby it's sweet dude it's
cooks been with you for three years now three long years girl long years over
1,000 days of pure bliss 525 thousand 600 times three you got you went on some
dates you had some good times met each other and each other's parents and
friends you all get along really well he's got a been true to you he's been
there for you he's got a really really important question to ask do it dude
it's coke or wait let's do the second one it's like a choose your own
adventure right oh that's rough man that's tough that's tough buddy hey
listen you there's so many other fish left in the sea yeah don't even worry
about it don't even worry about dating her because that's not gonna work
out it's no it's over you had your shot and you blew it you blew it you blew it
but if you did it and it worked congratulate yes I'm sure because those
kids are so so in love unless she didn't take a chance the reality of a
long distance relationship is way harder than you think it would be 100 miles
apart you know where I live 100 miles from fucking Kings Island I don't get
there up there and you love Kings Island that's a relationship you want
to I love the Viking the Viking fury I want to make that really beautiful boat
last night I went to my friend's 21st birthday party when suddenly his
girlfriend who was very drunk told me she had feelings for me I don't feel the
same about her so my question is how do I or even do I tell my friend okay hold
on you're at you're at your friend's birthday party his lady tells you she
has feelings for you you don't have feelings for you I get I get I guess what
you got buddy you got a little something I like to call a non problem you do not
have an issue that you need to address here's the important little segment
there she was very drunk doesn't matter I say things it's surfaced guys say
things you wouldn't believe it's astonishing how many questions we get
where my answer is just pack up and move away again because that's literally the
only the only solution I have for this maybe that's why I've been such a
globetrotter these past few years I just keep messing up social situations in my
mind this is unfixable and you have to get all the global reset I'm a 17 year
old New Zealander and over here any showing of anger to anyone will often
result in a physical fight I have the problem that I seem to either bottle it
up I've been meditating late and it seems to help a little in thinking about
things are completely far off the handle and hurt people badly I was wondering if
you guys could help Sean you're you're uh you're talking to three guys who are
raised Baptist if you're looking for guys here tell you to not bottle it up
you've come to the wrong um cork it to your bottle breaks and then you get a
bigger bottle here's one yahoo answer also sent to to me by action Alan thank
you action Alan this one comes from Kyle s he asks I need a list of the most
practical kicks oh just you wait I want a list of kicks all must be practical
and where they would land so far the obvious front kick to groin mid-area
head sidekick to groin mid-area I personally don't like this one because
it's hard to see round kick to lower leg back of knee all suggestions are welcome
I'm gonna kick the spirit yeah how about below to your sub self-conscious hey
listen why do you need this list Sean what are you doing guys can we get he's
got the front he's got the side he's got the round okay considered a donkey kick
a back kick as it's referred to it back some circles where an assailant comes
behind you you can usually kick the front of their knee or groin area and
that will that will completely take them out of the fight altogether have you
tried to spin kick spin kicks really good how about if the coolest kick you
can do how about a kick in which the point of your boot goes into their
butthole a well-aimed butthole kick have you tried perhaps like a reuse style
bicycle kick where you fly through the air for ten seconds and squeal like a
pig about an awesome kid where you literally take their head off in one
clean yeah yeah awesome the mental kick where you don't actually kick but they
think that you do and then about three days their stocks crash what about the
kick where you take your foot off and make the guy smell your foot like in a
funny movie that's pretty funny yeah have you tried it a taint kick what a
taint kick where you kick them square in the tank and it lifts them off of the
ground and into the air by about three feet could I know it's really hard to do
could I suggest a kick kick which is where you kick their kick and disrupt
their kick with you gotta be careful though because if you don't time it
right they'll kick your kick and then you're fucked
it's a kick kick kick let's triple kick the KKK no have you tried to punch kick
which is where you take your shoe off that's a that's a pretty comprehensive
list I feel yeah I think that's all the kids all the kicks I know about yes what
about the junior kick where you kick their kid yeah that's sometimes more
painful in the long run I mean what you need you need a starter that you can
always bring with you a baby is good yeah a dog you can get a dog is good or
you can get one of those giant pinwheel lollipops just like in the in the bus
just go to town on it and then when they they're gonna look because you're being
so loud with the slurping and licking and when they look just be like you want
to get down on this and that's a great there's enough on this sucker with me
these right here these are moon shoes I want to get to know you always carry
skis with you a bouncer I gotta go yeah I'm up to ski I'm going out to a skiing
I'm going to skiing mountain Yahoo answers user Dakota's mommy asks help me
name my mobile spray tanning business any suggestions would be appreciated it
is a spray tan business where I travel to your home please let me know what
name you like the best Caribbean tan to go Caribbean tan to you tropical tan to
you tropical tan to go beach tan to go beach tan to you tropic tan to go
tropic tan to you dark dark dark dark skin spray here it comes
dark says dark a van and tan how this is in the I don't think that we have a good
one for her no I really don't want to give up on Dakota's mommy because she
she's had a hard year and I think she could use any assistance we could afford
her how about how about you you call it the call it the Dakota Memorial spray
tanning mobile station and then people say oh I'm so sorry did your daughter
die and you look them straight in the eye and say someday and then see if they
still want to spray tan I bet you they will want to look youthful and full of
life and vigor more than they ever have before and you will be able to really
get them on the get them on the add-ons like the complimentary fake teeth
ticket chance now I've sworn into the USMC and it turns out she likes me but
if we get into relationship it could technically be considered fraternization
what should I do Tristan hmm yeah this sounds like a Richard Gere movie I love
it sounds like I hope this is scintillating
I think steel like yeah court-martial at the heart heartbreak on the waves an
officer and an officer of differing genders yeah important to know yeah I
know if there's anything wrong with that especially it love on the high seas you
find it where you can get it right mm-hmm did you join the USMC to to be
closer because if so you did not plan this shit out my man oh I'll say this
this is this is friend of the show Tristan he is dedicated to serving our
country I've been talking to him for a while now about his dedication to the
country thanks again Tristan doing a bang-up job of it you're doing great hey
how about this how about this Tristan world war how about you put your mind on
your duty no to protect me and my freedom dude listen Tristan is doing
something I was at the three of us could never do I have a busy schedule and I
need people to protect me day in and day out and Tristan is thinking about
swooping food I think about stupid Oh Sam okay the tunnels but with that
constant water that's why we have found him I'm just saying that if anyone's
gonna take down Osama it's gonna be Tristan or his girlfriend is old and by
which I mean anyone suddenly Tristan will be the one now we'll make the end
of that movie so much better Tristan's gonna take him down his girlfriend's
gonna hold the camera up while he is like hog tying him he's gonna make Osama
bin Laden say my brother my brother and me is the best podcast it's a test to
prove how well you know them it is so yeah get them something get it get your
your bow something that is specific to him get him a bowstaff get him a
crossbow with which he can blink in the wild a crossbow that shoots bowstaffs a giant
bow shooting crossbow a bow crossbow a bow crossbow a ballista a crossbow that shoots
a barista a crossbow that shoots baristas and then you go to jail for
murder just shot a Starbucks employee why did you do that Stacy that was the
worst present ever I got you this dead Starbucks employee I got you a bum rap
for murder you're gonna want to leave the country it's just the only girls I
find attractive are out of my league and can never work up the courage to actually
ask them out all let me help you out with this man
lower them standards you got them too high you're reaching for dust bunnies on
the ceiling we got shit under your couch it needs to be dealt with lower that
standard there's no such thing as out of your league brah yeah except there is
that wait wait let me correct you there's no such things out your league
if you're hugely physically attractive because then anything is within your
reach chicky chance hey Yahoo answers user Charlie asks
Christians if we did discover aliens should we share the gospel with them
does Jesus love aliens too deep I would think that it takes so much energy to
love people that like he's got to have an outlet and the outlet is probably
hating people from other I love everyone on earth but everywhere else fuck them
well do you remember Independence Day right the end of Independence Day right
when Will Smith he fired the new but it didn't go off until a miracle happened
and then I blew up the mothership and saving the planet that miracle was Randy
Quaid that miracle is Jesus love blowing up aliens through Randy Quaid through
Randy Quaid Randy Quaid wasn't in that film yeah it was you're too young to
remember because you just remember him as a hero because you're a child you've
replaced him in your mind's eye with Jesus now is Randy he does hate he does
hate people from other planets but at the millennial Jesus convention he
always covers it up like he doesn't tell Mars Jesus that he hates Martian so it's
a franchise right because I've always assumed the Jesus franchise Jupiter Jesus
is my new stage name you should have been there you should have been there
when they excommunicated Pluto Jesus it was crazy no no Jesus's for moons get
out of here Pluto Jesus is also my favorite Eddie Murphy this summer Eddie
Murphy is Pluto Jesus hey guys hey guys I got a question how you doing you guys
are trying not to laugh I wish they could see you're really hard but you're
smirking I really don't want to be labeled as some kind of pervert if you
guys have an easier way to tell the approximate age of a girl without
simply walking out to her like a creeper and just flat-out asking you
much appreciate have you considered have you considered cutting her in half and
counting her rings or is that all you can consider you sicko what is your life
straight I'm I assume your worry is that you don't have sex in the underage girl
cool what is going on with your life strategy that you think there's a fairly
good chance you could end up boning down on a girl before you figure out what her
like life situation is like before you figure out how old she is and stuff like
what kind of chicken and egg situation do you have where that's your that's
your approach also where are you meeting these women I have no idea how old you
are hey Justin Bieber concert hey yeah maybe don't maybe don't try and pick up
chicks in the Dave and Buster's arcade room man I love chicken nugget day do
you guys love chicken nugget day you finish that school rule what are you
doing after this this is such a good place to come eat I hear like five times
a week it seems like what are you guys want to get out of here I've got
cigarettes do any of us actually know who Prince William is and what he looks
like he's that cute one right he's the one but he dressed up like a Nazi one
time right in a Halloween party I remember seeing he's got a great sense
of humor on the Sun he'd be like you'd be like cool boy be Justin I don't know
here's what I would do I would wait until you know she's gonna walk in her
room then you get a bucket you fill the bucket with water and then you put the
water water bucket half on the door jam and half on the door and then when she
opens the door it it all tumbles on to her she'll be she'll get she'll get
moist from the water in the bucket and okay what you're saying this works both
ways if she broke up with you if she pulled a prank on you then you pointed
her after the water bucket falls on her and you laugh if she dumped you then you
pointed her and say well no one will have you now and the best you're gonna do
wedding film it and put it on YouTube and said you've just made a terrible
fool of yourself and then walk away that's going viral I'll see you this
evening for dinner we have dinner at Giovanni's a reservation I'll see you
there have you guys seen the bucket X oh she's so foolish no one would ever date
her it's a say I guess I just put hooking up with me back on your bucket
list and then walk out it's real good that's a good one that's real good no
for real though you don't need her she's you're too good for you listen to a great
podcast like this unless he's like a justifiable reason that she broke up
with you like you need to quit doing speed or pranks or pranks listen it was
funny the first time you have done the bucket 26 times and it is old until you
get a tattoo that says I'm the trickster supreme I'm not gonna stop pulling
pranks take a chance Michael when you die are you gonna be sad that you didn't
understand wakeboarding for a day are you gonna be sad because you didn't get
that that spray that ocean spray in your face as you wake boarded your way down
the coast spray get that sweet salty foamy spray Michaels in the front seat
he's driving the boat Michael spraying you in the face you're waking you're in
the back you're waking wait you don't even no cares in the world just wake and
spray wake and wait you guys just got up it's dawn and you're afraid you want
to understand what's there to understand it's two men who care about each other
one of them is driving a boat and spraying you in the face with salty
foam just like looking back at him thumbs up hey you're doing it remember
you were so afraid but now you're doing it oh god that's a great end of a movie
right there right the last line the last line of this moving screenplay is you
were so afraid but now you did it get that spray that sounds like the end of a
movie we'd check out from the church library when we were eight except I
don't think they had movies called wake and spray in the church library you're
right McGee spray salty life foam into Chaz's face get that foamy spray and
then talk about weird euphemisms for God Tim Tim McGraw said it best every
fucking episode with this live like you were dying you gotta get that sea foam
gonna spray it on your face your friend looks at you knowingly sharing a sweet
moment hey you know what's a good a great moment for the end of this
inspirational movie Michael looks at Chaz and just kind of smiles and says
hey he got a life mustache and reaches up and wipes yeah yeah who answers user
Holly asks is it weird to kiss your dad on the lips just a quick kiss on the
lips no tongue you hello bye I love you etc my sister used to do it too but
she's grown out of it now and I haven't I'm 20 BTW I love you daddy I love you
daddy come here I don't know good if you're kissing other people's dads on
the lips nope just her daddy still give her low hand what's up did did you uh the
the good part of this situation is that is a no loss because if you kiss your
dad on the lips and you think it's okay then other people if they say hey that's
weird you're a weird you're a weirdo you can say why why don't you get your
halibut or it's my dad sicko then they're the sick ones I think there's a
way to be creepy about it now I'm just kissing my dad on his sweet bristly lips
look at me what's up with that stainless double that I don't think you know though
until you do it I think everyone after they're done listening this episode needs
to go find their pet pup and plant one on him right on his sweet lips I've been
looking for a good sign-off for the show for so long and I think kiss your dad's
square on the lips it's probably square on his sweet plump lips here we go sent
in by Darwin or rather the question is from Darwin is Taylor Swift Illuminati
I'm Travis McElroy I'm Griffin McElroy and this has been my brother my brother
and me you will never know me kiss your dad square on the lips
you