The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to My Brother, My Brother, Me, an advice show for the
modern era. I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother Travis
McElroy. I'm your sweet baby brother and 30 under 30 media luminary Griffin McElroy.
Well, they did it again to us. Another year where they couldn't decide which one of us
should be the sexiest man alive and they went with a fourth party.
Every year we get the emails and it's like oh I don't know I think they're and you know what
I think when they send those emails to us pitting us against each other in a sexiest contest I think
they're looking for payola journalists. Well I should tell you guys I actually got the call
they said they were going to name me sexiest man alive but I would have to do an interview
and a photo shoot. Oh come on that's a lot. Very topical. Listen I shouldn't no no no no we can't
go one more second without giving congratulations to the sexiest man alive Blake Shelton.
Congratulations. I'm so proud of you. I do think where he sold it where where did we go wrong
where did Blake go right I think where he sent everyone polaroids of his biceps and I do mean
everyone if you on earth did check your mail recently in the last few weeks you almost
certainly got a polaroid in the mail of Blake Shelton's bicep each one was individually sort
of captured and rendered and along with a personal note that was sort of telling me
just give me some support for the things that are happening in my life right now which I don't know
I mean Blake Shelton is obviously very rich famous from voice and definitely has some sort
of panopticon in his house or laboratory that he uses to watch every living person send them
personalized notes and bicep selfies and thank you Blake Shelton you beautiful fucking waffle
house that a wizard turned into a human being. So proud of you. So proud of you you tall stack
of flapjacks. Who do y'all think is the sexiest man dead? There's a lot I mean we probably wouldn't
know them it was it was some like uh Italian painter from the you know the the 15th century
or something oh that I mean Leonardo da Vinci was fucking ripped you know super ripped he had to be
to lift up his big helicopters and stuff yeah and you just picture him just like he's painting the
Mona Lisa but also he's just like glistening and he's got like a like 16 pack was that him
yeah he did a lot of great stuff like like when he drew the Vitruvian man which was a self-portrait
he drew himself with all his arms and all his legs yeah and the reason if you see a lot of
erasing marks on the penis is because he kept saying like did I do it big enough and he would
ask people like does that look he wouldn't expose himself obviously but like he would ask them like
you look at my body look at what I'm working with here look how swole look how swole look at all the
arms count them count the legs do you feel like I put the penis on enough on this fucking sex
sexual Goro that I drew yeah oh boy guys I'm looking at the page now for the People magazine
they just updated it and Blake's off he got booted from the sexiest spot and they gave it hold on
it's still refreshing the data is being injected into the it is it's Martin Short now huh congratulations
Martin I didn't realize it was a real-time tracker Griffin yeah I mean Blake Shelton's you could
uh you know get cut in a terrible lawnmower accident on his face and body and then people
is gonna be like oh he's got terrible cuts from the lawnmower so now we're gonna get him Martin
Short and the image they use from him is him as Jack Frost from the Santa Claus 3 and they said
that the most erotic yeah he says the sexiest one of him did you guys get the the list sent to you
that ranks everybody you know how when you're like in like important members of the media they send
you actually the full list and it's about five billion pages and it lists like every living man
every living male and shows you where you place there's a little highlighter it takes forever to
find it but I got 12,364,322 I'm not bad there's a billion I am oh wow yeah I'm dead center I am
the average man yeah you're like 1.5 1.8 billion in there I mean I mean right billion so I feel
pretty good about that congratulations that's huge Jess I'm sorry you got the ugliest
list yeah last place again but I'm like rooting for you but it's the ugliest one again golly
hey guys is it possible that ranking people by their looks and talking about like the gender
of the person is it possible that this list might be inherently problematic oh yes oh yeah
yeah but that's why we're that's why we have put our fun irreverent spin South Park humor
yeah I see because we didn't take it seriously we've as they say taken the piss out we've
pissed on it all over it we've stolen its piss of the list because your piss your piss is on my list
the the um the big problem I have with is they almost always pick in November like late November
around this time period yeah and to me not picking Santa just seems like a huge missed opportunity
because you if you're at people and you're like listen I gotta get some juice with the big man
yeah you you you pick Santa right yeah you pick Santa and then like oh ho ho I'm gonna take extra
good care of you this year yeah and and also people you get to meet Santa you get to meet
Santa Claus for the photo shoot and do you think that that's what that would be one good way in
the future I don't know his status right now but like that would be one good way to catch
Chapo if you want to grab El Chapo just like name him name name is got you again El Chapo
and the other thing about doing it November is most showed up for the photo shoot the other thing
about doing November is most of our nation's lawnmower accidents happen in December people
get their new lawnmowers for Christmas they get all excited but they don't read the manual for
the safety instructions Blake comes off cuts them real bad and then all of a sudden your list is
stupid again do you think when they named it Blake Shelton they sat him down and like we need you to
drive five miles under the speed limit don't eat any old food we just need you to be super careful
because we've already taken the pictures we've already written the thing we just need you to
hang on till the end of November um so again we were overlooked we're not going to get all bent
out of shape about it like we always do we're going to move on and continue to do our podcasts
that we that we do um do you think we're the sexiest podcasters fuck no not even in the top
ten damn it uh sadly but are we the sexiest brother podcasters alive uh probably not I mean
probably not probably not you have apparently you have the ugliest person according to Griffin well
the physically ugliest person so like the average is going to be drawn down I just want to say
Justin I think you're beautiful and you have a beautiful body but the people but People magazine
voted and they agreed ugliest on you so and I didn't say it speaking of this uh I didn't tell
you guys this but um my when I told my dentist that we were had shot the tv show and I was
shooting another thing uh which you should hear about soon uh and I was telling her about this
she said that I should probably have my teeth fixed cool I had never even like considered it
before but she was like you have nice teeth you just need to pull them together a little bit the
year Justin gets adult braces can I get adult braces I don't think so I don't think that I could get
adult braces oh I would love for you to know my corn chips struggle my boy I'm not detracting from
anybody who has adult braces like please it had just never occurred to me but you know I'm trying
to make progress there so maybe I will get to a point where to reach peak physical perfection
which is so important so essential look at look at what DaVinci did with his body is the work of
art oh my god guys People magazine just updated Martin Short they put up a little brief uh message
from the editor saying like we made a mistake and now Justin is it yeah first your confidence
your confidence made you very sexual and really wants to fuck you People magazine thanks beans
let's get into the question well before we do okay stick around after the show for a special candle
night's announcement oh okay don't go nowhere make sure you see that ending why are we doing it right
now why are we doing a teaser for I love that I love a teaser okay we're gonna do a candle night
show I said is that straight okay well we'll talk about at the end my mom teaches taekwondo at an
elementary school and the other day one of her students declared that he could beat her in a
fight keep in mind my mom is a fully grown martial arts teacher and this kid is like seven his logic
was that boys are stronger than girls hachi machi so it must be stronger than my mom my mom said of
course come at me and the kid did his best to kick her so she just picked him up uh he thinks
he's won this fight and some of the other students agree how can my mom teach this boy that girls can
be strong too and win back the respect of her class without actually hitting a child that's
from surprised by sexist seven-year-old okay there is a lot going on holy shit unpack here
can we start with the basic premise of taekwondo school at elementary school that seems like a
uh that seems i i well i guess we don't know where to teach jump rope griffin pull-ups i guess huh
i don't think that it's okay all right i think it's great to teach kids taekwondo it's a great
physical mental i'm a huge fan of taekwondo this should be no like there should be no question
about that i think that i think that that is very good i think that where you start to get into some
muddy water is when you fight a seven-year-old to prove how tough you are that does seem to be
how tough women how tough women are which they you really shouldn't okay like agree but you are
this is where the issue gets complex is because by being an adult fighting a seven-year-old you're
not necessarily proving anything regarded to gender i think what you're more proving is in the
vein of adults versus kids which is always going to be like the confidence of that kid i mean it's
not confidence it's sexism it's like girls so i can beat up any girl i had a gym teacher once
who said that the best uh woman basketball player on earth could not be the worst male basketball
player this is middle school and it's like the dumbest like dude come on that's the dumbest you
you know that's the dumbest fucking shit you've ever said like i've ever heard in my entire life
i'm the worst male basketball player yeah has a list of best basketball players traps last place
again it's okay here's the here's the solution to this okay especially since all the kids are
getting in on it some of the other students agree you say i do agree that you doing your cool taekwondo
to a child doesn't prove anything but go to bath and body works okay you buy up all the pillows that
they got on their shelf you mean bed bath and beyond right what did i say bath and body works
you buy up all the lotions and potions get bed bath behind buy up all the bed builds that they
have on their shelf well just let me introduce myself i'm the person who's about to suggest that
you put pillows all over every boy in the classroom and fight all of them on box style and if they
have the pillow armor you can you don't have to restrain yourself you can really just wail on them
not to injure but to humiliate and you take down all of them and all of a sudden maybe now we've
we've proved there are very good answers here but like the answers the answers that we would have
would be if you want to teach this lesson what you need to do is train one of the girls in the
class is approximately this boy's age to beat the stuffing out of him and like but again yeah that
would be awesome that would be so cool for like a second and then not cool for all following
seconds all following seconds after that you are unemployable now i will say in the defense of your
students and sort of in their camp for a second uh as i understand it picking someone up
is not sort of a legal competitive taekwondo it's like some move you can't use your hands
in taekwondo that's just like no i mean no no no holding holding is not is not a thing in taekwondo
so like i don't think that you did win in taekwondo you can't do the thing where like you put your
palm on their forehead and let them kind of swing their arms oh that's good no that's so good but
like you know if you're going like yeah not taekwondo really here's here's the best solution
for this little boy comes up to you and says i want to fight you because all boys are stronger
than all women and you say okay go to the principal's office you have detention now
and then they get their principal's office for detention and then you turn to the wrestle class
and say anybody else want to espouse some dumb shit anybody else feeling froggy and want to leap
right i don't think you can imprison children for ideas i'm not sure how like oh no you would
falsify the you would falsify a report and say like you call me a fucker and did a big cuss in
front of that's strength that's pretty sure freedom of speech does not apply to an elementary
school class if this kid gets up and says i want to fight you i think you'd be like cool bye i want
to fight you to prove that men are stronger than women okay you are going to sit in a special room
during lunch and not be with your friends you piece of shit you are in trouble now because
you're being an asshole yeah i don't know where this kid got this uh message unless he's ever
turned on a tv or watched a movie or read a comic book like i i don't know where he's getting these
these wild ideas from um how about a yahoo uh wait did we fix it though yes i don't know
the fucking detention you don't you don't have to do a physical fight um how about a yahoo yeah
but this one's gonna keep me up at night yeah no it's not good it's it's it's it's not good because
it's it's everything it's all of it it's almost like it's almost like it's a pervasive issue
that reaches through every part of our society and culture it's one of the weirdest it's one
of the very weird outlier pervasive issues that influences every aspect of our culture
that you can't pick it fixed by punching a seven-year-old in the face and there are so
many that would be sort of fixed by the global warming global warming for sure obviously um
um wage gap wage gap definitely here's a yahoo from lauren mcgregor thank you lauren it's yeah
it's an anonymous yahoo answers user so i'm gonna call them uh david asks i got fired from a
restaurant does that mean i can't eat there anymore no additional details just were you
uh the olive garden was that sort of a you decision or a them decision olive garden was well
olive garden hired me as a dishwasher and then i saw the dishwasher that was going to train me
shoot a ramekin of uh uh uh zupa toscana uh shoot it like um uh an oatmeal cookie shot
just kind of like jam it off of somebody's tray that came back and i was like i cannot learn at
the feet of this man yeah and i lied and when they asked me what job they hired me for i lied
and said chef head chef i did sort of con my way into that gig uh my bad uh so they would have had
grounds to fire me at literally any moment definitely until they saw how good i was at uh
grilling swordfish piccata or chicken tenders um so they they you know they would have a hard time
saying goodbye to me then uh but i did quit that job and it's not because i disliked the cooking
i i liked that part but at the end of the night you'd have to get down on hands and knees
and spray the floor off with a hose and you would get soaked in what everyone in the kitchen called
ochi water and it was a very unpleasant powerful all around no it was unpleasant for us at home
because you would come home and now i lived in an olive garden yeah where where i was family always
and when you're there your family literally because there's your house uh so that is that
is why i resigned from there but if you had gotten fired for stealing gnocchi i don't think you could
i don't think going back legally you can go back but why would you want to why would you want to
that's the thing you're gonna sit there and like if you're like out to dinner with a companion
you're gonna look at them and be like uh do you want to know how they made this like you know
too much you know how you literally know how the sausage gets made yeah okay but what if it's the
only olive garden oh and you gotta eat you gotta eat that's their they have to when you're here
you're family and you have to eat something and we're right here wait there is a fast food
restaurant whose tagline is you gotta eat i think it's rallies no i think rallies you gotta eat
no i think rallies is you have to eat you have to rallies you have to eat this in 2001 the
tagline of rallies and by extension checkers is you gotta eat which is kind of which is sort of
depressing yeah they gave up i mean like you have to eat why not come here you could do it here if
you wanted we have to change it to you should eat something yeah olive garden is your body has to
eat or you'll die and when you get food here we give a lot of it to you please it's a olive garden
all our food is just wet everywhere so please please take this away please please we cannot
be trusted i have some breaking news this is not a munch squad it is just some breaking news about
olive garden that i i google olive garden because i want to see some new menu specials uh that i
could like say like i don't want to try it what if i want to try this you know it's new uh there's
an arkansas couple named jordan and justin garton and uh they had a unlimited pasta pass um so they
started going to a restaurant that you have probably guessed the name of and yes it's olive
garden and then they uh gave birth they're giving birth to their daughter december 6th is the due
date no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no you may if you remember their last name
is garton this little baby's name is going to be olivia garton oh okay and she is going
to save all of us olivia garton when you were born december 6th and then the beam of light
is in a shaft comes down from heaven uh you are going to be the one that will deliver us from
everything it's all been leading up to olivia garton and she's gonna turn it all around the
mother of pasta is olivia garton now we looked at a list of italian girl names and none of them
and none of them really felt perfect until we landed on olivia the pair also considered olive
but even though they liked the humor in the name sounding like the restaurant they said
it along something subtler can i say i prove very much yeah very good you have chosen the
funniest version of what you are doing do you think that she'll be able to and this may sound
a little wild but stick with me here speak to pasta commune with a bowl of alfredo sauce like
like understand like read its thoughts and communicate with it like aquaman
probably i mean what's the point otherwise okay so it is gonna sort of transition into
weird how that
i want a munch squad this is lowered in an octave i want too much
my voice is kind of fucked up this one comes to us from jonah i would like tomorrow it's not
necessarily not necessarily a fast food one we're branching out a little bit here but this is just
too good to pass up and i am gonna send y'all the link to this one in skype just so you can see
because the imagery on this is so fucking good this one comes to us from the kellogg's company
creators of pringles this thanksgiving pringles is giving bringing all your holiday favorites to
the snacking table you know the thing that exists with the new and exclusive limited edition
pringles thanksgiving dinner if you can't make it home for the real feast and are looking for the
saddest way to fill your day congratulations this dinner is so deliciously close to the real thing
it may become part of your own tradition so each pringles thanksgiving dinner which is a tray
with a picture of a real thanksgiving dinner on it just to make sure just you're very depressed
and the press photo of this shows the tray surrounded by a spoon knife and hilariously
two forks yeah i don't know necessarily if it wanted to show you what you were really going to
use as a supplement it would show you just a pair of nasty jeans that you're gonna rub the
the coating onto so each pringles thanksgiving tray it has the mouthwatering crisps they're not
chips they're crisp because they're rehydrated potato granules they uh in eight new thanksgiving
themed flavors here are the flavors which i'm going to say and they are going to be real let's
give them a let's can we give them a rating as we go because some of these are pretty out there
yeah one to ten one to ten turkey eight eight would would chew mashed potatoes that is pringles
you have described everything you've not described pringles yeah stuffing
maybe that i'm gonna say seven if they nail it cranberry sauce negative 20 100 billion gross no
point one save some room griffin of the bottom of the scale because after that is creamed corn
absolute zero no is it travis because right after that is green bean casserole dumpster
dumpster out of ten green bean casserole that i am in cream corn following that mac and cheese
all right probably y'all could probably swing that then right at the end there bringing up the real
rear in this fucking uh uh violet beau regard of a dinner is pumpkin pie yeah love dessert
pringles is a thing i let's this this it should just okay looking at the packaging how much
packaging there is for so few chips it should just say like oh also we hate the environment
fuck the environment love these chips we use 12 pounds of packaging for two ounces of chips
let's check in with kurt simon senior director of marketing for pringles uh easiest job in the
world by the way these little bad boys sell themselves yeah pringles are known for bold
flavors and endless flavor stacking possibilities so this holiday season we wanted to introduce
snack lovers to a new way to enjoy thanksgiving favorites the pringles thanksgiving dinner
flavors are not only new but cover every course of the real meal from the main event to sides
and even dessert kurt was really struggling for things to say so he decided to just re-describe
that's every fucking pr blast about every thing that's ever been in the munch these are chips
that we made strange can we talk about they have right below this an image with suggested combos
some recipes and so one the leftover sandwich okay turkey flavored chip stuffing flavored chip
and mashed potato flavored chip all right wood crush i'm gonna i'm gonna skip the second one
come back to that number three the touchdown green bean casserole mac and cheese cream corn okay now
in your mouth at the same time yeah your human mouth you know the only one you get until you
die as a that one is the one you're gonna put three chips of those flavors into it says in
parentheses underneath only eat as prank or dare only yeah and then number two titled the holiday
sweater cranberry sauce pumpkin pie and mashed potato it's called the holiday sweater because
your body reflexively rejects it and you vomit it on whatever shirt you're wearing at that time each
of these combinations is named after the thing you would rather eat than the chips so the leftover
sandwich obvious i would rather eat a touchdown than those three things and i would definitely
rather eat a holiday sweater than cranberry pumpkin mashed potato pringles yakaruni uh here's
the worst part are you ready for like the dagger through your heart for this exclusive rollout the
pringles thanksgiving dinner is a pilot taste test and has only limited availability the dinner is
not available for retail this season but who knows what the future of pringles stacking and
snacking will bring so you're gonna try this fucking out you're gonna show this to me and
then you're not even gonna let me buy it really as a joke pringles you are gonna challenge my
my concept of what it means to eat with my human mouth and then not let me buy it and make my
friends eat it assholes it's so cruel i just wanted to buy it let me buy it you've done such
a great job selling it i want to eat the holiday sweater p.o box 54 huntington west virginia 25706
if you can just get your hands on one of these and get that over to me yeah and i have
a pringles i got a special way of getting mailed to me and it's just if you put these in any
dumpster it'll find its way to austin hq guaranteed all right here's another question
so last weekend i got pretty drunk at a family wedding and i guess i ordered like six dozen
small plastic crawdads they arrived today they're actually pretty nice but like what am i supposed
to do with them that's from copious crawdads in the oregon capitol uh i've been there i think
i think we've talked about that amazon the amazon app should have a breathalyzer on it yeah i i buy
some things so i drank a few too many glasses of wine and then said to myself i'm an adult and i
could buy things if i want and went on amazon and for some reason impulsively bought pipes because
i'm an adult i guess and then when they came uh i was i forgot ordering them when they came they
were like tiny pipe replicas which i did not realize when i bought them i guess and i still
hold on to those to remind myself that i am not an adult yeah you're a child a little boy maybe
we could get these two together and we could put a little pipe in each one of these crawdads mouths
and now all of a sudden we got our arts what do you think what do you think the phrase they're
actually pretty nice means in relation to small plastic well we've all seen shitty fake plastic
crawdads these don't look real these don't look appetizing but these are top quality small plastic
crawdads i mean next time you have um you know a pot a pot boil what's it called the low country
boil you throw one of these in and it's like the king baby i feel like you would probably
you i mean you probably wouldn't be able to return these right like amazon would be so stoked
about getting rid of them that they would probably not let you these are jeff bezos's
crawdads and he hates them i hate all these i'm worth more 10 billion dollars but i money can't
buy you happiness only getting rid of all of these plastic crawdads that i have these
curtains the curse will be lifted these cursive crawdads what if you just started
handing them out to people as business cards and maybe on them you could write
what would you have room for your twitter handle i guess that's about it huh yeah probably but they
would never forget it no and then they would have it and it would be their problem now i have the
crot let me hit you with this do you possibly throw away the crawdad do you possibly have a
local sports team that does not have a mascot oh if it does have a mascot maybe you could be sort
of an unofficial like the towel man for the saint louis blues just like an enthusiastic fan who has
a really weird sort of get down and so you show up and oregon capitol which everybody knows is
the city the city of the oregon salem salem good that's the sound of griffin double checking
travis salem oregon you're in salem oregon and the salem oregon uh you know witches probably
that probably would be disrespectful well it's also a completely different salem yeah
they're into the country well who knows anyway it's the salem fruit bats and the salem fruit
bats are there and they're you know they got uh they got fruity the bat they got nanners uh the
bat that comes in and uh you know eats one of the members of the other team and everybody has a good
laugh at it but then you show up and you're wearing a suit that is covered in little fake crawdads
you're like what's up everybody i'm the crawdaddy and people like okay don't sit close to the
crawdaddy this sucks uh don't don't look at the crawdaddy i don't know this you do that one game
and you you will be you will be shunned you do it at two games oh there's that crawdaddy again weird
you remember him from the last game third game oh sick crawdaddy's here we should get a picture with
the crawdaddy fourth game guys we got a home run because the crawdaddy was drinking a beer we gotta
get another beer in the crawdaddy's hands fifth game fucking crawdaddy's up on the jumbo trunk
got his own cryron oh the crawdaddy is here i don't know why he's a crawdaddy and not a you
know sort of a bat themed guy 20th 30th game crawdaddy's not here i wonder is he sick crawdaddy
21st game you show up oh crawdaddy's back the crawdaddy okay i love this the crawdaddy's running
for mayor did you see that yeah he helped us win all those games so he's got my vote could you invent
a new thing in rocky horror and try to act like it's a thing that everybody does like you throw
the toilet paper and then in the one scene where the crawdaddy shows up at the giant talking one
it's all sexy yeah and it's got like stilettos and stuff every time he comes on the screen oh in my
town where we come from we always throw plastic crawdads oh you guys don't have any let me sell
you one for five dollars so you could definitely get the full experience you sell one to everyone
in the theater and the crawdaddy obviously doesn't appear in the film but you're gone already you're
good you're home county you're on to the next town just hustling we got trouble right here in
oregon city do you think that there are people that like like a person that would just see like
oh it's midnight and i'm bored what's this my local cineplex is showing something called rocky
horror picture show i'll go check that out and then goes to like goes to the workers and complains
like you need to get in there and do something you're out of control very i'm trying to enjoy
the sexy film and you're all being very rude i can't hear the picture trying to listen this very
sexual film crawdaddy you could try you could try bartering okay you wanted turkey at walmart well
how many crawdads am i gonna have to give you to get this turkey there is a number there's a number
if it probably is a negative yeah it probably won't be walmart but like a small ma and pa
that's shopping that's what i miss about mom and pop stores yeah it used to be you used to be able
to trade your drunken crawdads for goods and services and now walmart's like i want your
paper and shiny metal bits yeah it's just capitalism won't let me pay for things with
crawdads and there is a number though right because it's like here's there's a 20 pound turkey is a
good one i see you picked you got a good eye for turkey that'll be uh 56 dollars and you're like
here's six dozen crawdads and they're like well no we need money for uh utilities here's 12 dozen
crawdads that's a better offer than the first offer but it's still like i do need the money
here's 300 crawdads well hold on now hold on is that more than 12 dozen let's run the numbers
real quick that's a lot of crawdads but i'm here's 64,000 crawdads it's hard to say no to 64,000
anything right can you resell do they have a secondary market where you could resell them
like etsy oh my god put little gems on the eyes and sell them on etsy
little gems on the eyes and sell them on etsy yes and what do we call them they are called
glitter daddies no glitter daddies no no that's something else i'm sure um craw buddies sparkle
bugs sparkle bugs i didn't fuck up you know i didn't buy the crawdads i don't have to come up
with the name all right i've already overextended myself yeah sparkle bugs you heard about sparkle
bugs it was all over news where if you touch it your wish comes true i can i say this i know our
listeners if you bejewel the eyes of these 72 plastic crawdads and put them up on etsy you will
resell 72 of these bad boys absolutely also would help if you glued a safety pin to it made a tasteful
brooch now maybe that's some brooch yeah tasteful brooches or put them all here's another one uh
like hot glue them all over a suit and become crawdaddy and go to your local sports team
become a local celebrity maybe glue them to the side of like some cheap sunglasses and like maybe
right across the lens oh all living yeah or you can put them all over a suit and become crawdaddy
and then you would become local celebrity getting on all of the local car commercials
yeah you know where crawdaddy shops for his ford trucks is here at salem ford tell him crawdaddy
and that's your that's the voice he uses crawdaddy um people are gonna go wild for crawdaddy so don't
no more ideas please thanks yeah no more ideas thanks got traven juice i think we got it yeah
either one of those is gonna be really great well just not either one please don't mail us please
don't mail us crawdaddy fuck you mail me a film i ruined my box with crawdads fuck you guys okay
let me that's my favorite line from shades of gray all right quick jury let's assemble the jury
if that joke's gonna make the show or not i think it definitely definitely is in the show
let's hear the arguments from justice justin you already heard my arguments it was the beautiful
sound of human laughter it has to be in all right the motion passes uh speaking of passing
let's pass on through let's pass away into the money zone i would like to tell you this week
i would like to tell you about bowl and branch now this i've heard of this and it's a you take
a big bowl and you throw it up into the tree until it stays there and it's a fun game for
children and adults yes okay i didn't know you already knew about it yeah it's the new hot game
where you try to get a bowl to stay up in a tree and expert level you put water in the bowl and
it'll drip down on all the kids and they have a great time with it no griffin no you silly boy
bowling branch fuck you okay i uh recently moved into a new home and teresa and i decided it was
time to up update our sheets and towel game so we went to bull and branch i tell you what i don't
know shit about sheets but i do know that i can tell the difference between when i'm sleeping on
my bowl and branch sheets and when i'm sleeping on some like bargain bin clearance rack sheets
you know what i mean yeah you're a delicate man these sheets are great and each sheet is crafted
from 100 organic cotton and you'll get twice the comfort and style at half the price and you can
try them for 30 nights and see for yourself if you're not impressed return them for a full
refund so right now go to bowlandbranch.com that's b o l l a n d b r a n c h dot com today and you'll
get 50 off your first set of sheets plus free shipping when you use the promo code my brother
all one word that's $50 off plus free shipping right now at bowlandbranch.com spell b o l l
and branch dot com promo code my brother go do it get some sheets can you use the sheets come
up for bandages sure if you need to escape from your prison cell they're good and sturdy if you
want to make a really comfortable blanket for it if you want to put a sail on your homemade raft
you can use them for anything don't use them from parachutes it doesn't work trust me
Travis died doing parachutes that was sheets yeah and now there's an AI construct that we took all
of his old live journal posts and we fed it into the AI and that's what Travis is I love my chemical
romance yeah see there you go hey I want to also tell you about stamps.com this is a damn freaking
good way to get your stamps that you need for the letters because with the holidays here you're gonna
be sending a lot of letters but maybe you don't have time to scoot out of the house and go somewhere
like the post office I'm I almost never have time to leave the house or do anything um because I'm
busy with the with my just sort of life and just what a freaking mess it is but I'll tell you what
happens to me what happens I don't ever think about stamps until you need them until you need
them and you don't have them right then it's like well now I have to add something to my go get
stamps yeah but you can use stamps.com instead because you just go there and you can buy and
print official US postage for any letter any package and any class of mail using your own
computer and printer make it really easy you can print postage any day anytime stamps.com is always
open it's a website did you need me to tell you that you fucking animal anyway right now you can
enjoy the stamps.com service with a special offer that includes a free of four week trial plus
postage let me try again okay and tur includes it inters a oh no it's a special offer that includes
a four-week trial plus postage and a digital scale without long-term commitments go to stamps.com
click on the microphone at the top of the home page and type in my brother that's stamps.com
enter my brother enter my brother enter him it's all one word too my brother yeah come on
Justin he's still in the just went to the restroom he messaged us discreetly to say he's
going to the restroom and because he's been in there for a while I think we all know what kind
of restroom he's using I think it's a doozy of a twozy well I didn't want to get gross about it
Travis but I just wanted to I just want it cute though I just want to say you can infer a P takes
a certain amount of length of time and it's been this break has certainly exceeded that length of
time no I definitely think it's the butt one and that's for sure do you want to read this
jumbotron I do it's for Aaron and it's from Nick and Nick says thank you for marrying me
and letting me be your one and only squirting turtle man squirting turtle man oh Justin really
would love this one and what I love about this let's remind let's tell Justin Bowen gets back
from okay maybe if we just say it real loud he can hear us wherever he is yeah Justin you back
yeah Justin you back oh he's gonna love it we'll get it again Aaron and Nick don't worry I like
this because it's a reference to monster factory but anyone who's never seen monster factories is
probably a little uh a little confused I don't know I think it's still on message for our sort
of brand anyway here's another message and it's for dad Rick and it's it's from I mean you gotta
put that in because it's just like here's one for dad then it could be anybody anyway it's from Leanne
who says hi dad aka Rick thanks for listening to this podcast with me whenever I trap you during
our longer car rides I'm glad you enjoy most of the jokes and I will gladly suffer through all
the winking you've decided to do after that one episode to more podcast laughs hey dad Rick Rick
Rick I'm glad that Leanne has at least acknowledged that 90% of our listeners are some form of
prisoner locked in our comedy Iron Maiden being pierced by our our skillful goofs
Justin you back I thought I heard something I thought I heard a butt hit a seat
no still in the toilet should I call Sydney um I have a I've got an iPad uh-huh and it has a
uh garage band on it and what's funny is that you can do like um and then what I do with that is I
can go like that is fun so it won't be long till I'm gonna need somebody to lean on still in the
bathroom huh that's Mario no I got that that was okay all right I'm back you missed a good
Jumbotron Justin you hear it did you do the second Jumbotron we've done everything all right great
well but you should you should say something for the Jumbotron so that people feel like they got
their money worth if you can just say something like hey hey guys great Jumbotron maybe play
around in the space a little bit oh yeah Rick say like oh yeah Rick and then be like oh those are
great edit them edit them together yeah I'll edit them back I'll drop you back in and all the stuff
we did about you being a bathroom and doing a bad butt stink and uh the whole like I did like a lot
of fart jokes on the garage band I'll edit all that out too and what people are getting here is
gonna be really fluid very NPR no one will ever know you did a doozy or two days yeah yeah okay
well I'll just go I'll give you some like generic stuff yeah give me some generic stuff and wild
lines the yucky mess you just made in the toilet we're gonna get all that out of the show yeah
because we don't want people to know that you do that kind of thing all right all right so just
give me some congratulations Aaron yeah it's like a nice thanks so much for the support Nick yeah
uh-huh that's good hey way to go Rick yeah and I'll just put that in and and when I put that in
I'll drop it in one of the parts where he talked about all the uh horrible noises and the toilet
bowl stink and and Justin can I just say I let me assure you we're not going to use this but um
they asked for could we get one line where you apologize for what you did with your butt yeah
we're not gonna use it but you're not okay I don't really understand okay they just want it
for comparison that's all okay sorry about what I did with my butt yeah and so let me get one
more because I have the audio tools I use has noise canceling but you have to have the sample
of the noise uh first that you're canceling out so if you can just say like I made a toilet mess
and then I'll use that too and it'll catch in the filter all the other uh stuff that we said about
you making a toilet mess so just say that out loud I made a toilet mess and then yeah and I'll use
that and then nobody else is going to hear it for the rest of the perfect so good perfect how's it
going everyone I'm Oliver Wang and I'm Morgan Rhodes we have a brand new show on the maximum
fun network that we'd love to share with you it's called Heat Rocks Morgan we should probably
explain what a heat rock is it is a banger a fire track true fire right dope album each episode we
will bring on a special guest to join us to talk about one of their heat rocks it might be a musician
a writer maybe a scholar I mean I would have been happy to just talk to you about your heat rocks
but this is a different show yeah I think people might enjoy hearing maybe the guests instead to do
that you'll have to go to maximumfun.org so if you want to talk about hot music you should check us
out heat rocks hello yahoo oh okay yeah sure this one was sent in by Kevin Budnick thank you Kevin
it's from an another anonymous yahoo answers user I'm gonna call them um uh dancing hip-hop
goose super fun educational because that's the amazon ad that I have at the top of my website
right now perfect and let me say this goose does look like a really cool educational hip-hop goose
it's got a backwards hat on okay so anyway uh dancing hip-hop goose super fun educational asks
is it possible to eat a banana without feeling rude and this is funny to even think about when
sometimes people eat it and I'm not talking about it in the way that I did it where I changed the
course of human history but the way where everybody eats it and maybe somebody will make a
a foul joke and I hate these and so I think it would be much better if we had a different way of
doing this where you didn't open yourself up for that to that opportunity I'd like to make a pitch
okay fully on peel banana eat like corn on the cob now we're talking so you eat the the the skin
first fully on no you completely take remove the peel and then you hold it and then you eat it
no you completely take remove the peel and then you hold it long wise and then like take bites
down and rotate take bites down rotate yeah that's a good option in a film I like to call
pulver mull cop 2 a gentleman named myrtle eats a banana that's so repellently old that all the
comedy in the scene and there's plenty to go around yeah uh is is derived from the age of
the banana and not necessarily the phallic shape of the banana I think hey can we just
congratulate paul blart mall cop 2 for not taking that no pun intended low-hanging fruit
yeah they evolve the gag they evolve the gag a bit so you're saying just only eat old bananas
like our friend and paul blart mall cop 2 does very old bananas like myrtle the security guard
or the shipping whatever his job doesn't matter none of this fucking matters
uh that's one option can you unpeel it and put the whole thing your mouth sideways like a big
smile and then people will say like oh what a beautiful smile you have but they won't know
it's a banana or maybe just like put it in a blender and then drink it yeah or mush it up in
a cup with a fork or mush it with your hands in front of them and say like don't get any ideas
don't get any ideas and then smush it in a big ball with your hands uh-huh i like that or maybe
like start to eat it and then look at somebody and be like no you'll make this dirty and then
throw the whole banana away can we just only eat banana ruts and then you just can pop those right
in there and it's not even a thing what about deep fried banana is that a thing i mean you're
still this still gonna have the same sort of physical shape yeah but no one's ever eating
fried pickles and somebody's like like a wiener there's lots of ways we can evolve the banana
though like if we're gonna get into culinary solutions i think that's too broad i mean you
could split it in half and dump some ice cream on it and enjoy a delicious whoa slow down i would
still know you would know you're eating the rude fruit i would say good one i'm just eating a banana
split i'm at baskin roms with my family my son just won the big baseball game i know but dude
you're eating the rude fruit bud you know like but you ever seen anybody eat the norway bud
you get it you know that looks like
nice that is the worst baskin robbins employee possible if they just order like i'll have a
banana oh nice nice dude it's hilarious i think you should carry a megaphone around
and whenever you're eating the rude fruit banana and somebody says like like a penis you hand them
the megaphone and say why don't you tell the world and you know really stand by your joke you're very
funny very funny joke why don't you go ahead and broadcast here i'll open up all the windows of the
house turn this one full blast you can let everybody know your fun joke you fucking child
rip their phone out of their hand find find their mom or their mom or their pastor tell your pastor
this great joke you just said now tell your mom the joke you made about the rude fruit
and how it looks like a cock dennis yeah good joke i guess yeah pretty good joke dennis
i deliver pizzas but i've made a terrible mistake i let it slip that i've started doing stand-up
comedy to one of our regulars and he asked me to do a set on his front porch for him oh
oh my god i didn't make him laugh well but he tipped me really well and told me to keep it
the problem is that now he only orders when he knows i'm on shift and requests me as his driver
that doesn't seem like it should be in the pizza laws uh that's from me that's editorializing
that doesn't seem like something you should be able to do that seems like there's a lot of
problems with that he asked me to do a new set every time i haven't made him laugh yet and he
keeps offering me advice that doesn't help because he has never tried comedy as he keeps saying but
i'm running out of material i am tired of bombing to this one person on his porch in the middle of
a shift but he tips really well i don't know what to do brothers do i lie and tell him i've
stopped trying will that make his tips disappear please help that's from becoming more and more
dour in dallas you can't tell him you you stop trying he'd be so disappointed in you i bet it's
jerry seinfeld you think it's jerry i think it's jerry we all know he lives in dallas now big cowboys
fan and he's trying to he's trying to this is how he has to break you down before he can build you
back up again i don't know why he lied and said that he has never tried comedy and i don't know
why you didn't recognize very famous man jerry seinfeld but he's got the goatee now he does have
the goatee and he looks great oh that's what it is jerry you look real good maybe your problem is
you're trying jokes and not every comedian is going to find their way with that could you um
when you arrive and he opens the door just get a big hammer and smash his pizza right now that's
very good that's very good that could be very fun every time oh i i think you need to reframe this
you're a professional comedian yes what level wait hold on before we move on what level of
comedic desperation do you think gallagher was at when he said well i guess i could just smash
melons with a hammer like you have to be pretty frustrated with the whole joke game to decide
that that's how you're going in this scenario he had a whole bit about unsmashed melons and he was
like y'all ever seen a watermelon before what's this big green thing supposed to cut it up for
my family at a barbecue no thanks who wants to spit out seeds the whole time sounds like a lot
of work to me boo gallagher you fucking stink dude nobody cares about your melon jokes you're
right fuck smash oh damn hold on you're onto something my dude so here i am sitting on my
regular sized couches i keep losing things in between the cushions this sucks i wish the couch
was bigger oh great advice jerry seinfeld in the audience i think you have to fail a lot to get
good at stand-up comedy that's how i understand it that's why i'll never get into that particular
field because i think you do have to bomb repeatedly and i can think a few safer spaces
to bomb then on someone's porch and at the end you get money yeah right hold the pizza anymore
it seems like a pretty good place to try out new material honestly let me float this is it
possible this person who is ordering the pizzas is a big big pervert who is so drunk off of the
power differential here where they're like yes tell me a joke tell me a joke dominoes boy
very good not very good actually it sucked i'll never laugh at your jokes i'm i'm disappointed
in this pervert man well because you that should go without saying how high are your comedic
standards that you have made the pizza delivery person tell you a joke and then you think not
good enough maybe next time give them a laugh who is this masked stranger who says do a stand-up
who's got the gall to say do stand up for me pizza person i know you have other deliveries
to make but can you do a tight five for me who is this it's unthinkable it's unfathomable how
about uh you want to do another yahoo another question or will we do i mean there is this one
that was sent in by the delivery man seth carlson thank you seth is yahoo answers user geo who asks
is there a place that will turn my ashes into a bong after i die into a bong for weed no no i
get that but not into wheat like into weed you want them to first of all that's not how fucking
chemicals work i don't think so you you want to be a bong that would be a pretty cool funeral
of it's just like thanks derrick like and then you're just passing derrick on the left hand side
oh man do you have a name for your bong i do it's derrick it's derrick peterson my best friend
please don't bogart the derrick that's not what he would have wanted
thank you for the kind derrick
i do want to say that yahoo answers user open container laws says why do you care what happens
when you die you're going to hell anyway at this rate if you don't stop taking drugs
says me open container laws yeah um can you turn my ashes into vape juice after i die so i can be
a as close to a ghost for a few seconds as i possibly could gonna need a fucking pretty high
pg to not you know fuck up the coils with that kind of no i mean i'm gonna fuck up the coils
it'll be a one time one time burn yeah and it's gonna be a it's gonna be a heady rip like
i'm that would be pretty choice though if you could get one really good choice rip and then blow
it out over the atlantic ocean yeah because then anytime that your wife saw a cloud she could tell
your son that's your daddy your many daughters that's your daddy he watches over us he watches
over us from the sky your uncle justin blew him up there the big rip he did a rings trick
he did a huge rings trick he did a big rings trick and everyone said cool i love you griffin goodbye
it's time to let go but i miss cotton now honey i miss papa griffin you don't have to because he's
everywhere and all around us anytime you see someone rip a huge oh my god put my ashes into
the vape juice repository in new mexico the reserves so from then on anytime that someone
rips just some huge cotton that's really grilly cranks they crank some cotton out there's a little
bit of me in every cloud that gets puffed out over every um children's birthday party it's all
it's all got a little bit of me in there and then when it rains what is that sweat yeah people vape
enough and put enough of that in the environment can we safely assume at some point that the rain
will be more vape juice more cotton candy granny smith apples i want to live in that world but also
there's a little bit of me in there because i died and justin ripped me up into the sky
into the sky that's so beautiful hey when i die can you guys just put me in another person
like your brain like inject you interspace style i mean more just like i want to i want to be
another person or just me again yeah that's fine that's fine that's fine but uh-huh when gallagher
smashes that urn and since no i changed my mind that is exactly what i want nobody wants nobody
wants to die but if you could rest go to your final rest knowing that gallagher or his son
gallagher 3 because there's already gallagher 2 his son gallagher 3 will smash your ashes over
the crowd like that would be very comforting i feel like anytime you see someone that enjoys
great prop comedy you can rest assured that somewhere in there they've inhaled a little
bit of travis okay but what if instead of being cremated it was just my body
gallagher got fucking edgy it is like fuck he walked out of really don't want to sit in the
front row like for real he walked out of marin and off the off the deep end and now he smashed
travis up real good the mcroy brothers were such influential podcasters and comedians it's the year
23 60 and i just want to go to their gravestones to just wish them well the problem is they don't
have them trav got smashed by gallagher um griffin got vaped up into the sky and just when nobody's
seeing justin still alive he found the crystal skull so he's still so he's still going
gallagher would too that's the worst thing about it about this imaginary situation gallagher totally
would he didn't give a shit well he's not allowed to say no if you if you give him 30 he has to
legally has to smash he's equal opportunity he has to smash whatever he putting from him
a lot of uh you know small businesses use them for like waste management solutions oh boy oh boysie
um that's gonna do it for us this week folks i hope you had some fun and i hope you've enjoyed
yourself uh didn't want to hit you all with that candlelight's announcement uh we are doing a
candlelight show in huntington on december 22nd we're still ironing out some of the final details
there it's kind of a last minute thing but we did want to let you know so you could kind of
like arrange your schedule appropriately if you think that's something you want to
come in for uh it'll be great there'll be several podcasts of of our families and uh it'll be a hoot
and a half so we wanted to go ahead and let you know that that was happening so you could get
ready for it uh we'll let you know when when we have a lot just to follow our our twitter stuff
and we'll let you know when when it's ironed out when you can expect to grab tickets when they go
on sale um thank you to john roger in the long winters for the use of our theme song it's a
departure off the album putting the days to bed it's a very good album for you to enjoy this long
winter and thank you to maximum fun for having us you can go to maximumfund.org check out all
the great podcasts there shows like uh the greatest generation and beef and dairy network
and tights and fights and uh stop podcasting yourself and a bunch of great shows at maximumfund.org
and if you want to check out the other stuff we do just go to macroyshows.com speaking of other
shows we do we just put out uh the third episode of till death do us blart our uh yearly uh movie
review podcast it's us and tim and guy from the podcast the worst idea of all time we watch and
review paul blart mall cop 2 every year for the rest of linear time this year was this was a fun
one this is the best of our three episodes i watched it synced up with dark side of the moon
and it was perfect so good hey speaking of tim and guy those cats were at my house for thanksgiving
had those boys in to show them all around america thanksgiving to let them see what all the hubbub
is about and uh they are this is they are wrapping up their podcast the worst idea of all time they're
putting it to bed and if you're in the new york area you can go see one of their last ever shows
uh wednesday november 29th at uh the bell house so if you go to the bell house website you can get
tickets there but uh you should go check that out it's 15 bucks and i guarantee you will have a good
time they are very good boys absolutely please go enjoy their show uh you want that final yes
here comes that final this final yahoo was sent in by the delivery man seth carlson thank you seth
yahoo answers user annette who asks how do i send ellen degenerous a picture of my cat
thank you very much annette decker my name is justin mcelroy i'm travis i'm griffin mcelroy
it's been my brother my brother me kiss your dad swear on the lips
you
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported hey max fun fans it's me jesse
the owner of maximum fun i've got a question for you will you help us make our shows better
we wanted to find a way to find out what the max fun community thinks about our shows so we started
something called the max fun listener panel basically you subscribe to a podcast feed and
twice a month or so roughly speaking we'll send you an episode of a show and instructions on how
to fill out a quick survey about what you think about that show 10 questions nothing too crazy
you'll be hearing existing shows that we're thinking about making changes to secret pilots
of shows that we're developing that you'll only hear this way shows we're considering adding to
the network and what you think about them really matters to us so to join the panel is easy just
go to maximum fun.org listener panel that's maximum fun.org listener panel thanks for helping make max
fun better