The McElroy brothers are not experts.
And their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert.
But if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only
so the babies out there will know
how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
One, two, three, four.
It's the start of something beautiful.
A small acquaintance has blossomed.
It's ripened into a precious friendship.
I could have never seen what was coming for me.
Hangs at the skate park, hangs by the beach.
My life, it feels like life.
Ah, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, ah, it's better, it's better with you.
This is true, ah, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, ah, it's better with you.
Hello, everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother,
and Me, an advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
And I'm secret agent Damien Ice.
I'm secret agent Damien Ice Blade.
It's Griffin's first time wearing a tuxedo.
Who, who the fuck is Griffin?
I'm Damien Ice Blade, secret agent,
government agent for the spy one.
Oh, wait, Ice Blade of the Nantucket Ice Blades?
Yes.
I heard you were fired in disgrace
for playing by your own rules.
But they needed me when the terrorists did a,
did the, did a disease bomb.
Good luck picking something that isn't happening
in the real world now.
It's a, it's a small.
It's a narrow window.
Small sliver.
And who knows when this will air.
Yeah, right.
By the time this episode goes out, no matter what you say.
They knew about the Jell-O disaster.
How could they joke about it?
Bring them in.
They knew too much already.
I hate this.
You hate what?
You hate being fancy and dressed up?
I miss my tuxedo t-shirt for so many reasons.
The first of which being that it breathes
quite a bit better than my current attire.
Okay.
Okay, but hey.
You're the one who after Fox was like,
I'm sick of being the not.
So sloppy, the sloppy one.
Yeah, I want to be the not sloppy boy.
Everyone knows me as the sloppy one.
No, no, no.
Yeah, no.
It seemed like a great idea at the time.
Okay.
Hey, do you all want to hear, as long as you're here,
do you want to hear a story?
Is this about how the elephant got its tail?
No.
Griffin, are you going to leave the sunglasses on?
Probably.
Yeah.
Although this is fucked up.
I can see my own eyeballs because of the lights.
I'm going to spend this entire show
delivering all my incredible jokes to myself point blank.
Now, Griffin, you mean you can see the reflection
of your own eyeballs, right?
I don't even know anymore where, it might be Damien.
I think he wants out.
My, did you make a deal with Khonshu?
Because this could be a problem.
I want to hear Justin's incredible story.
You all know my Grandpa Dan?
He's Sidney's grandfather on her dad's side.
Grandpa Dan?
He went to Auburn?
Okay.
He's a southern fellow and he kind of talks like this
when I do an impression of him.
It's more the essence of Grandpa Dan.
It was, the story starts off sad.
He had a fall and he's so old that he couldn't get up from it.
Why are you laughing at that?
That's so mean.
We're not to the funny part yet.
Still laughing.
You monsters.
So he fell over.
He fell and he couldn't get up.
What's funny about that?
He fell and he couldn't get up or get to the phone
or call anybody and eventually we went over and he'd been,
and we had to take him to the hospital and we thought.
Pretty funny, huh?
Yeah.
Pretty funny stuff.
Shuckle busters.
Keep it going.
Let me get past this part, okay?
Yeah, no, please, Justin.
No, Justin, they're relishing in it.
They're loving this.
Yeah, their sides are slitting.
They're going to have to go to the hospital now
to have their sides stitched up.
He thought he was going to die.
Yeah.
Because he's old.
All right.
He's not.
He didn't, which is not the story,
but it is important to know that Grandpa Dan
has been a reserved man his whole life
and he's never done a lot of stuff that you've done,
like, for instance, go to Taco Bell.
So my 88-year-old Grandpa Dan this week went to Taco Bell
for the first time in his life.
Now, is this...
Are we calling this like a backdoor Munch Squad light?
No, it's not.
I mean, it is important to remember that brand eating
affects all of us in different ways.
Right, sure, yeah.
So Grandpa Dan goes to Taco Bell.
That's my favorite children's book, by the way.
Yeah.
Grandpa Dan goes to Taco Bell,
and as he related the story, he said...
Well, I looked at the menu and I just...
I had no idea what to order.
It's overwhelming.
So I got a taco.
He got...
It could be worse.
He could have ordered a bell.
He got a taco with beef and lettuce,
and he said he was not impressed.
No.
You've really tied Taco Bell's hands behind its back.
Not only that, but I love that no one had told Dan
up to that point,
if your expectation is to be impressed...
Well, no, you're not going to be impressed
with a crunchy hard shell taco and beef and lettuce.
No one would be.
So Tommy got on his case.
That's Sidney's dad.
He said, oh, you should have let me take you
because Tommy's got a whole thing, right?
He's banging out a customized crunch wrap
with beans and nacho cheese on there
and like a quesadilla and stuff like that.
And I was telling Sidney, he can't do that.
No.
You can't jump 40 years of Taco Bell evolution.
There's got to be a middle ground there.
You're handing a caveman a Swiffer wet jet at that point.
He can't contextualize what are floors.
You know, like he can't contextualize a Swiffer wet jet
in much the same way that if you hand that man
a naked chicken chalupa.
No way.
He's down on the ground again.
But we are going to make a return trip to Taco Bell
with Grandpa Dan.
My plan is just to get him one thing from each decade
so we can ease him into the naked chicken chalupa
quesadilla supreme.
Can you imagine sitting down and doing like the Munch Squad
about the giant cheese that to start it to Grandpa Dan?
Oh my God.
Where he's like, wait, did I die and wake up
in an alternate universe?
Is that what's happening here?
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, I just, the lack of cheese on there
is really fucking with me.
Yeah, right?
Anyway, it is, he didn't want to go that far outside
of his comfort zone.
Anyway, cheese?
I don't know.
So this is an advice show.
If Grandpa Dan had asked for my advice about Taco Bell,
I'm sure I would have been very helpful to him,
but I was not consulted.
Did he not do cinnamon twists?
Because that's like the best thing at Taco Bell.
We still got that, right?
Yeah, he did not get cinnamon twists.
No, he got a crunchy taco.
I am.
And he went crunchy too.
I'm busting up over here.
I'm trying to move on to the advice portion in Travis.
It's just I never talked to Justin
and I want to know what's going on.
It is nice to catch up at these live events.
I'm also waiting for Justin's iPad to link to his phone
so he can get Wi-Fi.
Yeah, you guys vamp for a second.
I was trying to.
I can read the first question here if you'd like.
I would love that actually.
He loaded it up backstage where the Wi-Fi is so nice.
Swimming in it.
You can feel it in the air in the green room.
Oh, now I got it.
Will I have...
This is a brief one.
Will I have time to go to Olive Garden after your show today?
And that's from a something in Salt Lake.
Are you here?
Wait, no, this is a very important one.
Yeah.
I think I heard a yeah.
Okay.
It's possible that they didn't come because their priorities are...
They Googled it and they're like,
I'm not making it to Olive Garden if I go to that show.
Now, okay, so I pulled the questions
and I realized something now that I didn't realize then.
And I can assume what you meant,
but I realize now that you just wrote like,
can you go to Olive Garden after the show?
Yeah.
You can go to Olive Garden anytime.
Sure.
I don't know that you'll be able to go in and dine there.
It might be closed,
but if you just want to see it after the show.
But let me...
Travis, if you came to my house,
they close at 10 PM by the way,
so that would be...
Yeah, you got time.
We can get you out of here.
Yeah.
We got a timer going right there.
We're going to go rain pace everyone and get you out of here.
It is.
In time to hit the OG.
At most, how far I drive?
3.9 miles away.
Okay.
We're going to do three on course though.
It's an hour and 45 minute walk.
So if you're walking, you're not...
You're boned, dude.
13 minutes drive.
There's scooters outside though.
Justin did the scooter here.
Oh, yeah, I guess I did.
Thanks, Travis.
Not in the tuxedo because that would have been too much.
Says the guy wearing a tiara.
When I got out on the app, by the way,
I don't do this at home.
We don't have scooters,
so I was very swept up in the novelty.
It was hot and I went for it.
It says on the app,
make sure you don't ride on sidewalks.
Make sure you stay in the street.
Do you want me to fucking die?
Do you know how many...
Do you know that's where cars is?
Because they are.
That's what cars is.
I'm sorry, app.
Cars is big scooters.
Cars...
You know how there's two little wheels on a little scooter
and no engine but my leg?
Imagine if you will.
No one's impressed.
If I leave the sidewalk,
I lose my competitive advantage.
No one's impressed by a tiny shitty car in the street,
but if I zoom someone past...
Thank you, Paul.
Here's what we're looking at.
We got a diagram of the drive.
Here's what I cannot imagine happening
in a scooter on a street scenario.
How long a drive are we talking there?
Fifteen.
Fifteen minutes.
Okay, we could get you there one minute before it closes.
They ain't kicking you out after that.
No.
Because if Travis came to my house right before bedtime,
I was like, can I have some spaghetti, please?
Of course I would do it because he is my family.
Now, it might be begrudging and it might be begrudging there as well.
I might say, Griffin, I know it's 9.59,
but I need some pasta.
I'm carving up for a big race tomorrow like I do.
And Griffin would be like, again?
Can I get that?
I get that?
And then I would say, you got to try this new shit.
It's like spaghetti but not wet
and it has this crunch to it that'll...
I wouldn't fall for it.
Drive you wild.
I'm a grown man with a pocket square.
I would like to see a car wave a scooter in.
Like, no, you go in front of me.
Please, please.
I'm happy to be behind you, a person on a scooter.
Why would they up the ante?
You just gave me a direction in the app about how to go
and now you're like, you're ready for the big show.
And now with that, at the end it says,
be sure to always wear a helmet.
Hey, fucko, if I had a helmet, I'd have a scooter.
Yeah.
Like, if I had planned for this, I certainly would have...
Like, I'd have the things I need.
I don't have the things I need.
Is there something on there that's like,
and don't go on the highway.
Yes.
And make sure you leave this here and get a car
because you shouldn't be doing this.
How about another question?
I'd love that.
Just give me one second.
Did you close?
Are you new?
It's just that my battery's really low,
so I'm trying to conserve it.
If only you had had a chance today.
I had to be ready for the 10 PM show right after this one.
I get that, yeah.
I'm trying to conserve.
That's where we bring out the good stuff.
All the jokes are the same, though.
You're not missing anything.
Don't worry about it.
I oftentimes have a deep thirst for milk.
And now the question.
No.
I oftentimes have a deep thirst for milk.
At home, this usually isn't a problem.
Wait, usually?
It might be out of milk.
Yeah.
At home, this usually isn't a problem,
but some bar and restaurant waitstaff are taken aback
and unsure if they can help quench this desire.
The problem is that on more than one occasion,
the server will come back triumphant or surprised
and say that they, quote, found some.
Should I be worried about this unexpected surprise milk?
Would not downing the glass be a dishonor
upon the hard work they did?
That's from Leery Lactose in Las Vegas.
Are you here?
All right.
Thanks for making the drive.
That's a strong, just calcium-filled woo.
So calcified that woo was.
I also want to say maybe the reason they're taken aback
is if you say something like, I have a deep passion for milk.
Yeah, that's no good.
I have an unshakable thirst for milk.
If you can give me some of that beautiful mood juice, please.
This is not an issue if you only eat at Dave and Buster's,
because they got you.
Dave and Buster's, a lot of milk there?
They got milk.
I had Dave and Buster's milk today.
It's very ethical.
They let Dave and Buster watch Netflix,
and they hook them up to this apparatus.
It's got plenty of vitamin D and B.
Yeah.
They like to watch old boxing documentaries as it withdraws.
And they've actually scientifically determined
there's more production during the actual fight.
Yeah.
It is gray.
Don't look directly at it.
And don't drink directly at it.
No.
And it costs 200 tickets.
And don't drink Buster's before they mix it with Dave's.
You know what they say, Buster before Dave, catch the wave.
Dave before Buster, you're feeling flustered.
Yeah.
Oh, Dave and Buster's.
Don't drink that milk.
You have to know.
They worked so hard to bring you that milk.
So?
They worked hard.
If you didn't want, you don't put the requirements of that
on any other food item that they bring.
If only there was some way, like maybe a monetary way
that you could reward someone for their hard work at a restaurant
that had nothing to do with you consuming 25-year-old milk.
Everything's all about money.
Yeah.
If this is the sort of person that throws cash around
to fix problems, I don't think they're quite so hung up
on what the person thinks of them for ordering milk.
Oh, sorry, Justin.
You can't be conscientious and rich.
No.
I'm just saying.
I would say pretty empirically no.
No, yeah.
Yeah, I didn't think I'd be able to ride that one too far.
Yeah.
Could you ask, could you drink some?
Let me show you what drinking looks like.
Could you drink some and say, I got to be honest with you,
this is the best milk I've ever had,
and I need you to bring the container
so I can always buy this milk.
And then you check the date surreptitiously.
Is that our concern?
The concern is the date, right?
Yeah, you can check the date while you're having a conversation
when you're like, oh, how interesting, current events.
JonBenét Ramsey is missing.
Oh, no.
Is this Star Wars, The Phantom Menace?
I love that flick.
This milk is a tie-in with Pirates of the Caribbean, The Ride.
Unfathomable.
I mean, I know how it is.
I mean, you got to have your milk.
I think you just got to take your chances.
Worst case scenario.
No.
Milk is like the worst food to say, take your chances.
Yeah, I need to see it from teat to bucket to,
I want Louis Pasteur to be like, you're good.
You're good.
I did this one myself, my man.
I guess.
I mean, I guess.
No, it is the one food.
If you say spoiled blank, the answer is,
no one's ever like spoiled potato chips.
It's always milk.
Milk is the thing you're most worried about being bad.
But expiration dates are made up by the government.
Not, but to a point, Justin.
Tell me about it.
Thank you.
They're not real.
If someone said, I've been saving this yogurt for a special occasion.
No, don't act like that.
Worst case scenario, you got some celebratory cheese.
No big deal.
Sure.
No, worst case scenario, you have some celebratory diarrhea.
That too.
Thank you.
The neighbors we share a wall with seem to be starting a band.
We've never really spoken to them, but we think they sound pretty good
and want to let them know we enjoy hearing them.
What is the best way to say this to them
without sounding creepy or passive aggressive?
That's from nosy noise neighbors in Provo.
Are you here?
How many of you are there?
Wait.
Hold on.
Are you here?
Okay.
Thank you.
This is a fast one.
I have a slam dunk answer for you.
Great.
That's awesome.
Because I didn't want to get a hand on this ball.
Yeah.
This is about moving through these as quickly as possible.
So we can get our friend Olive Garden.
Change your Wi-Fi network name.
Oh, yes.
New band next door.
Love it.
I don't know that they can be that long.
New band?
Cool.
New band cool.
N-U-B-A-N-D.
Cool.
New band cool would be a good name for a band.
Yeah.
You could also do C.
If you're worried about characters, C-U with an umlaut L.
Yeah.
That would save you some serious.
That's the same exact number of characters I feel like.
Well, the umlaut's not separate.
Oh, yes.
Fine.
That's cool, but we'll allow it.
I don't think you can have an umlaut in the...
Because the SSID I think would be...
You'd have to have an umlaut in there.
Anyway.
Just go over to their phone and write it on the...
Love your stuff, by the way.
Hold on.
Do you...
Are you...
Are you sure you want to be the only fan of this band?
Because they're in Skunk Works territory right now.
They're just playing to try to figure out if it's anything.
Yeah.
I feel like if you come in that early and you're just like, bada bada bop, I'm loving
it.
You are setting up a wild, unrealistic expectation for support.
Yeah.
You could be on a date in your apartment and just hear like, hey, what do you think
about this?
Was that anything?
You like that?
Did that go too hard?
Well, there's...
I was worried it went too hard.
There's also the possibility that they're just noodling and having fun.
Yeah.
They're like, I love this new band.
And they're like, I guess we need to...
It's not ready yet.
I guess we need to start a band now, girl.
It is a little presumptuous, right?
It's not being played for your enjoyment.
What if it's just a guy with weird sneezes?
Or a very, very lonely one-man band.
You knock on the door like, I love your stuff.
And he's like, thanks.
I'm going to walk to the kitchen sadly now.
That's my impression of what a one-man band sounds like.
Thanks.
Before I would make this leap, I would need to know what the music of every band in the
world sounds like to make sure they're not playing a CD.
Oh, my God.
I would need to know with 100% certainty this is a new sound, new creation, new band.
Because I do not want to open up the door and be like, dude, this is fucking sick.
And they're like, it's Crosby, Stills, Nash, and Young?
It's John Philip Sousa.
John Philip Sousa?
Yeah, I guess it's good.
How did you get a key?
Can I borrow it?
Can I borrow your John Philip Sousa CD?
I don't think you need to be...
I was streaming it.
Can I borrow your computer?
I don't think you need to be a student of music to know when someone's laying it down
like they're in the studio versus they're in their apartment trying to learn Master of
Puppets because it was on Stranger Things.
But you accept Mountain Goats, you know?
Yeah, you can't tell the difference between professional band Mountain Goats and just some dudes.
Someone plays early Mountain Goats through their wall, you're not going to know if it's
really someone playing guitar or not.
But that's why we like it.
I'm not complaining, I'm just saying.
You love that scuffed shit.
Hear that, John Darnell?
We love that scuffed shit.
Keep it coming, baby.
You know, he's writing books now.
Like, leave some for the rest of us.
Yeah, right.
Dude.
Finally, someone's putting him in his place.
Somebody's finally putting that stinker John Darnell in his place.
Another question?
Yeah, please.
I'm about to start flight school to become a pilot.
Yeah.
While this is an exciting step in my career, I have a problem.
I am terrified of heights.
I have a practice flight coming up and I really don't want to spend it slumped down my seat
mortified and scrambling for a barf bag.
Bad first impression.
What are some ways I can overcome this fear and walk into this first flight cool as a
cucumber showing them I'm super chill about heights and flying around in them?
That's from my stomach.
Would rather be a train conductor.
Are you from Mapleton?
Are you that narrows it down?
Because they're a little bit embarrassed that they're trying to be a pilot when they're
afraid of heights.
Yeah.
And they didn't realize it until they heard a stranger say it out loud.
But to be fair, I was thinking about it, right?
Okay.
Well, two of us have almost theater degrees.
You almost have a theater degree.
I have a theater degree.
I thought you switched to journalism.
No.
No, I have a minor in journalism and I use neither.
Thank you.
I went to college for five years because I have failed Spanish.
I was able to, before going to college for a theater degree, act in stuff.
You know what you don't get to do before going to flight school?
Fly a plane to see if you like it.
But you know, they didn't discover the first time they went up in the big beautiful sky,
like, oh, I hate this.
I wish I hadn't picked this as my job forever.
I have to assume you have a parent or overbearing grandfather who is a pilot,
who was like, this is the life for you.
It's unfathomable.
Other than astronaut, you have picked the most up job that you could possibly have.
Yeah.
Maybe those people that do those fucking Red Bull halo jumps are a little bit higher than you.
At least they're like, I'm headed down.
I'm going down.
Yeah, I'm going down.
I want to fix this.
Also, once they're in the plane, not up to them until you reach that point.
Yeah.
A pilot, you're just there the whole way.
Just up, up, up, up, up.
You can't zone out as far as I know.
I don't know why you would try to have such an up job if you don't like up.
Yeah.
But I will say this.
In a plane, it's not really like you're going to fall.
You're not going to fall out of the plane.
In a perfect world.
In a perfect world, yes.
If you are, if you find yourself falling from a plane,
there has been a bigger whoopsie doodle that has happened.
In that context, though, I do want the pilot to be afraid of not being up anymore.
Yeah.
That fear is healthy, right?
I don't want a pilot who's like, I don't know, man, up, down.
It's all the same to me.
Yeah.
I want you to have a healthy, healthy man.
Hey, what do you guys want?
Let's show our hands.
You guys want up or down?
Up or down.
It don't make any difference to yours truly.
I'm chill either way.
Either way is fine.
Who wants to see the stars?
I can go further up.
I can go further down.
You know what I hate?
Radio towers.
What's the number one piece of advice you give someone who's afraid of heights?
What's that?
Don't look down.
Yeah.
That is also good advice for a pilot.
Keep looking forward.
Because if you spend the whole flight looking out the window, they have those, right?
Yeah, yeah.
They probably have a cool name for them.
You're going the wrong direction, you're going reverse Sully, you're hitting the geese,
you're going down.
Yeah.
You got to look in front for geese the whole time.
But the problem is that Sully was looking in front of him, saw the geese, and was like,
I'm going to get those motherfuckers.
You think you're so cool, geese?
I'm a plain geese.
Get out of my way.
Oh, yeah?
Okay.
You bet I won't.
They don't talk about that enough in the movie.
No, they don't.
Tom Hanks is there, and he's like, I'm a perfect angel.
When really that dude was like, fuck these geese up.
I lost at bar trivia last night.
I'm fucking pissed.
Did that happen in the movie?
I'm going to shred these geese.
I need to watch Sully.
Yeah, it's a sick film.
You ever seen it?
No, I've never seen it.
So anyway, let me set it up.
Can we be serious now?
That's my impression of Tom Hanks and Sully.
Yeah.
I'm going to stick with it, if I can say.
It was really good.
Can we be serious?
I can't do it a second time.
But the first time I think we can all agree sounded a lot like Thomas Hanks.
No arguments here.
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
I just had to, I got to read this verbatim.
I'm sorry.
It's like, I'm sorry.
I'll just read it verbatim.
If your power is a dream, then make the dream take flight.
You and Squarespace are going to make it all right.
Just a few clicks and key presses, all that you need.
Whether you're making a good website or a bad website.
Hi, Justin McElroy here.
Squarespace will let you make good websites.
They make it easy to make good websites, make tools that are simple to use, even if you're
not an expert, drag and drop, beautiful, easy to make a great website.
But what a lot of people won't tell you is that you are allowed to make a bad website
with Squarespace.
They will not step in and forbid you.
They don't make it easy because everything's so beautiful and they have such great customer
support.
And there's a Squarespace video studio that makes videos easy and you can sell products
with a physical or digital.
Squarespace has all those tools.
So like they don't make it easy to make a bad website.
But if you want to make a bad website, they're not going to stop you.
So fulfill your dream with Squarespace, whether your site is good or bad.
Head on over to squarespace.com slash my brother, or you'll make me sad.
There's a free trial when you're ready to launch, use offer code my brother to save
10% off your first purchase of a website or domain.
Squarespace, you can make a bad one if you want.
Hey there, quick favor to ask.
Will you help us out by taking a five minute survey at maximumfund.org slash survey?
As you know, most of the support for Max Fund comes directly from folks like you.
But many of our shows and our network also rely on limited advertising for some revenue.
This survey helps us attract advertisers that are a good fit for the audiences of our shows.
And it helps many of our hosts secure a bit of extra income.
It should only take a few minutes to complete and you'll get a discount at Max Fund store
when you do.
That's maximumfund.org slash survey.
Thanks.
I'm Lisa Hanawalt, and I'm Emily Heller.
Nine years ago, we started a podcast to try and learn something new every episode.
Things have gone a little off the rails since then.
Tune in to hear about low stakes, neighborhood drama, gardening, the sordid nasty underbelly
of the horse girl lifestyle, hot sauce, addiction to TV and sweaty takes on celebrity culture.
And the weirdest, grossest stuff you can find on Wikipedia.org.
We'll read all of it no matter how gross.
There's something for everyone on our podcast, Baby Geniuses.
Hosted by us, two horny adult idiots.
Hang out with us as we try and fail to retain any knowledge at all.
Every other week on Maximum Fun.
This can't be right.
A haunted doll watch?
I'm trying to do a show.
Did you all see that Vulture did a write up about the white wine, about this new drink
that I invented?
The drink of the summer, you mean?
The drink of the summer, they called it.
That's not it.
Look it up.
All right.
Yeah.
You already did that.
OK.
Today we're going to be kind of zooming in, focusing in on one particular purveyor of
haunted dolls, and that is haunted honeys.
So this is really a haunt.
I don't think that's how you spell honeys.
Yeah, it is on.
I'm looking at eBay.
I mean, that's haunted honeys.
Yeah, but it's haunted honeys.
I'm looking at it.
No, but I mean, it might be spelled that way, but I'm just telling you anyway.
OK.
Travis, we get it.
They spelled it in a different way.
OK.
Let's...
Welcome to the stage, Stella.
All right.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Is that a promo code at the top?
Did that get cut off, or is it really fucking 5% off?
What do you want?
There's slim margins here, pal.
So this paranormal doll, 70s, neutral.
Please read.
Neutral?
This doll was part of a paranormal study.
You will receive the physical doll.
I should hope so.
Hey, stop that.
This is Stella.
She's in her 70s.
Oh, she looks great.
Yeah.
Well, her vessel is 16 inches tall.
Stella was not very happy with me getting her at first.
What?
Why would she be happy when I purchase her on the eBay service?
I think once she saw the other spirits here, she realized she'll be OK.
Stella passed away in the late 1800s.
She thought...
Wait.
She's how old?
She...
Well, she's dead.
But how...
Oh, so according to the Haunted Honey, she does not continue to age after that.
Correct.
So she's 70s.
Forever.
Yeah.
Cool.
She thought many times that her life was going to end.
Then all of a sudden, she would get better.
Sure.
I bet there was a lot of that in the 18...
Yeah, you know what?
I bet pretty much everybody in the 1800s had a moment where they're like, oh, I fell down
once.
This is it, I guess.
Wait.
You guys heard about all the diseases?
Yeah.
I fell down at work and now my arm is green.
I guess this is it.
Nope.
Cool.
So you've talked to Grandpa Dan already.
If you knew the story, you should have just said something.
I think...
OK.
Stella had many near-death experiences throughout her life.
She lives in a void of paper towels.
I don't think a near-death experience is when you think you're going to be fit and you're
like, ah, never mind.
I'm getting better.
She was known to be a bit of a careless daredevil in her younger years.
OK.
I can see that.
Stella is neutral, but that doesn't mean she's not friendly.
No.
Neutral or bitter is very friendly.
Yeah.
She's just got somewhat of a temperamental personality.
Then that's not neutral.
She likes things to go her way, lol.
She enjoys...
Wait.
Because she...
Well, doesn't everyone?
No.
Why the lol after that sentence?
Because she's like sassy, lol.
But we're talking about a ghost.
She enjoys a spot in the living room next to the cute decorations.
She enjoys judging my company, lol.
She works great with any divination tools.
She's not really picky over gifts.
She likes everything from jewelry to flowers.
When you get her, don't forget to give her a gift and light a white candle with some
incense to welcome her.
I don't want to be pedantic, but jewelry to flowers is not a good scale of things.
It's all the gifts that there are.
Between jewelry and flowers.
I'm sorry, everyone.
This is a boring ass doll.
Neutral.
Well, maybe...
I want something spicy.
Maybe our...
Maybe Jenga will be more to your liking.
Now Jenga I can get into.
Welcome to...
Yes!
No!
Baby!
Yes, baby!
Branded as shit!
$35 with 15% off using the code Haunted15.
I do believe I will, thank you very much.
This doll was part of a paranormal study.
You will receive the physical doll.
Yes.
This is Jenga.
Yeah!
Yeah, it is.
His age is unknown, but his vessel is nine inches tall.
Wink.
Oh, a little guy!
Wait, is there a wink in there?
Nope.
Jenga is in his mid-20s, except he is dead.
He's a friendly little guy.
He was sent to me from Canada.
The lady that had him felt he may be negative.
She sent me photos and videos of him, and I assured him he's positive.
But she wanted him gone.
Did they do your butt backwards, Jenga?
Maybe his butt was knocked backwards when Jenga was hit walking along the side of the
road.
He was hit so hard, his butt was knocked.
His butt switched sides with his privacy.
We've all been there.
That was my favorite Grey's Anatomy episode.
I really-
We can save you, but your butt's always going to be on the front.
It's okay.
I still love you.
And nothing but.
Dr. McPoop's weird.
I think it's going to be okay.
I really believe that Jenga was a photographer.
Does Jenga sit on the toilet like a cool teacher?
Hey, we've had a lot of fun here today, but you know what's not fun?
How does this doll poop?
When I did his reading, I got a vision of him walking beside the road with a camera
in hand, presumably moments before he was tragically killed, I guess.
He's definitely got a very artistic side for a doll.
He gets along great with all others, and pets just adore him.
I bet they do.
He loves- this sentence has never been written before.
He loves any type of art as an offering, and he also likes green candy.
Oh, my two turn-ons, easy, fine art and green candy.
When you get in, don't forget to give a gift and some incense to welcome him.
I do love how his hair has a natural windswept look.
Sure.
Such a festive- such a festive doll.
But let's take a moment, if we may, to meet a new friend.
Hold on.
Wait for it.
Wait.
Hold on.
Hi, Miguel.
Shit.
Oh, boy.
Paul-
Now, why is Miguel worth $3 more, do you think?
This is Miguel.
He is a teenager.
Griffin, can you just read the, like, four descriptive terms there?
Paul, if you'd go back.
Paranormal doll, haunted honey's Miguel, M45, teen, positive, very sweet, clingy.
That sounds like the description of a relationship.
Like, at first, he was a teen and really positive and so sweet.
So sweet.
But he got a little clingy.
A little clingy when college rolled around.
This is Miguel.
He's a teenager, and his vessel is nine inches tall.
Yeah, it is.
Finally.
This guy is ready to find his forever home.
Every time I would ask him if he was ready, I would get a strong no.
Please don't sell me, mama.
Please, mama.
It's time, Miguel.
No, no.
This is my forever home.
You're ready to find your forever home.
I found my forever home.
I need $38 for cigarettes.
So this is a challenge-
Mama.
Can I sit on the chair?
Yes, Miguel.
This is a challenging sentence.
He has seen some of the updates from other spirits that got adopted in their new homes,
and he's ready.
I thought he just said no.
Yeah, but now he's finally ready.
And this does-
I was on the forums on Reddit.
It looks great.
Yeah.
Is your doll on the internet?
Are you-
Do you have screen time?
Not the internet, as we know it.
Okay.
Sort of a ethereal bae.
All right.
He has seen some updates.
He's ready.
He's seen some shit.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He had a tough time in the home I got him from, and that had him scared.
What?
Well, Miguel passed away in the 1950s.
He was a very energetic teen and known to be a daredevil.
And when he ate spicy food, he turned into a car.
He was a very energetic teen, and he was known to be a daredevil.
He jumped out the window of the abandoned house down his street and ended up breaking
his neck.
And folks, I'm here to tell you, that'll do it every time.
I love that version of It's a Wonderful Life, where it's like, I'm going to buy that house
and live in it when we get older and married.
He's like, oh, yeah?
Well, check this shit out.
Ooh, crack.
Murray, you got to call someone married.
I'm actually going to go.
I can't.
I got some prior.
What?
Joseph?
Did that man just die?
Dude, job's off.
You're good, Clarence.
He went hardcore this time.
One, two, three, and fuck it.
So he jumped out the window.
He just a very, such an energetic teen that he is a daredevil.
Like a daredevil is one thing, right?
We all know what that means.
I don't think it means, hey, check this out.
I do think, listen, once again, stupid abandonment.
Hey, you guys want to see a dead body?
Cool.
Once again, not to be pathetic, I think a daredevil has to at least survive one thing.
Sure.
He got to do one thing.
Oh, man.
So he broke his neck.
He was so surprised.
Yeah.
No, not about that.
Okay.
Not about that.
What?
Well, I thought I could stick that shit.
He was surprised to see all the gifts and people who showed up to support and honor
him at his funeral, which like after the dumb shit he pulled, I get it, I guess.
I wouldn't be surprised if people showed up for me too.
Miguel is very sweet.
He will bond deeply with anyone who shows him kindness.
He works great with any divination tools.
He enjoys going through the home.
Great at Adobe.
Making little tipping and clacking noises.
When you get him home, don't forget to give him a gift and light a white candle with some
incense to welcome him.
And I am only reading this end part that's at the end of all the posts because we're
coming up on the end of the show here in a little bit.
Follow Haunted Honeys on Instagram and TikTok.
Thank you.
Yes.
But hey, listen, as somebody who's been by there, who ducked his head in a little bit
earlier today, you better really be sure that you want to check in a lot of these on TikTok.
Okay?
Uh-huh.
And don't leave weird comments because I'm tired of people selling dolls, putting notes
in the boxes that are like, I checked out your podcast, it was really funny.
And then they have my home address and I don't like that.
So please stop talking to the people who sell the dolls, everyone.
Anyway, that's our Haunted Doll Watch.
Thank you for that.
Let's, let's take it to the streets with some live audience questions.
We have prepared a list of people we're going to call you down.
Please do not approach the microphone.
Oh, bye Justin.
Hello.
Yeah.
Um, my name's Laurie.
I go by she, her.
Hi Laurie.
And my question is, I wrote a steamy alien romance book and I need a title for it.
Can you give us, yeah, like a paragraph synopsis?
Imagine being in the back and, and getting all worked up.
What sort of the, you know, what's the summation?
It's about this girl who gets kidnapped by aliens, well, abducted, I guess is the right
term.
Yeah.
Sure.
That's the term they prefer.
Yeah.
But you're the writer, of course, any word choice that you want to go with?
Okay.
Go ahead.
Spin your web.
Yeah, that's true.
And then, so she escapes the aliens and becomes a bounty hunter, but then she falls in love
with an alien, um, who she's supposed to capture and they have a fun time together.
So the first two that occurred to me is beam me up lover and booty bounty 2099.
Booty bounty 2099, is that what you said?
Yeah.
Okay.
Is it set near 2099?
Could it be?
Could it be set near 2099?
It could be.
Yeah.
It's 77 years from now.
Are you sure?
Hey, Griffin, you can't assume that aliens use the same calendar we do.
Yeah, that's fair.
That's so weird.
We're actually on the same month, 77 years difference.
It's also January.
Then what about closer encounters?
Oh, that's good.
I like that one.
Or it could be close encounters of the fourth kind, which is doing it.
What about probe me regular?
What about probe me globular?
Is the characters name globular and it's important to ask, get your hands on me, you bitch.
Is he a big gelatinous sphere that you can climb inside and be transported into an dimension
of X?
Let me finish!
Area 69.
And here's the thing, I know I just said it.
There's no way that's not taken.
What about, no, seriously, welcome to earth.
What about cocoon two?
Actually, I think it's already a movie.
What about cocoon three?
One of those has got to help, right?
What about Uranus?
Call my, am I right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Also, if you use any of those TM, TM, TM, TM, TM, TM.
Hello.
Hi, I'm Erin.
Hi, Erin.
My question is immediately actionable.
Yeah, please, please.
So before the show, I was playing with my fidget because I got ADHD, so I got it on
your baby.
And I did.
I have dropped it on my face before.
Okay.
I dropped it.
It is an orb.
It is a crystal orb and it rolled forward and I thought I'd never see it again, but
I figured I'd toss out into the audience.
Who's got the orb?
Jesus Christ.
The orb made it so far.
Erin, the orb went.
Wait, Erin, where were you sitting?
I was sitting in the back.
Erin, where were you sitting?
The very back.
The very back?
That little orb.
It was like the fucking forest goat feather.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I have to know.
It was like the beach ball stuff.
Raise your hand if something bumped your foot during the show.
Now hold on.
There's a record.
I have so many questions.
The voyage of the boy.
An incredible journey.
Can you approach the microphone please?
I need to know the story of the person who orb rolled up to your feet.
And you were like, hmm, free orb.
No, but wouldn't this be wild if it's a different orb?
I would not.
No, that's not mine.
That's a different orb.
Is that the correct orb?
It is the correct orb.
It's the right orb.
We got the orb back in Erin's hands everybody.
Yes.
Hey, big cheer.
You'll love to see it.
I love it.
We need to do more of those, by the way.
We've never done lost and found audience questions.
I love that.
It's really great.
You know what I like?
No jokes required.
Yeah.
And it does something good.
Okay.
Next up.
Hello.
Approach the microphone.
Welcome.
Hi.
My name is Kaylee.
Hi, Kaylee.
Me and my fiancé are getting married next year, and he's pretty insistent that we cut
our wedding cake with a sword.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
You only...
Okay.
And I keep trying to tell him no.
Why?
Yeah.
I agree.
What?
No.
Kaylee needs our support right now.
Okay.
It seems great.
Here's the problem, right?
No.
Was that the rest of the question?
Sorry, Kaylee.
Oh, yeah.
How do I tell him no?
Yeah.
He actually listens.
I...
You cut...
Think about it, folks.
You cut the cake with the sword once.
Great.
But you got to cut a lot of slices of cake.
Sure.
Kaylee, you're just sitting there with a sword like a doofus, cutting small slices with a
sword, and you look ridiculous.
I will say, at mine and Rachel's wedding, it was like 20 degrees outside, and we could
not get through our cake.
And had I known in the moment that having a fucking Hattori Hanzo steel was an option,
I would have taken it.
Now, I'm getting...
This isn't funny, but have a groom's cake that your groom can cut with a sword.
Can fuck up like a doofus.
You're going to want to have two.
Like you do at a one-year-old's birthday party, you know?
Yeah.
This one's just for him, everybody.
Let him have his fun.
Yeah.
One cool thing that you could do is say absolutely, and then when he rears back and he's like
swings forward, you pull out a short sword, block him.
Hell yeah, dude.
No, wait.
Okay.
I am immortal.
I have inside me blood of kings.
And then long eye contact.
Not today.
And then it's...
That's first dance right there, baby.
Yeah.
I don't know what happens after that.
Maybe I'll sword fight or get hurt or something.
Then you throw sand in his eyes.
Yeah.
That's good.
No.
Icing sugar.
And then you hook onto the roof and then you run away.
You stab him.
You cut his head off.
Cut off his fucking head.
At a certain point, your stunt doubles have taken over.
It's fine.
Yeah, yeah.
You're not doing any more.
This is all CG.
Does your...
Do you have the budget to motion capture your...
Does your fiance know how to use a sword?
Not yet, no.
Okay.
So let me tell you.
It's not as easy as I make it look in the movies.
And I know what you're...
Are you here, fiance?
Yeah.
Okay.
I know you're thinking, big knife.
It's different.
Now, listen.
It's not going to be...
Listen.
No, no, no.
Now, here we see Queen Elizabeth cutting a cake with a saber.
I believe the wrong way.
Yeah, the wrong...
Yeah, hey, guys.
Hey, guys.
It actually looks like she's pointing to a part of the cake with the...
Right about here?
Right about here.
Can we not...
Can we not actually the Queen of England cutting a cake with a sword?
I bet she probably knows what she's doing, right?
Now, Justin, I'm sorry, but nothing about the Queen's face here is, I know what I'm
doing.
Step back, idiots.
Look at the guy in the pink striped tie in the background.
Is everyone like, do you believe this?
Can I say...
Okay, real quick about this guy.
The Queen of England is cutting a cake with a sword?
Fucking stand up and go check that shit out, man.
How are you sitting there like, oh, this happens to me constantly?
Okay, that guy is so thrilled beyond...
That person has been big from a 12-year-old child to that age.
Anyway, so sorry, Kaylee, but I do need to ask, do you think Queen Elizabeth has eaten
Taco Bell before?
Probably not, right?
No.
No, probably not.
What do you think she'd go with?
Oh, if she did?
Yeah.
I think she'd go with the pink.
For sure.
Can I tell you?
No joke.
That was right there in my brain.
Okay.
Has anything we've done today helped?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Kaylee.
Congratulations, everybody.
Congrats.
We need to wrap up soon if they're going to get to Olive Garden.
Yes.
Charles, make it snappy.
Okay.
Hi, Charles.
I'm Charles.
He him.
Hi, Charles.
I tried to get my surgical instructor not to fail me after I made her listen to ska for
the entire duration of a seven-hour surgery.
Now, wait, Charles, here's my question.
Sure.
Have they expressed to you frustration about this?
Four hours in, they looked at me, and were kind of like—
Four hours?
They made it four fucking hours, huh, Charles?
It kind of plays low in the background because they don't want it to be distracting, but
at a particularly long trumpet solo, they looked at me and were like, this is interesting.
Yeah, sure.
Now, hold on, Charles.
Hold on.
You all have—
Is it possible that—
Hey, wait, wait, real quick.
I need to know if this is a universal experience.
Have you ever played music for a gathering or a group of people or just one person, and
you get to a point in the music where you're like, they're not going to like this?
Yes.
I'm seeing a lot of nodding like, oh, man, this is really grating.
I really wish this would sink back into the background.
I feel really weird about this now.
I want to quit.
Can we quit?
Charles?
Someone, while you're performing surgery, saying, well, this is interesting.
Is it possible it was not music-related at all?
What were you doing in that moment with your hands?
I was just standing there holding the retractor uncomfortably, sweating, because I—
How uncomfortably?
What's a retractor?
Wait, wait, wait.
Sorry, sorry.
Were you skanking it while you were holding the retractor, because that will, that is
no good, my friend.
That goes right against that Hippocratic Oath.
The Hippocratic Oath should say, do no harm, and also, when someone is open, don't skank
it right next to them.
Skanking is generally discouraging.
Are you kind of a loose cannon surgeon, who like, scaw powers you through?
Have you ever had to knock on wood?
What's great is you could, you know, there could be like a, you know, I don't know much
about medicine, but like an aorta explodes.
I know less about scaw.
Yeah, right?
But an aorta explodes while you're doing heart surgery, and it's like, the pressure is on,
and then you can just look at the like, commanding surgeon, officer, and just be like, pick it
up, pick it up, pick it up, pick it up.
This man needs mouth to mouth, as you trombone into his mouth.
Trombone in his mouth, yeah.
Trombone into my mouth is.
That's a good name for your book, if you can have an alien play trombone.
From the creators of Call Me By Your Name.
Charles, I've lost the plot.
How can we help here?
Hey, go to your commanding surgical officer, Griffon Assange.
As Griffon has said, yeah.
Did you know Oscar Isaac was in a scaw band before he became famous?
You're going to change the story.
Sure.
He was in the Blinking Underdogs.
This is true.
I'm just a big fan.
Their music rules.
Yeah.
Sure.
What are some of your favorite scaw bands?
Everyone in the room.
Did they pull through?
Oh, yeah.
The surgery went great.
Great.
You can't say, oh, yeah, like it's obvious.
From what I understand.
It was seven hours long.
Charles was behind the retractor.
Of course it went smooth.
Yeah, sure.
Nothing detracted when it wasn't supposed to.
Did the patient wake up and was like, what the fuck was that?
Because I loved it.
You have my brain open and I got that shit without the radiation shielding of my skull
and skin.
And you're not supposed to.
I will say I followed up on them over the past several days and they have seemed pretty
chill.
Okay.
Wait.
The patient?
Yeah.
Nailed it.
I mean, you crushed it.
Did that happen?
Now, you know what it sounds like now.
You got to write a paper about scaw, my man.
Yeah.
The power of scaw.
And don't research it anymore.
You have all the evidence you need.
You did it.
Trust me.
Does that help, Charles?
Yes.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
This is, I don't know, Salt Lake City has, this is our second show here, it is so fun
every time.
Yeah.
We all get so rowdy and I'm so excited to be here.
I'm very, very here for it.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Salt Lake City.
And all the usual thank yous.
Thank you.
A huge thank you to Schmanners.
Thank you to Paul Saboren of Paul and Storm fame.
Thank you to the Abravanel Theater for having us.
This is our second show here and it's absolutely gorgeous.
Thank you to Tyler Reed for the amazing posters.
Yes.
Grab yourself a poster on your way out if there are still some.
Thank you to Rachel, yes, for manning the ones and twos over there recording our audio.
Sometimes even the threes.
Yeah.
I know.
It got wild.
Clinton McElroy.
You all know him?
And Carol McElroy, our stepmom, Carol is here too to make sure he doesn't wander into traffic.
That's always nice to have.
Oh, thanks to Montaigne.
Thanks to Montaigne for the use of our theme song, My Life is Better with You.
Thank you to Matt.
Oh, sorry.
Listen, if we don't get them out of here in the next minute, they're going to knock it
to Olive Garden.
Thank you, that's going to do it.
Yeah.
So Griff, just real quick, just a quick, real quick impression of Grandpa Dan ordering a
naked chicken chalupa at Taco Bell.
Easy.
Can I have a naked, chomping, cheeky, chubo?
My name is Justin McElroy.
This has been My Brother, My Brother.
Kiss your dad's square on the lips.