The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed
hello and welcome to my brother my brother mean advice show for the
modern era I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy well my name well it's
Travis aka big dog aka wolf in sheep's clothing aka Ruff Ruff McElroy and I'm
my name is Fredo cool jazz it's a new era my bim-bam baby new song new Pete
new characters new storylines new love new Rome I feel like going with Fredo is
a bold shot Griffin Fredo famously the brother who was the biggest
disappointment in Godfather of the three brothers I believe Fredo who's
Griffin I'm Fredo cool jazz and this is a different guy baby okay and we got
music new characters new storylines new places I've got a new cool thought
T-bird car that's gonna be in a lot of the scenes now and oh is it like a
character all its own yeah it's a and it takes place in New York City and yeah
and it's that's also kind of a character so you just heard our new theme song
it's called my life is better with you by Montaigne who is a very talented
artist who you should seek out immediately love to get her in on the
show it would be cool if we could get her on the show in the next like 28
minutes question comes along yeah yeah like later this episode yeah we'll see
yeah yeah it's maybe in the works it's wild it's it's wild enough to me that we
know somebody who's competing on Eurovision let alone that we have now
worked with somebody and will now be on a weekly basis sort of you know played
on by somebody who's gonna be on your vision and do you think that means we
can go to Eurovision ticks can we get can we compete will we be able to leave
our nation is that is a huge question in America we join Europe can we read
sub in sub in the UK's out that's fine sub us in baby I mean if they're
including Australia I'm just saying we're ready why not America let me we'll
start out by doing we'll infiltrate some backup dancers for some of the other for
some of the smaller countries that don't really have a shot and I feel like we'd
really blend in with like say uh-huh let me think maybe like France France yeah I
think we could get in there and get like experimental with it and then we'll take
off our masks at the end and be like it's us America and we can do it and we
can hang out too yeah and oh what's that we're building bridges both figuratively
and literally across the Atlantic Ocean yeah oh man you are so cool where's that
bridge thank you come on thank you it's 2021 let's build a bridge across the
ocean or under the ocean this is what I'm saying rich to Europe back to us
drive in your car you'll go very far hope it don't collapse actually it's a
walking it's a it's a walking it's like one of those escalator ground escalator
things you just kind of stand on it and you start a little life down there and
then like a month and a half later good good evening governor oh you're on the
other side here that's means you're on the other side and then we can change it
to like oh yeah under the pond and that's what we'll say across the pond
it's like oh I came under the pond in the tube and they're like on the subway
you're like no in the tube there's a tube it's about like three feet wide and
like six and a half feet tall it's very tight very dark do you know there's a
special British RSS feed of this show that just has content warnings but in
front of every episode everyone the people in Eurovision who are responsible
for Eurovision are gonna listen to the last two and a half minutes of this show
and say damn not yet they ain't ready yet to be called I feel like in three
minutes we started to establish new bonds and separate them violently oh boy
oh boy we should build the bridge over the Atlantic Ocean and then set fire to
it as we're driving in the last golden spike I love it hey can we do our show I
would love that actually that would be fantastic that would be cool yeah I feel
like we haven't done it in a while you know what I mean like I don't think we
answered any questions last week yeah did we not I don't know it got rowdy we
talked about here's a regular one okay oh my wife and I had our first baby last
year a girl she's now ten months old my father-in-law bought her a gift and he's
very excited to see her playing with the problem is it's clearly labeled a dog
toy oh yeah tag the tag say to keep it away from babies he ordered it online so
he may not have noticed this how do I navigate this without hurting his
feelings I can't tell him that he actually bought our daughter a dog toy
but I also don't want her to play with a dog toy helicopter parent am I right
yeah really and I'm free in California I like the ones where they set it up so
that there is no writing here there's two things that could happen both are
bad yeah so I've lived this we we were killing time at some strip mall
somewhere with Henry and he picked up a dog toy at a pet land we were just kind
of walking around cuz we thought hey maybe he'll look at fish and be
distracted for a little bit and he picked up a little little squishy dog
toy and enjoyed it and we took a picture must post it online and then my my my
mother and father-in-law sent that toy for Henry and he was like fuck yeah and
started to play with it and then we looked at the tag later like this is kid
poison this is this dogs love it kids hate it kids bodies hate it dogs bodies
can withstand it but don't let a child put this in his mouth whatever you do
whatever you do don't do that so what we did is we immediately took the toy away
and we told the parents and we said hey this is funny you got our human child a
dog toy and then we all had a good laugh about it and it was a mistake that was
never made again so really you gotta say something but make it fun be like you
poisoned my child that can be fun and then it's like they're not gonna feel
bad cuz it's like a funny joke what kind of toy is it cuz if he got her a
Nylabone it might be on purpose maybe he's just being really mean god I hate
brushing my son's teeth if I could just toss a Nylabone in there and let that
do the work enjoy that would be cool the kids don't appreciate if you've never
tried to brush the teeth of a human that does not want their teeth brush yeah
that is the one any place where kids can flex nuts they absolutely will right and
this is the one place where kids will can absolutely flex nuts on you and they
do every single fucking time yeah if you ever want to feel powerless be brushing
a kid's teeth and have them bite down on you're done and I can't pull on it
without some like marathon man bullshit that's gonna have you staring into the
mirror for the next two hours like questioning who you your very soul yeah
like there's no play you just let go of it at that point yeah all right
you let your teeth fall out they don't need those teeth anyway that's what I'm
saying that's why it's kind of hard we took BB to the dentist you know when it
was time cuz we're good parents or whatever and they're like yeah you got
to start flossing and I could think it's like ooh I don't know I'll bring her
back my friend how often can I bring her in yeah if we just chuck a bone in there
and let the bone do the brushing it's weird that there's not a child we got
that we got that we got that tech for dogs but I don't have that tech for
toddlers that's hey science how's your priorities pretty fucking bad I think
yeah actually thank you also a squeaker inside those things they'd love that I
would love that I'm just saying that I bought BB a lot of stuffed animals and
now dot a lot of stuffed animals and very few of them have like tough tech
technology that let him really rag doll him around to get that squeaker out I'm
just saying let's keep our kids a little busier and maybe make those true toys
last a little bit longer for the kids okay yeah um hey you wanna Yahoo yes
this one was sent in by several people thank you everybody it's extremely
unhelpful answer by the way yeah yeah no yeah do tell them I'm telling you I
lived this and I got through okay and it's fun so thank you everybody who sent
this in it's yahoo answers user Natalie who asks shipping a horse from Canada
to Australia I want to transport my horse from Canada to Australia in a few
years he is a gelding and at that time will be for is this dangerous to do can
he get sick for it how much will it cost about has anyone else done this that can
give please give me some information on this what are some good company that can
do this via ship or by air that can give me a quote gotta get is it and let's go
ahead and just say operation Dumbo drop out loud yeah and then we can move on to
like more creative waters okay I'm on a plane yeah now that that's out of the
way here's the problem I can think of so many ways to get a horse from Canada to
Australia yeah if they can be dead at the oh at the end of oh at the end of it
right well I guess the other way around wouldn't work would the other way around
you know some like powerful magic unless you kill the horse ship it left ways
over the international date line it shows up in Australia feeling Hale and
Hardy no that would be tomorrow fuck no still dead dead for a day it might
actually be easier to shoot the horse up into the sky in a rocket let the earth
rotate underneath it rocket come back down oh cool and land in Australia if it
goes might be easier and we could really interstellar it and launch around old
Jupiter up in the sky and have a cut slingshot all the way back and when it
comes back we have it's been ten years on earth but for the horse it's been
like nine years and like 11 months and it's still a lot of time it's pretty
it's pretty you would need to go how many seats would you have to buy on a
plane oh to go with before they let you take the horse on yeah carry on horse
yeah I've seen okay for reference yeah I once saw a large pitbull yeah that was
like a rescue animal that had been trained to be like an assistive animal
right and he I would put him at probably 80 pounds that's a little horse that's
this is what I'm saying so if we scale that up that was like one seat right
right so horse is what like 800 pounds that's 10 seats there's gonna be a
four-year-old horse so we're not talking about a little full straight out the out
the gate I'm checking the pet travel page on Delta okay and just control F
horse some pets can travel with Delta as a carry-on shipped as very special
cargo depending on their size okay review the requirements okay I'm
checking the guidelines and requirements okay yeah there's a section here on
inappropriate animal behavior so all rude dogs need not apply oh no not this
this ponies are real saint it's this ponies a fucking gentleman one of the
inappropriate animal behaviors is barking excessively not in response to
a handler's needs or distress yeah I want to I did listen it does that dog
sense distress because if so I need him to let me in on what the problem is
because we are in an airplane this dog's having a chill time and he's got his
favorite tunes plan and it's nice and cool in here but he's being extremely
loud art now are we 25,000 feet up in the air and is that uncomfortable for a
dog yeah one of the things one of the things that'll get your your pet kicked
off the plane is relieving themselves in the gate area or cabin if my dog
relieves themselves in the cabin obviously that's clear I actually that's
absolutely a hundred percent I'm with you I agree I would love to have this
dog off the plane too because it's obviously not working out what is your
plan right your ex Phil that's a threat hey yeah we're we're in the middle of
the ocean you gotta pop that door open even if you're that serious about it
that's putting others in danger I'm gonna steal you directly in the eye but
while Rex pisses in coach there they no longer allow as of January 11th 2021
they no longer allow what are listed here as non-dog service animals I love I
think all animals love to think of themselves as non dogs yeah so here's
what they don't permit small mammals or pocket pets like hedgehogs or sugar
okay that's not a problem this is a huge mammal so we're fine so far no
insects or spiders and to be fair I believe I will be the judge of that
because you will never know yeah there's no rodents mice rats the
hamsters they list they list out rodents mice rats hamsters gerbils guinea pigs I
feel like if I'm planning to bring an animal like that on the plane I should
at least know if it's a rodent or not right you don't have to specify you
don't mention chinchillas interesting now they do have they list here
amphibians uh-huh birds obviously they just get competitive right that with the
plane animals improperly cleaned or with a foul odor that's fine this this again
this ponies a gentleman it's gonna smell fucking so far we're in the clear yeah
this is good so far last one animals with tusks horns or hooves oh gee goats
and pigs but does not specifically list horses but they do have hook okay okay
I'm just saying some large sneakers yeah never know well but they x-rays so the
hooves can the hooves come off for like a minute do they regrow like Tony do
they come back and I'm sure this is a horrible thing to say I'm sure it hurts
and there's probably some monstrous sort of practice that is being done to
horses that is not funny in the least but this isn't fine this is serious
we're trying to solve a really serious issue or else this horse is gonna get
left behind the horse hang their hooves out the windows and they're not on the
plane that's good that's good you could also just bring them to the to the gate
and just be like look at it look at his big wet eyes that animals got hooves ah
fuck you're right he does oh well we can still get on right we're still cool
right we're still okay right I can tell you're a pretty cool person who
probably likes a hundred dollars am I right can you imagine get to the gate
with your your hoof list sneaker wearing horse that has been through hell and you
are walking up the tarmac and then the horse lets out a dookie and you're like
we were so close mr. Chamberlain fuck I I just want to say for the record I
think that lost would have been 25% better if there had been a horse
survivor on the island that had been on the plane the horse lands and then they
just treated it like another it was like there's yeah there's Jack yeah hey
there's Sawyer there's more Chamberlain there's her and every time they make
horse we gotta get off this island I would love that man I'd be so into that
yeah it's making me happy thinking about it one of the things they do list I
want to move from the FAQ page and this doesn't help us necessarily but I did
want to mention it they're one of the FAQs is what if I have a service or
support animal in training oh and they say that a service animal in training
does not meet qualifications for a trained animal but I do love the idea of
pull it up to the gate be like listen I'm gonna warn you right up front this
guy's a fucking loose cannon yeah he will serve he services me for sure but
sometimes he goes too far I've asked for his badge and gun repeatedly but he
won't step down I actually have to support animals one of them very by the
book yeah he's six months for retirement he's training this new rookie but that
rookie cannot be controlled and they butt heads but you know what they get
the job done and you're gonna be glad they're on this plane you're gonna be
glad they're on this plane yeah you may need some real service done but not maybe
off-book service right service they don't teach it service talk yeah cool
recently my girlfriend and I moved into a new house where the landlord
conveniently already provides the internet we're both biologists in our
late 20s and today discovered that safe search is on through some entirely
innocent and work-related web searches how do we ask our landlord to remove
safe search without him immediately jumping to the conclusion that we want
to desecrate his house with filthy unspeakable pornography that's from not
so lewd lodgers in Leeds UK well my theory my supposition would be that if
you have some sort of safe search software enabled some sort of sort of
net nanny mm-hmm that there's some sort of whitelisting that you could do right
which makes me know I feel like all you have to do is go to your landlord and
tell him exactly the nasty URLs that you are going to be exploring yeah this is
tough why because yeah I understand that it's probably 99.9 percent of the time
not from unspeakable things yeah but what about that point one percent you
don't want to go to him about K thanks for letting us look at like I don't know
bird genitals or whatever because we're biologists but also but we actually I
gotta tell you mark we accidentally did look at a dick today and we need you to
tighten up the algorithms mark this is a cool this is a Christian household
that's his deal his deal is he'll turn off safe search but if you it's a
otter system yeah you see anything that you're not supposed to you have to let
me know and I'll explain it to you yeah I'll make what you saw make sense I
promise I won't leave you alone in this hey mark I saw some and they look like
adults doing some stuff to each other like okay sit down I've walked so many
tenants through this okay it was the mommy daddy hug do you know what I'm
talking about you know mark also our disposals broken the disposals broken
and I can't get my sights to load where they do the special mommy daddy hug can
you come tweak both why are they dancing so hard mark they seem so angry at each
other there's no music if you're like there we're fairly positive that your
landlord is able to see your entire internet history right if this is the
setup like 100% right yeah yeah I guess it's literally like this sounds like
you're connected straight to his gmail account yeah you have to go borrow his
his his lappy his laptop the computer is in the dining room that you all share
and your landlord is also your dad yeah you just admit it your dad for
complimentary internet access you just have to come to my place and ask to use
my book yeah I'll crack it open for you my web book and it's just a sticker on
it it just says the internet on it wouldn't the dad lord lets us use the
internet sometimes we see some sites I think you should have a conversation
with work about whether he keeps the net nanny on on his computer yes if he's
doing that fair you know fair play fair play I was not he needs to let you get
all the nasty corners you need ask him if you can pay extra for the dirty
sites in your in your rental agreement well it will increase just like how you
have a pet addendum this is just like yeah you can look at whatever you want
for an extra $50 a month let me choose three dirty sites on your premium
package that sucks and it should I don't think it's legal I think you should be
able to do something about I don't know who you complain to the better biz the
Better Business Bureau somebody somebody I don't know if they do that in the UK
but this there's got to be there has to be an answer to this that we don't know
because it's such a preposterous situation it shouldn't be happening do
you have a 14 year old nephew who you could ask for like the creative
spellings of words that he uses oh yeah to like search yeah probably hook you up
he's probably got some weird ones he's like have you tried typing in Stiffy
Stiffy sometimes gets through and surprisingly teats works quite often if
you tape in teats but not cow sometimes you can get through teats minus cow
there's a thin crack in the wall I want to munch I want to munch breaking news
at this hour another update for the front lines oh no welcome to Munch Squad
chicken wars where we bring you the latest in greats and brand-eating as it
pertains to these heinous never-ending chicken sandwich wars that were in
fight has anyone died yet in the chicken sandwich wars not immediately but you
know they certainly are shortening lifespans right with these delicious
sandwiches I did try the new McDonald's chicken sandwich and I have to give it a
okay out of whoa right that's the highest possible rating right first
let's check in on Zaxby's they got a signature sandwich that is prepping for
a national launch all across its 909 locations in 17 different states dazzle
me come on folks dazzle me Zaxby's during a test that they launched in the
test market Zaxby's new signature chicken sandwich exceeded the
performance of the existing hand-breaded filet by six hundred percent whoa what
are they what does that is the next sentence yeah so we learned that our old
sandwich sucked shit oh fucking disgusting it was actually just a
flip-flop with salt we did not know it was so bad when it comes to portion
size flavor and quality ingredients Zaxby's is in it to win it says Joel
Bulger CMO while we may not be the largest brand competing in the sandwich
war I'm confident we have the right ingredients to win on taste and make
chicken sandwich enthusiasts switch to Zaxby's and we'll literally do whatever
it takes you ask and we'll do we will smooch everyone on earth till Zaxby's
is the most famous we will kill Colonel Sanders in all his forms yeah he can
shape-shift but we'll get him we will hunt the Colonel Sanders Horcruxes that
have kept him so how are we gonna know when the chicken sandwich wars are over
wait when we're all dead yeah we're all dead there's no one left to chew okay
back on October 26th the company fired off the tweet that reignited the chicken
sandwich wars since then numerous brands have entered the fray Zaxby's is
actively engaging in the battle of the brands on social media and converting
customers daily with a distinct taste and impressive size of its singular
chicken sandwich can I can I ask you something I want you to really think
this this just pods in my head what would be the real world ramifications if
Zaxby's just one day took to Twitter and with full support of all of their like
CEOs and leaders and stuff just tweeted Wendy suck shit Wendy's chicken
sandwich suck shit Wendy's has a pretty high fee Twitter account they could
probably get away with it honestly it gets it gets it let me finish this
release because I've got other news in the front to bring you Zaxby's
commemorated the national rollout with a quote buns fired tweet whoa and they
quote basic training tik-tok video cool showing employees gearing up for the big
holy shit imagine being so can I sidebar can you imagine being so fucking out of
it that you're reading a press release and you're like hmm a tik-tok video
they're really committed to this thing prior activations include a military
themed codename generator and chicken flage uniforms for team members in the
front line get the fuck out let's have fun with the military industrial complex
baby yeah retains a chicken yummy let's pivot over here a and w are you are you
I know you're a root beer but you're also a fast food chain are you up in the
mix I just want to read you this one quote because they're bringing back cod
sliders for lent this is how far off the ball they miss and I just wanted to
mention it because this absolutely inscrutable quote from from a and w with
many of the country's full-service restaurants closed or facing dine-in
restrictions a and w is pleased to offer consumers a variety of popular seafood
options says CEO Kevin Bessner I'm fucking asleep whether what no but like
what's the fucking weather guests enjoy them in our dining rooms that are open
or take them home and WC food items are tasty and affordable way to observe
lint it does kind of seem like you're like with many with many restaurants
closed we've been watching a lot of TV lately okay
fucking talk about Zach's pieces over here like we taught our employees how to
build improvised explosive devices right and here's our last update from burger
phi a chain I'm not familiar then then I and every time you do this Justin where
you bring one that nobody's heard of before it's usually the rowdiest
imaginable thing it's really rowdy after having nationwide success with the spicy
fried chicken sandwich burger fight international is launching a new type of
sandwich war what and this one has to do with burgers you can't well imagine if
in the middle of World War two someone's like we're starting World War three like
now you let's finish this one first shit yeah burger fires like December 7th is a
day that will live in infamy and it is about burgers so this one's about
burgers yeah is the burger fine menu is array of chef inspired selections and
high-quality Wagyu beef it was only name it was only natural for the premium fast
casual concept to take it to the next level with a one-of-a-kind spicy burger
sensation whoa the swag burger features double Wagyu and a brisket burger a
brisket blend burger charred jalapenos candy ghost pepper bacon to pack the
heat sweet tomato relish to add a bit of sweet habanero pepper jack cheese and
hot steak sauce so it's so I feel like we're in a lot of ingredient territory
already right it seems like there may be shooting the cannon into burger fights
credit it doesn't go out of sins there is a couple restaurants out there who
are so focused on the chicken war that they're not watching their home fronts
you know I mean here comes burger fire like sneaking in the back fuck you all
up y'all so busy worried about chicken we're here with that beef game for the
new product burger fi initiated a consumer research study focused on the
initial reaction to the product use utilizing its savory description to test
the appeal cool do you understand what I just said we asked people people what's
on the sandwich exactly we described this sandwich would y'all like that
would that good what if we added one more thing to it it says here in the
press release do you like it this burger is hot as fuck and I'll melt a hole
through the back of your skull do you want it yeah they conducted a concept
test on the flavor build product name and price if they're like okay what if
we called it Dave super smash burger that's pretty good what if instead of
four pieces of bacon you had three I don't know that seems less good okay no
did thank you does okay but Justin that does kind of makes sense as to why it's
called the swag burger why it's called the swag burger oh yeah I'm not there
yet over 2,500 participants were part of the study with approximately 500 people
per concept tested so what they said is they came up with five different rad
burgers the research proved invaluable in determining the selection of Wagyu
beef versus Angus beef in the burger wow that's a long way of saying that
let's check in with Paul Griffin burger fries chief culinary officer the CCO
burger fries foundation is burgers and because the spicy chicken wars have
been part of the cultural conversation over the past few years they're safe I
think it's cuz that's the only one they have something more they've picked a
little notch of the war that they could carve out for themselves right well it's
a war on many fronts you have the ground war you have the at sea you have the
sky ground before I see the grilling war yeah the chicken wars have been part of
the cultural conversation over the past few years is that really I mean I know
you guys talk about it a lot but I haven't heard a single human being alive
references we've been talking about it a lot Justin well in our little corner of
culture which is obviously a biased sample yeah one where you talk about
fast food all the time the proc it's this whole thing started as a way to
find a new chick-fil-a that everyone can eat without feeling like dog shit about
it and it started out as emotionally started out as something fun and it
started as something virtuous and everybody was just like all hands on
deck but then it turned into well I think Popeye's is the best replacement
well I think Zaxby's is the best replacement and then Popeye's and
Zaxby's was like it's a war baby and it's not we're having fun while thwarting
fucking chick-fil-a but can we remember what it's all about and now other people
are talking about like no it's burgers war now it's gonna be car war I will say
Griffin that there's still some virtue to it I see a lot of young folks out
there they're you know they're recycling their scrap metal they're turning in
their nylons to support the troops out there sure everybody's a part of this
effort Griffin I won't sit here and let you besmirch the honor yeah of our
troops you know what I mean and Griffin I think maybe if you had a little bit
more patriotism thank you um it cared a little bit more about the chicken wars
just let me wrap this up please Paul Griffin is not done Paul Griffin could
have stopped there but instead Paul Griffin continued once we had the idea
of the spicy burger it was fun to start playing with ingredients and texture it
was the best day of my life it was so fun this has been actually super fun the
candy ghost pepper bacon is perfect for those guests are more adventurous and
that makes with the boldness of Wagyu and the creamy and this and the kick of
habanero pepper jack cheese it really rounds out the burger to make it one of
the most flavorful menu items at burger fight and you could tell the person like
dictating this it was just like still nodding and maybe Paul was like um I say
something else or are we okay that seems like enough that's good yeah I should
stop there taking this while sitting on the toilet they had been sitting on for
the last hour and a half trying to pass one of these through their system but
then Julio Ramirez the burger fight CEO yeah he heard Paul fucking bomb right so
he throws open the door he's like hold on let me take this one the swag burger
takes our unique Wagyu beef offering featured in our CEO burger and it kicks
it up a notch with different textures and flavors that create a daring
spiciness with each bite is there anyone above the CEO who can kick in another
door behind him hey it's me it's me the owner of burger fire Justin McElroy I
want to tell you about this burger and that's how we find out the truth
creating the spicy burger sensation is another example of how we're
redefining the way world eats burgers okay oh boy
burger fi will always find ways to continue to grow pioneer trends and
create iconic offerings as part of our mission to provide the best burger
experience okay damn I could go for a burger no yeah I get I mean that's the
one that's the terrible part about this segment is I always end up extremely
yeah do you know what this is gonna be the worst outcome for burger fi is that
no one will rise to their challenge no one will even acknowledge that they have
attempted to start a burger war and if and life's just gonna go on without
burger fi sort of being a part of it and that's him that's gonna be embarrassing
they're gonna have to get more thirsty with these press releases
Julio Ramirez was a Burger King for 26 years then he knows what he's doing he
knows what he's oh yeah he's better get said at your fucking parent he came in
in October 2020 okay are you kidding me can you think of a more challenging time
to step into these waters Julio doesn't give a shit anyway that's
that's a update please let me know if you tried different chicken sandwiches
you can just tweet those at Barack Obama and you know maybe he would like to know
about it or you could to him at me if you want I just always like to try to
get people to tweet an Obama because I bet he's lonely right now you don't have
presidents have to do anymore yeah do you think he's ever like Joe do you
need any help I president stuff today hey Joe I don't want to be I don't want
to be a dickhead joke but when I was president I let you help me with stuff
yeah so just doesn't it seem like maybe I could come by you're in office I'll
let you hang out help me with different stuff so maybe you just got I mean the
kids are growing up now Joe there I did give you that big medal
Joe look at it you remember so we're gonna take a quick break and right now
and then we'll come back with more great content until then let's kick it over to
the money zone
stamps are great you can put them on mail to make the mail go places and you
can collect them and create decks of stamps that you battle against other
folks for their stance that lasts forever sure yeah there's stamps that
lasts forever and then there's hollow hollow foil ones yeah and they're chase
there's chase stamps and those can be fun but going you know it's not fun it's
just going to the post office when you're not feeling like it well stance
calm is gonna keep you from having to make such a dreary afternoon of it
because they let you print off postage right there it's your freaking computer
you can send letters or packages and you can pay a lot less with discounted rates
from USPS UPS and more so it cuts out a lot of the BS yeah I think and yeah
whoever do a stamps calm and so good that they'll put us on stamps oh man
though we could probably get them to put us on stamps calm like a picture of us
like having a great time battling our stamps against each other but I don't
know if they would actually put us on the postage itself I want to be on the
postage I want to do that that feels like a cool thing that not everybody
gets to do right well gotta be president or go to space and make a big space
so much work though can I just do a really good ad read in the middle of my
podcast you gotta invent some medicine go to space and make a space discovery
or be the president trap they got discounts up to 40% off post office
rates and up to 62% off UPS shipping rates it's a wild deal and if you ship a
lot of stuff you should I assume you're already using stamps calm but if not
correct that mistake stop wasting time going to the post office and go to
stamps calm instead there's no risk and with our promo code my brother all one
word you get a special offer that includes a four-week trial plus free
postage and they stopped doing the digital scale just kidding I still
definitely do the digital scale there's no long-term commitments or contracts
freaked me out you prank I shit myself when you Travis shit I shit and I'm in a
small booth Griffin yeah now this whole booth smells like shit well go to
stamps calm and click on the microphone at the top of the home page and type in
my brother all one word that's stamps calm promo code my brother all one word
stamps calm go to the post office every day that was another prank they don't
want you to please don't never please don't please don't go to oh you know
what we never do that stamps calm go to stamps calm calm please and use the
promo code my brother please please speaking of sheeting yourself I want to
tell you about Brooklyn and this is the fastest we've had to do a make good yeah
this is the fastest they're actually monitoring this recording and they've
just told I just actually went to speedrun calm he said fastest fuck add
fuck up to require a make good shit yourself today with Brooklyn calm cool
they got the best sheet around you're not getting too old for this sheet no
perfect age this sheet is right up your alley sorry read the copier it says
please do not make any jokes about how sheet kind of sounds like oh I love my
sheet my sheet don't stink you know I'm in so cuz I wash them I'm
gonna start reading the ad copy underneath this and try to get fast
start over this is a new app now okay that was all disconnected yeah now it's
time for the make good it's great some mornings you wait what's wrong what's
wrong I'll do it okay everybody sleeps if we're
lucky and sometimes you gotta upgrade your presentation in bed if you have
ever woken up if you've ever woken up and not been able to move because some
kind of sleep ghost is holding you down that's because of bad sheets yeah
Brooklyn sheets aren't bad she know it's the first direct consumer bedding
company they work directly with manufacturers to make luxury available
directly to you without the luxury level markup and they're guaranteed not
haunted yeah Brooklyn has a variety of sheets colors patterns materials to fit
your needs and tastes even if that need is to cut two holes for eyes and have a
great easy Halloween cause then that's fake haunted let's be clear that's not a
real ghost a real high out human interact these are not haunted guaranteed
kidding aside I love these oh wait hold on sorry let me switch gears okay
kidding aside go out of the room I love these sheets they're really good I sleep
great and you know what's great every time I wash them which is the normal
amount and frequency not too much not this think in your head of what the just
about exact average normal amount is and that's how much I do it yep once they
just get softer for me I think it was once a college oh they got more than
sheets by the way they got comforters pillows towels even loungewear and more
go to Brooklyn and calm and use promo code my brother to get $25 off when you
spend $100 or more plus free shipping that's B R O OK L I N E in calm and
enter code my brother to get $25 off when you spend $100 or more plus free
shipping Brooklyn and calm and use promo code my brother at checkout Brooklyn and
that's the good sheet you I now we gotta I'm not starting over now we'll get it
that was a different thing that wasn't the commercial anymore
hey folks it's me James Arthur M hosts of minority corner your home through
these but wild times for weekly doses of pop culture history news nerdy stuff and
more through a VIP OC queer and allied lens I already took you back in time
through one time machine we're going back even further I'm holding on I know
it seems scary because now we're in the 1830s I know continuing along on the
white people's apology for Justin Timberlake that is minority corner
having those difficult conversations those necessary conversations this is
now the moment for for white people to be rising up and going this is our
problem so join me and some of your new BFFs every Friday here on maximum fun to
stay informed empowered and have some fun minority corner because together
we're the majority a here's a here's another question from our dear listeners
I'm a college student and decided to spontaneously bleach my hair at home
it's kind of a disaster flash forwards now I want to get it cut but I'm
absolutely terrified the hairdresser will somehow find a way to yell at me
for bleaching my hair at home what should I do if I get bombarded with guilt from
a professional that's from son of a bleach in Ohio there is no one in the
contiguous United States of America that would know how to answer this question
I'm going through my US contacts I'm fucking coming up empty oh you know who
can help yeah we could reach across the pond and then down through the bigger
pond across the pond a sort of diagonal vertex across many pond let's just call
call Australia I think it's like I know it's like Friday there what do you
yeah it's Friday so sure I didn't have the answer Montaigne we'll just call
Montaigne who created who created the my brother my brother me theme song yeah
right there you heard earlier so let's just call hold on don't forget to dial
the extra numbers oh thanks now you're saying you great
extra number thing I didn't bring bring hey hello it's Montaigne hi Montaigne
I'm Justin McElroy you probably saw that on the caller ID though I'm actually
you know so I don't have it saved but I'll wait yeah no I'll do it give me a
sec all of our guests do this I did it really very very uncomfortable for me
and Travis if he asked you about LinkedIn just hang up thank you so much for for
answering this I think unsolvable paradox for us and also for writing one
one real slap in tune slap a rip the first thing is now that I'm 40 there's
literally no good way for me to refer to a piece of music I mean like there's
not there's nothing that is it woefully sort of antiquated or like sweaty beyond
all recognition yeah that's why I just lean into it at this point and I just
say like this is a swinging to but I have to hear you say I have to hear you
say that cost the real human cost Montaigne you have hair I actually I have
I've pretty little hair at the moment I have a buzz cut and it's yeah sorry but
you've met you've met you've messed around with your hair probably at
different times you know others with hair how do you deal with okay you're in a
professional setting I know I just want to say I know that the concedes that we
need in Montaigne's Hell on this I also have dyed hair I'm just gonna say no
it's not the same Montaigne you're a professional setting with people how do
you how do you deal okay I'll give you I'll re I'll refigure it for like your
experience when you're talking to a nobody like ourselves about music and
you know so much about music yeah where where are you at with that are you in
like a judgmental place usually are you in a place where you're like wanting to
help where are you at definitely not um definitely not judgmental that I yeah
yeah music is for everyone you know no matter how much knowledge or wisdom is
involved it is you know to be shared and loved in whatever way that each
individual person wants it to be shared and loved and I think like you guys good
with that love music I think so definitely no judgment there very nice
I think that's very pleasant if you go to a hairdresser with a bad home bleached
on they're not going to be angry at you they're going to judge you and feel bad
for you it's going to be you're gonna hear a lot of oh yeah to carry the
analogy when I'm sure when Montaigne heard my Rugrats theme song for the
show Montaigne what didn't send me an email like you suck shit yeah don't do
music I genuinely loved I genuinely loved the Rugrats cover quite frankly I
thought it was so nice if you loved it so much Montaigne we're gonna need that
huge novelty check back that we left on your on your back for now just forward
that to class what's your approach to hair do you just feel like you were
talking about you keep it very short right now is that just like the look you
like do you experiment a lot do you just say like hey whatever just sort of
entertains you right now that's what I'm going with I've had the same haircut
since I was six my approach is fairly impulsive I'd say for the Eurovision
stuff in particular I had a very particular aesthetic that I wanted which
was have really short buzz cut hair that is like ultra colorful so my hair for
Eurovision will be quite rainbow and buzz cut it but like a year ago my hair
was just like natural color like short but not buzz cut and then the year
before that was blue it was quite long and the year before that was pink so
just like whatever I feel like really must be nice keeping keeping everybody's
heads on swivel exactly I made the mistake of having my purple hair become
part of our merchandise and now Justin and Griffin won't let me change it you
know you mentioned Eurovision I that's such a coincidence because your your
Eurovision track see even track like track my mouth it turns to actual my
lips Technicolor is the name of the song the video came out today as we're
recording this I gotta go almost go as you're listening to it it's called
Technicolor you can find it on YouTube I think it's streaming on Spotify
Eurovision that's massive congratulations thank you it is big in a
way that I find rather intimidating really yeah oh my god I'm like no not
really big I know it's big you seem so cool and confident I think I mostly am I
think every like other week my anxiety will start to like build up there a
little bit just because like there's a lot I think the issue is that there's
this enormous compression of like time and the number of things that we can get
done in a certain number of time and you want to do things well and when you don't
have time it's hard to do that in a way that is like foolproof so that's been
a bit of a stress oh yeah thanks for wasting time on our song this to God
literally a dream come true we're gonna talk about that and just one second I
want to talk about Technicolor for one more second cuz it is so fucking good
and if you go listen to it you're gonna listen to it on repeat everybody on our
staff has been listening to it literally constantly sharing the be around we are
in love with it I I want to ask you I was watching the the performance video
today that did you wish at any point while you have been recording in this
and do you ever wish you put fewer notes in it because maybe you guys sing a lot
of notes in front of like but a bajillion people on a massive stage
you're like god I put a lot of notes in this mother fucking five notes not five
but certainly not this many it's a lot honestly there is very little time to
breathe in the song which is quite difficult because we have organized
this choreography for it as well I think like all of it is manageable if I
stand still but I've I've opted I've opted not to which country are you most
gunning for yeah yeah I don't know if you guys paid any attention to Eurovision
last year but Iceland put forward the most ripping guys like absolutely
fantastic god it makes you mad how good it is
Jimmy comes up listen this fucking song it's amazing and the video and the
conceit like it's about his unborn or like too little to have any
consciousness kid who's wondering about the thoughts of and it's just like so
sweet and the video is so funny it's just he's amazing I'm actually a huge
fan of him you're gonna crush him right you guys you guys you guys heard this
song right here here I want to play you five seconds of the song I'm allowed to
like Eurovision I don't care and just be quiet for a
second unbelievable but you're gonna beat their ass beat them all the way
back to Iceland um hey let's talk about the my brother my brother me theme song
which I guess is not gonna be called I titled it in the file I sent to you my
life and then in brackets is better with you exclamation mark from my brother my
brother and we can work on that we can Sufjan it up a bit and just be like in
brackets just be like a fateful occurrence on the shores of the on the
great wide Mississippi exactly yeah what what is amazing about your song is we
had a very I mean it couldn't have been a more abstract brief that we slid across
your proverbial desk I didn't find it abstract at all actually I thought was
really clear oh well that's good to hear but you really I mean we told you sort
of kind of what we were in the market for and it's like you reach into our
brains and found a song that somehow fulfilled all of it without us being
able to like actually articulate any of that so how'd you do that I guess is my
question which is I mean I am your demo like I was already a listener of the
show for like a few years and like I'm into comedy and Sam and my partner
writes funny things and yeah I guess like that's already a genre and a type
of music that I'm familiar with and amenable to and enjoy making a lot and
also like there's a bit of a 2000s revival happening right and like let's
sort of based on the brief I what I imagined was a kind of like high school
coming-of-age like comedy film where it's like incredibly corny and but very
like instead of being about awful boys who do terrible things in high school it
was gonna be about like these two friends who like meet each other and
they just generally oh hello my cat captain poodles has just walked in yeah
it was just gonna be about like two wholesome friends who like meet each
other enjoy each other's company and then realize like oh this is really
great and my life is is nice and I thought that was that fit the vibe of
the show yeah it's great who's the friend who's the friends and I get like
if we're gonna miss to miss if you want sir I can make no no no because I want
this to be like the who's the me and my brother my brother and me I we need more
we need more mystique around our show at this point we've given so much away it
makes me you know the fact the first time I thought about it listen to the
song and this is so I don't know this is perhaps overly modeling but um it it
really exemplifies the way that not how I think about my brother is really at
all but okay that's kind of a zero sum but how I think about our our listeners
like the people who listen to the show like it really captures my the
exuberance I have for like making stuff for them and because of the pandemic
like the extent to which I have missed seeing people like seeing people that
like listen to our stuff and meeting our listeners who are kind of like an
extended family for us like it really captured that that sense I have like not
kind of a little bit of the the bittersweet part of like missing seeing
them and missing seeing them in person and doing shows for them but also like
how how much they have improved our life just by listening to our stuff it really
captures that energy I didn't get that at all cool that's all right that's
music for you huh it just made it made me miss going to the movies you know what
I mean like why'd you have to cut out my rap verse yeah let's talk about the
third and fourth and fifth verses that we wrote for the song that you did not
include you know what Griffin we'll include it now Griffin if you just want
to do it yeah well the problem is in the note that I got back from Montana and I
thought it was fair and I didn't have an answer to it she said this is mostly
numbers right I said that's I guess you have a good point there I hadn't thought
about it is that this this verse is most it's more numbers than words and it is
basically math equation and you did and you said that doesn't match the vibe and
I took that I took that very personally yeah I'm sorry but sometimes the truth
hurts and you're just gonna live with it and and and grow strong and move on you
know do you think it's weird Martin that your song technicolor includes the line
yeah I promise you yes all you nasty dudes and that's not in our song it
seems impossible that you wrote that lyric but it's not part of our again it
didn't feel like it fit the vibe of the song but again if we do a remix and I'm
happy to splice the two and make a technicolor move in BAM themed mashup I
want to do a remix of the song that's just this song exactly as it is but it
includes clips from the show interspersed like they do I'm like Batman Michael
Keaton come in like of good good work last time you all watch the kids from a
rose music video because it's just shots from the movie interspersed with seal
like standing next to like a floodlight and it's all lit the same as the movie
clip yeah like so it's like seal is on it I'm on an adjacent rooftop I'm
watching Batman and Nicole Kidman Montaigne what's next for you obviously
very focused on Eurovision that's gonna be this spring and then what's what's
what's after that um maybe album three I guess last year I made a lot of music
with the same guy who did the theme song and who did the Eurovision song and I
think it's probably it's probably adding up to a third album which I'm excited
about who is that who is that that did his name's Dave Hammer Dave Hammer yeah
he's a key guy his name is Dave Hammer and you waited now to mention it he his
name is Dave Hammer well his real name is David Haddad but his his like former
official sort of name is Dave Hammer both great names his real name is dr.
smashing style but yeah so just like a lot of hammer based music production in
the studio that's not true no he's a really awesome lovely person who
listens to all my crazy ideas and yeah just so easy to work with and we've made
really really cool stuff like over the last year which I'm really excited about
and hopefully can do more of this coming well I we're so thrilled to have you as
part of our sort of extended extended extended family and I stuttered that I
didn't mean to say extended seven times because it really it really imbued it
with a distance and arms reach that I do live very far away but oh my god Montaigne
when we do get down there to or over there it's kind of down it's basically
down it's a perspective in it but when we get down there we'll do a shot you
will do a show together it's gonna be great I just gonna say really quickly as
well I recently did an interview from like the Mardi Gras event with Courtney
Act who's this amazing drag queen and was done on top of the Harbour Bridge
and what was so funny to me it was like entering the facility where they like
hosts the Harbour Bridge climbs and stuff like that they have all these
pictures of like all these celebrities who've done the bridge climb and I
forgot like how much of a staple of like tourism and like celebrities visiting
Australia that was like doing the bridge climb because like everyone like the
village people had a photo there and like Danny Radcliffe when he was 11 and
like all these people it was very funny anyway you guys go to the bridge climb
and I climb a bridge sure yeah absolutely okay we got a bridge here
that Montaigne all right over we've all got breaks over the New River to West
Virginia it's over the New River Gorge which is a just a massive thing very
deep hole like really gorgeous it's a deep hole and it's weird the weirdest
thing about it is there's this thing called bridge day where for one not real
for one day it's legal to jump off the bridge like yeah but very localized to
be clear jump off the bridge like with a parachute yeah with the parachute or
base jump or whatever your flavor is but there's this I don't know how I just
wish I had been there when it started so he's like okay everybody I've
adopted to make a sheriff everyone can jump off the bridge today asking that's
really funny that's great thank you so much for for being with us and thanks
for the help and thanks for writing our song where can people find more Montaigne
oh man so many places there's obviously like you said like my music streams on
Spotify but it also you know Apple music and you should build all that stuff I
also twitch stream and I like make music live on my twitch often I haven't
streamed for a while because I've been so tanked with like Eurovision stuff but
me my partner also sometimes just play games and I also have a discord if
anyone wants to join the disco it's a really wholesome lovely place we've
mostly just sent each other pictures of like our animals gosh what else I think
that's kind of it and like if you live in Australia or in Sydney you'll
probably see me around on the street because I've got the brightest head
visible from all kinds of kilometers away nice all right thank you so much
enjoy the rest of your morning night fantastic nice one that times a charm
Norris thank you guys for having me so much hey guys real thank you so real
quick before we wrap up I just shared a link and the slack I want you guys to
look at this tweet because just real quick I want you to think about what the
implications of this are I've never watched The Masked Singer before but
apparently it was revealed that the giant snail contained well you see in
the video a celebrity and it was this really weird reveal and then the
celebrity in the giant snail when you guys see it just say it out loud hey
kidding me with this this is so unfair
spoilers for The Masked Singer but the giant snail was Kermit the Frog what
does that mean what does that mean hey how was anybody supposed to fucking
guess that how what is that wait what does that mean but Kermit the Frog who's
Kermit yes thank you but it wasn't Kermit it was the person it was that's not
that's nothing I'm so fucking furious but hey you got us talking didn't you
Holly we're got us again thank you so much for listening to our program we
hope you've enjoyed yourself we know that we've enjoyed doing a show for you
and just wanted to say we got a book about podcasting called everybody has a
podcast except you if you want to learn how to podcast you just want to read a
funny book by some brothers yeah then go for it also I want to say that my
brother Travis McElroy has a twitch channel I stream not an FMV game with
him the last week as you're listening to this I'm sure we'll do it again it's a
really fun channel and he's got a good energy it's a fun watch yeah it's
twitch.tv slash the Travis McElroy I can't go on I can't go I got banned
from twitch for playing a whole Beyonce record yeah well I'll sneak you on okay
just don't do it again I'll try not to hey we got a new graphic novel coming
out in July called The Adventure Zone Crystal Kingdom it's a the fourth
adaptation of our D&D podcast goof show and you can pre-order it right now at
theadventurezonecomic.com it would be real cool if you did that well there's
also we've as we've repeatedly said the pandemic will be completely over by the
time that book comes out and you'll be able to read it in large gatherings
shoulder-to-shoulder with your shoulder-to-shoulder no masks in the
trash it will have fixed COVID by the time it is released so that's we have
some cool merch over at McElroyMerch.com pin of the month it's sausage to me
benefiting feeding Texas we got the empty bowl pin which is designed by
Samuel Reardon we got the 20 big dog run pin designed by Mel Westfall all that
over there and more McElroyMerch.com thank you to Maximum Fun our podcast
home thank you to all you for listening and supporting our show and thank you to
Montaigne for the new theme song yeah a real bopper and thank you also Montaigne
for being on the show that's two two thanks is for Montaigne go listen to all
of Montaigne's music right now if you if you enjoyed the theme song you've never
really dove in to Montaigne's catalog you are a viewer a fucking lucky duck my
friend yeah cuz there's a lot of good stuff waiting for you hey do you want
the final yes please okay this final yahoo was
sent in by Graham Roebuck thank you Graham it's asked by yahoo answers user
sprimbles jackhammer who asks how many hot dogs is too many to eat before mouth
surgery my name is Justin McElroy I'm Travis McElroy I'm Griffin McElroy this
has been my brother my brother may kiss your dad square on the lips
maximum fun org comedy and culture artist-owned audience supported