Hello, what you are about to hear is a podcast.
And what that means is we're gonna talk into microphones
and then broadcast it on pods, in your iPods.
You're gonna hear this on your iPod.
And so I just wanted to give you an intro
in case you were confused as to what was happening.
Sometimes we'll say pretty silly stuff.
But we're not being wrong.
We're doing a joke to make you laugh.
And also, I wanted to say to my grandpa, Dan,
who I asked to listen to this one.
Well, I'm glad that you figured, I knew you could do it.
Yeah.
I knew you could do it, G-Pod Dan.
I knew you could listen to a podcast.
Downloaded it through Napster and now you're listening to it.
And listen, folks.
Thank you for pirating our podcast, Grandpa Dan.
Just a little prologue.
You're gonna hear us make some pretty obscure references
and you're gonna think, oh, I don't get this
because I'm not a regular listener.
But the truth is you don't get it
because you're not one of the three of us
and sometimes not even then.
Yeah, true.
Sometimes the things we say just isn't funny.
No, listen.
And it's nothing.
We'll be interrupting the show throughout
to try to give you some context,
but we think you're set up now.
What you're gonna hear next is the introduction.
Now, in my brother, my brother and me,
this is our show that we do.
That's where we normally do sort of a slice of life,
skewed view, twisted perspective on current events.
Sometimes we talk about movies for a really long time
and it's unclear even to us
if we're actually excited about them or not.
And sometimes when we struggle to think
of something funny to say, we just cuss a lot.
So please be prepared for that.
That's kind of throughout though.
That's not just an introduction thing.
We're gonna begin now, okay?
But if you get scared at any point,
please, please tell one of us and we will stop.
Just raise your hands.
It's an interactive experience.
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
The McElroy brothers are not experts
and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert,
but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids,
which I mentioned only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
One, two, three, four.
It's the start of something beautiful.
A small acquaintance has blossomed.
It's ripen into a precious friendship.
I could have never seen what was coming for me.
Hangs at the skate park, hangs by the beach.
My life, it feels like life.
Oh, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, oh, it's better, it's better with you.
This is true, oh, it's better, it's better with you.
My life, oh, it's better with you.
Hello, everybody, and welcome.
Oh, no, wait, no, Justin.
Quieter.
No, why is it quiet?
They can like hot, just because they're new
doesn't mean they don't like it fucking hot.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hello, everybody, and welcome.
Wait, this is the music we always play.
Okay, hello, everybody, it was too annoying.
I couldn't even do more than this.
It's so short, every episode.
Hey, everybody, welcome to My Brother, My Brother,
the advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I've always said modern like that.
Yeah, and then I'm gonna say middle-est,
which isn't a real word as far as I know,
but I am the most middle, right?
And I'm, oh, I'm also gonna say like a big dog woof woof,
and that's because every year we brand the year,
and this is 20 Big Dog Run.
What does that mean, you ask?
I don't know.
And I'm your middle-est brother,
Travis Big Dog Woof Woof McElroy.
What's up, shit stains?
Whoa, wait, now hold on.
Griffin has never brought this energy before.
I think Griffin's trying to re-brand.
That's sort of how I come into the beginning of it.
Every episode is very complicated.
It's not, don't lie to them, they don't know the joke.
That is never, you've never done it before.
Is it the voice?
Do you think is it the voice?
You called them shit stains, Griffin.
Hold on, let me try it, let me try again.
What's up, skid marks?
No, well, that's, I mean, better.
That's noticeably better.
It's better.
Not quite, it feels more affectionate,
it has an affectionate energy.
What's up, droopy drawers?
It's Griffin McElroy, the youngest one.
But Griffin, you're usually kind of the sweet one,
and I'm kind of the bad boy in the group.
And I need you to bring some more like sweet energy
so people know that like you're the safe one.
What's up, shit stains?
Okay, just to get some questions out of the way
for new listeners, this is the Max Fun Block Party,
which is where we're trying to onboard new people,
say welcome in.
This show actually doesn't lean on,
people accuse us of doing a lot of in-jokes.
I try to avoid that actually, hilariously.
I try to avoid that in this show.
It just is a lot of non-secret, it's a lot of times.
It feels like in-jokes that you assume like,
oh, people have listened before,
understand what they're talking about.
But as I said earlier, no.
No, no, but we're trying to make, here's the setup, right?
We're actual ass brothers, like real brothers.
Not a joke, we're the McElroys who grew up together.
Our dad's Clint, we do the Adventure Zone together.
And we have done since 2010, April 2010,
we've done an advice program that you are now listening to
and enjoying, we hope, I mean, right now.
So we've been doing it for a long time.
This is our 580th episode.
And the show has evolved,
but not as much as like you would think, right?
It's not like, you know, a general hospital
where 11 years later it would be unrecognizable.
This is still basically the same thing.
It's the same stick, but we're a lot tireder.
That's true, we're older now, we've got kids.
And God knows how many at this point.
And I also know- We have six kids, two each.
You can't do this.
Oh, you're right, you're right.
This is our first year of the show, we have two kids.
We have two kids each, six total.
We share two kids.
We have two kids, it's a timeshare program.
We went in together to buy the kids.
We each get four months.
But, and I know what you're wondering,
I've been listening now to the show for a while
and they haven't given any advice yet.
Anybody get used to that.
That doesn't happen.
Not as much advice these days.
We're not qualified in any way.
And we've also, at this point, as you said,
581 episodes in, basically answered
every problem the world has.
There's nothing new under the sun.
Right, it's just no one listens is the problem.
Yeah.
You know what I mean, no one listens.
No one ever does always say, yeah.
Well, it's because Bob Ball back there in the beginning
is like, don't listen to the brothers.
And it's like, God damn it, Bob Ball.
So, I know you're wondering,
if this is a block party, where is the snacks?
Where are the snacks?
The answer is, you gotta download them.
We are uploading pictures of some amazing snacks.
I made a Jell-O mold.
Yeah, Travis did a Jell-O mold.
I got some pimento pasta salad.
Ooh.
And that's gonna be a beautiful JPEG.
And you're gonna really taste the highlights
and shadows and colors on that one.
So, enjoy that.
We got some bands coming out.
What's up, Blues Traveler coming out
on main stage at 7 p.m. Not him.
Not gonna have, not, it's Blues Traveler,
but without John Popper, because he kind of sucks.
Oh, okay, well then it's a harmonica-free
Blues Traveler experience.
It's just kind of an acoustic, non-harmonica Blues Traveler.
Let me be rad if the Blues Traveler guy one time
forgot his harmonicas, like he left his harmonica vest
in his trunk with all his guns.
And when the concert started, that's when he realized
that he had to make harmonica noises in his mouth.
Let's see if anybody noticed.
Hey, does anybody have any like wax paper
I can put on the comb?
Anybody?
Damn it.
I went to Juilliard.
So, just to kind of start, do you know where
Dracula's setting music?
Where?
Boo-li-yard.
Oh, God.
Why would it be Dracula and not a ghost?
Dracula doesn't say fucking boo.
The past seven minutes of recording that we have done
have been, not a joke, a pretty good cross-section
of the experience we provide here.
Well, I thought this would be a good opportunity
for people at home to maybe get to know us
on a deeper level.
And Colin sent this in, and this is just kind of
a getting to know you icebreaker question.
The original question here on some kind of web forum was,
what would be the worst torture to you?
And a woman named Laura answered,
you make me live in a cabin in the mountains in winter,
and every Saturday I would have to host a garage sale,
and you would not give me any frozen or fresh vegetables
or fruits to eat.
That is the worst torture Laura can imagine.
So, I want to deposit to us,
what is the worst torture we can imagine?
I'm not gonna go with anything better
than Laura Williams-May, who, by the way,
put in her bio, Laura Williams-May, comma,
I offer alternative explanations and viewpoints.
Indeed.
Good on ya.
And you can tell that because Laura has offered
almost 13,000 answers to questions
on whatever website this is.
They're almost all about how little she wants to be
in a cabin in the mountains in winter
and host a garage sale every Saturday.
Are these, do you think that these are three
like stacking tortures, or like,
you have to live in a cabin?
Oh man, this sucks, but I think I could get used to this.
Well, guess what?
This Saturday, you have to host a garage sale.
Oh man, well, every Saturday.
God damn it.
Well, at least give me some fresh or frozen vegetables
or fruits to eat while I'm hosting the garage sale.
Wait, why are you laughing?
I like that Laura has now,
that's all the vegetables and fruits, Laura.
Frozen or fresh, right?
That's it.
I mean, I guess dried.
Canned.
That's a different kind.
Canned, yeah.
Pickled.
Mushed.
She only likes them frozen or fresh.
Yeah, that's her deal, man.
It's one of the two opposite ends of the spectrum.
Okay, so here's what we do.
We take questions from listeners,
we answer them to the best of our ability.
We're gonna try to get through more than usual,
which is to say more than one, or maybe two.
Let's see how, let's do it.
During lunch, I accidentally dropped a few black beans
and they wrote, by the way, I feel like we never say this,
but if you have a question, you can send it to MBMBAM,
I know what you're thinking.
Wow, a very bad nickname for a podcast.
And yes, you are not wrong, MBMBAM at MaximumFun.org.
Hey, another thing real quick.
Speaking of the bad name of our podcast,
a listener pointed out on the YouTube comments,
cause I was watching our theme song by Montaigne,
cause my kids love it.
They pointed out that my brother, my brother and me
fits exactly with the cadence of the chorus.
My brother, my brother and me.
Yeah, that's fun, that's good stuff.
It's fun.
Anyway, okay, so I accidentally dropped a few black beans
and they rolled under my cubicle into my coworkers
that sit straight across from me.
This is already a nightmare.
And just, oh, for listeners at home, you might be confused.
This didn't happen to Justin.
Justin is reading a question from a listener
and it's written in first person,
but Justin is merely the conduit.
Yeah, sometimes I'll just launch right into him
and you think I'm talking about myself
and then at the end I'm like doofus in Dakota or whatever.
Because you know Justin loves beans.
Right, long time listeners will remember
that Justin exclusively did eat beans for several years.
So I could understand the confusion there.
I used to be a bean boy.
I know.
Now I'm not anymore.
No, now you're a bean man.
Too dense.
I have never met them.
I think they vacuum here on the weekends,
but this happened on Monday.
And by then they will be moldy, it may be so.
Should I go pick up the beans when they are away
and risk being caught in the act and having to explain?
Should I just leave them be?
And leave them be.
There's no way to make this joke land.
Just leave them be.
It's not an audible sort of format, yeah.
And by the way, we'll do the jokes right here, thanks.
This from being there, smell that in Minnesota.
I love, by the way, that in this question,
at no point is go over there while they're there
and explain an option provided.
Hey bro, see if it's a drop some bean beans over here,
gonna clear you out, one sec.
But here's the thing, if you're caught over there
and then you say, I'm over here because I dropped some beans
and they rolled under your cubicle,
that is the most fishy explanation I've ever heard.
Yeah, that's a weird one.
They're definitely gonna think you've accidentally
dropped your stash, like in rent,
and now they are on the case.
Here's what I'm gonna say.
But if you say, if you go over there and say like,
I dropped some beans and they rolled under,
sorry about that, that's so wild that there's no way
they're gonna think you're lying, right?
That's a good point.
Okay.
I'm gonna say, it's just a couple beans.
It's just a couple beans. That's what fucking
Jack and the Beanstalk thought, Griffin.
Just a couple beans, and then pretty soon,
a giant falls and levels half the city.
But Jack didn't roll the beans accidentally.
Like Jack's mom was like, get these fucking beans
out of here, yeet!
And then a big Beanstalk came out,
and then we all know the rest of that story.
Everybody got squished and died from it.
But I would like to, just a side note,
I know this is pretty, some Monday morning quarterbacking
on the author of Jack and the Beanstalk.
When the mysterious stranger said,
trade me your cow for these magic beans,
wouldn't anybody, no matter what level of curiosity
they have, anybody would say, in what way are they magic?
Yeah, what kind of spell do they contain?
Like, it's not like magic bean is like a category of bean.
They're like, oh, these are some of those magic beans
I've heard.
Because if the mysterious stranger was like,
oh, it'll grow a giant Beanstalk that you'll have to climb?
And then hide from a man-eating giant.
How did I get them, you ask?
Don't worry about that.
Give me your cow.
Give me that cow right now.
Anyway, if I was in the cubicle across from this person
and I came over like, hey, a couple beans those
did roll under, and I looked down there,
I would be like, oh, it's fine, it's just a couple beans.
If it was 50 beans, and I looked under my desk
and there was a small pile of beans under there,
I would be like, yeah, you should get those.
You need to clean those up.
This is where I work.
I think about this a lot, right?
You do?
Well, no, it's just this idea of like, one is nothing.
And a million is a huge thing.
So there's some number, there's a fixed number, right?
Like if one bean is on the floor,
you probably wouldn't even notice.
If a hundred beans are in a small pyramid,
arranged perfectly, like sitting in your cubicle,
that's a huge deal.
That's a massive deal.
So there's some number in between one and 100 beans
where it becomes a topic,
where it becomes something that needs dealt with.
I think I've got it.
I think I know the number.
Oh, really?
You know the number?
I absolutely know the number.
I think it's five beans.
Okay, okay, wait, we'll shush that.
Shush, shush.
If I look under my desk and there's-
It's your thesis.
If there's one bean under my desk, oh, that's fun.
Two beans, oh, there's a couple beans down here.
Three beans, that's a few beans.
Four beans is like, should I do something about this?
Nah, it's just four beans.
Five beans is insane.
That's way too many beans to have under your desk.
I don't think it's a binary, right?
Because I actually think a singular bean in the wild,
if I saw just a black bean under my desk,
how the fuck did one bean get there?
Okay, so there's like a feature, not a bug,
a feature of the human experience,
where it's like if something's small
and you maybe don't necessarily wanna think about it
that much, you could filter out a bean.
You could be like, I don't know,
my awareness is not going to engage with that one bean.
I can't deal with that.
Aw, man, it must be nice not having ADHD, but go on.
I see that bean, it's my whole day.
What the fuck is that bean doing here?
I'm on the hunt.
So that's one of our many bean questions we do.
We like to open things up with a bean segment.
Yeah, and now there's another segment here
that I would say is much beloved
and everyone loves it when I do it.
And I'll pull you aside, folks.
This next is gonna be a little bit loud,
but riddle me piss, boys.
And now let me pull you aside real quick
to say that we don't like this.
Well, there are some folks out there that do.
Yeah, that's important context, but that we don't like it.
I'll give you guys, new listeners, a little explanation.
So there are people who will submit riddles
to the internet.
And every time they put that riddle up,
they think this is an absolute slam dunk.
But actually, as you will see from this riddle,
this is not the case.
So this was submitted by- You probably don't need
to explain that.
I think people are gonna get
that the riddles aren't very good.
This is submitted by Kayla.
Thank you, Kayla.
If all Wibbles are Kriggles, all Borkens are Kwamblings.
What? I already, I already don't want it.
If all Wibbles are Kriggles, all Borkens are Kwamblings,
excuse me, no Hoggles are Borkens,
and all Kriggles are Borkens,
is it true that all Borkens are Kriggles?
This sucks.
It sucks, Travis.
Do you wanna hear it again?
No, absolutely not.
I don't wanna hear it, got it, got it, got it.
I just wanna hear the-
If all Wibbles are Kriggles, all Borkens are Kwamblings,
no Hoggles are Borkens, and all Kriggles are Borkens,
is it true that all Borkens are Kriggles?
I can't, I try, actually, you know what's funny?
I tried to make my brain engage with it that time,
and it could, and it-
Slides right off, doesn't it?
It just slides, it just bounced out.
It couldn't do it.
So what was it, was it, no?
Is, Juice, you say yes, I'll say no.
So that's- Okay, yes.
No.
Griffin's right.
The answer, what they've actually written here is nope.
So there you go, Borkens aren't Kriggles.
Borkens aren't Kriggles.
I guess what I'd say is Borkens aren't Kriggles.
Yep.
That's fantastic.
Jesus.
We used to do Yahoo Answers on this show,
but then that website got suffocated, killed,
got shut down and deleted off the internet.
So this is a nascent segment, I would say, fresh.
And it's very exciting where we approach
the Wizard of the Cloud and we look
at questions on WikiHow instead.
And we learn things instead of, when Yahoo Answers,
it was just, you know, mystery atop a mystery.
WikiHow is like a teacher.
It's like a teacher that comes to teach you things.
And today's WikiHow is in-
Kind of like Nanny McPhee when you think about it.
It's basically Nanny McPhee.
Yeah, it's like Nanny McPhee, it teaches you lessons
that maybe you don't even realize you're learning.
It's like Dr. Parnassus.
Just like Dr. Parnassus.
And Mr. Magorium, which I haven't seen, but okay.
This is a subject that has near and dear to,
I think, all our hearts, and it's how to mosh in a mosh pit.
Thank you.
I've always been curious about the level of violence
that you are supposed to bring to that sort of encounter.
Yeah, I've always been worried I'll get in there
and fling myself at like a 10,
and then they'll be like, whoa, dude.
Whoa, dude, fucking stop.
We're on like a three.
Fucking Slipknot on stage is like,
stop, stop the rock music.
Look at, that guy did a big hit.
Get the fuck out of here.
Hey, this is a shared experience.
Yeah.
Mosh like that at home.
The first few things are preparatory, preparatory.
What?
Preparatory?
Proprietary.
Griffin invented them just for this.
Step one.
These are patented.
Wear clothes you don't care about getting ruined.
Wear old worn clothes or a cheap outfit
you don't feel attached to.
Clothing can get easily ripped or stained in a mosh pit.
Spelled how?
What if I wear my stained T-shirt?
There you go.
Yeah, that's a very, it's a risk that you can.
What's stained?
I mean, it's a bummer.
It must be a bummer to go to a stained show
from the band Stained,
and then later you go to Wienerschnitzel
and you're having yourself a nice hot dog.
Yeah.
And then you layer it up with all your favorite topics.
Your moose stars, your cats ups.
Everyone be quiet.
Okay.
And then you first fight, I got this.
Your first fight, catch your mustard,
squirts out onto your shirt.
And you look down at your new stained T-shirt
that you bought at the concert earlier,
and you think, I can never express this to other people.
I'll never be able to express this situation.
Hey, what happened to that new show shirt you bought?
The language hasn't evolved enough.
Yeah, it's stained.
Oh, I know.
Yeah, I was with you.
No, no, no.
It also said that the very next step
is actually don't bring big bottles of mustard
into the mosh pit.
That's fair.
That's rude.
Hey, as someone who grew up listening to music
in the 90s and stuff,
is Stained one of those bands that was like,
sounded like really hardcore,
but was actually secretly a Christian rock band?
Christian, I don't know.
I think Puddle of Mud is.
I don't know.
That feels right.
All right, wear contact lenses instead of glasses.
Ovs, avoid wearing loose jewelry or accessories.
Partially, I think because you don't want to get choked,
but also because of mosh bandits.
And we know.
Mosh mime women.
And I don't want to point fingers,
but I do remember one time Justin went to a rock concert
and came back with a beeper that wasn't his.
You want to talk about that?
Oh my God, what?
Do you not remember that?
I don't remember this.
No, tell me more.
You went to a concert and you said you brought,
maybe this was a lie you told your brother.
Maybe you bought a beeper and you were embarrassed about it,
but you said you found a beeper on the floor
at a rock concert after a mosh pit
and you brought it on home, which is fantastic.
I know that one time I traded in enough Pepsi points
to get a Mountain Dew beeper.
Yes, that's it.
You did do that.
That wasn't it.
I think this is a different situation though,
it sounds like.
Okay, this seems like the kind of thing you would.
I don't remember this.
Oh my gosh.
Make sure your shoes are tied.
Fantastic.
Yes.
All right, wait for the mosh.
This is joining the mosh pit.
This is where we,
this is where the fucking rubber hits the road.
Wait for the mosh pit to open up.
Yeah.
You'll know it's getting ready to start.
Will there be a signal or?
Well, Travis, you'll know it's getting ready to start
when the performer announces it or other concert goers
begin to make a clearing near the stage.
Probably not the first one.
Okay, everyone.
On three?
It's me, Jeremy Slipknot.
And I'm, I've got the red flag here.
Wave, wave, begin.
Begin the shoving.
There is a flaw with the second one though,
which is if you're waiting for other people
to start the moshing,
then what if everybody's waiting?
You could be a mosh pioneer.
Right, yeah.
Finish your drink.
Don't bring a drink, duh.
Enter the mosh pit once you're ready.
Yeah, don't be surprised if people are pushing you
and bumping you as you get to the edge of the circle.
If you don't wanna dive right into the mosh pit,
stay at the edge of the pit for a little bit
and observe until you feel ready to enter.
What's the number of people
standing on the perimeter of the mosh pit
staring intently at the people moshing
that makes the people moshing feel uncomfortable?
Like at what level do you,
even though you're jumping and feeling the vibe
of the music and hurting and pushing
and shoving and hurting other people,
are you like, I can't ignore the fact
that there are just like a dozen people looking at me.
Well, I think much like the bean question
we can start with,
if it's just two people moshing,
that's a romantic or at least very intense,
emotional experience. What is the sound
of two people moshing?
That's like a wedding's first dance there, right?
You don't wanna, when two people are moshing together,
you don't wanna interrupt what they've got going.
Now, as soon as a third party enters, right,
now the energy I think is spread out as such
that you need a fourth person to balance out
or else inevitably two of the three
are gonna start moshing together
while the third is excluded.
Oh, God. Yeah.
You need to share the load with four,
at which point then it just is gonna escalate from there.
That's gonna snowball for sure.
So yeah, start moshing, jump up and down in place,
make a lap around the pit,
have both your hands open
and your arms up at about chest level.
That's a cool look, that's probably not true.
Gently push people or bump into them.
It's okay to push people around,
everyone's in the pit expecting it,
but remember, you're not there to hurt anyone.
Avoid elbowing anyone in the chest.
As for some people, that can be quite sensitive,
if not painful.
I would say most people.
Yeah, unless it's like fucking Colossus.
Most people getting elbowed in the chest
is gonna feel that.
Not gonna feel good.
Keep with the pace of the music and those around you.
Cool off with a breather during slow songs.
Oh, yeah.
One of Stain's slow songs.
And be prepared for- One of their ballads.
Be prepared for everyone to start moshing harder
once the music picks up again.
Okay, cool.
This is, I know you're thinking,
I'm definitely gonna hurt somebody.
Like somebody's going to get hurt here.
Not if you follow mosh pit etiquette, the next segment.
One, stop and help anyone up should they fall.
Yes.
That's true in life as it is in mosh.
Yeah, if you see anyone fall down
and you're close to them,
it's a good thing to do in general,
regardless of whether or not a bunch of sweaty butt rock fans
are out there jumping down nearby.
It does become especially important
when that is happening.
Yeah.
Pick up dropped items and hold them above your head.
Is this anyone's beeper?
Nope.
Bye.
I don't know how to transfer service on a beeper.
So I guess I'll be answering Doug's pages.
That was the biggest mystery to me.
If you see anyone's shoe or cell phone on the ground,
stop and pick it up.
The image that WikiHouse provided,
which if you've never been to the website is always good,
is somebody very happily holding a shoe above their head.
And I like to think like, I'd get into the music, right?
You all know me.
I like to ride those vibes.
But if my shoe comes off, that's priority number one.
At the very least, it's gonna create a physical imbalance
in your body.
You're gonna notice.
Yes.
Don't throw things in the mosh pit.
Thank you.
That's good.
Or the sand pit.
And don't try to mosh with people who aren't in the pit.
Get in here.
Yeah, don't try to start an ancillary mosh pit.
That's a weird, that is a weird sort of state of mind
for the person who's like, I'm the edge of the mosh pit.
This mosh, no mosher.
I hate this mosh pit.
I'm standing guard of you.
I won't let this, I won't let you pass.
See, I thought that this was saying,
don't try to start a secondary mosh pit
at a different location in the audience.
Like you're like, you know what?
I don't like that mosh pit anymore.
They observe rules I don't like.
I lost my shoe in there.
No one held it above their head.
Hey, you, you're a beefy person.
Come mosh with me.
You're on my team.
What?
We're a rival mosh.
I just really wanna watch the show.
Begin jumping, we're a team now.
Squid game, hurt them.
Sick of them.
Stank ironically.
Everyone, stank ironically.
Don't bother the venue staff in the pit.
Oh man, you're shoving too hard.
Okay, I'll stop.
That's what they're there for.
They're there to be, you know, in charge.
They're the parent of the mosh pit.
You need to, hey, they're not doing it
because they're mad at you.
They're doing it because they care about you.
Yeah, I gotta say, that's the last sort of tip here.
If I'm like in it, if I'm like,
if I'm skanking it to Hoobastank
and really riding the vibe and doing a lot of pushing
and someone tells me, hey, you need to stop.
I don't know that that sort of like,
you know, primitive, just in my soul instinct to mosh
is going to be able to be contained at that point.
Oh, that's so interesting, Griffin,
because if I was moshing at a concert
and someone told me you need to stop,
I would assume it was my inner monologue saying like,
this is done now.
This is not your thing, Travis.
Hey, Travis, I think you and I can both agree
you're forcing this.
The venue staff should not be there
to police the intensity of people's moshing.
They should be there for folks like me
who they see me like very nervously start
walking in and they just grab me by the scruff of my neck
like no friend, no friend, this is not for you.
We actually have seating over here,
secret seating that we didn't tell anyone about,
but it looks like your human body might need it.
Yeah.
Hey, why don't you go buy a t-shirt, huh?
A nice t-shirt and then maybe head on home.
This is a funny joke that somebody asking the questions,
the community Q and A, what do I do
if somebody starts doing the Macarena
whilst in the pit, goopity-goop?
The community answered, nobody would do the Macarena
in the mosh pit.
Only moshing is done in a mosh pit.
What if the person does what I used to do
at middle school dances,
which is they're too awkward to dance
so they just kind of sing along to the song
in the middle of the dance floor.
Yeah.
What if someone tries to make a big holding hand circle
in the mosh pit?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What if they try to do that like,
and now we're gonna highlight individual moshers.
We've created a mosh circle.
Now you get in there and let us watch you mosh by yourself.
Mosh train.
Yes.
I'm into that.
Anyway, now we all know how to do this.
So let's all go to a rock concert together.
Yeah.
Man, that'd be fun.
That would be fucking fun.
I'd like that.
I'd love to man.
What's stopping us?
Well.
A lot of stuff.
Where to begin?
What do you mean, where to begin?
Our bodies.
Oh, this is actually good to talk about.
We stop in the middle,
like just when you're really starting to have fun.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know what you're thinking.
This is an advice show.
They've done very little advice.
Well, we're hanging there.
There's a lot more coming.
I just around the bend.
We take a break to do advertisements.
And what is great is if you can like frequent the businesses
that we talked about.
And we make it funny.
We're not like some of those other advertisers.
Don't skip them.
It's not a robot or something.
It's really the guys that you love already.
And we're kind of like the Geico cavemen
of podcast commercials.
We're like, fuck, that's funny.
Cool.
That's funny, yeah.
So, oh, I begin this by I say,
let's, I'll go to the money then.
It's better, it's better with you.
Stamps.
So for those of you at home, stamps are a thing
that you have to like.
And they know about stamps.
How do you know that?
Well, we have to assume a base level of confidence.
Okay, fair, fair, fair.
So if you've got a small business
and you know there's nothing more available than your time,
so stop wasting on trips to the post office
and start wasting it on listening to our podcast.
Stamps.com makes it easy to mail
and ship right from your computer.
Stamps.com brings the service of the US Postal Service
and UPS shipping right to your computer
and the band, Postal Service, right to your computer.
They will, I, now.
They will do it.
Now that I have committed them to it,
they're working on a media player as we speak.
So whether you're saying-
They are trying to Tron Ben Gibbard today.
That's our Stamps.com guarantee to you.
We are going to blast Ben Gibbard with a Tron gun.
Guys, stop it.
I said I would-
If you've ever wanted your computer
to describe your girlfriend dying,
now the chance is here.
It will happen.
Do you have an old mattress?
Now the world is 2021.
This disc on your back, yes, it's vinyl.
You've guessed it.
Whether you're an office sending invoices,
a side hustle Etsy shop,
or a full blown warehouse shipping our orders,
Stamps.com will make your life easier.
All you need is a computer and standard printer,
no special supplies or equipment,
and you'll get exclusive discounts
on all of our products and services.
No special supplies or equipment,
and you'll get exclusive discounts on postage
and shipping from USPS and UPS.
Save time and money with Stamps.com.
There's no risk.
And with my promo code, my brother, all one word,
you get a- Our-
My promo code.
I called Stamps.com and I said,
can I please have a promo code?
And they said, yes, Travis,
but don't let your brothers use it.
We should make an advertisement that's cool
generate us three promo codes
to see which- Oh, oh, I like that.
We can't come up with that up.
My brother, all one word,
you get a special offer that includes a four week trial,
plus free postage and a digital scale.
No long-term commitments or contracts.
Now I know you're wondering,
sometimes that can be confusing.
The digital scale means it has like a digital readout,
not that it's like a computerized, like 3D scale.
I just wanna make sure that it's clear.
It's not made of lasers or something.
So- Right, I think, yeah.
Okay, you don't know that.
It confuses me.
Just go to stamps.com, click on the microphone
at the top of the homepage and type in my brother,
all one word.
That's stamps.com, promo code, my brother.
Stamps.com, never go to the post office again.
Unless you work there.
Unless you- Yeah.
Oh, can you imagine if you worked at the post office
and the post office found out you had a stamps.com account?
Oh boy.
I think it would go a little something like this.
Hey Derek, you got a stamps.com account?
Uh, yeah.
Ah, cool, can you sort those packages please?
He actually did the skit.
Yeah, that's a good skit.
Let me talk about this next one.
Okay.
It's ZipRecruiter.
Oh, okay.
You know, I like to hand select things in my life.
Like what?
No, like every day when I go into my,
you know, toothpaste closet
and I pick the paste of the day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And what am I feeling like?
Baking soda, I'm baking soda peroxide, whatever.
Do you like the ones with the stripes?
I need the whitening.
Yeah, I like the ones with the stripes sometimes
if I feel a little bit saucy.
But that's me, you know what I mean?
I like to choose, it says in the ad copy,
it says I can choose my own, so I guess I did.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, don't let me off the leash again.
ZipRecruiter, that's what you get.
You can do the same thing I do for toothpaste,
you can do it for hiring though.
Oh, so if I wanted to like hire a toothpaste selector?
You wouldn't think that it's a big draw, right?
I could choose the people that like get the job.
No, no, no, that's not what ZipRecruiter means.
You can invite people to apply for the job.
It lets you pick your favorites from the best candidates.
ZipRecruiter will send you qualified candidates
and you can easily invite your top choices
to apply for the job.
You can't beat it.
It's so hard finding the best people for the job
and ZipRecruiter makes it easy.
See for yourself.
Go to ziprecruiter.com slash M-Y-B-R-O-T-H-E-R
to try ZipRecruiter for free.
That's ziprecruiter.com slash M-Y-B-R-O-T-H-E-R.
I'm Lisa Hanawalt.
And I'm Emily Heller.
Nine years ago, we started a podcast
to try and learn something new every episode.
Things have gone a little off the rails since then.
Tune in to hear about.
Low stakes neighborhood drama.
Gardening.
The sordid, nasty underbelly of the horse girl lifestyle.
Hot sauce.
Addiction to TV and sweaty takes on celebrities.
Celebrity culture.
And the weirdest, grossest stuff you can find
on wikipedia.org.
We'll read all of it, no matter how gross.
There's something for everyone on our podcast,
Baby Geniuses.
Hosted by us, two horny adult idiots.
Hang out with us as we try and fail
to retain any knowledge at all.
Every other week on Maximum Fun.
Baby Geniuses, tell us something we don't know.
Hey Griff, do you have another, do you want to start?
Do you want to start a bit?
I don't know.
And this is a thing Justin likes to do
where he basically starts things
and then he really puts me in the toilet.
Yeah Juice, here comes a segment that I've prepared
and worked really hard on.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
Okay, now what you've heard there
is the opening strains to the intro music
to a bit within a bit.
This is called the Munch Squad,
where I talk about, well you'll see.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
There's a call and response section of this.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
I wanna Munch Squad.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
I want to Munch Squad.
Toronto!
Now, welcome Munch Squad, it's a podcast
within a podcast where I profile
the latest and greatest in brand eating.
That means like fast food,
or brand eating, I think really covers it.
Yeah.
When you eat a brand.
Guys ever heard of Culver's?
Oh yeah, we got Culver's here.
You got Culver's here?
Oh yeah, I like Culver's.
I got big news for you, bud.
The Curda Burger.
What?
Everyone say it once.
No, I don't know what you said.
I can't.
Curda Burger? Curda Burger?
Sorry, just say, just say, Curda Burger.
Curda Burger.
It's very, very egg-nuggy.
Curda Burger. Curda Burger.
Curda Burger.
That was a very funny joke that Culver's did,
which is one of the most irritating things that anybody does
where it makes up a fake item
to get social media to talk about it.
They did it with the Curda Burger.
And then that is a, it's a burger, huh?
It's a Culver Butter Burger.
Now that sounds different.
It's a less Culver Butter Burger,
the top with golden fried cheese or curds.
It's a cheese-cored Curd Burger or a Curda Burger.
Oh, I see.
So they did this as a joke.
Ah.
It's a Butter Burger with curd on top.
Okay.
The Curda Burger.
I get it.
But for once, someone did the right thing.
Sued them.
And looked at the social media response.
As we know, I'm sure, fucking uproarious
to this April Fool's gag.
Yeah.
And the people were so incensed
that the idea of Curda Burger had been created,
but the physical manifestation of Curda Burger
was denied to them.
Right.
That they realized, Culver's realized
it was their moral obligation
to bring the menu item to life.
For one day only on National Cheese Curd Day,
which is, as we all know, say it together.
November 17th.
October 15th.
Yeah.
I said it.
Sorry, there was a lag.
October 15th.
They're launching the Curda Burger.
We got a delicious crown of golden fried cheese.
Damn.
Makes this burger one of a kind.
The cheese crown, which is-
Which is a good thing.
One of the names you could choose.
They chose that one.
Yeah.
The cheese crown.
I believe that was what our Lord and Savior,
Jesus Christ, had to put on the crust.
Travis, Travis.
I think you mean cheesy crust.
Cheesy crust.
I'm sorry.
We're incredibly proud of our, this is an answer.
This is, if you hear me talking
in the voice of a creative type,
this is Quinn Adkins,
Culver's Director of Menu Development.
Quinn Adkins.
The delicious crown of golden fried cheese
is what makes this burger one of a kind.
The cheese crown is made up of a blend of yellow
and white cheddar cheese curds,
all surrounded by crispy seasoned breadcrumbs.
We're incredibly proud of our Wisconsin cheese curds,
which is why they've slapped them into a butter burger,
and our relationship with Wisconsin dairy.
So the Curda Burger is just another way
to showcase our trademark quality,
and Wisconsin roots.
Beyond the burger itself,
the way the Curda Burger came into existence
is a story worth telling.
It all began on April Fool's Day
with a prank we posted on social media.
But when guests made it clear,
they wanted it to be a real menu item,
which was such a surprise, I think, to them.
They in no way were backdoor announcing a new menu item
to see the response.
For sure not.
Who would do that?
It completely caught them by surprise.
Justin, can I ask you a question legitimately?
I'm trying to find a picture of this thing.
What's the joke?
What was the joke?
It's so funny that they would put cheese.
I know, this is what,
everyone's doing things that are exponentially nastier.
The whole world is nastier than this.
It's almost sort of quaint.
It's elegant.
Like that they are coming out with the Curda Burger
and expecting us to be like,
you did what? You're wild.
You what?
I gotta give,
I'm always dunking on people
who answer the questions for QSR,
which is sort of my hookup for this information.
But on this one, I do have to call QSR itself out
on the question they've decided to ask here,
which to be fair,
coming up with questions to ask
about the Curda Burger can't be easy.
QSR asks, why does it work from a flavor perspective?
What do you think, motherfucker?
It's fried cheese on a burger.
It's a fried cheese on a burger, dipshit.
It's not like a complex fried cheese on a burger.
It's cheese and meat, but fried.
From a flavor perspective, the Curda Burger,
which by the way, it fails in almost every other respect.
Like it is not pleasant to look upon.
Or say.
Let's talk about it just from a flavor perspective.
The Curda Burger is an evolution
of our classic Burger Burger,
but adds an additional savory component
with our signature blend of herbs and spices,
a textural contrast with the fried crown
and a tremendous visual dynamic.
So from a flavor perspective,
it adds a tremendous visual dynamic.
I know what you're wondering, guys,
because it's the same question I had.
What was the R&D process like?
How many attempts did it take to get it right,
fried cheese on a hamburger?
This, says Quinn, was a personal project of love.
Was it?
It developed in three months,
starting in late May after the menu team
saw all the attention the April Fool's message received.
So just to be clear,
it took you two months to read your mentions?
I mean, I get it.
There's probably not a lot of like,
culvert discussion on there,
but it seems like a long time to realize like,
hey, people really want this burger.
The extraordinary development speed
was made possible by the talent and dedication of our team,
along with the strength of our relationships
with our manufacturing and supplier network
without our strategic supplier.
You want more cheese?
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, the logistics of that.
In this economy?
Really?
Okay.
How much should it cost?
A hundred dollars?
That's too much.
Five dollars?
Sounds good.
Guests have a high,
for this item in particular,
we wanted to wow our guests.
So we designed a burger that went above and beyond.
And this is where Quinn,
like people are always using team language.
I've never seen anyone do this
in one of these press releases.
Quinn then says,
when executing my vision for the curder burger,
I created a list of must haves,
including functionality of design
that reflected what we deliver
with our current cheese curds.
So both the yellow and white curds were evident.
Optimizing the eating experience of the burger.
So the cheese crown not only is visually appealing,
but also holds together after taking a bite.
Three, perfecting the size and weight of the crown
so it can be consistently prepared
to the highest quality in restaurant.
And a high ceiling in the garage so that I can,
oh, no, wait, sorry.
That's for my must haves for the new house I'm going to buy
after the curder burger comes out.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
But here's the wild thing.
All this work, all of it,
for the curder burger,
which is available for one day.
Can you imagine?
This is like a corpse flower.
Yeah.
Right?
Like all this work,
in one day of, who cares if it's consistent?
It's one day.
Buy it or don't.
You know what I mean?
It's the worst.
That's the dedication to quality I can say about it.
I'll tell you what, Justin,
you've really ruined me on this.
After talking about the absolute R&D mad lad
that worked at Wendy's that worked on a new fry recipe
for two and a half years.
And it's hard for me now to take anybody's R&D seriously
when they're like three months we put into this.
I'm like, that's nothing.
That's nothing.
You're a child.
Talk to me when you've spent two and a half years
figuring out how to make french fries.
That's all I think about.
I want this R&D to submerge you into a pool of madness.
Yes.
From which you might never return.
I want this to be your Mr. Holland's opus.
It tastes better to me when you don't return
from the madness pool.
Yes.
Speaking of Wendy's fries,
if I can just pivot briefly,
this week, Carl Laredo, the CMO at Wendy's,
posted a picture of him and his family
enjoying some new Wendy's fries.
And the text of this photo is,
the whole family loves Wendy's new hot and crispy fries.
Really, Carl?
Except for Doug. What a shock.
Not pictured.
My shithead son, Doug, hates my fries.
He's out.
The company that puts food on your table
put food on your table and you enjoyed it?
I'll tell you what though, those fries are fucking good.
And they survived the drive home in a very-
Listen, I noticed too, Trav.
I didn't even realize we were getting them.
And then Sydney and I both ate some fries
and we're like, damn.
What's up?
Yeah.
These fries, they're good.
Okay, Carl, you're right.
You did, Carl.
I don't think you and your family are lying, Carl.
They're good fries.
I would never say that.
Not about Doris.
Not about-
I'd say it about-
Robethany.
I'd say it about Doug.
Doug's a piece of shit.
I don't know Carl's children's names,
but I'm just going to guess it's Robethany.
Robethany and Doug.
Don't you?
This is Carl Laredo's son, Doug Jr.
He's a real twisted ride.
He's the junior of a different Doug.
Just a Doug that Carl knows.
Is this named after my barber?
He reminds me of my road dog, Doug.
He's a great barber.
I don't go there anymore.
My name's Carl Laredo.
This is my son, Dave Thomas Jr.
We don't cut corners here in my family.
Does Wendy's still make square patties?
They don't, do they?
Trav, can I charge you with getting a Curderburger?
If you've got Culver's around you,
will you get a Curderburger and gram it?
Just gram it.
Yeah, I'll put it on the gram.
Yeah, how incensed would you be
if you went into a non-participating Culver's-
On this one day.
On October 15th and know it's slipping.
They're like, I don't know, let me look in the back.
And you're like, I could be eating it now.
This is the one chance I have.
Could I get 30 of them and 29 of them are frozen?
Is that possible?
All the wasted time.
All the Curderburgers.
Okay, listen.
If you only had time.
That's how you go.
Here's a question.
Here's another question.
We're gonna help two people this week.
I live in a duplex,
and I've only interacted with my neighbor once
back when we moved in.
The other day, I could hear him singing a song
from Les Miserables through the wall.
Here's the thing.
I also love to sing show tunes.
How do I approach him about our shared interests?
Without letting him know,
I could hear his private singing moments.
That's from Perplexed in a duplex.
Why not let him know?
This is very strange to me.
Why?
It's very strange.
Why is that?
Because this is a new bit that I've invented for the show
where I say, I don't know, and I let my brothers help me.
Cause I have one version of this,
a different version of this exact same problem.
Yesterday, or no, it's been a few days now.
I was driving up to my home and I passed a neighbor.
He's an older gentleman who I've since learned is a widower
living there on his own.
And I passed him and his cars
are always in the driveway, right?
I passed him.
I looked in his garage and he had this fucking sick
woodworking shop, like sick,
like real, real choice stuff, right?
And I'm like, oh damn, that guy's deep in the paint
on woodworking.
And then I started thinking like,
it would be cool to have someone who lives
like a couple of houses away be like-
Work wood with.
A fellow woodworker, like if I get some scraps,
I'll kick him his way.
He comes in, he's like, Justin,
I need a number eight, three inch deck screw.
I can help him out, you know what I mean?
But I can't for the life of me think of a way.
I don't know him at all.
So I can't for the life of me think of a way
to elegantly be like-
And I've expressed this concern to my wife.
She can't think of anything.
She's the smartest person I know.
Can't think of anything.
I don't know how to elegantly knock on the door
and be like, listen, I looked in your garage.
And it was bright in there and I looked in there
and I saw that you love wood and I love wood too.
And I just want you to know I'm here for you.
We could be like, not friends in the traditional sense,
but you know-
We could share a connection.
We could be wood buddies.
So what are you guys saying?
Your problem is Justin,
you're hung up on the elegant part.
There isn't.
Hold on, I'm getting some water.
You can just keep talking.
Can you hear me?
Wait.
Why would he ask for your advice?
He asked me for advice and then he was like,
I'm fucking leaving.
Pay you back.
The problem is, Justin, you're caught up on the elegant.
There isn't an elegant.
Well, I don't want it to be weird.
But here's the thing, man.
We get asked all the time,
how do I make friends with an adult?
And that is because we are worried about that weird moment.
You know who I'm fucking worried about that?
Five-year-olds.
You know?
You're just gonna have to roll up and say,
hey, I noticed that you have woodworking stuff.
I also am interested in woodworking.
Okay, imagine it.
Like really start to break it down
to its base components though.
Is he in the shop when I do this?
I don't know.
But-
Exactly.
Yeah, Justin.
I mean, do I knock on his front door?
Yes.
In the middle of dinner, Travis?
No, why did I dinner with him?
I didn't say that.
Travis, why am I interrupting his dinner?
He was spraying, Travis.
No, don't interrupt his dinner.
He got out of the bath.
Four o'clock, Justin.
Four p.m. is a save for the husky neighbor boys
that's always carrying terrible wood scraps
out through his trash.
And Justin saw everything, Travis.
How can their relationship possibly recover from this?
Well, then he answered the door in the nude.
Great idea, Travis.
Pervert.
Okay, well, I was trying to, okay.
I was trying to actually help our brother, Justin.
And then you guys call me-
No, help him.
I'm telling you, I'm serious.
Do I knock on his door?
Is there someone at the door?
Yeah, you knock on-
And then imagine it, whatever you tell-
I'm gonna move the mic.
Whatever you tell me, imagine it happening to you, Travis.
Hey, I heard your podcast.
I'm a stranger.
Yeah.
No.
There is risk involved, Justin.
Don't get me wrong.
There is a risk involved,
but the reward of having your own wood buddy-
Yeah.
Is the reward.
Like, you think you're just gonna get that for free?
You're waiting for the universe to give you
like an excuse to talk to this wood friend?
Do I, now, let me ask you this.
Here's some alternate plans.
If I don't have the bravery for what you said,
because he's in dinner, do I send a note?
Is I send a letter?
No.
If it's black wood, do you like me?
Check yes or no.
No, Justin.
What's up with that?
He's not gonna-
And if so, would I mail it?
Cause that's weird, right?
Now, if you carve a plaque that says that,
and you deliver a hand-carved wooden-
You're saying that's the introduction,
just to be like, here is where my skills are at.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Oh, I thought you were saying leave it at his doorstep.
Like, this is from your secret wood-
Oh no, I did mean that.
Okay, good.
But it's a carved wooden plaque.
So he's gonna see, like, this is weird, but-
Bring it to the table, right?
There's something here.
I see, also, I know that this is Justin,
cause he's still walking away.
I could see him, right?
He rang the doorbell and I answered it,
and I see him walking away.
And at a leisurely pace, frankly.
And he's watching me very closely
to check my reactions to what he, to-
Hey, Justin, come on.
Yeah, yeah, this is good.
I have some notes.
I think people who are experienced in a craft or hobby
are always looking for an opportunity
to flex that on other people.
Yes.
So you need to supplicate yourself to him.
And maybe, like, you go up with a shitty bird house
that is glued to the side of your head.
And you'd be like, um, hi, I'm your neighbor.
I can help but notice that you have some wood stuff.
And I am also into it, but I did this.
And do you have any kind of solvent or something
that won't be bad for my skin?
Cause I have really goofed up over here.
That person will be so excited for the opportunity to-
Yeah, that's probably true.
That's probably true.
But then they're gonna know the next time you make a,
you know, a nice stool.
They're gonna be like, you fucking rope-a-doped me.
And then you say, no, I couldn't have done it
without your tutelage.
Yeah, when you- You've inspired me.
When you pried that bird house off my face.
That was- It must have released something
in my brain. Right.
By which I mean a pneumatic staple
that I think I accidentally fired.
It's somewhere in there.
From what I know about rotary saws,
is they like to just fly on off the handle
and just go zip zap and wherever they wanna go.
So maybe you could embed one of those
in the side of his house and then knock on his door
and just be like, hey, this happened.
And as a fellow woodsman, I'm sure you know
all about these stinkers.
What if he, I'm more, I think there's a non-zero chance
that he would take my tools away.
Oh. Wait, you're saying
that if you introduced yourself as a fellow woodworker,
he'd be like, no, not you.
No, you're not. You're not grown up enough
for this. He would confiscate them
from you, a 40-year-old parent of two.
He might confiscate my saws, all my beautiful saws.
And what if, maybe he just takes the screws
until I've learned my lesson.
But then, isn't that what we all want, Justin?
You're looking for a wood father figure.
Yeah.
Well, the problem is like, just this past week,
I made a footstool for my daughter
and I couldn't get it balanced.
Like, you know how you build something,
it's always a crapshoot when you make something
that's supposed to stand on the ground on multiple legs.
And I said it was like wobbly, so I cut it down
and then it was still wobbly, but the wrong way.
And I kept cutting it until it eventually
was offering a negligible height differential
from the ground.
And then I got so frustrated that I threw it on the ground
and smashed it with a big hammer.
And I think that he should,
I think maybe he should take my tools away.
Oh, Justin.
I don't think that, I think someone should be parenting.
Maybe you need to approach him in that way then
and be like, well, can I apprentice with you?
Can I trust you to stop me?
Because that's what I did, man.
I found myself a blacksmith teacher,
I apprenticed with him.
It makes him really uncomfortable
when I refer to myself as his apprentice,
but here we are, you know?
Makes me uncomfortable
and I'm not even part of the equation.
I will often say like, am I a journeyman yet?
And he's like, what the fuck are you talking about, Travis?
I'm like, ah, thank you, that's wise.
Juice, next time you fuck up a project like that,
hold on to it, or at least hold on to the scraps
of when you smash it because of your insatiable rage.
And then look at the 10-day forecast,
see when the next big rainstorm's coming,
and then show up at his door soaked to the bone.
Oh, yay, yay.
Maybe even if you want to go this route,
your t-shirt sticking to your body a little bit
and you show up with the scraps.
Not in a sexual way, but in a sensual way, for sure.
Well, or just a, you know, however kind of way
you want to frame it, but with the scraps in your hands.
And then you can make yourself cry and just be like,
I don't, just say like, I don't know.
And then have him just, shh, shh, shh, shh, come on in.
And I think he's going to be into it.
I'm going to give you this one for free, Justin.
Would you help me with this?
That's funny.
And he's going to know that you're a real deal guy
when you come at him with genuine Goodwood humor like that.
Now what's going to be confusing is when he responds,
I think not.
And you're not going to be sure if that's a no
or if that's another pun.
Yeah.
That's going to be hard to parse.
I understand that, but that's the test.
What if I start misinterpreting like,
I saw you walking towards my house, so I called the cops.
And they're like, whoa, saw, I get it, funny.
Good stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I heard you hammering on my door screaming,
please, please let me in.
I wish you'd cut it out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cut, it's funny.
Like Woods, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I get it.
Thank you so much for listening to our podcast.
If this is your first time,
we hope you've enjoyed yourself.
We release a new one of these almost every Monday.
We used to miss a lot, but we barely ever do that anymore.
Sometimes it's just a little late because of life.
Yeah, or a little bad.
Yeah.
You never know.
Come hell or high water though,
there'll be something here for you.
Statistically, there are about 300 good episodes
in here somewhere, so.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, run the numbers.
Oh, speaking of, if you are a new listener,
just start on like 150 or 200 and work forward from there.
Yeah. Yeah.
Or start at the newest one, but not the last one.
Skip the last one.
The last episode was fantastic.
I won't take this slander.
Okay, good.
Yeah, listen to whatever one's-
And as you're working backwards,
when you hit a point, you're like,
well, this seems weird.
Stop.
Stop there.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Oh God.
Yeah, yeah.
If the mics get bad, it's-
The content will follow.
The thoughts, the thoughts will also be bad.
And you know what?
This is also a good time if you are,
if you've been a listener of My Brother,
My Brother and Me for a while,
why not check out other MaxFun shows during this period?
They're gonna be doing other kind of intro shows like this
to welcome in a new audience.
We've got some crossover stuff that we did
that's gonna be in a new feed.
We did a crossover with Maximum Film
where we talked about good and bad advice
that we learned for the-
Oh, this is fun.
Fun as hell.
Teresa and I did a Schmaners crossover with Titan Fights
where we talked about the etiquette of pro wrestling
and some famous rivalries and some locker room etiquette.
It was an absolute blast.
So check that out.
You can find out more at MaximumFun.org slash Block Party.
It's going until October 22nd.
And it's not just shows and stuff on the network.
There's gonna be volunteer events
and limited edition posters and games.
I'm doing a Jackbox game stream on this Thursday
at 9 p.m. Eastern time with Janet Varney
and Carrie Poppe and James Arthur.
And it's gonna be an absolute blast.
Justin, you and Sydney are doing a stream too, right?
Yeah, I think it's Friday night after that
where we're watching F9 finally and live streaming that.
There you go.
So make sure you check that out.
More info at MaximumFun.org slash Block Party.
We've also got an Adventure Zone Live
and virtual show coming out November 5th.
Tickets are on sale now.
That's November 5th at 9 p.m. Eastern time.
Tickets are only $10.
And if you're not able to make it on the 5th,
video on demand will be available
for two weeks after the show.
We're doing another Hootenanny episode,
which is our Lasers and Feelings RPG
where we play a space, like country band,
traveling the stars, playing country music.
You can get tickets for that at bit.ly slash TazVirtual.
Our theme song is My Life is Better With You by Montaigne.
It's a great track and the music video is very fun.
It's got us and Montaigne in it.
Go listen to all of Montaigne's music
if you've never made that dive.
She's incredible and her tunes really slap, man.
Yeah, they really slap.
We also have new merch over at McElroyMerch.com,
including our pin of the month,
which is from TazJustUs,
Gryphon's character Hellraven, AKA Del Craven.
Sales of that pin of the month benefit
the National Latina Institute for Reproductive Justice,
which builds Latina and Latinx power
to fight for the fundamental human right
to reproductive health, dignity, and justice.
There's other stuff there too.
Go check it out, McElroyMerch.com.
And this is where we come to a bit of an awkward moment
for new listeners. Not for me.
Because there's no way for you to know
that we used to use the Yahoo answer service a lot
as our source of questions,
but we don't do that as much anymore.
Because it died.
So now we're kind of lost on that front.
Except for all the ones that I stockpiled.
Okay, okay, and Gryphon pretend.
All the ones I stockpiled before we got gone.
So this one was sent in by Jim.
From the office?
Davis.
Oh.
Oh, from the Garfields.
Yes, and.
From the Garfield office where they make Garfield.
And it's asked by Rudy.
Rudy Giuliani, the scary Rudy Giuliani.
That's just scarier.
Yeah, I was gonna say.
It's from BootyGuliani who says.
Oh no, you're making me like that character now.
Oh, Booty, don't get me wrong.
BootyGuliani is fantastic.
BootyGuliani asks.
Yeah?
What?
Yeah, what?
Just read it, Gryphon.
BootyGuliani asks,
does anyone want to join me in
in filing a class action lawsuit
against Dick's Last Resort?
They made me feel very small.
That's the one that wasn't guilty, it's the guilty one.
Oh, God bless.
Oh no, that, you know what's funny?
That would be like the fifth most embarrassing thing
he's done in his life.
I mean, it wouldn't even top the chart.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Gryphon McElroy.
This has been my brother and me,
Gryphon McElroy, and I'll see you guys next time.
It's better with you.
Ah, okay, says the doctor.
In which case, try listening
to the Beef and Dairy Network podcast.
The Beef and Dairy Network podcast
is a multi-award-winning comedy podcast,
and you can find it at MaximumFun.org
or wherever you get your podcasts.