The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother mean advice show for the modern era.
My name is Justin McElroy and I'm your oldest brother?
My name is Miller's brother and I and I'm Travis your brother.
I'm your sweet baby brother Griffin rock and roll McElroy.
I have an emergency that needs to be addressed immediately.
Is it Travis's microphone?
Should we Travis's microphone is fine don't see you fucking draw people's attention to it now
they're now they can't unsee.
I think they'll figure out that he's talking to us.
No you did the same thing with the person mowing the lawn and you're like they'll hear it they'll
hear it and then we got a million complaints and now I'm gonna get a million tweets saying
why was Travis recording on a fucking talk boy why was he recording on a goddamn yak back?
Can I get to my emergency?
Do your bit.
We all it's not a bit it's life or death uh we are recording we have one hour to record
the best show of our lives uh it's kind of like the movie Speed we're under a deadline
uh and right before we like right once the call had started and we had started the recording
I reached for my can of crisp refreshing pepsi max and realized that it was empty.
Oh my god brothers I have no beverages can you hear it already?
I can you're getting all creaky and croaky like some sort of mountain man like some sort of man
made it like cleft into a mountain face.
Oil can pepsi max.
Yeah pepsi max me.
It's not inaccurate because once while living in Chicago I had to change my license plate but the
screws were rusted on and I fucking used pepsi max to dissolve the to dissolve that that rust
right off there and it works that's a thing you can do but I'm like I'm you're putting that you're
putting that in your shit box Justin so just for thought I'm freaking out though like I'm freaking
out because I have no beverage and I must record a comedy podcast with no drink at all yeah as
those of you who are at the Midwest live shows know I need a certain sort of drink for those
but I'm just talking about like a general beverage yeah like a wet like a wet fluid I'm freaking out
I'm already thinking about exit strategies.
Hey Justin we're gonna make it through this together and I just I know that you're in a
panic state but I do have to point out that the movie Speed did not involve them having to drive
for an hour or else the film would have been called Duration.
Well it would have been great though if it was like we have to drive for an hour because that's
the closest store that has Pepsi Max. I have two other qualifying factors to this uh one I ate
three spicy buffalo wheat thins before I realized the beverage situation and also I have a bowl of
leftover Honey Nut Cheerios milk that is next to me and this episode for me is about not
drinking it because I am I'm worried I'm gonna get desperate you know what I mean like without
a beverage. So when we hear the sound the telltale sound of sloppy slopping coming from your oh
and there it goes. Not yet not yet I'm not I can't do it. Jesus take the wheel
as specifically from Justin's hand. And when you say leftover Cheerios it's five o'clock
it's five p.m somewhere specifically sitting sitting for a while. Oh god damn it don't
don't do it just do it I'm not gonna ask your question instead. This is an advice show for
the modern era I should have mentioned before uh also a quick thank you to everybody who came to
those shows we'll be um trickling those out uh over the next few months I'm assuming uh so if
we make like recurring jokes they were recorded in three nights in succession but thank you to
everybody who came out that was a lot of fun. I think the I think the only thing we'll probably
end up referring back to from the trip was the time that we did a live show that two people
two and a half people got engaged well sorry four and a half people five people got engaged at our
live show. Also speaking of live shows I believe we'll be announcing a new batch of those at the
end of this episode. Holy shit will we that is correct yeah we will yes we will serendipity
wow god damn stay tuned where's it gonna be ah they're already gone they all fast forwarded
you guys want to kick it for a little while yeah yeah let's just get do I so I have time to go
grab a drink fuck no you don't let's get some answers dog all right let's get some answers
going here we go first I want to tell you guys about I was watching Survivor last night you
guys watched Survivor oh fuck yeah well we got time to chat um the it there was an amazing moment
last night Survivor where Jeff was like it was the reward challenge and Jeff Probst says and once you
get to the end of that zipline what's gonna be waiting for you is a picnic and these adults were
like whoo and then Jeff Probst adds a pizza picnic and these 13 adults lose their minds like the idea
of a pizza picnic was so thrilling to them that they that they were willing to climb or or solve
or whatever Jeff has swallow whatever Jeff had in store for them they had to get to that pizza and
when I get it they were trying one guy was trying to decide somebody else to take on the trip and
this woman was like super fan of what pizza picnics yeah all of us are yeah all of it that
describes all of us super fan of pizza picnics or do you mean Survivor as in like as if to say
that somehow qualifies you more what's your favorite part of Survivor ooh definitely when
they eat pizza on it I like the parts of Survivor when they visit like uh developing nations and
they bring school books to the kids so enriching this cultural exchange you're welcome and then they
have a secret meal they always have a secret meal before or after that they don't invite the native
peoples too that's just the secret uh secret american meal anyway here's the questions I have
several jobs where I lost and found bins would fill up with pretty nice clothes that stayed there
for months on end my question is twofold first oh oh that cotton mouth first what is the statute
of limits what if I got like really good at pronunciation my problem that's the secret your
mouth has been too wet in case a moist mouth though myself what is the statute of limitations
on lost and found items how long do I have to wait until I can claim one as my own second what
is the statute of limitations on wearing clothes to work that I scored from lost and found at work
that's for free clothes in California there's an important factor here do you think and of course
they can't answer because that's not how this communication system works but do you think that
this is a job in which they are pretty sure that the clothing are left by customers or left by
other people that work there or it is left by the ceo or whatever boss-like figure exists
in this establishment um who just stocks the lost and found with tight looking clothes
to make them think that they have a certain level of clientele coming in that can just
lackadaisically leave their their clothes lying around and so they think the business is doing
very very well is that a mark echo hoodie nice nice summit we we're doing great we're pulling
in that mark echo money apparently I know we laid off 14 people last week but I guess we're doing
mark echo good are those are those Dolce and Gabbana jams who wore those into the store we
we are attracting quite the clientele here maybe it's a test what what what how could this be
brothers how can how are people leaving their fucking clothes behind but that's what I'm saying
because if it's customers I totally get it because like that's the kind of thing where it's like did
I leave it at the movies today we went out for coffee at where did I leave my hoodie you know
that thing but like if you work there then you're like okay I had it when I got to work I didn't
have it when I got home like where's my under where's my oxford shirt I wore it to work and
I got home and I didn't have it on was I robbed where's my sweet under armor workout clothes
I wear my pants I went to see 50 shades of gray and then I oh okay now I remember solved I took
my pants off and jerked off into it I was trying to do a more tasteful prairie home companion style
bit about that griffin but that's fine if you want to get if you want to get jerky boys raunch
in the in the episode that's fine I don't see let's take your peanut butter and my chocolate
and jerk off into it it's me garrison keeler nailing it that's really good it's running you
better go catch prince albert pranks jerky jerky it's garrison keeler I got red shoes
jerky you sing a fake song about biscuits jerky charvis are you okay what you sound very you
sound the sickest I've ever heard a person's out maybe just when you're doing jerky boys
that's my jerky men you're jerky keeler okay I just got worried about you for a second
I've been ill lately and I haven't been able to drink many beverages jerky wow it's like a it's
like a very lucid death rattle do you guys want to yahoo it sounds like a disease that should be
named after him like that's my loved ones I'll miss them jerky I've got terminal jerky keeler
how about a yahoo answer yeah what is that uh it's a service where people barf onto the internet
and people scrape it up and present it to me like dogs we lap it up and shit out jokes uh-huh um
thank you to matt estives who scraped this barf up and presented it to me like a like a proud dog
it's by yahoo answer this dead bird darn doorstep uh it's by uh dead bird ethan who asks
best non-beginner snake I am getting a new snake but I don't want an amateur level snake such as
a ball python or corn snake update I have a budget of four hundred dollars or update please help
snake attack okay slightly less on the expertise scale something between ball python and the
ball python and the anaconda from anaconda maybe you go with snake pliskin he requires a lot of
care and feeding and he's always trying to escape uh-huh that's a different that's a challenge his
depth perception is terrible so don't try some sort of solid snake yeah just one long solid snake
yeah don't try and get any liquid snakes I always wondered about that that's not a good code name
for like a super super duper spy because I'm out of rats Timmy hasn't come back to feed me yeah
do you think that was a subtle reference to like solid thing was like a boner
like I saw Debbie last night she was looking real good I got a real solid snake I'm not
gonna fucking yes and this shit if you want to see it through to its natural conclusion that's
on you no I'll help you out I'll do a whole self-dialogue about it you're saying Hideo
Kojima was like what can we do what can we name this person that will be the most dude studliest
name imaginable and it's like how about Guy Hardcock and no can we get something with a
little bit more illusion than that something a little bit more a little bit more prairie home
companion a little bit less jerky boys I really like the idea of somebody like looking at somebody
else with a ball python and being like uh can I can I ask an important question though how do you
measure snake expertise how do you how do you here's here's my snake expertise you want to know
what it is I've never been bitten by a snake so I think I'm pretty fucking good at it right I think
I'm pretty good at snakes I live in Texas it's not out of the the realm of possibilities I've seen a
snake when you uh when you buy a snake they actually give you a little counter that you hang
on the wall and says like day since swallowed right and if he and it ticks up every day and
if you get to like a hundred that seems like a pretty good streak you're ready for the next level
you get to cash that card in and they're like oh in 100 days okay here's a king cobra but you well
well king cobras can be sweethearts actually if you milk them properly I think the the hardest
thing about owning a snake would be learning to overcome the urge like when you see the snake
when you walk into your room like give me an axe yeah it's a snake I gotta kill it well I bought
you do you guys want to hear a fun a fun true snake anecdote is it even remotely funny yeah
Bob and Bradbury and Teresa and I we went to the Cincinnati zoo okay and we were walking around we
were drinking some beers we were getting a mild zoo drunk they have that yeah and we walked into
the reptile house and as we walked in I passed this tiny bearded gentleman who who was wearing
a zoo staff shirt panicking at a door and he just turned to me with no preface and said hold this
and dumped a giant snake in my arms that's and turned back to the door and his key had gotten
stuck in the door and he was panicking which did not put me at ease but then you left me standing
there with no explanation there is no way this happened this did not happen at a professional
proof of it was it was it a zoo or was it like a dream zoo in your mind that you dreamed no this
was real and I it was fucking terrifying what kind of snake was it it was a yellow one oh maybe a uh
San Francisco garter snake maybe it's a corn snake no it was bigger than that he seemed he had a mean
look in his eye how um what do you do with your old snake when you because you obviously can't
keep these snakes together snakes hate each other so much you know why snakes are so fast is they
have to be fast as soon as they're born their mom turns around like a swallow gulp they are the
gulpinest animals around and for that reason I I have a sinister love for them um but what do you
do when you get a new harder snake you have to pass your snake to a novice I guess that's true
yeah there's probably a craigslist like chapter a chapter of craigslist just full of old snakes
just old basic snakes you got a real basic snake there do you get snake trade-in credit
if you trade in here at snake stop do you get snake trading credit for your all-use snakes
hey I guess you'll never believe it we got a western hog nose dropping next month that's
really gonna blow your mind you want to reserve it and we also can sell you a subscription to
snake informer for 15 a month it's a really great deal and that's going to get you 10 off
the taiwan beauty snake start brushing up on your flute because we've got some of those scary vipers
and baskets you ready for the next level mario's at it again I'm bad at this yeah my girlfriend
and I attend planet fitness regularly the first monday of every month they provide free pizza
pizza okay due to my worst okay okay wait do my my girlfriend and I attend planet reading
it again is not gonna make this goddamn sentence make any more fucking sense of every month they
provide free pizza why does a gym have a fucking cheat day built I guess I get it like make them
feel like pizza garbage and then get them up on those fucking ellipticals or whatever people
I guess it's literally like people who are like god it's so hard to get to the gym and someone's
like well once a week it is not once a week once a week is very easy there is a pre-scheduled
pizza picnic anyway due to my work schedule we can only get there at the tail end of the
pizza offerings and we don't want to eat then work out so is it okay to just go eat some pizza
and leave are we good that's from planet pizza in pennsylvania what is happening what the fuck
I mean you're lying to us hey guys 420 you're lying to us which I don't appreciate um because
there's no way that why would it no there's no unless it's like fucking flat bread you know
what what did they call it squid pizza it's like square flat pizza it's like a pizza flat bread
yeah flat bread I'm pretty much over it by the way there was flat bread at every hotel we went to
uh that's pizza you're you're either pizza or shit like just be pizza flat bread stop trying to
sound healthier than you are yeah there was a flat bread at one of the hotels that had marinara
pepperoni and cheese on it hey hey you're a pizza Travis has sent us an image Travis wants to send
us an image file gonna look at this and Travis has just sent us a picture of him with a snake
sorry Travis didn't mean to doubt you that wasn't a lie but this fucking workout pizza
definitely still is uh I don't understand wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute
what if this isn't like a planet fitness promotion because that again is fucking patently insane
maybe one person who works at planet fitness uh buys a pizza for themselves every week to enjoy
and then leaves the room and comes back is like again
man yogi I'm gonna get you pizza thief somebody keeps like teenager ninja turtles in me
they scarf my za I have a more sinister theory and that is that there's a sort of
panopticon that exists in the planet fitness um universe where it's probably the most personal
panopticon a personal panopticon a network of surveillance for mr fitness himself the owner
of the whole franchise uh once a month can just watch people just slam down on some pizza in his
place of business and like the denial of pizza from himself gives gives him like the raging
a solid snake like you could ever imagine a human being and it's like fucking it's just
super fit and muscular boner um and it's like the best one that you could that anyone can
possibly get and the only way he can get it is through his big brother style pizza surveillance
system is it possible that this is a honeypot that they're trying to keep you needing the planet
fitness services for longer how's his progress going jeremy it's going pretty good fill fitness
i think he's just about really fit well unleash the za and then you order he orders pizza from
a store right that's by unleashing it he gets another place to make it don't tip very well
planet fitness isn't doing super great i'm not made of money jeremy is it possible single topping
jeremy is this a uh is this like a muscle confusion like a tummy confusion type of thing
whereas your tummy's like oh fuck yeah thanks griffin we're taking it to pizza town why are you
running why are you running i want to watch all the episodes of parks and recreation and just
chill for once i thought we were gonna play persona on the couch and now you're running
you confused me oh man i just lost 30 pounds thanks griffin i i i think that the the problem
with that is that your tummy upon sensing the workout this is the way the body works
your tummy upon sensing the workouts like oh no the pizza i gotta hold on to it stay with me
pizza don't run away so your tummy's gonna hold all that pizza it's not gonna digest it
because it's so worried about losing those precious pizza calories exactly that's exactly
right justin because when you're like running on a treadmill you know what's happening that pizza's
just fallen out of you just falling out of your tummy and so your tummy's gotta hold on tight
oh good stay in me stay in me i love you pizza you guys i think you've picked a bad place to
get fit i think you should change this question should end with should i change gyms because this
is a bad one apparently where they serve pizza i think it sounds like the best possible gym uh
i can't believe that wasn't a yahoo yeah that's a really weird situation to find yourself in that
was a human being question wait wait we didn't actually answer it oh uh fucking absolutely not
it's like you can't go to church on doughnut sunday and slam those doughnuts and then say
i don't need to hear the lord's word this week later i got my doughnuts and like through them
i channeled the lord's good blessing this yahoo was sent in by recognize the game of rachel
sperling thank you rachel it's by yahoo answers user sdx zxz didn't even try who asks ladies
i bring my guitar almost everywhere to impress women does this work for example if i go to a
party or a store i'll usually bring my case with me and if i see a woman i like i will get it out
and play it hoping she hears what i don't understand is why it doesn't seem to work
the other day i was at target the most attractive woman i've seen in years was shopping
and got my guitar out and played wonder wall but she didn't come over i went and asked her out and
she said no frigid jerk don't women love guitar players confused right now it's work a few times
but not as often as i thought my co-workers like it at least i think my co-workers at the weed store
love it i think the problem is song choice you have to pick the right song that's going to lure
them in i uh personally have always found that bob dylan's i know how to use this thing between
my legs real good would you like to try it out sometime uh off of bob dylan unplugged and
unrecorded give me a good it's just a person that album is just a person telling you about
how great that album was yeah can you give me a few bars of i know how to use this thing between
my legs between my legs and you're gonna see the thing that i'm talking about it's so this
is an early one i'm guessing this is before he goes electric but right around when he went
eclectic uh he did a lot of novelty hits i know how to use this thing between my legs
and then do you want to see how i use it on you it's good this is a song about vaginas too
all right it's all inclusive no matter what you want to use i know how to use it on you
so bob don't hang all up in blue oh see okay what happened there later that song no that
actually that was a mishap with a blue cable his penis got tangled up into it
it could be removed surgically his penis and his vagina he gives me a great idea
yeah your your dylan sounds a little urkely just a little bit you sound like billy bob from the
rocket fire explosion can i get some cheese please did i do that did i do that tangled up in carl
you're gonna make me stephan when you go
i'm trying to i'm trying to uh uh i'm trying to figure out if i uh don't know more dylan
songs or don't know more urkel references really it's hard to make the two apparently i know
exactly the same that means you just store them in the same filing cabinet in your brain right
oh this over here uh let's see what's stored in here oh looks like uh this is dylan references
and urkel quotes i don't know why these got filed together i'm so thirsty should we go to
the money zone so you can get a fucking drink yeah you guys do this our first sponsor today is
me undies uh we are tired of a drought down there or tired of moisture down there i should say i
guess like the opposite problem from what i have in my mouth right now uh then you're gonna need
a pair of me undies they're magical underwear they're not magical sorry they're um they're
the most comfortable underwear that you are ever gonna put on they fit great they don't ride up
and they actually pull moisture away from your skin it could be cool and dry can you prove they're
not magical is there is there is there substantial proof that they're not magical because i'm i'm
betting if you put these like over a dead goose it'll come back to life there's magic everywhere
i'm telling you right now that i'm wearing me undies and they feel pretty dang magical
okay on my zone i just want to reiterate our policy of not informing our brothers of what is
touching our dicks okay you guys hold your ears hold your ears brothers okay okay it's touching
my dick right now and it feels terrific i'm not wearing me undies i'm ashamed to admit i'm not
wearing me undies right now i'm wearing some store brand uh boxer briefs and it feels like
i'm sitting on a fucking man witch it's just sloppy and terrible down there me have you checked
me undies yeah are you maybe um note that me undies will not protect you if you sit on a
man which they will they will again people are sitting on a man which at any point in the world
and they don't know it you're really short selling these me undies justin because you don't know if
that's true or not that's true griffin me undies.com my brother is going to save you 20 off this level
of quality normally to cost you twice as much as you're going to pay at me undies and now you can
save even more go to me undies.com my brother and get 20 off your first order and you're going to
get free shipping save even more when you buy a pack so go get them we hear from people all the
time about how much they love me undies uh and you should get on that list uh we also want to
tell you it's it's a favorite of ours it's a favorite of max funds i'm sure you've heard
all about it but in case you haven't in case you are maybe new to the world were you just
born baby well then listen up we're gonna tell you about harry's harry's is a a razor uh supply
company is that the best way to describe it would you say a razor giver a razor giver but you do
have to you do have to pay for them i'm sorry they don't just give you them yes just like in
the giver you have to pay for your memories um my brother my brother me is sponsored by harry's.com
um we love them we shave our faces with them harry's razors offer high quality shave that's
better for your face and your wallet we've all been there we've all walked into the we won't
use any brand name stores here but let's say the bvs and we've said like we'll take a razor and
they have all greens all greens the the fruits that's probably fine fruits fuck fruits though
right aid fuck you too you're done more like wrong aid and then you go to the person of the county
you say i want a razor they unlock it for you they ring it up and it's like 40 and you're like that's
bs bs then they take one of the razors out they cut themselves with it just to show you that these
are in fact very sharp blades and they cut themselves on the arm with it and and you feel
really guilty about that i don't i don't want to watch another person cut their arm with the razor
that i'm ostensibly going to use later just to prove to me that it's sharp enough it's not right
spent 40 and you've lost a little bit of yourself yeah yeah well what if i told you you could get
from harry's a starter set for just 15 whoa what do you know and it includes a razor foaming shave
gel or shave cream and three razor blades plus free shipping we're gonna give it to you for
ten dollars if you go to harry's.com you get five dollars off the starter set with the code my
brother all one word you're gonna get it for ten dollars that's such a good deal start shaving
better today harry's.com my brother uh got a uh this is a new one for us uh a friend of the show
by which i mean a listener who gave us money i'm gonna introduce you to a listener named chance
gibbs here's a message from chance he's an english teacher who has lost 175 pounds that's right
175 pounds as you can imagine extra skin hangs off me like a flappy flag when there's no breeze
it's not cute i've done all the hard work to lose weight now i need the help of the speak for
yourself am yeah daddy like to write the he needs the help from our army to raise 33 000 uh he needs
to get that extra skin removed uh go to uh bit.ly forward slash chance needs surgery that's bit.ly
forward slash chance needs surgery and uh kick in some cash and he's gonna send you some of the skin
they can hold and i gotta say 33 000 seems a little steep i think i can probably get that
shit off you for maybe a good no problem at all 1500 i can probably do about 1500 for you if you
want uh yeah oh sorry did you want to be alive afterwards oh you didn't want to live through it
did you oh okay well if you want to be alive through it you may want to do this 33k if you
donate if you donate uh uh 12 000 he'll explain the ending of lost to you so that's you got that
to look forward to because the secrets are hidden in his folds go to bit.ly forward slash chance
needs surgery and peel back one of the folds and says here's why there were only four toes on that
statue thank you for visiting my skin my skin palace griffin what's the next message this
finally uh this final yahoo wow what no this uh final message is for the people of earth
i just read it i'm gonna just take us fucking sprinting leap at it the the fiery chasms in
front of us the the exit rocket ship the the escape pod is right in front of us we have to jump
over the pit i'm running this message is for the people of earth and it's from chris who says
tp from a bunghole so if you've ever spent a hundred dollars and think oh i just wasted it
you have not wasted it the worst that anybody's ever wasted a hundred dollars and i don't know
what you're talking about that is solid that was a solid goof i gotta be explicitly clear here
the message is parenthetical to the tune of welcome to the jungle in parenthetical tp for
my bunghole so that's the whole bit chris solid i didn't well spit i did as good as i could i
still got a little bit of a sore throat from the live show you want me to try uh yeah i'm
worried that your was that better no a little too high let me try maybe even about two octaves too
high on that one you yep tp for my bunghole nailed it that's somebody's new text message alert
hi i'm julie sabatier host of rendered it's a show about making meaning and breaking rules
we're answering important questions like can you build a space suit in your living room
i went to my brother's place in beaverton and he has a swimming pool and i pressurized the suit
and sat down there underwater for about 10 minutes the thing that i built was supporting my life
that felt really good what does it sound like when you play a polka record through a styrofoam cup
and what happens when an airport carpet gains a cult following oh my goodness the carpet
the carpet has an instagram check out rendered now at maximum fun.org
or wherever you like to listen to podcasts i've been doing comedy for about a year now and i find
that more and more i'm being introduced to people as a comedian how do i deal with the dreaded oh
you're a comedian tell me a joke let me try again oh you're a comedian tell me a joke and that's
from that's from mrs big head from rocco's modern life obviously i don't feel the need to prove my
merits to the boorish people who ask this you sound funny but uh what i like to hear you three
do in this situation you must get this crap once in a while uh what am i a joke jukebox is the name
of that question asker you actually don't get a lot when you say like i'm a podcaster right oh
then podcast for me i i have literally in my life never described myself as a comedian in my fucking
life i would never do that no not a crazy thing to say like no one's like oh i'm a baker and like
no one's like oh you're a baker bake something for me right now i need some fucking banana bread
now let's see what you got motherfucker here's some yeast oh you're a butcher kill this dog kill
this dog in front of me you can't just say shit butcher wait you're a sociopath here prove it on
this bird sicko uh i mean i never would say like i don't let anybody know that i'm supposed to do
jokes on the internet like i just never tell anybody that's my workaround i tell people i uh
people ask what i do i say i write about video games and then i just watch as the interest drains
from their face you can it's like sand from an hourglass yeah the conversation just fizzles out
like i can't fire someone just dump gatorade on sometimes i'll just start explaining the rules
to magic the gathering until they walk away in excruciating detail great question great
here's how resources work you're gonna want to tamp the tap your mana and then um oh man i feel
like the appropriate response to this is if someone's like oh you're a comedian tell me a
joke you just go like no and then you like say anything else that seems good trev well i mean
like what are they gonna say if they're like no i said tell me a joke this has been classic
conversation enders which i was mcroy who who is this person who who is this person that is
this is not a joke by the way it'd be great if you busted out like some seinfeld shit
like i'm about to but um who is who is this person that hears your comedian and then responds with
tell me a joke what what person exists that does that no i i can't it's beyond the fucking pale
that anybody would ever do this to you enough to to give you this psychosis that you've obviously
developed i i imagine not being a comedian myself that it's the kind of job title that when you say
it people are immediately incredulous because it's not like you could say like i'm a teacher
and people are just like okay why would you lie about that but imagine if you say like oh i'm
i'm like a comedian professionally i think as people have a hard time believing that they might
actually meet somebody who is funny professionally you know what i mean so they feel the need to like
oh really prove it which is like the worst i had an experience along these lines yesterday i called
the uh uh sort of like a customer service place about something that's too boring to recount
and uh a guy asked you know how how i was doing and i said well i'm a little tired just got back
from uh i was doing a uh i was in these cities you know in the midwest he said what are you doing
he said what are you doing it and it was like a little tour my brothers and i do a comedy show
because he said he was in minneapolis right so that's what prompted it now i remember
and uh he said well um i wish i'd heard about that i would have tried to make it out
really really i think that would have been a weird show for you to come out to but like i
appreciate it and then he adds yeah i mean everybody needs to laugh and i was like yeah
yeah it's especially you it sounds like i guess yeah like how how bad do you need to laugh where
you hear about a comedy show from three chuckleheads you've never heard of and thought
man i wish i could have made it out damn that sounds fucking good wish i could have gone to
that thing with no context whatsoever i know it was just a pleasantry but man i it was a bridge
too far you should have held them to it i'm like can i get your contact info yeah we might be
coming out again i'll put you on the vip list is that what it's called yeah the vipple yeah i get
that a lot for my job as game journalist i tell people i'm a game journalist and they say well
you think the new battlefield and i say i don't play that fucking garbage and then i cash a 15
thousand dollar check from activision and they see me they see me do all of that and they say
okay well done now i get i buy it it seems like a good field how much 15 15 000 okay it sounds
about right how about yahoo yeah i was about to ask by the way everybody at some point during
this program i covertly have obtained a pepsi max you'll never know how uh uh wow it's people
are gonna be ferreting that one out for years this yahoo is sent in by zoe kinski uh she's
been sending out a lot of good stuff she's moving up the leaderboards thank you zoe it's
about i need a bit for her soon yeah i know it's breaking my back it's the new it's the new jingles
it's by yahoo answers user josh who asks what would you do if an arby's manager punched you in
the face all right ironically if you're about to eat arby's it's not the worst thing to have
happened to you in that moment uh so uh buckle in it's a little bit long okay so my friend and i
go into an arby's to get some food last night not gonna lie kind of short on cash so we don't order
any drinks instead ask for a water cup when our food is ready you know the manager tells us in a
real douchebag way that the water isn't working and no we can't have a water cup it was like we
were asking him anything outrages just a cup i ask for something else and he just continues to be
way too concerned about his job i'm a server i work in a restaurant so i think this guy's crazy
one for being so rude too he has to be able to supply us with something to drink we finish our
meal and i decide it would be funny if i knock a rather large stack of cubs that are sitting on the
counter oops jesus now this real chuckle fest now this is where it gets interesting my friend and i
proceed to the exit there's a guy at the door he's using the usual fuck you blah blah blah verbal
fighting stuff we kind of laugh and continue walking towards the car halfway to the car i get
clocked in the face from behind you someone punched you through the back of your skull and punched
you the front of your face bones off my manager ran out of the store with two other employees
punched me in the face and the other employee shoved my friend to the ground
i got hit pretty good this guy had a running start and i was completely blindsided
i was what you didn't see is if you looked to your left you would have seen tyler durden like
yeah that's right how do you feel like a man uh feel like a strong man i was knocked over your
cups my friend jumped right up from being shoved he saw me get whacked so naturally he's defending
me i didn't really see that part but i know he got him a few good times the guy ended up running
in with blood all over his lip and shirt the other two guys are just talking shit to me surrounding
me trying to scare me a man pulls up and breaks up the fight we go straight home i have a huge fat
lip my jaw won't even close right my teeth hurt really bad friend's shirt is ripped up blood all
over it we talked about it for a while figure we should call the cops so we do arby's had called
the cops too exaggerated the story told them we threw stuff and fought them first whatever you
know we called we told the cops our story but what do we do now what would you do if an arby's
manager punched you in the fucking grill don't you guys feel like listening to this story that
that this person telling the story like is about to say oh i guess i should also mention we were
really belligerently drunk but i don't think that has any impact on the story whatsoever
i should mention we were very high on um uh hallucinogenic mushrooms and we may have been
at our home the entire time this may be a fiction like the time we might have been fighting each
other this might have been like the time the world's worst zoo employee handed travis a snake
in his mind yeah he hastily photoshopped a picture of it and then i called the police and the police
said travis you've been home all day because you've called us 20 times also the snake called
us beforehand and told us inside of this said i'm worried about travis he's been locked in his house
all day also you're still high and you'll never not be high travis whoa um what do you i'm not
interested in talking about the fight if fucking happened it's wrong violence is not the answer
it's not funny we shouldn't laugh at the violence what is hilarious gut buster is how you seek
justice for this act call the cops the cops said they called us first and told us their side story
we have no proof it's an arby's the fucking beef oils all over the place just completely get rid
of any fingerprints we could have used to figure out this crime uh it's gonna be hard to csi this
one so it's your word against theirs and they work at arby's so you lose just sort of de facto
right do you do you know how decrepit you have to be for the cops to say well i hear what you're
saying but this arby's manager is giving us a different story and we're gonna have to go with
him because he it's an institution yeah why do we always have to be so hard on arby's i like arby's
they serve fine food everyone i've ever interacted with there has always been pleasant yeah i'm sure
we have people listen they're working on arby's so they so they fucking cold clock every 10th
person that comes so you punch the occasional dildo who cares they shouldn't have been in the
store knocking over your cups and throwing things and fighting with people and starting fights
that's right i i bought the arby's story too i don't buy this email you're an arbypologist
this sounds like you're trying you're angling for a class action lawsuit get everybody together
who's ever been punched by an arby's manager and you guys are gonna try to bring down big beef
and i'm not having it but the sheer number of people who've been punched in the fucking grill
by an arby's manager is so enormous at this point that you'd end up getting like a buck 16
maybe you have to you would ironically have just enough to buy some jalapeno hush puppies and
arby's and you promised yourself never again never again because you bought some and you got fucking
cold clocked and then you ate one of them and oh the capucin what if your what if your settlement
came in the form of an arby's gift certificate and it just had like a picture that manager like
here we go let's do this again okay are you gonna come to tango with me name the place and time
motherfucker name the place and time except this offer is not good on friday up on me and punch me
in the face again try i've been ready for you oh you and your two friends buford and big buford
i was taking you down i just was there a small buford sandwich by the way talking about rallies
they hate each other they're different oh you gotta go to rallies and claim sanctuary
oh gang war that's what i'm saying you go to rallies and you say i'm willing i'm willing to
commit to you it's okay man what'd they do to you over there now listen we can figure out a way to
get back at them but i need to know are you willing to die for this are you willing to beef in
beef out motherfucker beef beef or die motherfucker get out there here's a chain here's a box of tots
you're gonna need both on that hard battlefield yeah you're gonna find keep your strength up
yes don't confuse them you make sure if you get hit with i don't know a knife
if so they hit you with an arby's knife you eat those tots and your hit points are gonna come
right back take this it's dangerous to go alone take this it's a curly fry it's arby's city rampage
the problem with the curly fries at arby's is it's very hard to judge how many fries you've eaten
no because i like to eat about 20 fries a day and if with the arby's uh fries they're very
curly and long sometimes they're like four or five fries in there just like a fry you know come on
obama yeah come on obama it could be it could be more accurately described as a bouquet yeah as a
fry arrangement that's where you have to judge it by weight or tummy feel are we done with the
podcast yeah that was the end of it it felt like the end of it to me oh exciting news yeah let's
chop this shit on them i'm tired of sitting on this on this news this bomb this news bomb uh we're
gonna gonna go back out in the road when you ask well funny you should ask this august the last
weekend of august we at my brother my brother and me industries are coming to portland oregon
seattle washington and beautiful vancouver bc that's right our first international tour how
many people how many people are listening that hoping like the third city would be like demoyne
like just fucking that's a clear path baby portland straight to seattle and then down to
houston now this is a really exciting bit if you are going to be in seattle for pax
you will be able to come see us that saturday night it's uh august 28th 29th and 30th
it's uh portland the 28th seattle the 29th and in vancouver bc on the 30th and i'm super excited
by the way it's gonna be crazy i've never been to portland or canada so like i'm pretty excited
about i've never been to seattle i've never been to portland i've never been to canada this is
big for me this is the hat trick the canadian the blues of colin tossed salad and scrambled eggs so
that's the kind of stuff you can expect can some really good seattle themed goofs what do you got
for canada what do you got in store there maybe some uh i'm just gonna talk about canadian
dragon's den i'm just gonna talk talk about kevin o'leary and uh are we gonna tell him when and
where and how to get tickets uh well charlie you're gonna make bitly links we're not gonna
have tickets on sale until friday uh where can they go to like get those links like we'll put
them out on our twitter page obviously yeah that's probably the most convenient but you can also go
to our facebook page just my brother my brother and me it's my brother my brother my appreciation
group yeah that one and they'll all be up on there and you know what we'll probably also post a video
uh to our youtube channel announcing it there so any of those three ways but we'll uh we'll
probably put those links out earlier than the on sale date which is going to be on little griffin's
birthday april 17th yeah tickets will go on sale uh for those shows so if they sell out super fast
you don't get any please don't yell at me it's my fucking birthday fucking birthday and and they
tend to so just don't hesitate don't wait yeah yeah don't sleep on it we never have any idea of
how these things are going to do the seattle venue in particular is like a pretty big venue but there's
going to be like 80 000 people at pax so like i have no fucking clue i have no fucking clue but
be oh and it's not just my brother my brother me it's saw bones as well what yeah so you get two
awesome podcasts in one night i'm just gonna say i noticed that one of these has a curfew
that's nice hey boys time to get to bed we had one another show we did didn't have
you my sleepy boys go to bed we had a curfew at the minneapolis show i think i didn't realize
that anyway uh i hope we didn't exceed it i was not aware of it no uh anyway uh our shows are
uh usually pretty uh fun according to people who go to them uh sometimes five people get engaged
sometimes five people get engaged sometimes i get a little tipsy sometimes yeah uh so anyway we're
coming to seattle portland and vancouver and tickets are on sale on april 17th which is a
what is that friday yeah friday yeah uh and oh should we say we're gonna be we're gonna
be at the aladdin theater in portland the moore theater in seattle and the chan center uh vancouver
so uh we're super excited about it we hope you'll come out and and see us and go to all of those
shows come to the mall can we get they're pretty close can we get john roderick here's the problem
can we get john roderick to play for us the intro at the seattle show now that he is running for
seattle city council uh i you know what the only way i'd agree to that and by the way if you want
to read more about his platforms you can go to vote roderick dot com uh and i don't understand
any of it because it's all government i thought it was a goof at first it's a very serious no
it's a yeah yeah no it's a it's it's real yeah we don't usually like to get political here but
yeah i'm like i like the cut of his jib he's got some fucking good ideas and um his albums uh
inspired me more in college than any other musician on earth so let's hear what he has
to say about sewer maintenance yeah uh john roderick uh i will i would love to have him play
the intro to our show in seattle but what i want is for him to play the intro and then once it's
done stand on stage and stare at us with his fucking fingers on the fretboard just waiting
for the outro that's what i mean i need him to be like and the money and the money is this now is
this it now here comes uh that would let him decide when the show ends yeah yeah if he starts
playing the outro that's it that's all the jokes can we also time it so that during the show he
wins his city council election that would be so fucking enormous i want it to be a very important
night for all of us um anyway speaking speaking of thank you john roger and along with issues
for theme song it's a departure off the album putting the days to bed oh we also want to say
thank you to everyone who came out to our midwest here like they were three awesome shows and you
guys were incredible and everybody was lovely and thank you thank you all the venues were lovely all
the cities were lovely all the people were lovely it was amazing i'm also was um i'm sorry that if
i met you and i was kind of very drunk very chicago just that's just for the chicago audience
they i feel like the other ones you held your your shit together i have no memory is that
problematic that's a that's i would say yeah inherently the name of this this tour is justin
is not as drunk as last time so i hope you'll come out the tour the tour uh we also want to
say what follow us on twitter and facebook so you don't miss those announcements this is enough this
is we put these people through enough okay there's a lot of excitement so far we love you griffin
last yahoo yeah this final yahoo was sent in by zoe kensky moving up that fucking ladder maybe
that's her thing up the ladder no it doesn't work zoe kensky i'll think of something thank you zoe
it's by yahoo answers user engineer adam who asks my life hasn't been the same since pluto lost its
planet recognition i'm justin mcroy i'm travis mcroy i'm griffin mcroy this has been my brother
my brother me kid's your dad
do maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
oh hey there everybody i'm guy brannum and welcome to pop rocket a new weekly show picking over the
pop culture we all love to love with me to talk tv film music and anything else entertaining
our journalist margaret wopler academic writer and dj oliver wang digital strategist winner
mitchell and comedians and tina muhoff it's an intellectual and incredibly snark-filled
discussion about pop culture by five cranky hollywood 30-somethings no name calling no
rudeness just straight talk and a lot of role play i'm only 30-something for another year
me too and i don't tell anybody i'm 30-something pop rocket comes out every week from maximum fun.org