The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother and my brother mean advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I'm your middlest brother Travis McElroy.
And I'm your sweet baby brother Griffin McElroy. Hey Griff, what's wrong? Why are you being so
quiet? It's gonna it's gonna be a skit. Oh I didn't oh I didn't want to worry you guys and
I'll cut this out but it's gonna be a sketch. I know it's a sketch. I'm playing along. We're
trying to lead into the- No and I'll cut this part out but I didn't want the two of you guys
to be afraid. Okay let me I'll get back in now. Well I'm just I'm so scared of um listen listen
I'll cut that out too. Listen the PGA Tour has made is marched on Austin and taken over the town and
there's- PGA? Yeah professional golfers all right and they've made their way to Austin. All the
weirdos from South By just left and in the void they left all these rich jocks showed up and
started just golfing wherever the fuck they wanted. I don't know if the PGA Tour has ever been in the
city where you live but it's just like my house is covered in holes from their powerful drives
that they just blast right through. Are they doing like and one street golf? They're doing and one
street golf extreme street golf. I saw Rory McIlroy first of all he's been tormenting me
because he says he he keeps saying I want it back and that's what he sounds that's what he sounds
like as he yells at me and my family through the windows of my house and while he's blasting me with
balls um but then I see- Once what back? The name I guess even though it's spelled different I told
him that but then a ball hit me in the head and I went to sleep for an hour um but I did see him
playing some extreme street golf with the other big golfers of today. Name three other ones. Yeah
sure Rory McIlroy is one. Well you already said that one three other ones. One and and you know
three other ones that don't have your name let's just like go for it. Okay can I do Tiger? Yeah
yeah yeah. Tigers? Tiger? Yes. Jack Nicklaus. Golden Bear. Golden Bear and I think there's one
named Buddy. Anyway he's I saw Rory McIlroy take a golf ball and run and slam dunk it into a hole
that he made in the street that's a pothole now my son's gonna trip in um it's real tough stuff
it's real tough I would think after we got rich from the max fun drive that I would start liking
golf more but it's the way they're doing it is very riotous it's very destructive. Uh yeah just
a quick side note thank you everyone who donated we're recording this on the Wednesday uh previous
so I have to assume we just ended up at like 60,000 new and upgrading. I assume we're extremely
wealthy Travis pass me one of those kahibas that I purchased prematurely and will eventually regret
I'm sure. Griffin have you thought about getting super good at it yourself to like well if you
can't beat them join them and then beat them? Uh I mean I've been thinking about it slide me one
of those stinky smoke logs too while you're at it Travy. Yeah of course of course. It's just
let me light it with this other stinky. It's just for looks I don't light it um I and so
I thought about getting good at golf Travis but you know my my elbow. Yeah so I'm sorry I forgot
about that Griffin. I forgot about the hinge and the flaps in there. If you hear a loud smash and
then uh you know or maybe a four and then a smash uh it's because the PGA Tour has uh is doing it
in Austin. The end. Okay. Oh Griffin look out behind you a golf ball's coming your way. Uh oh.
That was supposed to be my glass breaking noise. Fuck. Fuck me Justin. God damn it. You know what
what's weird what's weird is I have Seinfeld glass uh in every window of my house and it's great
because it's insular which is great because it keeps the AC in in the hot summer and but the
only bad thing is when it smashes like when Michael Richards jumps through it it doesn't
make the traditional noise it does make the boogie ball wow wow. Should I have a Michael
Richards more Michael Richards representation on the soundboard? No. I think the only sort of
clip that he's known for would not work very well on our show because of our format. Yeah how
horrible it is and he is and all that jazz. Well this is an advice show that is funded by you
the listeners and uh we do appreciate you just not to harp on it but it's like
and we have a lot of fun here but it really means a lot to us so thank you so much for your
eternal support. Um did I not mention it was an eternal pledge you're making? Yeah this is forever.
Yeah this is forever. Uh let's get into the advice. I work in wildlife rehabilitation.
One week into this job I was cleaning one of the owls enclosures. Justin did you use your new
found max fund wealth to buy a new narrator voice? Yeah it's nice it sounds like you've got four or
five Cohibas going in there. Do you know what's irritating? Why? One of the reasons I really don't
enjoy you guys and wow this is much more professional it's more of a professional
relationship at this point than a familiar one yeah is because I was in my head thinking like
this is sounding good. I was already congratulating myself for how well I was reading it and not
stumbling or messing it up at all and then you fucking dill wheat. It was nice it was good.
Yeah it was like I just wanted to finish it with like my streak. All right try again. I work in
wildlife rehabilitation. One week into this job I was cleaning one of the owls enclosures and when
I turned to leave she attacked the back of my head. She didn't draw blood but I definitely felt
her talons graze my scalp. It was startling as fuck and since then the owl and I have had a
strained relationship. I feel like she hates me. How do I learn to trust this animal again? And
that's from living in fear in Louisiana. Sounds like you need to get the animal to trust you
first and foremost. And with owls that that's a tough one. That's a tough one with owls. They're
a tricky they're a tricky one because um of the ill omens and all that yeah sure you could throw
up a you know field mouse for them to catch and play a big game with that but then you know the
field mouse certainly is not going to trust you at that point. You can you can try to do something
behind an owl's back but it's just going to turn right the fuck around and see it with that crazy
head they have. That weird head. When you were attacked did you snitch on them? Did you go tell
like the head of the wildlife or maybe the owl was testing to see if you could keep your mouth shut?
That's amazing. When I was in elementary school uh I my my my friend well we were more acquaintances
John cut in front of me he had about a foot and a half on me and he cut in front of me in the
four square line I said hey you just cut in front of me and he slapped he slapped me on the face
and I guess somebody reported it and we got sent to the principal's office and I didn't fucking
snitch and me and John were so tight from that point on so that's one way to do it is to just
keep your cool about this owl and you know maybe they'll apologize no blood drawn which first of
all good scalp you got there holy shit tough one yeah if this but like if this owl had wanted to
fuck you up oh yeah you'd be fucked up yeah this was this is the owl sending a message here's where
you've already ruined it you've already botched this as bad as you possibly can if an owl does
this you have to owl tax your scalp spin around in one smooth motion and punch it in the face
and then it's like dominance respect hey yeah it'll give you this kind of like okay look all
right get it I see what's happening you and I respect and then you fight and if you beat it
it's not ready to go out into it is not rehabilitated yet that is a good it's a good
question like wildlife rehabilitation it doesn't mention rehabilitation for what
so maybe this is always a bad seed counter owl and it's just acting out it's a behavioral
rehabilitation yes it's got a problem with authority it's got dissociative personality
disorder it's got some antisocial tendencies and it just uh it just doesn't like people that much
let's just say like hey I'm not fine I may seem fine I put on a brave face I'm still kind of
kind of messed up I need to chill here for a little bit longer listen can I tell you something
question asker owl attacked human that seems pretty normal to me actually yeah that's it
I think it'll be weirder if you walked in there and like the owl like waved at you happy to see
you the owl's not ready to go back out there like that owl attacks you that owl is ready to be on
its own that you should go back in like hey the owl attacked me and they'd be like oh that's good
news that's so cool hey that owl's fucking fine yeah let it go it's fine it's doing what owls do
I think the Japanese owl cafes got all the nice owls already and there's none left for the rest
of us let's make room for a timid bird sure um I've got a yahoo here can I read it yeah please
uh this one was sent in by level 9000 yahoo drew drew davenport thank you drew
it's from yahoo answers user they're anonymous i'm gonna call them um uh no no no asks
why don't scientists make military armor from bug shells yes bugs have hard shells that scientists
can backwards engineer manufacture in their laboratories if you take a bug and you make
the bug as large as a human or even bigger no gun would penetrate the shell also shells from
bugs can be regenerated imagine having armor that can regenerate itself wait what say again
shells there question asker shells from bugs can be regenerated imagine having armor that
can regenerate itself okay so you went you went some ways that I used them to make material okay
great engineer a bug as big as a human wait yeah wait whoa whoa whoa whoa this is a little old
lady who swallowed a flycatcher the enemy army is beating us because their their new cool guns
get through our get through our armor well I'm gonna take this uh this goliath beetle I'm gonna
make it uh like way bigger than us and then I guess I'll try and take its skin and wear that
yeah sounds like a good plan to me boop boop boop boop I've been gored by the goliath beetle
and now it covered three minutes three minutes elapsed it was really bad you know I also I don't
know listen I'm not a bug expert that should surprise no one but I'm pretty sure if you like
peel bug armor off of it it's not like oh totally cool I'll just regrow that I'm pretty sure what
you're talking about is like it's skin maybe I mean I can get skin back when it falls off sometimes
so who knows how bugs do it um they're littler than me so I assume they can't they don't have
all of my remarkable human powers um they can't drive but I can't but at the same time if I shoot
a ladybug bullet bounce right off because it's very very powerful chitin and I guess what I'm
wondering is how can I wear a big ladybug or why not just get a bunch of ladybugs and wear them
all at the same time and now it's good yeah I'm alone three ladybug lady um hey that was the plot
of the Rodney Dangerfield movie ladybugs yes what what human power would you trade away for chitin
for chitinous plates hmm um you know maybe empathy wow yes good yes yes yes my my brother
my brother and gyver this is a chitinous cyborg free of emotion um I would say jumping
I just wouldn't be able to great point great point underused hardly using it for anything
anymore if you think about it guys I I'm trying let me stop and think about the last time I
jumped let me think about the last time that I I had cause to jump uh you think about that in like
in like a lot of uh something like the heart like the from software games like the hardcore action
games it's always note of it is made like you can't even jump like well so what yeah who still
jumps I'm god guys I swear I'm trying to think of the last big jump I did and I just I have I have
nothing I have nothing it must have been to get over a rock or something or to you know get the
health potion I don't fucking remember the last time I jumped it may have been the last time I
played basketball which is a long time ago just what about you what human power would you give away
they're all so great they're all good gift I think it would be regrowing hair oh I think
I would be okay with I to roll the dice I know I can't get any frosted tips that I later regret
uh I guess I gotta always die it but no I get this one hair and that's it this is all the hair
I have but I do have this incredible bulletproof chitin it lets me clean up the streets of Chicago
you know what along now you've made me think because you said this one hair which made me
think that instead of individual hairs you just have one adorable baby huey no but just more like
your entire head of hair was one solid piece a coiled rope yes and I thought here's what I would
go with um I would be willing to give up the space between my individual teeth to get bug
armor I would have just one big top tooth and one big bottom tooth one horseshoe shaped tooth
and I think I know amazing that actually might be more powerful than individual teeth now that I
think about it violated the spirit of the game then yeah I was at my coworker's birthday we're
not super close but it's civil holy shit okay I uh want to stab them quite bad yeah I'd like to
stab them but don't that's what civil means if it weren't for your human laws yes I gave her
a birthday card I keep in my glove box for emergencies that's some next level shit I hope
you mean emergency birthdays not just like oh no flat tire use it use it to stop the bleeding
it had love you lots on the front and gold letters I didn't think it was weird I just thought the
design was pretty when she read the front she said whoa I didn't know you felt that way really
stepping up this relationship how do I live in this atmosphere I've created that's from
platonic proposal in Chicago well congrats on realizing that this is completely your fuck up
this is completely your fuck up yeah this is like if you're gonna get an emergency card it
needs to say something like celebrate like just like I don't even think you want to go specific
as birthday now it's like celebrate and the side it's like this is a day yes or it just says
occasion exclamation point it's now the time is now for this day sorry thank you and congratulations
this day is here and you are here too you've made it to this day maybe more it could also
just be a sort of innocuous compliment like a picture of a dinosaur and on the inside it says
like I think you're a dino might and then they open that and read it and they're like oh it's
cool that's too much oh okay do you know how many times I've been at somebody's birthday and
I realized like oh I didn't get them anything I really should get through anything and then I'll
like sit there on my phone and send them an iTunes gift card from my phone yeah and then get the eye
contact from across the like I don't mean for it to happen right then but they'll get the
notification like bing bing oh hold on I got a text from Justin it's right this second it just
says I'm inconsiderate that's weird but it says it says I'm inconsiderate please enjoy the new
Drake album on me wow seven dollars Justin thanks so much I'll be able to enjoy half an album it's
a problem with gift cards right it's a problem with gift cards is you are saying here is exactly
what you're worth to me yeah here's the exact dollar value that you are that I value you this
is that could have gone 20 listen to technology today there should be an option when you purchase
like a gift card online for someone to backdate it like they'll just wedge it in in their gmail
like five days ago and it's like oh yeah we'll date it like you said it on Monday don't worry
about it we got that is that is psychotic what you just said Travis that is if we if Tim Cook's
listening you're welcome yeah but if we do that what the fuck are we all doing here on earth as
part of this one sort of beautiful consciousness if we can trick each other with time time traveling
birthday cards I'm sorry I got rid of my empathy in exchange for this shit and you got me that
you got me that empathy polish and I got you that chitin polish but I don't know how ironic
well I can use the chitin polish I just can't uh jump to get it where you put it on the high
shelf put it on the high shelf that was my fault it was I uh uh I'm recording this on
Sydney's birthday and Charlie asked uh my my four-year-old daughter asked uh what I got
Sydney so I showed her this gift certificate that I got and it was really more of a this is like one
of the things they email you I got her as I sponsored a um a baby incubator for like a
nation in crisis where they don't have access to medical care and I thought well that would be a
lovely gift my wife would really appreciate that and I'm I'm showing this it's got a picture of
the baby incubator and everything on the thing I'm showing this on the chair and explaining it to her
and I finished this whole explanation and she took like three beats and said
why would she want this like well sweetie she doesn't she doesn't she she's not gonna she said
mommy doesn't even have a baby she won't like this like okay but it's a gift but it's her birthday
I know okay fine sorry you didn't even have to finish that story I could have told you
how it panned out when you explained to your four-year-old I got mommy a something she won't
be able to touch and bright something she won't use like cool that sucks dad yeah it sucks check
out this this uh this ceramic jimmy buffett parrot that I got her at hallmark this is a gift
I got her this bag of slime that I made her yeah um so this is the longest we've ever gone without
actually talking about the question because I think that that is the that is the severity of
this mistake you've made um terrible mistake terrible mistake but mistake feels the term
mistake almost feels like it um suggests an accident happened you can't look at the card that
says uh I what was it love you lots and thank you lots you know what that you know love is subjective
yes but we all sort of have a kind of agreement on what it means and then lots lots as a modifier
as if to say a great deal of love I possess for you and you gave this to somebody who is not true
for I will argue though that it's not like this the the front of the card said I must tell you
about my deep and very real feelings for you it's said in gold letters love you lots a thing one
might write in somebody's yearbook so no no no no I would say that maybe like us love you like a
sister that's exactly that one's to be forgotten yes yeah I would say that have a course on this
blame yes part of this blame does fall on the co-worker who looked at a greeting card since
we purchased at a store that you handed them and thought this is a declaration of true emotion
I think no one should ever think when they look at a greeting card what's anything greeting cards
are man can we just talk about them for a second I hope you've got your finger on that fucking
Seinfeld button yeah light them up just light them up dude get this to get this uh get this
whole industry that's existed for thousands of years and it's definitely been the the butt of
many many stand-up routines they're the worst and I always get them because it feels like we
have to and sometimes they're nice but it just seems like hey you're right let's go to fucking
a hack hit it no okay you're right I earned this now sit in that stew in that shit stew in it and
think about what you've done sorry you're right that's both for the question asker and for Justin
yeah we all we've all made some mistakes here yeah um you want another yahoo okay no we didn't
give any sort of help like I want to send them get them on a card the next day that just says
like no I don't no I don't I think you I think you need to okay you said it's been civil with
this person you're not really close fine I think you need to the relationship is now at a different
level right it's obviously been escalated to a different kind of relationship I think you need
to see how long you can sort of maintain that level of relationship and maybe the like uh
nothing gold can stay perhaps the relationship will fade in time and you'll revert to this sort
of like civil thing the but the but possibly a dear friend has been made this is the moment
some sliding doors have a dear friend walk yes walk through the sliding doors thank you Travis
yes that is my official TM advice is I think give it a whirl just see if you can maintain it
you didn't plan to be here but now you're here it's like you know you got on the wrong home alone
plane and you ended up in New York instead of uh Florida or whatever and you know what maybe have
some fun in Florida remind you though that isn't what happened this person got on a plane that was
labeled get on this plane to go to Paris without your son Kevin and then they were like that
sounds good I'll try it and then they got on the plane and landed and was like Kevin it's like well
no you remember you saw the planes but it was labeled what what then what you are suggesting
Justin is they have arrived and said oh wait right Kevin's my son and I left him at home
oh well I better have somebody pay as well I can yeah that's fair yeah mine's mine not that hopefully
your scenario Justin makes it sound like Kevin McAllister is the victim in the home alone films
when I would argue that that is true of everyone else in his family but not Kevin McAllister
yes that's how that yes I want to die on that hill that's how you feel I just decided Kevin's
not the victim here it is the rest of the family not not the eight-year-old boy left home alone
because his family hated him and forgot about him well hate is a strong word don't you think
he's just uh being a little pervert uh to his uncle and so he doesn't get woken up for this
plane ride it's I think a lot of it is perspective we showed Charlie that movie for the first time
about a year ago and she was I mean for her it's a horror movie right for a year for for months
afterwards she talked about they left him alone which is the name of the film from her perspective
was they left him alone with the name of that film yeah but me I'm a father too watching this
is as a 38 year old father of two people I watch it from Catherine Harris perspective and think
yeah I get it you know I get it you just want to relax your kid has zero chill you just want to
relax in Paris for a little while you know they don't talk about all the time that Catherine
Harris gets to sit in fucking silence you know a day like at least a good 24 hours I'll just be
able to sit in fucking silence flight there and like a 14-hour flight back where yes she must have
gotten on the plane right on the return and be like I feel so terrible but you can only maintain
that feeling for so long before then they bring you like the warm nuts and like yeah okay I
actually haven't seen a movie in three years do you have movies on this flight I mean I do feel
terrible but I've been meaning to see if Greatest Showman was a hit or miss miss my boy I hope the
sticky men aren't gonna get him but um can I take a airplane wine nap now please oh the seats are
clawing all the way well that's nice Kevin would want me to check that out all right yeah that's
that we're the polka boys that's nice anyone holding is anybody holding I haven't smoked weed
since 1977 so this is probably fine yeah that's the only unrealistic thing is this motherfucker
started playing tuba and she doesn't bury a shiv in one of their throats like please this is my
moment just let me be why do we talk about home alone so much it's a touchstone apparently a
cultural touchstone I would say we do talk about it a lot um okay I have a yahoo here can we talk
about it okay it's sent by a few yeah we'll talk about that half as much as we talk about home
alone yes thank you uh everybody who sent this one and it's yahoo answers user fritz who asks
how did king triton get so buff yeah right he lived underwater where there's no resistance
how could he get so buff I'm not sure that your terminology is right here because I think water
is all resistance if that's the logic that you're using then uh mer folks who live in the water
would be getting jacked from all the swimming that they do because that's exercise false that's just
exercise I would say probably first heavy diet of plankton okay so he yeah okay so he has a sort
of he has a webbing in his mouth and we don't see that but when he does extend his jaws wide open
you see the webbing get in there and he does swallow up a million things and you know they're
trying to play the the xylophone or whatever and then they did get eaten that would be rad if she
walked on land for the first time with her human legs and she just collapsed like oh my bones my
terrible weakened bones oh she just collapsed because her gills were dried out she's like I
don't have lungs um but how to get so jacked up though he's very strong I don't know if you guys
remember the movie but he has a very strong upper body I mean probably magic right like
it's a very magical culture well that's true I feel like that's kind of a bullshit answer though
trav like just magic that doesn't really okay he works out 24 seven he's spotted by sebastian is
that what you want to hear swimming around is gonna get you a good tail yeah like everyone's
gonna have a good tail I know you've but like usually their arms are just like gracefully
behind them as they zip along you don't see a lot of like ripped jack huge chested dolphins
yeah exactly well what you just said is wrong they're all the fucking muscle man the dolphins
are all fuck muscle I do not know if you ever touched one of these bad boys but it is basically
yes but they don't have definition griffin yes they've got the muscle mass yeah where's the
definition the dolphin doesn't have a six-pack maybe anytime king trends on the screen he's
lifting sea rocks he's just goes to his cave and there's not a lot to do down there that's what it
is he has one of those grottos where it's like you can swim and it's like even though it's
underwater it's almost like sea lab right where it's like pressurized so he can just like lift
the top half of his body out pump some iron and then go back to swimming what if every merfolk
or maybe it's just people who are sort of higher up the uh the the ladder uh people who in the
royal family perhaps or uh people living in sort of the royal domain have this and it is your own
personal fighting octopus and it's an octopus that you and uh you you fight and so every time you see
him go off stage from the play of the movie uh he blows up all his daughter's stuff and then is like
i'm a good dad and then he swims away and then you know while ariel's having a sad time in there with
all her broken tchotchkes uh he's like i i feel so bad about what i've done to my daughter's
collectibles and figurines ah fuck it get over here
oh no fight no tridents no tridents you're right you're right that's my god come here sorry sorry
sorry i uh i do love this idea that he has a secret rock gym somewhere though the the as i
i'll think of it the grotto of gains where he just goes and car carves himself out aqua man's too
yeah it's him man in there you know aqua man has secret rocks and octopus that he fights
he blasted up his daughter's collectibles because he's a real jackass scene is wild in it it's
actually batman he shows up at batman's house and batman sing a song about all of his great
tools and where did all my cool stuff i built with all my money where do you get all these
wonderful toys zap zap zap oh he uses his magic trident what a good flick i mean i've been a dad
for only two years now and tridents got like eight daughters and they all appear to be like
you know teenage to older so he's been a dad for a while now what a fucking rookie mistake
you'd be like i know a cool dad move blast up all the shit she cares about yeah of course
she went to the sea witch you dumb ass you drove her right into ursula's arms you piece of shit
it'd be cool if if aquaman came down and because he's the king of fish he like made triton clean
it all up you fix this hey fix it fix it you fucked up dad fucking asshole yeah triton should
have immediately come back i'm like you know what that was on me um i'm gonna fix this statue
i need to find some waterproof super glue and then i will fix this i think he just said everybody
else hey everybody go find more trash go get more trash for my kid maybe to find another statue that
fell off a boat yeah the way that this would actually play out is aqua would be like clean
this up you're a bad dad and then up half would be like no get the fuck out of here what are you
but then his butt would be like oh you're right you're right let me let me slap it around with
my is this helping no it's a clock you can't just slap it with your weird fish tail and fix it you
blew it the fuck up ass stop it hey fish ass get away who's in charge here he is a message to my
daughter not to like things why's he got a beard that's got to be bad under this under that is
matted that's full of i don't know probably like bacteria maybe that's where he absorbs food from
that's where he harvests guaranteed where's the scene of all the little fish that followed triton
around just picking bacteria and algae out of his beard that's it's got to be hard to get much
protein down there for those muscles too you eat anything other you'd see a tasty little shrimp but
it turns around to you and you're like oh hell yeah i'm starving sure turns her eyes like under
the sea under the sea like okay fine fuck you're sentient god damn it i have a family oh all right
oh i know your family yes i know you work for me you all work for me damn it uh let's uh let's
take a trip to the money zone also none of them wear shirts what's up with that mattresses okay
what's that about oh god get that hit the fucking can we please with the seinfeld sort of formulation
can we please what is thank you because you know he's gonna do that mattresses that's okay here
comes my ad for cat this is my ad i'm gonna do an ad for casper you gotta sleep and have sex
and there's only one place where both of those things are cool and it's not just for couches
anymore someone invented beds and it's casper casper has invented beds as it's a sleep brand
that continues to revolutionize this line of products now they have beds and you could sleep
on them one night at a time they're perfectly designed for for humans no dogs allowed on these
fucking things even if you're someone who doesn't have sex i highly recommend these beds for the
sleeping part the sleeping part's good but justin what about my weird shapes that make up my body
say a cylinder and i've got a pyramid shoulders what about those this is still designed for you
you're technically a human if you're in the u.s or canada you get free shipping and returns uh no
hassle by the way if you're not completely satisfied which you will be you could be sure of
your purchase with casper's 100 night risk-free sleep on it trial these are great beds you're
gonna love sleeping on them and you're gonna love having sex on them you get fifty dollars towards
select where you're gonna love not having sex on them either way either there's no lot travis
obviously travis it's not binary you're not either having sex or sleeping you're not a cicada
eating mating or sleeping on a gas room mattress they're great if you need a place to eat oak
leaves check out this mattress give fifty dollars towards select mattresses by visiting casper.com
slash brother and using promo code brother at checkout that's casper.com slash brother and
promo code brother brother brother for just one brother for fifty dollars towards like mattresses
terms conditions apply how about stomps stomps these sticky they're fun stickers like um maybe
maybe i shouldn't also do have you heard of this thing that we all know about based i'll make it
sound like they invented it nah it's more fun the other way you know stickers and sometimes they can
have elmo or pikachu or mario on them and you stick them when you've been a good boy you can
put them on your journal yeah sometimes you need those for mail so that the mail carrier will pick
it up because the mail mail carriers like stickers and you need stamps that's what those are and
stamps.com makes it so that you can print your own postage from home so you don't have to go to
the post office and you can save money with discounts on these wonderful stickers that you
can't even get at the post office they bring all the amazing services of the us postal service right
to your computer we're talking about stamps and then you will print those stamps and you can use
them for any letter any package any class of mail anywhere that you want to send it um and so with
stamps.com you get five cents off every first class stamp and up to 40 off priority mail holy
shit that's a big old chunk of change stumps stumps.com is a no-brainer saving you time and
money it's no wonder over 700 trillion small businesses already use stamps right now our
listeners get a special offer that includes a four-week trial plus free postage and a digital
scale without any long-term commitment just go to stamps.com click on the microphone at the top of
the home page and type my brother that's stamps.com enter my brother i wish they wouldn't i wish they
would just write it different that's stamps.com and then you press the return key and then you
enter my click on the microphone and then you type in the word my brother you insert yourself
slowly you don't so
hey everybody this is jake keith fans tratton host of go fact yourself a live game show here
in the maximum fun network make sure to listen to our next episode of go fact yourself with guest
kurt brown outer i did a show in flagstaff arizona where the venue just didn't list that
the show existed amazing uh and i and it is the smallest crowd that i've ever done a full hour
of stand up for it was three people oh my god and sarah shaffer yes i love crafting it's my hobby
i have a craft nook in my home you do i do it has all my supplies displayed in an adorable manner
wow yes yes applause applause for that's go fact yourself here at maximum fun.org
or wherever you get podcasts
i don't even have one i just need to stop you
digging digging digging digging digging looking at the page and then i found a page here we go here it comes i want a munch!
welcome to munch squad it's a podcast within a podcast duncan uh we got a duncan in huntington
this isn't the munch squad i'm just mentioning now i'll be able to try the duncan offerings first
hand you don't do you don't do that with the garbage that you bring here for the show right
now you're not you're not actually like experimenting firsthand with these things
right sometimes sometimes the picture looks good oh um and i want to try it and i probably would
have tried it anyway i get excited listen my ride got ride got bought out by walgreens
and i'm the idiot that walked in after they did their remodel and is like commenting to the
employees like god it's really bright in here it looks great this is so spacious don't you love
this i'm loving this you guys loving this this is not an exaggeration that i did that uh so duncan
has launched peeps coffee and a peeps donut for spring okay peep flavor is starting to get into
get into things there's peeps creamer now i got and peeps cereal and peeps don't have a flavor
folks it's marshmallows with sugar on it folks and marshmallow really is puffed sugar so we're just
kind of talking about sugar mostly folks yeah you're telling me that you've made sugar flavored
creamer that's right and it doesn't taste like anything except sugar and now that's in a coffee
and a donut it's peeps marshmallow flavor coffee and espresso drinks and the peeps donut is topped
with an iconic yellow chick that's right folks they just put a chick on the donut one right on
there and the shelf life of these bad boys after you remove them from the packaging is about nine
seconds before they turn crunchy and inedible so are they doing these things to order because that
would be kind of wild uh yeah they're they're just slapped they're opening up a discrete package
uh as you as you uh pull up and uh slapping it on there so you can just enjoy a donut with a peep
on it um now because i did pick this so quickly there's not really anything funny about this one
because i was just trying to get you to stop talking about the dirty stuff so there's not
really anything good well hold on let's find let's find the i had a joke earlier i didn't
really have time to do but maybe it could make it funny when you just say that like a sugar
flavored creamer again so they did that oh so they made sugar flavored creamer sugar creamer
okay all right sugar and then you put it in the creamer okay carls here that was a much quad jr
then carls jr and i have one hold on hold on okay did you have one you want to do you want to get
a handle i want to kind of piggyback off of what griffin said and this is kind of an alley out to
justin okay please see where i'm going with this sugar creamer more like sugar creamer
sugar sugar creamer i hardly sugar new know her
that was the three-pointer that's what you got for that uh the real quick note carls jr added a bacon
truffle burger and a bacon truffle cheese fries this image is not gonna drive me anywhere except
out of my fucking mind this is this is a horrid thing that you should seek out and see for yourself
i'm gonna link you guys just so you can see in the chat there you can see the image of the burger
that's a tall one that is it's just layers upon layers of horrid and it's a menu innovation they
call it here with no trace of irony it features a decadent truffle infused white cheddar sauce
which has a deep rich and savory flavor including notes of garlic toasted onion and egg parmesan
the burger includes a charbroiled 100 black angus beef patty topped with premium white
cheddar truffle sauce two slices of applewood smoked bacon crispy onion straws swiss cheese
caramelized onions fucking they made this they made that they made that okay and then at the end
they were like and mayonnaise and then yes mayonnaise good on this thing here's a quote
about this crime the launch of our new bacon truffle angus burger connects back to our dedication
to introducing bold craveable and unexpected flavors to our menu in interesting ways this guy
had to come up with it i think they like ran into his office like we already started recording
quick say something about the black angus truffle burger it um connects back to our dedication
to introducing bold craveable and unexpected flavors in interesting ways you already said
unexpected yeah i know but i'm just making it up as a go truffle is traditionally viewed as a rare
indulgence and we're bringing it to the everyday dining experience do you do you trust us hardies
with that and we're we are hardies don't forget we have a different name but we're still hardies
but anyway do you want this fancy forest mushroom that a pig dug up i i want to meet the bruce who's
eating this he's like look at me vicki i'm eating truffles i'm like a king oh my god oh and that's
from uh uh is infusing the distinct truffle flavor into an entirely new offering for our
burger loving customers oh sorry dirt bag says here owen says owen klein from the chain during
the testing phase imagine this during the testing phase carl's junior bacon truffle angus burger
outperformed all benchmarks including taste uniqueness and quality sir it's off the charts
my god my god my god now we've done it again now we're all sons of bitches
we're and it says here we're thrilled to add the elegant taste of truffle to this this sandwich has
bacon and onion straws and swiss cheese and hamburger and cheddar truffle sauce and mayonnaise
on it and you are going to take the word elegant and just jam it up your ass like there's no me
there's no meaning behind anything anymore yeah this bad boy this is a this looks like a wet
agro crag that i have to climb and eat from the top down this is a big big mound of it's a
challenging challenging fight challenging sandwich a challenging burger anyway that's all there is
to know about that that carl's junior now it doesn't mention specifically hardies so i don't
know if they're leaving hardies out in the cold on this one this may just be a carl junior ridge
our hardies would never serve a burger like this how about another question please i recently
started working in an office setting i only work there three days a week and i am a graduate student
so i'm not close with the full-time staff there's a small basket of candy that sits near the
secretary and i pass it every day on my way in i grab a few pieces throughout the day my question
is how many pieces is too many i feel bad taking too many as i'm not full-time staff and also as a
grad student it's hard to pass on free candy do i cut back on the candy do i just sneakily take
more at one time do i create a diversion to draw the secretary's attention so they at least know
it's not me depleting the resources and that's morgan i mean when you get to the point where
you're doing a little heist every time you get the candy i think you know it's too much candy
at that point am i wrong in my feeling about the candy at the front desk that's for visitors right
is that isn't that visitor candy as a way of saying like welcome here this isn't for the staff
this is for you our visitor please enjoy a tootsie roll i always thought if somebody puts out a bowl
of candy that's like the basic human way of signaling like i'm someone who likes interaction
this reminds me of the funny office uh the office episode american version of course
yes the original um and it the the scene where pam puts out all the candy uh and then dwight walks
up and he's gonna have a piece of candy and he puts his hand in the bowl and he starts to unwrap
it and then uh jim jumps up from behind the plant and gives him a good scare and he swallows it and
chokes on it no no he gets it out no but yeah i'm like it it's fine all right but he does pee himself
yeah so did we help i think let me let me i will uh take this way off your shoulders the like that
you're taking too many because you're not full time i think that's okay i think i don't think
anyone's like hey you only work 20 hours a week that's worth two pieces of candy the president
and the company doesn't walk in and just up in the bowl into their mouth and then say i earned this
this is mine this is my put in the hours and became the the the bar so this one listen to
the real answer and i hate to give real advice here it feels weird but you could offer to buy
the next bag of candy you could just do that but that would defeat the purpose if this person knew
how to buy candy we wouldn't be in this mess right okay have you heard of stores listen people put
out candy on their desks at work so for conversation starters i think it's a it's a it's the water
cooler come talk to me about lost still because it's all i think about and uh that's why i put
this thing on and oh uh tuesday's right with mori have you read it book club this week on tuesday
weirdly enough so get there yes there will be candy there will be candy some good and uh so
nobody read the book again i see um but i do notice that the worthers are gone um that is
fine that's fine it's this old man kidnaps a child and gives him lessons every tuesday kids
that kids kid snaps him his kid snaps this kid snaps him over and over again kid snaps the shoot
out of him and gives him lessons and um you're all leaving because the worthers are see it okay
it's visitor candy i'm gonna stick by my guns visitor candy uh my dad i've got another can
do another one yes okay dear brothers i recently started working in a pasta factory on the ravioli
line this job would be perfect for me except for one thing i can't stop thinking about eating the
uncooked raviolis as they as they move past me the worst is but i have to stand there on the
the worst is but i have to stand there on the line and make sure no defective one gets passed i've
come so close to stuffing my pockets and getting the hell out of that sinner's paradise i can't
see goodbye arrow shortly because please tell me how to sedate the ravioli monster inside of me or
fill that's from randy for ravioli thank you so much it's on it's i just i want to just hit one
thing that it's an uncooked but i do understand that after a certain point of watching them roll
by that probably like fades to the back of your mind and you're just like but now i just want to
like yeah i know it's not gonna be good i just want to eat what i wanted to compulsion doesn't
have to make complete logical sense in fact oftentimes it does not although i will say
as somebody who recently learned that they had been um horribly maligned by his two older brothers
who he trusted very much into eating uncooked uh fettuccine every time we went to olive garden
i do hope that i would have had the good sense not to eat uncooked ravioli because there's a lot of
other sort of matter a lot of other sort of material floating around in that in that one
the problem is if you eat it and anyone sees you won't i don't even know that you'd so much get in
trouble for eating the product so much as everyone around you would be like what are you doing what
are you doing that's not cooked it's not cooked the other problem would be if i am working on
this line across from you and i saw you finally break and within one deft maneuver just shove
even like a defective one into your mouth i am my first assumption will not be oh i'm i'm sure
that's the first time they've done that it will be they have done this 400 times a day across from
me and this is the first time i have ever noticed or worse what if you do it and everyone's like oh
thank god someone did it first and then just the whole floor just to grab and go everyone's going
crazy shoving those little circles in their mouths this is the new foot loose this is foot
loose too but there's not any dancing and you're just just bowels loose you're the jeans wearing
rebel who comes in and shows everybody it's okay to eat this uncooked ravioli we're supposed to be
packaging wait but what do you do with the defective ones why can't you eat those here's
how i would do when you get a defective one be like just yell lala like oh god no and then
pick it up and throw it across the room but throw it in the same place every time and then at the
end of the day go get a ziploc baggie and scoop up all your dirty floor all your dirty defective
floor ravioli go have yourself a treat at home or oh hey bring a bag of uncooked ravioli from home
have them put a sticker on it or something when you come in and when you get that craving just
pop one of your own in there what if you went to your boss and you're like listen i have this
problem and you describe the problem and it's like i would i don't want to steal things but i do want
to eat the raviolis they're all pastry can i just keep a tally of the ones i've eaten and and just
deducted my paycheck at the end or alternately i will pay you a hundred dollars now and we'll
have a kind of budget that i can give into whatever i want it's like a gas station you're like i i
have this problem i want to eat it and he's like just puts a finger to his lips and then goes up
and like closes the blinds he's like come with me and opens and there's just like there's just a
room full of uncooked ravioli like whenever you need to you can come in here and satiate your
dark passenger wear this maybe they're waiting for some maybe the the boss is waiting for somebody to
be like hey listen i can't do this anymore i fucking love these pillowy bad boys too much
i can't work this job this close to him not even he and he's like finally i found special boy i'm
going to give my factory to someone who loves to eat these delicious little bastards as much as i
do the man who ate all the uncooked ravioli he wanted he shit himself it's not cooked it was
really really quite yucky don't don't do that but here are the keys um to the building anyway
get in this uh death box we're gonna fly up it's gonna be cool is there somebody you hate at work
where you could like eat them and then if you get caught just like actually i saw jared jared was
doing it and he i thought it was fine because jared is beloved here and i thought it was kind
of a fine company policy to eat them for everyone i've eaten yeah it's true smell is nasty ricotta
mouth and and like they open his locker and you've stuffed a bunch of uncooked ravioli do it
it's really i mean i was just thinking why can't you just buy a box of this uncooked ravioli but
it's not the same right like you want it you want it fresh out of mama's kitchen yeah but what you
can do what you can do is while you're on the assembly line you have brought a box of say 16
uncooked raviolis and then you dump them out onto the line and you real quick run further down the
belt and scoop up 16 fresh from mama's kitchen ones and then no one is the wiser except for the
fact this would be a very conspicuous thing to do maybe just whenever you go on break for lunch just
say like okay i'm on break and once you clock out just lay down at the end of the conveyor
belt and let them fall in your mouth you're on break they can't fire you no could you they can
only arrest could you suggest to your bosses that you open the factory to the public and start doing
tours and one of the the perks of the tour is at the end you get to pop of one of the sweet raviolis
in your mouth no problem no questions asked uncooked and then when the tours open you take
the day off show up in a fake mustache and go and you just keep doing disguises you do disguises
where you can show up and take like hello my name is jim posterson and i have heard good things
that's my favorite part of the louisville slugger tour is at the end where you get the unfinished
bat and you're just allowed to smash it on the ground just blast it everybody gets one
justin you mentioned disguises you don't even have to set up this whole plot about the tour
you could just dress up in a big hairy suit and run in and start eating all the ravioli right off
the belt and then everybody else there be like oh no the beast the beast is back the beast is back
and they have to lock themselves in the safety room and start lighting the torches
you might have to do a little groundwork beforehand and say like hey guys i was just
outside uh getting something for my car and i saw a beast running around and that might take weeks
to really establish the myth that you couldn't do it same day you couldn't like the morning
i'll say the beast and come in the afternoon you'd have to spot it when no one else did just like hey
did you guys see the i saw the beast okay but you're gonna have to you're gonna have to clear
this with your boss first so go into your boss and he said um excuse me uh hello can i can i come in
yes come in it's it's uh it's me fert um i had an idea for one thing that might make it good
to work here make it make it better finally yes please i've been waiting for some kind of suggestion
on what would make it good to work here please tell me it would be um citing if sometimes a
werewolf showed up not a werewolf not a werewolf the beast please the beast oh thank you thank you
other boss that's a much better suggestion i can see we're on the same page here please do not
treat him with the same level of respect you can tell from my big diaper so um it might be a good
thing sometimes it might make it fun exciting uh-huh um and now what would these bees do would
he come in and do maybe a funny dance or wave some pom-poms around yeah sure whatever and then he
would probably eat some of the ravioli like like coming with a big steaming plate of it that he had
made at home boiling water that the baby boss that's the ball that's a great question no he
would just come in and um he would just kind of he would just kind of eat him raw he just kind of
eat him raw like a beast i do understand the connection but i don't know if that's uh i'll do
it it's no problem i'll do it that for us i'll be the beast and i'll make it like a fun it'd be fun
to work here you you're awe-inspiring son your level of commitment you're the hero we need eat
the uncooked pasta donuts great thanks so much thanks so much i really love i'm thinking of
tortellini and i meant oh ravioli is like little pillows isn't it oh fuck wait you run this you run
this yeah i'm cut listen it was my father's business i i wanted to be a tortellini man
now you're the but now you're the diaper one because you messed up we gotta switch off again
uh this has been our podcast my brother my brother and me um and we hope you that you have enjoyed
it um we we are i guess we're current well hey we're about to be i guess in san jose and in
soulek city and there may be tickets for them if you want to come see us uh we would very much
love it if you would uh uh join us there like i said i think there's a few seats left not a ton
but uh that's gonna be april 3rd in san jose at city national civic and salt lake it's
abravanel hall april 4th so um that's mackerel dot family if you go there and click tours you can
find links to tickets uh we're gonna be in um san jose with the adventure zone 2 on april 2nd but
i think that's sold out now um but uh please please please if you have questions for those shows and
yahoo's please send those in there's still time yeah also if if you're in denver or anywhere near
it um i'm going to be at dink uh in the middle of april april 13th and 14th in denver colorado
uh i'm doing a couple different events there's like a vip q and a meet and greet thing i'm doing
um and i'm working on like a screening of a movie thing uh like a b movie that i'm gonna kind of
riff over a bunch of different stuff i'll tweet more schedules out for it but i'd love to see you
there uh april 13th and 14th in denver colorado i want to thank john roderick and the long winters
for these four theme songs it's a departure off the album putting the days to bed uh which you
should be you know cranking on the reg uh and big thanks to maximum fun uh for having us on
the network we you just heard us for two straight weeks talk about how great this network is and
being a part of it uh is and um yeah we we it wasn't just bullshit to get your money uh we
really mean it and go listen to some great new shows like mission to zix go listen to beef and
dairy network and uh who shotcha and all the shows on maximum fun dot org catch up on mission to zix
they just started their third season their new show on the network go check them out i you might
see uh a brother on there at some point here in the near future so just pick it up like 301 it's
a sort of sci-fi improvised comedy show but like you can pick it up uh you'll probably want to go
back and listen more but uh go check it out you will like it if you're a fan of stuff like um
welcome to the magic tavern uh then you will you will enjoy a mission oh yeah quick plug two z y x
x um we got this with mark gagliardi and how loveland have had great guests on all month uh
justin sydney did best west wing character um i did an episode that i don't think is out yet but
it's uh well i won't say it but i did an episode it's coming up soon dad did an episode about like
best hannah barbara character i think and oh and sydney my wife sydney uh was on the jv club with
janet varney uh most recent episode by now it's probably the second rachel was on that recently
as well and i was on on can i pick your dog talked about our new dog lily so dang guys all over the
place yeah it's great network one last thing before you go it's it's the new month and that
means new merch go to mcroymerch.com please um final yahoo this one was sent in by a couple
folks thank you it's an anonymous yahoo answers users so i'm gonna call them uh jump asks
why does frying tomatoes turn them green
my name is justin mcelroy i'm griffin mcelroy it's been my brother my brother
may kiss your dad square on the lips
um
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
all right sorry is about some books
one two one two three four hi everybody my name is justin mcelroy and i'm sydney mcelroy and
together we're the hosts of saw bones a marital tour of misguided medicine what does that mean for
you the podcast consumer well it means that you're going to get a lot of stories about how
we used to do weird stuff to people in order to try to fix them do you know that we used to think
diseases were caused by bad smells and that we used to eat mummies for medicine that's super
funny i kind of like it well thanks and we hope you'll kind of like our show saw bones a marital
tour of misguided medicine it's available every friday wherever fine podcasts are sold
or at its beautiful picturesque home at maximum fun.org
all right