The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
you will you remember me boys in the house don't let your smiles pass you by
smiles not for the booty to welcome to my brother my brother and me insert number here
here funeral for a friend i can't bye bye ty ty how could this happen did i do this
did i do this because i've been the last episode i made fun of beauty tamer it's listen if i could
take it back it's me griffin if i could take it back i would take it i'm gonna do i've made my
decision i'm gonna delete the last episode of the podcast from the internet because i was making
jokes i was making jokes with a t because that's what i've started to call them that's what tyler
calls them that's what tyra calls him because she just has to get as much tyra and stuff as
she possibly can i was making jokes at the expense of america's next top model cycle 2.2 or 22 depends
on who you ask boys in the house boys in the house boys still in the house boys are inextricable
from the house if i may interject boys please interject i didn't i have not kept up with
america's next top model boys well it's because you're a piece of shit and you don't care about
things that make me and justin happy but this is a rare opportunity it's just so real it's so nice
that we have someone here whose fault it is yeah yeah it's me that i can but let me ask you this
was it cancelled because uh of flagging quality was is the has the last season you know ty tyra
noticeably bad uh no you stupid piece of shit dumb dumb idiot flew too close to the sun yeah
and it was too close to perfection and god killed it well it sounds like tired tired put out a
statement on instagram on the ig platform uh that i'm sure she posted with her opal phone or whatever
and she posted it and was like i think cycle 22 is the last one that was her statement and as if
it was tyra's choice if it was our choice that's fine that's fine that's fine i'm starting to think
that there is maybe some external pressure maybe you saw i wanted to renegotiate his contract and
as a power move instead of renegotiating contract they just burned the whole fucking showdown around
him i don't know maybe miss jay maybe miss jay's tired of doing this maybe miss jay wants to become
an astronaut or something maybe miss jay just wants to focus on travel or something i don't
know and they just burn the showdown what if what if what if what if they're gearing up for 3.0 no
stop it don't even first of all that would mean cgi tire bags no that first of all that would mean
they were skipping eight seasons to jump directly to season 30 listen i'm i'm happy don't be sad
because it's gone be happy because you loved it in the first place and it was here and gave us 22
great years of programming but it's uh when tyra was just seven years old she started um yeah miss
banks is 29 and it's that's how she looks is uh basically it was the best show ever is ever on
television it was i was just hoping we could start oh it's uh by the way it's um my brother my brother
made some ice cream for the modern no that we said my oldest brother did we introduce ourselves we
didn't introduce ourselves i don't think so i'm i'm travis i'm your middle brother i don't get
a name this week all you need to know about this voice that you're hearing your ears right now is
that it's desperately sad this is not a joke i think about stuff like i think about i think
about things because i'm a i see 30 coming i see 30 coming and once i hit 30 it's like what's the
point i've reached this point where like cool i see i see him like uh i eat like a really good
pizza and it's like that's great but now that pizza is behind me for the rest of my life i've
eaten that pizza that pizza moment has passed and now i have that about the thing in my life that
meant the absolute most to me yeah uh i was hoping we could start this episode with just some
remembrances okay if we could do that some of our favorite moments griffin do you think we could um
kill a few minutes by inserting your remembrance of the freshest moment in all of top model history
just to oh yeah we'll cut that we'll cut that in right now and um please enjoy this is our clip
show in remembrance of in remembrance of auntie em the boys were in the house and now no one's
in the house no one's in the fucking house for three you gave us you gave us three seasons
you gave us three seasons they found their footing after 20 fucking seasons this how you do me
me it's the clip i praise you for years that's how you do me uh the new cycle of america's next
top model started which i was not aware yeah it started fucking justin 2.0 they changed the goddamn
game boys in the house so they're boys in the house there are girls in the house too but there's
also boys in the house and let's just say things get a little sexy did you sorry did you hear that
i put i put a little too much smoke in that i missed a month that was a little smoky yeah
i can describe everything that's happened in every season so in every episode first episode
first episode they line them all up at the top of staircase and they say guys go pick a girl from the
other side walk down the staircase do a pose and that's how they introduce all the guys and girls
to each other this one super fucking fresh dude walks to the stairs looks at the women shakes his
head no this will not do turns around to the dudes picks a dude walks down the stairs kisses him on
the mouth turns to everyone like what's up fucking crowd like just burns the fucking building down
around them just like starts tearing downstairs like the dopest thing i've ever seen fuck
it's the fucking dopest moment in reality show history the other dude the other dude was like
straight as an arrow like i don't even fucking care that was the freshest and dopest thing i'll
ever be a part of it is required watching also they've changed the theme song so it does the
want to be on top a guy's voice comes in and goes boys in the house and it's my favorite
it's it beats out growing pains it beats out full house it beats out family matters for
greatest theme song still fresh you know he actually retweeted that clip he did thank you
oh god yeah we are gone i tried to get him on as a guest but i forgot his first name
it was either cory or cody or that was cody i think it was coby i think it was cory i think
it was coby smolders he was the freshest dude ever and it and it doesn't matter because the
show's over now uh it i think it was cody right cory it was definitely it was cory i think it
was cory roy hi cory wade i was just kidding i knew your name all the time he's you're fucking
fresh as hell you're fucking fresh couldn't get cory we did get catarsina from cycle uh 16 um but
unfortunately she didn't want to didn't want to didn't wasn't contacted about it i want to tell
you the bet my favorite uh antm moment that i i think uh sydney and i have uh probably talked
about more than any other is um at one point um they were in i would assume africa uh it was one
of if you never watched uh the girls and sometimes the guys in the in the later years three beautiful
fucking seasons yeah for three perfect seasons uh they at the second the back half of the of the
season uh they would uh take the uh the girls or the guys to a an exotic locale um and in in
in one cycle uh it was uh cycle six if memory serves uh there was a an elephant in this challenge
uh and the girls were supposed to pose with the elephant uh and uh one of the models uh decided
she tried something a little crazy and uh she stood on an elephant's foot um and then the next
model saw that shot and then she stood on the elephant's foot as well for her shot and she got
called out on it by the other models and her defense was i i'm never gonna have an opportunity
like this again i just wanted to stand on an elephant's foot for once yeah still like it was
amazing like this was a lifelong dream that she finally finally uh uh being able to fulfill and
the other uh models are trying to rob her dear mom and dad it's finally happened it's happened
i think my favorite moment was in season i think don't you don't no you don't you haven't earned
this dare you i think the second episode someone in the house was murdered and the rest of the
season was a who done it with detective tyra i think that was my favorite that was the that
was the aborted abc series who done it and they only did one season of that which is also another
show tv crime and i cannot delve into this with you that show was a tv crime i agree with you
listen hi just it had something to do with the broken aquarium i didn't watch it that's literally
the first episode you watched a commercial for it once that might be true it all blends together i
think there were boys in that house too though i think there have been boys on a lot of houses
griffin travis right now yes you're running right now you're running your mouth like a lot of our i
love you dear listeners a lot of you guys when this shit when this horrible news dropped and
i was devastated and i got on twitter just like tearing open my heart and just squishing it down
on the internet and let everybody know just like where i was as a person i was really putting myself
out there and i got a lot of people like looks like no one's in the house and it's like do you
guys not do you not get it like do you not get the basic human like connection they used to have
with all of us we were doing this podcast in the hopes of someday being called on in a guest judge
maybe as part of a teach maybe like those brothers that taught the models the swirl remember the
swirl remember the swirl to teach i'm excluding myself from this uh because i would not qualify
what would you two teach the models travis they had twins named the a swirl twins that taught the
women how to swirl that was the whole teach um i could do i could teach them the stanky leg
let's move on to talking about questions that people have because honestly i can't do this
eulogy that we've been delivering i thought was going to be like weirdly liberating but no i'm
just this is just my life now is i'm just going to be sad about antiem forever if you know tyra
banks and you want to put this in front of her just to let her know about how her selfishness
or whatever happened has has just completely destroyed two human souls um uh please do that
uh you sigh what what what if we take this tragedy we turn it to opportunity we kick start
art season 23 we fund it we produce it independent we stream it on like crackle and it's all macaroi
funded okay i would feel really uncomfortable yeah i'm not gonna be too close to the art
no like if i had to like evaluate people's bodies and shit that no we wouldn't host it we wouldn't
oh i see we're just funded we're the money i'm not gonna step on tyra's intellectual property
yeah no she would keep doing it we're just giving her the money to keep doing it
i don't think the money was the issue let's move on i can't i can't even do
fun goofs about it it's the saddest thing that's ever happened ever when one change
come on do you want me to read it fucking shit yeah if you don't mind trap when one
changes their avatar or profile picture to support a worthy cause or to mourn a tragic event how long
should one wait before changing their profile back to some meaningless bullshit filled with
cats that's from supportive but don't want it to be my whole thing can i change is there any sort of
twibbing i can put on my profile just let everybody know how just completely
gutted i am about antm yeah where is that antm memorial ribbon twibbing
um at what point girlfriend would you change it back never never this is i've i've still got the
um i still have rainbow avatar on facebook for from when they uh made all all the marriage
great and when they fixed marriage yeah when they when they tweaked it um and uh i still have not
changed that back i pretty much i think i'm the last bastion because i'm i see i see everybody
i know who's changed it back like i wrote already huh yeah well okay i would just like they just
like fixed basically a homophobe i mean well i wouldn't say go that far it's just like your
priorities are maybe um not uh not not especially good it's like go royals here's my royals pride
here's me in a royals hat and it's like well that's fine and everything but i guess the thing
that's like more important to me is how like a whole like group of people were disenfranchised
and then like we sort of like fixed that it came together you know what the problem is huh we don't
have like a a profile picture palette cleanser like so say you switch your profile picture to
like support like anything you know what i you support like gay marriage right whatever you
change it to next people are like oh i guess you care about that more than that cost so what you
need is like just a neutral like beach shot like it's just a picture that everyone uses a picture
of some pickled ginger yes something that everybody like when you put it up everyone goes
like oh okay he's gonna transition but he's letting us know he's resetting back to one
yeah and then the next picture is something else rather than it's not about which one you care
about more i uh i i think that what you're missing is if you hang on to one of these uh causes long
enough eventually it's going to be ironically hysterical like don't you wish you had sat on
your coney 2012 ribbon until now because people would think you were just off the chain that's
our at this point yeah you're loathe for coney i'm still coming by the way coney i'm still coming
after you i'm fucking for you this is just on my eye out listen new year's eve 2012 the ball dropped
a lot of people were like all right guys time to move on not me no i was seething three two one
ah fuck it i can't even get excited about 2013 i can't get excited about 2013 because they're
gonna cancel amtm in two years what do i go from there what if every day you just scooted
your profile picture over like one percent and scooted a new picture in one percent
and if you did it slow enough people wouldn't notice yeah it says i see a picture of it looks
like half your face and it looks like you might be eating like a big piece of deep dish pizza
and then like but weirdly to the right like there's a weird jump cut and then it says coat
and i'm not sure like what's going what's going on there what's going on there um you guys want
a yahoo yeah i guess that's what we do on this dumb shit we gotta get over this fucking thing
this yahoo was sent in by level 9 000 yahoo drew drew davenport thank you true it's by an anonymous
yahoo user call him coney coney asks we found him well he wasn't he wasn't missing was he why
i have no idea okay great by the way that was about two years before i started caring about
current events just so everybody doesn't think we're like total idiots i'm sure coney's still
out there and still sucks there's nothing funny about coney there is something funny about coney
2012 that was the craziest name for a campaign ever just want to say okay yeah coney's the worst
all right so coney asks listen we don't want to make light of coney but anyway i'm imagining that
coney is on yahoo answers and ask this teen fun crazy camps oh does anyone know a camp for teenagers
where you just go crazy and have insane parties like a rave kind of party without drugs or alcohol
i'm looking for an organization that's weekly um wait a weekly camp yeah it's like a week or you
go every week to party camp i think they're saying every seven days uh-huh you roll up to rave camp
uh-huh but no drugs and alcohol no drugs and alcohol you're just high on being at camp and
you just lose your mind in a dark room i was thinking this person was basically describing
the burn until they got to the part about no drugs or alcohol and then they were definitely
definitely not describing it burning man like for sure not um did you know it sounds like they go to
teen clubs i mean when you were a teen not like well yeah i think we've god we've talked at length
about the gym factory before haven't we i believe so if so it's been a while but yeah i used to go
there was a place called the gym factory which does not sound like a place where hundreds of
like 14 year olds would go to get their first hand job um but it is where hundreds of 14 year
olds went to get their first hand job because there's a dark room in the back of a sort of
gymnastics facility where you go train for gymnastics but then there's a dark stinky back
room where 14 year olds would go and be in the dark and just get wild on each other no alcohol
no drugs but all the hand jobs you can handle you know the show wild you know that show wild and
crazy kids that show got its name from the time that fucking um anyone from that show
oh my god no was it omar gooding and donnie jeff coat jeff coat yeah yeah they were in they walked
up and i want to say the woman's name was annito but i'm not sure no you're wrong on that but they
rolled up on the gym factory on a fateful friday night and then just the the stink blast just hit
him and donnie yelled these are some wild and crazy kids and omar snapped his fingers and
pointed at the sky that's it magic and then they started just butt freaking on each other because
that's what happens oh my god you go there on friday night and you have yourself a butt party
and um so yeah i mean i used to go there and that was weekly but it wasn't camp like there
weren't any pup tents i mean there were if you know what i'm talking about teen boners
uh for sure team boners there is a film of course from 1987 called party camp
yeah uh if i may be so bold as to read the one sentence descriptor from wikipedia yeah please
the plot revolved around a teenager who takes a job as a summer camp counselor
only to spend the whole experience partying and creating hijinks and then say what movie is that
and people are like uh eight thousand movies uh heavyweights all of them all movies meatballs
inception i'm pretty sure you've just described apocalypse now uh look this would be a pretty
dope camp i feel like i would really enjoy being at camp lightstick it sounds like it would be a
pretty sick time if you showed up and you like had watched all of these like meatballs one through
12 and you're like oh whimsical crazy experiences at camp and you showed up and it was just like you
know uh around about five we'll do dinner and you're like and then it gets crazy and they're
like no no no we might have like a cookout maybe roast marshmallows but everybody's usually in bed
by eight and then the counselors get to get no no we just do why were they advertising as a party
camp travis yeah this is party you've just described something that's owned by donald party
and his family it's a family oh shit the the party the uh the the donald jay party camp of falconry
and early bedtimes why do they have this camp a black limo just blasting uh drum and bass music
like rolls up into the middle of camp they're like oh my god it's him he opens the door falcons fly
out it's don party that was the falcons fly out and it's just an old bald man he says what are
you guys still doing up donald it's 5 45 yeah i know this is my camp i set the rules just kidding
he shoots an arrow into a bullseye clear across camp fuck yeah but the bullseye explodes and it
was full of dmt the spirit molecule he's like i guess you're wondering why i'm all oh i'm here
and everybody's like yeah and he's like does anybody remember the password to our quickbooks
account i forgot it and then he plays the guitar oh i thought that was falcons it was a falcon
playing all your guitar oh fuck this sounds good for a lame old man don party sounds pretty cool
wouldn't this be exhausting though like wouldn't you also need a chill out camp like next door
like to camp across the lake that's the feud like oh they're so chill
like i was about to describe chill out camp which would be a camp where you just chill out like sit
around a fire relax make like uh some crafts and shit and then i realized yeah you're just
describing camp yeah like you have some orange juice and some snacks oh wait have every camp
i ever been to has everyone been a chill out camp for another cooler party camp next door
that i just didn't get the memo on there's always a cooler camp there's always a cooler camp you're
never at the coolest camp unless that place was crazy yeah camp that was wild oh man you guys all
hey listeners you all know that justin travis and i were all in the hit film camp nowhere right
i was christopher lloyd's butt double we get residuals anytime a podcast mentions it
you watched camp nowhere and you went with your parents thinking like this is going to be a fun
summer romp and it and it was same for like the six or seven explicit Christopher look sexy
that butt that you saw you're like i don't want to see doc brown's asshole that wasn't here's a
little bit of movie magic let me take you bts that was my asshole they did those extended scenes
completely unnecessary and contextless that was the year that we invented cgi i have fucking
fucking weta doing stuff on this asshole did you also do the love scenes with Susan Lucci
or where was that uh uh that was that christopher lloyd improper uh no that was actually uh they
they were very much in love during the making of that movie white shots lloyd close-ups griffin
right all of the passion that you got from that romance that was real passion and i can't i'm i'm
a great butt actor i can't fake that no that kind of butt chemistry you can't you can't learn that
Stanislavsky said that can't teach that butt chemistry i have a close friend who is falling
headfirst into what is so clearly a pyramid scheme and it's changed him noticeably in the
past few weeks he's always been a classic hippie stoner type but recently he's been dressing like
ward cleaver and speaking like a life coach he's also trying to get another friend and i to come
into what he calls dinners with the business and he paid up front what i expected thousands of
dollars to these people without knowing what he was getting into how does my how do my friend and
i get him to see that he's being sucked into something shitty that's from concerned in
connecticut you got to be careful about this because you know some people are getting rich
somehow and maybe this guy's plugged in somebody's got to be at the top of the pyramid yeah um also i
feel like you're very casually throwing pyramid scheme in there when i think that this is much
more likely a cult yeah for sure i got a real culty vibe i get real culty i think it's the um
the change of dress the ward cleaver very uh oh what if we're dealing with like a stepford
husbands or a stepford single guy i had a single guys i had a friend that i once thought was
getting into like a pyramid scheme she was selling uh uh well it doesn't matter but i it first went
to a party at her house where she was selling this stuff and i thought oh man i like this girl a lot
she's getting into a pyramid scheme i think i'm really worried about her flash forward to like
two years later she's fucking taking vacations to mexico and has an army of people working
underneath her like she's at the top of the pyramid you know somebody gets there
yeah somebody's gonna be at the top i mean i would say in your friend's defense if he's
making the transition from hippie stoner type to like dressing well and speaking positively
and doing a thing maybe just let it play out like yeah it doesn't sound like he had his shit
together to begin with now let me say this okay you missed the point where you can do anything
for this friend because they're already they are already like tens of thousands of dollars
in oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah what's he gonna do walk away you don't he's not getting a refund
you cannot walk away type friend get thousands of dollars well maybe throw away on dinners maybe
he's been saving up um but anyway that money's gone now and if he leaves now then tyra's gonna
hunt him down i mean uh the whoever is running this pyramid scheme's gonna hunt him down and so
uh so i i just need the two of you to please buy some fucking makeup for me please
griffin are you having some problems being an inner beauty tainer
i'm i am having problems but they are not unsolvable they're called probabilities yeah
tyra told us to call them probable prunies close and and i the two of you hold the keys
griffin where are you where are you recording from i'm in i'm in my house and then that's
i'm in my house and then that's that's uh where i can't leave the key illusions if you will
you guys have the key illusions to my problem punities okay close and um please i've never
asked you two for anything please please god please how much money do you need griffin
all the money you have this is a this is a family-wide shakedown miss banks
this bank said i'm going to ruin the mackaroy family that's why she quit anto because she's
she said quote i'm gonna own their asses full time she does guys i this is bad this is real real bad
i didn't read anything because ty tyra delivered me the contract in a sterling silver briefcase
that said tyra on it and she cracked it open and showed it to me and i said tyra i don't know why
you would try and fuck me and so i signed it without reading it and she didn't just fuck me
she fucked my everyone she fucked everyone in her whole family i'm so sorry um justin your
your beautiful baby daughter i'm afraid that her name is not charlie anymore what is it it's tooch
your daughter's my niece's name is tooch it's tyra adopting her
nope but she does have her griffin signed her away what like jareth and labrador stole my
baby when i wasn't paying attention yeah i mean you still have to like take care of her because
miss tyra is busy but and please it's miss tyra um she does not guys i'm in a lot of trouble i
don't understand why you don't just go to the dinner like i'd go to the dinner it's free what
are they gonna do they can't make you do anything it's still america when i go to the dinners tyra
makes me eat the silverware okay well not this is evolved past you owe her money to she is
torturing you yeah she's turning you out at this point she's a bully she is not a bully she is the
ruler she's the precious queen of america and if i hear you say one more bad word about her travis
i'll burn your shit down do you still need money i need all the money you have please okay she
needs it griffin won't really interact with him much griffin's more of a conduit a funnel
um i'm just kidding this is this has all been a joke i'm sure tyra banks is a lovely person um
uh it was not a joke i really do need all the money that the two of you have just just venmo
it to me i'll send you some i'll send you a couple requests i don't know how to use venmo yeah can i
just like mail you a cashier's check i had to sign up for it today to help pay for a pizza
and i realized that you can request money from people using the app and so i immediately
requested 100 000 american dollars for my friend eric and i told him you know what it's for
uh but here's the thing if he pays it i never have to work again a day in my fucking life
that's true it's a good risk i know you're listening thinking a hundred thousand dollars
that's not you don't know i can stretch that shit wide out first of all it's an extreme couponer
i'm gonna take 50 g's put it all on black spin that wheel 50 g's on red and put 50 g's on red
too win win baby oh shit it hit the green one oh oh it bounced out and rolled down the carpet
and went outside then eric's gonna get another venmo request another hundred stacks
all right i'm getting this show back on track do one of the things that we normally do a yahoo
answer maybe you got one of those another thing that we also do a lot of um is we go to the money
zone have we earned if only we talked about money enough to make a good transition oh well this is
me venmoing everybody eliciting their ear dollars folks i want to take a second to tell you about
zip recruiter now before you tell us about zap router um do you know about zap router you
stumbled with the name of the thing zip recruiter zip recruiter he's a space ace he's also an hr
representative he's a 1950s space ace who just happens to be uh in the hr field as well when he's
on on land uh earth side as he says when you're short staff there's no time to deal with dozens
of different job sites with zip recruiter.com you can post to a hundred plus job sites with
one single click and be instantly matched to candidates from over six million resumes
i knew you were gonna say that did you yeah i did are you a pre-cog i'm a pre-cock
a hundred plus job sites and six million resumes that's like that's a really good return like i i
have done hiring for a couple different businesses now and it is grueling like to try to find a way
to get your job posting in front of the right people and then to kind of sort through and say
well yeah but how do i know we got the best applicant how do we know we got everyone we
possibly could six million resumes you're getting the best people you're getting the right people
for the job applying for your thing zip recruiter has been used by over 400 000 businesses and you
can try it right now for free if you go to zip recruiter.com my brother zip recruiter.com my
brother you can try it for free and get access to like get your shit in front of six million
resumes like that's um that's good if you use the my brother coupon code um it's not a coupon code
it's a url extension when you use that url extension it automatically filters out all the
resumes of racist people that's correct that's and i put you into the running to be hired as
the fourth mcroy brother that's true they say they post 100 plus job sites i'm sitting here
thinking about that number for the first time that's a lot i'm pretty sure there aren't that
many like do people need jobs that bad in the world are there people looking for jobs they
must be getting into some niche stuff right like arkansas ice cream tasters for you.com stuff like
that like funjobs.fart that only qualifies you to work at the funny bone how many of those are geo
cities now listen funjobs.fart it's it's a fun name right yeah obviously we're all laughing
and having a great time on this podcast saying the words funjobs.fart and it is with a z thanks
for asking yeah funjobs.fart what kind of jobs are on funjobs.fart okay here's the thing though
charles it it started as a joke right and they did like a joke commercial that joke commercial
accidentally ran during the super bowl now everybody's using funjobs.fart but they can't
change the name or else people won't be able to find the website anymore let that be a lesson to
you is it branding slash my brother that's the that's the url for you i know it's not a competitor
zip recruiter.com definitely post a funjobs.fart so you're covering all your bases you're all good
now listen making making up beautiful websites in my brain and sharing them with the world is
exhausting and hungry work well there's only one thing you can do about that griffin let's go to
naturebox.com slash my brother uh from sacks like peanut butter nom noms or serrano check hash use
uh it says here i can substitute in my favorites if i like the uh favorite for me is of course
parmesan garlic pop pops i was enjoying some before we started the recording and it almost
tore my family apart because they auditory flavor taste dream sensation auditory can i give you an
auditory sample of parmesan no you fucking can't no i'm gonna edit it out and you'd only be doing
it to me and travis and i hate that don't do that don't do it don't do that don't do that
don't do it no problem i said no problem you're just sitting there with them in your fucking
mouth now i can hear how it's changed your tongue shapes god no no from snacks like peanut butter
nom noms or sriracha cashews uh my favorite is uh oh i left that in the show oh good mini belgian
waffles i like that okay naturebox has over 100 delicious snacks to choose from they get delivered
directly to your doorstep they have brand new choices every single month naturebox is full of
flavor but without any of the junk so head to naturebox.com slash my brother and unbox a world
of taste and possibility that's naturebox.com slash my brother for your first box of our hand
fixing act sent directly to your doorstep a world of taste and possibly like ribbon you open you
open the box of naturebox and you're transported to a world in which everything tastes like
something a world of pure imagination if you will you eat some peanut butter nom noms and then you
see a little goat man he's doing a dance he's giving you a lullaby on an ocarina the lion the
witch and the pup do not follow him don't i cannot stress this enough god he has killed before and he
will kill again so listen you're gonna be confronted with his horny visage every time you eat anything
from naturebox but the flavors are great it's worth it you take a bite and you swallow it you're
gonna see this goat man turn right around do not acknowledge do not go with him do not go he will
tell you that unless he knows the secret password that your parents gave you when they sent someone
to pick you up do not go with that goat man i know you're thinking in this fantasy world i
feel like i'm invincible you're not you're not that is merely the flavor that's the flavor
overwhelming you if you die in the naturebox dream fever you die in real life i got a message for
emma yeah the most amazing girlfriend ever blankenship that's a mouthful of a name but
that's from her incredibly handsome and talented loving and modest boyfriend oh who does not
provide his name here so i'm going to call him dougie happy birthday emma congrats on it's me
dougie your boyfriend that you love your boyfriend named dougie congrats on reaching 21 teach me how
to no can i finish this fucking please please do you're amazing and beautiful p.s how cool is it
that the macaroons are talking about you well dougie it's very cool i feel like maybe we're
giving dougie a little bit more attention to emma and i don't think that's what dougie intended so
let's turn our our gaze away from dougie we've had a lot of fun with him today uh okay i'm opening
my heart to emma the most amazing girlfriend ever blankenship uh doesn't have many details for us to
sort of ruminate about emma 21 huh time to sip on some alcohol or if you don't drink alcohol that's
fine too either way um i'm gonna see what i can uncover about her on facebook oh god no that's
creepy yeah i'll just open up her facebook and see what jesus justin no that's no problem no
problem at all it says right here she's into fetty wap sorry how about this i got another message
that i'm ready for it and it's for everyone oh shit let me try this again and give it up maybe
the proper uh uh i don't know broadcast it deserves this message is for you listener at
home you're listening to this or in your car or on the street wherever you are this message is for
you and it's from ryan huppertz and ryan huppertz wants you the listener at home he wants to say to
you hey what's up and i left a little pause there for you to answer ryan don't say it now because
you'll interrupt one of us um but i just hope that sort of instinctively you're like not much ryan
just chilling or eating a hot dog ryan with my dad or um you know back at the back of the gym it's uh
it's chest day or something like that whatever just blast it yeah um but just let ryan know
what you're doing he's worried about you um maybe he wants to take part maybe he wants to be a part
of of what you're doing maybe he also wants to eat hot dogs with your dad yeah why don't you
just connect with him i'm sure he's on linkedin you can email yeah how come you never call ryan
yeah right rye dog at uh uh right i'll dot fart dog dot fart is another place he's contactable
um but anyway ryan uh i'm recording a podcast with my brothers to answer your question i'm
checking my fantasy football scores son of a bitch ryan i'm worrying that the first half of
our podcast wasn't very funny because we started on a very honest yet dour note for about 10 minutes
so that's what i'm doing right now ryan that's what we do though we throw ourselves in the
comedy briar patch by being not funny for a long time and then from that we hone it like a diamond
or a sword hi i'm lisa hanna walt and i'm emily heller and if you're not listening to our podcast
baby geniuses you're missing out on stuff like camille nanjiani solving the zodiac murders
oh who's like would you ever go to a friend and you're like hey could you lick all these
lick all these envelopes for me you'd be like you're a serial killer
definitely i'm leaving right now guy brandon talking about ruth bader ginsburg
um and it was it was just a great moment of leg oh no i'm here boys like i'm on this side of the
bench megan amram talking about intimidating baristas just feel like they're always in
character like they're always in character as like cool hipster girl and i just want to
break through that barrier plus every week we explore a new wikipedia page and talk to a crazy
expert in the field of nonsense well any any hack can make you not have a boner i mean that's it's
about how you do it right and we're the only podcast with regular updates about martha
stewart's pony or your money back we're not gonna give them their money back are we no let's keep
it yeah listen to our show every other monday on maximum fun yay do you guys want to yahoo
yeah yeah yeah yeah this yahoo was sent in by zoe kensky climbing the ladder thank you zoe
it's by yahoo answers user sellacake who asks a good name for a sports drink i have to design a
brand new product and it had to be a sports drink do you guys have any good name ideas
thank you so much smiley face me and my partner can't think of a good name i don't know if this
is like a school project and they're talking about like their um like their school partner
in economics class or something or if it's just like their light their life partner their love
partner but i do like that they gave us literally no information to work off except that it is a
sports drink yeah is that a like flavored drink does it have electrolytes in it well is it some
kind of protein milk this is how things work in in r&d travis and i've worked on a lot of
rad is what we call it in the business i've worked on a lot of rad and really the name informs the
product you name you name the shit and then you decide what the shit's going to be based on the
cool name that you've decided because you sell the name you don't sell the juice do kids still like
irony in names of stuff now they're they're they're post-ironic at this point oh shit okay
i was gonna say lazy juice lazy juice that'd be ironic um that's just what i call alcohol though
has anybody actually listen listen listen i like that good but that may be very heavy thank you
listen has anybody actually made haterade like has anybody made it like he's gonna be taking
nobody owns that trademark right like could you buy some actual thing called haterade
haterade i'm pretty sure they wouldn't let you get that in the same way that they wouldn't let
me go out and they wouldn't let me trademark like joca cola because the sound they wouldn't let me
go out and they wouldn't let me trademark depsy which is a difference brown carbonated uh sugar
water for you to enjoy at home or diet depsy or pie it would actually be pie at depsy you could
probably though get patrick dempsey to be your spokesman for depsy hi everybody this is patrick
dempsey this is gonna get confusing but stick with me here you might want to turn subtitles on
folks you're gonna notice this ad is four minutes and 30 seconds long you're gonna need to hang in
there okay listen it's not pepsi and it's also not dempsey although it sounds like it no it's
not dim no it's not called dempsey i and i think you have to worry about someone going out and
making dempsey yeah or no they couldn't call it dempsey they would have to call it like simpsey or
something i'm johnny depsy and this is uh the good news is i know we're struggling we brew it
here in pepsi yeah maybe good news would be like a good name for it give me some of that good news
like pour me up a glass of good news oh i like that whenever i go to a bar ever again justin
that's what i'm gonna say to the bartender let me get some of that good news pardon
excuse me what do you want oh you know can i get a good news in vodka please
um uh here's can i give you guys some answers that yahoo provided fuck yes you can uh
alicia uh provided the best answer which was in all caps and it's pretty good exersport
okay that's real good tm and then question mark provided a bunch of real stinkeroos
like frizzen frizzen what does that have to do with sport is that unless you're like directly
marketing to sports in prison yeah no like f-r-i-z-z-e-n not like not like prison is that
what you thought i said was prison i thought you said frizzen i did say frizz because it's for
prison for for prison for prison that's actually the next suggestion uh the one after that is cool
quick and then there's quicks and then there's i sport and then there's bolt beta and then there's
whoa hold on hold on hold on bolt beta it hasn't quite made it out of the research
development phase yet working on thank you for helping us test our fluid uh let's talk about
power beat give me a glass that power beat you gotta drink it out of a glass because fucking
artisanal i just won the big sports game thanks power beat you gave me jumping energy i want to
talk to you guys about aqua elite what's aqua elite you say well i think it's aqua athlete
like you know what like aquaman here's a similar vein freshly freshly is very good how about vox
just in my employer and it means power in latin i'm like 100 sure that's not true that's not
accurate yeah pretty sure it does not mean that levitas means lightning in latin again pretty
sure you screwed the pooch there yeah incorrect you know it's a whole market that no one's
capitalized on power beat sports drinks served hot oh that's right that's a great point where's
your like hot sports drinks give me some of that power tea yeah that's what i'm saying maybe a nice
like just a boiling hot cup of tea because you watch these sportsmen right the sportsmen they
play out in the snow sometimes yeah sometimes it's like raining and it's cold and you don't
want something icy and cold when you are icy and cold what about like a hot cocoa kind of hair are
you drinking a hot toddy no it's hot body get on right it's right there we're gonna lose gotta say
something though we're gonna end a lot of coaching careers early no no no no no uh what should we do
coach it's uh third and one uh um punt uh definitely punt are you sure where is anybody
seeing coach he's like he just left we're in field goal range you think no no no no no this is you
do we're gonna do the old ball dropsy what's the ball dropsy just you'll figure it out just get
out there please god don't win this game it's another it's another zero zero game in quintuple
overtime these coaches seem very nervous the coaches are standing back to back in the center
of the field circling protecting one another they've crafted spears out of the down markers
it's their only natural defense oh shit
and now and now an interview with bill belichick bill uh tell us about the secret to victory today
because he's been melted down okay what's he a coach yeah fuck yeah
got it from downtown put a sports one right in the bucket oops there's another one looks
like i'm deep in the paint three sports jokes how come you never see coach like if it cold or hot
if i was a coach the game is going well like you'd have to find me like i think if especially if the
score's high i'll think well they've got it from here i'm gonna go if any coaches are listening
the next time somebody dumps gator i want you to turn around smack them in the face yeah how dare
no um if i was a coach yeah what's so fucking funny about that tribes you think it's un
unbelievable i could coach a team no it's just more this dreamlike way in which you said it
if i was a coach you know what i'd do when i am coach when griffin coach guys when i am
guys when i am coach guys when i'm dauber okay hey guys yeah coach when i am coach
not there yet slow your slow your whistle down yes offensive coordinator when i am coach
when i am coach of team
when i am sports boss
when i am president sports when i would do when i'm the points mayor
when i'm dr touchdown the first thing i'll do oh fuck me all right when i am coach of team
i would not let that shit fly are you kidding me i need to be respected because if i don't
have to respect then they're just gonna do their own plays out there that's like they can't they
need to do my plays that's why teams only ever win one super bowl because they start practice
the next year and every player on that team is thinking i dumped some sticky juice on your head
yeah remember that you don't have nothing on me i don't respect no sticky coach you're probably
still sticky right now aren't you coach let me let me touch you oh sticky boy who's a sticky boy
there's a power beat residue oh shit i've always considered myself a fashionable guy
but as i approached my mid-30s i find myself questioning if i can still rock new fashion
trends so you've come to the right place should i pull off a flat brim baseball cap with a brightly
colored shirt or should i hang it all up and just rock the hallway less like a runway and more like
a hallway that's from mid-30s swagger well now i'm thinking about ntm again so thanks
dude you know what you do you look to one man that man is jay-z okay okay he transitioned
yeah from fashionable young cool guy yeah to fashionable adult man a fashionable father cool
guy suit guy he's not like cool he's not cool jersey and sneakers guy he's like fashionable
suit and tie guy now that's a transition you get to make it 30 i certainly appreciate jay-z's
style and his art and everything about him but i i get nervous about i get nervous about my own
authenticity when i do anything new with my luck i went to the gap are you more of a pitbull man
no i'm saying i fell into the gap yesterday and um i was with a group of my friends today having
brunch and i referenced the juliet lewis commercial where she's dancing with the daft punk robots
and they all looked at me like i was a psychopath that mood i feel like everybody knows that
commercial right i didn't invent it in my mind in a dream state did i i didn't pass through the
anyway griffin i love you i've never heard of this god no fuck fuck okay anyway uh i went to
the gap yesterday because i had to buy some khakis because i was uh going to a wedding
and i saw these brown jeans and they looked tight legged and i said get those fucking jeans and i
did i did get those fucking jeans and i put them on i thought they looked good and i thought they
really uh encased my meat in a nice way that was pleasing to my eye but it's new like i don't own
tight pants and i certainly don't own brown jeans that and that small like that modicum of change
was enough to make me worry like my friends are gonna see me like what are you doing wearing these
tight brown jeans idiot that's not that's not your style you wear things with like those little
loops on them that you put hammers in even though you're not like a guy who uses hammers every
that's your that is your look cargo cargo boy there's another man to look to here griffin
that's bruno mars i can't okay you keep referencing people that like i can't look
i can't you know what okay there's two different kinds of style and i can't have that on a pink
colored t shirt but hear me out there's two kinds of style right there is like uh uh world style
there's like the fashionable trend style and there's personal style which i think is deeply
respected more so in mid-30s than that like trendy style that idea of like oh that's a guy
who like has figured it all out for himself yeah it's just exhaust it's either exhausting because
you have to keep evolving that personal style because if you don't the other thing happens which
is just like you get hemmed in to a look and like i don't want to put justin on blast but justin
you've got a very personal style when i see you i say that's justin i'm not confused with you
not confused about who it is because at this point like i know your personal style how would you
describe it um mostly just like um cool vacation dad cool vacation dad yeah for sure for sure but
i and i don't want to criticize you and i don't want to like i i again keep in mind there's no
i mean i couldn't care less that's also part of your style is showy hipster cowboy showy hipster
cowboy is definitely travis's thing me i'm just sort of amorphous clothes horse but what i but
driven's an inscrutable blob i might you can't wrap your mind around me but just what i'm saying
is i feel like you're not your look hasn't evolved nor will it first okay and you're okay with that
you're cool at that well i i spend that time it takes x number of seconds to think about
how your clothes make you look this is the this is the opening i'm just i'm just quoting the opening
of jesse thorns put this on but let me just encapsulate for you it takes x number of seconds
to think about how you look if you decide you're not going to think about anymore that's a lot of
free thinking seconds that you got to think about how much you miss antm for example that's god yeah
see and now i'm looking maybe i should get into fashion just to fill my fucking days with anything
other than the weeping and gnashing of my own my style my style icon is paul f tompkins because
there was a time when that man was podcasting 23 and a half hours out of every day the fact that
he wore pants at all is a personal triumph and he single-handedly he walked into the podcasting
community say hey we don't all have to dress like dipshits just because we record podcasts
and he elevated the game guy looks fresh fucking every time i see him he is also a self-described
late bloomer and like you can like look back over his career and he has not always been
the trendy motherfucker that he is now like he at some point in his adult life went you know what
i'm gonna choose my look and i'm sticking with it i just find it really hard to i'm i'm like not to
turn this into a pity party but i'm i'm an overweight gentleman there's a in my in the
visage department there's a lot of work i have to do to get my look right that that is not relate
it right now me spending a lot of money on clothes would be like buying diamond paint for a house
where the pipes are falling out the windows like it doesn't make sense yeah you're so trust me on
this when we took you don't get to tell me i'm wrong we took you to that men's jacket store
yeah we all tried on jackets and we looked good we look good we look good and then you know what
you know what didn't happen then after that travis um about five minutes in our podcast i took the
jacket off you know why because i was sweating i was sweating everywhere that's what i think
every when we went to max fun con and paul thomkins was there john roderick was there
and john hodgeman was there and you look at these three dudes who are like wearing suits and looking
real good real fly and it was hot as shit i was in a t-shirt and shorts and sweating no yeah you
gotta risk it for the biscuit that is for sure travis that is the most essential element of
fashion is pleasure is pain and i agree with you there do you remember the uh uh cincinnati live
show when i believe his name was cole cole asked about like having a uniform where he was like
black t-shirt jeans every day i the older i get the more i am on board with it i own so many black
t-shirts and jeans it's a good way to go man well i wear i wear a white t-shirt with a green sweater
vest and khaki shorts every single day and a belt on your head on your underwear on the outside of
your pants because i'm bug funny i'm quail man sometimes no we got you um this question got
pretty real huh i just yeah i mean like anytime i i do think there is an element also to be considered
this like and people say well you know if you just comb the straight like there's a there's a
financial aspect of this question too right like there's a financial there's a lot of different
aspects this question but like i think we can't we can't ignore the fact that like when we bought
those jackets we took them off during our show because it was 250 fucking degrees up there we
were basically performing inside of an easy bake oven but it was it was you felt good when you
bought that jacket you put it on you look to yourself say hey there's a new look and i look
good in it just go to the gap sometimes just go just drink it in fall into the gap and just like
take a look around and say i don't own this and this would probably look good on me and then just
try it on and then buy it at the gap please support the gap the gap needs you now more than ever
it's important to me that you trust the gap trust them i'm jealous of people who are into fashion i
would like very much yes absolutely y'all are into into that like i feel i would be i think
if i was like a little more confident i feel like i would be the sort of person that would get like
deep into cool clothes and have like cool suits and everybody thought hey you know cool guy you
know i'm jealous of i actually have some friends in town who are like this they get like cool shoes
yeah those like cool shoes friends like they have different they have these like loud colored kicks
and i see those and i say those are fresh i don't own those i am i i own like three pairs of brown
slip-on loafers with gel insoles built into them shit birds i can't i say friend look at your shoes
friend look at my shoes they are the opposite shoes you know some people i was looking for
shoes to wear with jeans because it's see because i wear tennis shoes with jeans a lot that looks
like shit a lot of people know the secret i don't know the secret people are wearing shoes with jeans
i googled shoes you wear with jeans like to look good like what shoes you wear with jeans and
googled is that are you serious like serious i went into i went into macy's and in my effort to
try to phrase this question i actually think i asked the saleswoman where are like the shoes
that people wear
zip zap zip zap zorp i am an alien trying to fit in i i am a human looking for human shoes
you know how people wear those things that humans put upon your feets you know people wear shoes
just like regular people are out there wearing shoes yeah and they're not just every day wearing
the same pair of like like slip-on sperries with no socks can i give you the secret yeah what are
shoes the secret is not in the shoe justin it's in the cut of the leg of the gene and how it fits
over well that's that's easy that's an easy one uh my cut of my gene is rolled up because they don't
have any they're short enough for my stupid legs next question what else you got justin i'm not
gonna listen to this in any more of your shit i will not listen to your justin fucking done with
it okay okay there's a difference between being uh self-acceptance and like being down on yourself
i guess that's what i'm saying i guess i'm an inspiration i guess that's what i'm saying okay
um i'm proud of you and your strength let's end the show now thanks for listening to my brother
my brother me and vice show for the modern era i feel like we held a lot of people today
well a lot of time talking about fashion and sports yeah we had some fun time in there um and uh
sorry the show started off slow but if it makes you feel any better we'll never talk about amtm
ever again because it's gone forever bye bye it's gonna eternal sunshine it right out of there yeah
yep yep yep if only i mean we did promise to remember you literally at the beginning of the
show yeah but we're just not gonna bring it up on the podcast okay we would like to say thank you
again at the nature box uh where you can order hundreds of great tasting snacks you can go to
nature box dot com slash my brother to sign up for a box of great tasting snacks i'd give you
some snack advice right now but i think i've concretely proven myself to be a non-reliable
snack narrator at this point uh i uh i wanted to thank john roger and the long winters for
these different theme song it's departure off the album putting the days to bed good time um good
album front to back listen uh i want to uh say go listen to all the other shows on maximum fun network
uh shows like jordan and jesse go uh shows like throwing shade shows like wham bam pow we all do
other shows on the network hey this week uh we've got a new episode of the adventure zone coming out
the three of us recorded with our dad and i'm gonna go out on a limb and say it's the best episode yet
um i think so i'm i was getting caught up in the action yeah the thrills if you have a great new
character on the show this week that is true if you don't listen to the show um we're only like 25
episodes in so it's easy to get caught up and it's a show where you play dnd if you ever play dnd you
don't know anything about dnd that's fine i would argue probably most of our listeners don't it's
also broken up into chapters so you could start it at the beginning of a certain chapter of the
show and start listening from there if you want to you will probably miss out on some stuff but
like if you want to hop on that's that's and you don't want to go through a big back catalog that's
you know that's the way to do it just missed 420 didn't we fuck it's five years what you did i got
two hours oh yeah baby settle down traf let me know how i do um so yeah go see all the other max
fun shows there's shows like saw bones justin does his wife sitting and it's a show about
medical history um travis uh does uh can i pet your dog you produce that i produce it and i
talk on it yeah you get up on it um also bunker buddies bunker buddies you got that one there's a
lot of good stuff a lot of good programming on the maximum fun network my youtube food review
show things i bought at sheets is back oh my god you've been on a tear these past few apps have
been like next level yeah thanks there so that's back you can find that on youtube you can go to
actually just go to sheets show.com that's sheets with a z show.com it's just a regular food review
show where i buy things at the uh gas station convenience store restaurant uh sheets and i
review them and that's what happens this is a regular show i also have a show with my friend
brento floss where we talk about what's trending on the internet that's not a name what well his
name is brent but i mean on the internet he is known as brent it's his nom de internet um
but check it out it's called trends like these i think it's nom.com right nom.com is that a thing
nom.com trendslikethese.com nom.com nom de fart uh we also have the same thing everybody who sent
us stuff in the in the p.o boxes i i'm saving up some stuff to talk about uh once we got like a
big bunch of it but if you got anything you would like to send us you can send it to the west coast
is p.o box uh 341769 los angeles california 90034 um and my p.o box is just kidding i'll never open
a p.o box sorry thracks heads and the east coast p.o box is p.o box 54 honey's west virginia 25706
please don't send perishables i rarely check it or the thracks or the thracks that would also be
great if you would please don't send the thracks please don't thracks me dude don't thracks my
boy uh his final uh yahoo is sent in by level 9000 yahoo it's by yahoo answers user edgar oh
shit edgar only has one percent best answers that's the lowest rating i've ever seen that
means he does this a lot it means he's answered at least at least 100 right he's done 280 total
answers and exactly one percent of those 2.8 times he's really got it anyway edgar asks
in all caps why on earth does jamie oliver ruin an asian salad with fucking pomegranate seeds
that's pushing my ideals jamie
i'm just a mackerel my brother my brother gives me mad square on the lips
you
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported hello i'm taco the
elven magician moral high church here the master of clerical magic i'm magnus burnsides the fighter
did you guys like that did you the listener like that you were just swept up in a world of high
fantasy and magic where anything can happen and anything is possible hi i'm griffin mcroy dungeon
master for the adventure zone a new podcast on maximum fun in which magic and mystery intertwine
for a very erotically charged role-playing experience you can catch it every other thursday
here on maximum fun.org it's for dungeons and dragons but with family