The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother and my brother mean advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I'm your middle brother Travis McElroy.
I'm your babiest brother Griffin Liebowitz. Boy, Griffin are you using your married name?
I'm using my stage name Griffin Liebowitz. Griffin, Griffin the experience Liebowitz.
I like that. You know guys I'm getting pretty excited. It's back to school time.
And how does that affect your day-to-day life Justin? Well finally I can ship this kid off for
eight hours a day and get a little time back to myself. I don't see why you can't. Get it get a
leg up get an early start. It takes 10,000 hours to become a master of school. Start it now. Start
it now. All right does your uh are your is your entire school are all the sharp edges foamed over?
Have you foamed over every sharp edge in your school? Listen I'm gonna. These stairs that you
have what is that about like stairs? I'm gonna need a strict no bullying guarantee from you
because my baby can't stand it can't she's an amazing child she cannot stand up to much
physical bullying. She can't stand up very well. She can't stand up either but but if she starts
getting bullied it's she doesn't have the tools to protect herself. I noticed that uh at 10 a.m.
you have her scheduled for uh pre-algebra that's crazy because she'll be asleep. Where is her
where is her nap zone? Um is there a class I can enroll her in where she watches shapes and colors
move on an iPad? Do you have any uh parental incentives for good grades like some sort of
Pizza Hut program for me? Wait that doesn't happen for like regular kids in school. Yeah but I've
never been a parent before Travis I don't know this stuff maybe that maybe parents have been
getting pizza kickbacks the entire time. That's the only reason I can think of that parents care
about grades. Maybe the whole reason parents have been so uptight about grades since time
immemorial is that they've been getting pizza kickbacks. You're suggesting that when kids pull
down a tight GPA their parents reap the the that sweet pie that sweet pizza pie as a reward? They
get if the kids get a good GPA the parents get a PWATF which is a pizza with all the fixings. Okay
and some maybe some tokens if they do real good. Maybe a few tokens for the folks. Is there an
adult equivalent to like back to school is it first day on the job? This is that that is Travis
you have highlighted one of the primary problems with adulthood is the lack of like sort of a
a cyclical period of renewal. You know that that's what adulthood is lacking that's why
adulthood is what it is bad because they lack. Hey turn it off now we're getting real. Nobody
said like when you're a kid it is the okay being a kid is the time in your life where I think you
least need someone to be like just take a break my man. You are burning the candle at both ends
Devin. Yeah just this is so what you work from seven to three and then you have nothing to do
at all like you can literally have a time when you sit and say I don't have anything to worry
about right now like I don't have anything I should be doing. That's crazy. Yeah that's insane. Do you
know how crazy it is there are humans walking across this earth who like can sit in a chair
and not have something they should be doing at that exact instant and then someone comes and says
hey you look tired take three months off. Oh and by the way in taking three months off you are
generating another thing for the adults that live with you to be worried about like you're creating
more stress for them but you seriously you look beat take three months off. It's insane. Do you
guys think that the three of us are slowly becoming this this this um this weekly podcast that we put
out is slowly becoming some sort of digital embodiment of Andy Rooney like it's somehow
you know that movie transcendence where Johnny Depp uploads himself into the matrix or some
shit I didn't see it I watched a little bit of it on I'm playing muted. I listened to Flophouse
they pretty much ran through it for me. Okay um I think that might be I think Andy Rooney might
be us in the podcast form. Maybe but maybe it's like not that Andy Rooney like maybe we're not
growing into like cantankerous old men like Andy Rooney maybe like the older I get Andy Rooney just
starts to make some sense right like what are all these different fruits the supermarket right?
Do you remember when yogurt used to just taste like yogurt?
Maybe it just tasted like tangy yogurt. I can't go with you guys on this one.
You will Griffin, see you in three hours.
I like exotic fruits I like exotic yogurt flavors.
I had a I had a fun exotic fruit experience a couple weeks ago I bought I was at the the
Cha-Cha Kroger again epicenter of all the best anecdotes and I found a fruit that I didn't
recognize it was really weird it had like a spiny outside and like it looked kind of good like I
don't know I'll try anything once and I got to the cash register and the woman didn't obviously
like because who does she didn't notice what the fruit was called there was no sticker or anything
on it so she asked me what it was so she could ring it up and I had no like I had no glare so
I'm in this situation where I'm looking like this woman's like so you're buying it yes
you know what it is I do not know I don't Justin to be fair she's the most in the wrong because
she should be like the the experienced professional working there you're you're going on a new flavor
experience she's the one who's supposed to be in the know she's paid to work there yeah but like
I okay Travis this poor woman works at Kroger at like one o'clock in the afternoon like I don't
expect her to be my exotic flavor sommelier but don't you feel like you look cooler when she's
like do you know what it's called and you're like nope but I'm gonna eat it no I look like an idiot
you look like an impulsive idiot yeah because you're also in that moment you're also admitting
I don't know I just saw it and I thought me and you are this is destiny I can eat this you're a
weird fruit get in my face was it a durian maybe it was a no it was like a it was like inside it
was like a grape but on the outside it had hard I think you ate like some sort of alien seed
that the government put there and now you're gonna have like superpowers it's gonna be like district
nine I would like to think that it's that would have started this culminated with me this culminated
with me googling a loose description of the image of the fruit in the hopes that I could figure out
what it was called spiny spiny fruit Justin wants to eat spiny fruit to eat for inside small
spiny fruit how to eat cash cashier also doesn't know what is sold at Kroger Kroger exotic spike
fruit dear Jeeves what is this fruit yes my favorite search engine dear Jeeves Justin ask a
question they were rambutans by the way okay well I've learned this since because they were delicious
rambutans and there and there's your weekly fruit recommendation this has been fruit records stay
tuned next week for strawberries this has been juicy Justin remind you to get that seed that you
crave vitamin C I mean in a month I'll be defending myself in court over a speeding ticket do the
three of you have any experience with contesting a ticket any advice for a first-time defendant
court hacks your pal and shaman shaman thanks Drew your pal and Drew Davenport and not Shyamalan
Justin didn't you want I feel like you once told me or read a thing that was like pick a day when
you know the cops off duty and then he won't show up and like write down his badge number and yes
Travis I have some hacks that I read on the internet 10 years ago that I've never tried
that may or may not work that's the first one is figure out when the officer the arresting
officer will have the day off because you're supposed to be able to face your accuser in court
how do you get that information you call them and say hey I'd like to give you a free vacation you
got any time off coming up this is uh Disney this is Walt Disney this is Craig Disney you got kids
what are the names it's good for grown-ups too we just got a margaritaville get down here
you gotta get down here right on the mystic mountain have the other one I've I've I heard
is that if you go to the uh like the courthouse and you file a discovery motion on your case
then you can find out when the last time the speed gun that they used to get you was uh uh
updated or like checked for and there's like a certain time period in which they're supposed to
be checked and if it hasn't been checked in during that time period then you can get it thrown out
I've heard that too have you guys ever contested anything in court yes I got a ticket for an
expired inspection wiped a few times because that's how I would know when it was time to
actually get my inspection oh yeah that's a McElroy special I did that took me three years
they towed the car and the dude tearing the car when I was like I'll go get it right now and he
was like it's been three years man I don't know what you want me to do um like he apologized to
me for towing my car Griffin what did you what did you contest in court so there was after Justin
you gave me the Oldsmobile and thank you I don't thank you enough for that thank you the Cutlass
thank you for that Supreme car that tight Cutlass Sierra um that had no brakes when you gave it to
me and I never just repaired that particular malady uh I uh there was a cop that came by
and gave me a ticket every day for like two weeks he just drove by the house and gave me a ticket
and like there's a long period where the car wouldn't run uh we didn't like have the title for
it for some reason I was in the process of like requesting a new title but there was so much other
paperwork I had to get there was nothing I could do this car was just gonna sit in place and get
tickets until I could get the paperwork and I was waiting on the paperwork and this dick cop would
just like roll by every day and give me a ticket in the same spot uh and so I stopped paying them
until I got all that stuff figured out and knowing that I could like go to court and explain the
situation away and one morning he caught me getting into my car going to school and he was like
riding me up a ticket and he was like you can either come with me to court right now and pay
these off or I'm gonna take you to jail and I was like whoa damn because at that point it was like
maybe almost a grand I was in college I didn't have a grand so I went and I paid half of it and
then they said you have to pay half of it now and you can contest the rest later and so I went to
jail I went to I didn't go to jail I was in jail I went to court I was facing like 500 other dollars
in fines and uh my secret here's my little pro tip for you drew davenport I was a I was a freshman
in college knee-high to a frog cherubic in every way uh and I just uh cried a little bit nice that's
what I was gonna say I contested a noise violation and wept in court yeah I just cried a little bit
sophomore in college because like I had been driving for like a month I was like I just don't
I just it's so fresh I just like I don't have that money like I don't have anywhere you can
get that money and it's just like I want I want to I want to take care of this I do but I
and then they saw me out I didn't have to pay it but that dick cop am I right that cop
was a dick I'm I'm listen support our troops but that cop was a dick that's that's support
our street troops that's some grade a shit I even explained it to him and he like caught me
out time it's like dude listen I'm yes I'll do this I'll take care of this I can't take care of
this until I get this like one paper back he said I don't care man I'll take you to the take you to
the pokey really dick you're gonna take me to the pokey I just remembered that I fought a ticket that
I got in college because I couldn't read it uh like I couldn't read what they were charging with
like it was literally it was chicken scratch and I told the clerk I was like listen I can't contest
this I can't tell you if it like what the deal is because I can't read the ticket so I don't
I don't know what it's for I knew what it was for but I was like I don't know what it's because it
was I was too far away from the curb that used to be a big problem for me because I only drove
big cars I drove a Chevy Malibu and then a Cutlass Sierra it's hard to park those bad boys here's
what I'll say Drew Davenport I know you you are a you are a mountain of a man statuesque uh very
tall and I don't think anything is sadder than a very big man crying am I right you get that
you got like shoulders shaking oh my god because yeah you can put a lot of a lot of like muscle
behind that cry and you can you oh a whale herd down the street mine mine was sort of a pitiful
like and that's not the style that you want to go for you need a full complete emotional breakdown
yeah just like drop your axe to the ground let it like create a crevice in the courtroom floor
maybe get babe your blue ox to start crying alongside of you and you cry the colorado river
cry the colorado river right the people like this isn't a this isn't an offender this is a legend
a single uh perfect orb shaped tear falls out of your one cyclops eyeball do you guys want a yahoo
if all else fails Drew just mention our name well there should be an asterisk under after every tip
we just gave in the past like 10 minutes that just says only if you are a white oh right right
right white person like get like that that it's it's it's important to recognize that the loopholes
in the system that we have mentioned here are are pretty much just applicable to white people
because the the country is broken but other than that go go go for it but i think i i don't know i
think white people is a pretty big group of people and it's oh you think there are a lot of white
people go on griffin i'm just saying more malcolm gladwell i'm not i'm not i'm not saying that we've
won the numbers game what i'm saying is that our advice is rarely applicable to
to modest groups of people and this is a lot of white people there's a lot of them you guys want
a yahoo please yeah okay yes it's sitting yeah it's in by level 9 000 cyclops crier drew down
the port thank you open weeper drew down laving baby man drew davenport sent this in thank you
it's by uh yahoo answers user vadid who asks which celebrities love watching pokemon or reading
pokemon fan fiction stories please answer i want a list of celebrities that love watching pokemon
or reading fan fiction stories thanks in advance now i i will admit i'll confess that i only brought
this up and i don't think we're gonna get a lot of talking talking points out of this but this week
ronda rousey the strongest human being currently living did an interview on some red carpet where
she talked about pokemon flight five minutes god she just keeps getting cooler and cooler
she buys every pokemon game all the pokemon cards she's got them all she catches them all
and i think i want to get we have a lot of listeners at this point billions basically
i want to try and get some sort of campaign going to have a pokemon duel with ronda rousey
oh can we please make that happen okay here's how we'll sweeten the pot ronda rousey if you're
listening griffin will duel you in pokemon and then you guys can fight like in a ring
so that way you get griffin's strength you get your strength and then we'll do a tie breaker
if it comes to that griffin are you prepared to get beat up by ronda rousey i
i think i could stand a pretty good chance i don't know she beat up turtle real good
in the entourage oh god i was hoping we could talk about ronda rousey without talking about
the on you hoped wrong you can't hope wrong i will tell you two things i know of two celebrities
off the top of my head um uh that that uh that are pokemon fans i know for a fact william hung
was a uh you remember william hung he had his his star shined brightly but fast he was an american
idol bad singer he did she bangs remember that guy yeah that guy was into pokemon and uh harry
potter i know he's into pokemon daniel radcliffe he loved pokemon uh he compared he compared
horcruxes to pokemon on an interview i saw once ernie hudson none is that true yeah ernie hudson's
yeah ernie hudson's big big big big in a pokemon cards uh anyway i just listened this was all this
is um a little self-serving a little self-serving but i did just want to get that out there if
anybody knows ronda uh i'm not even i'm not even like bragging like i want to take down ronda i
i'm i she would probably beat me in that like she's she probably knows the best way to fight in any
like terms right like if right if we played uh canasta like she would she just would know how
to be a champion how did you punch me how did you find a rule that let you punch me in the head
it says right here i can't contest it this is a this is a deep index how about this other yadru
uh it's in my drew davenport it's by yadru answers user miss who asks
i need good ideas on a trap to set up on my roommate who is snooping through my
my four asterisks i'm gonna guess shit but who's snooping through my butt every time i leave
i don't oh that's funny i don't want water traps i want something that is going to make her think
twice about going in my room ever again so like incendiary devices we're looking how deadly do
you want to go is this like punitive or like uh i have a suggestion uh that i'd like to suggest
if i may be a so bold oh my god i know exactly where it's going this is a suggestion that you
can employ with uh under three dollars i think probably two if you buy store brand how could i
not see this coming what if you the next time your roommate goes to peruse your belongings
in your underwear drawer they find oh surprise surprise their hand has not been embedded in
your delicates your delicate unmentionables but in fact has found its way to a jar of jelly okay
so now just wait i have a very important question here yes do you remove your unmentionables first
before you fill the drawer with jelly yeah there's gonna be flies that's uh that's one
of many problems the jelly underneath a particularly tantalizing pair of oh my god
one that they definitely try to rifle through maybe you put on the jar drugs and money here
uh-huh and you replace the label and then they go to retrieve their treasure and instead find
some strawberry preserves wait hold on you're changing your story are we talking preserves
or are we talking jelly sir uh it depends on the part of the country and seasonal availability you
have to buy locally grown fair enough is the thing or else she could become allergic go to your
farmers market ask for the jar that the people would least like to have their hand stuck in
they'll know what you're what's your best prank jelly can i justin i don't want to be contrarian
here because i know how deeply you subscribe to this this jelly notion also jelly the knobs
oh my god you jelly those drawer knobs oh big okay now you're just being redundant then because
if you're if you jelly the knobs they're not going to move they're not going to go deeper into the
drawer unless they're using unless they're using a handkerchief to hide their fingerprints in which
case they wouldn't even notice the primary oh i see always always have backup jelly um let me
hit you with this idea though without jelly because jelly's good it'll stain your whites
and that's i guess has a sort of a long-lasting prank effect and um i'm into that i think a more
more effective deterrent solution would be honey you get honey on your hands that's your whole day
i used to watch winnie the pooh and i would have anxiety attacks oh that's his whole day he's got
honey on his face and his hands and he's covered in fur and that's going to complicate things even
further i don't have fur and it takes me a good two to three hours of scrubbing to get any honey
off my body but even if it's only a smack roll a smack a smack roll doesn't matter the amount i'm
saying the effort is going to be the same i'm sorry it doesn't matter the amount griffin i
think it does there is one huge flaw with your plan okay the the difference and i hate to get
into the aesthetics of this no get into it that's why that's why people listen to the show if you
dip your hand in a jar of honey you human instinct will will kick in and say well just lick it off
you're fine if you put your hand in a jar of jelly you can't it's too you just can't you can't lick
the jelly off like honey you can lick off you can't lick the jelly off you feel like an animal
there's no way there's no way that's not a deterrent because they'll lick the honey off
thanks for the smack roll and then they'll dig right back into your jar but then they will get
stuck in the hole trying to climb out of your room and then piglet will have to push on them
eeyore will have to push on them you just you're gonna get stuck you're seeing honey as being uh
almost a treat a a prank reward if you will i'm we can channel human nature to further the prank
what's that you go off to lick lick the honey off your hands but it's prank stink honey
it's stink honey it's jb custer's stink honey and you go to lick it off you get one taste of that
your mouth oh no this isn't funny at all hi folks i'm jb custer oh settle down butch that's my dog
butch listen when you're looking for the best in prankables reach for a jar of jb custer's stink
honey it's delicious it tastes great and it tastes great and stinks to high heaven how does it taste
smell is such a big factor in taste how does it smell so bad and tastes so damn good
the trick about my stink the stink honey trick is if you wait like a half hour it smells good
so it's like uh it's like invisible ink disappearing stink is like it you you it smells
bad and then if you wait long enough you just have patience aerate it out a little bit then it starts
to smell good again but if you wait too long it does harden into an unbreakable crust the other
problem with your playing griffin is that honey is poison to babies so if there's a baby going
through your drawer you just killed a baby so congratulations but they would sway you
but the person knows that unless do you have unless do you have a baby roommate do you have
a roommate who's using a baby as a front line of defense oh a baby agent a disarming baby a baby
in the coal mine if you will you're they're sending the baby out first to check for trap jars
how is it living with ashton kutcher it's pretty good um the rent isn't as expensive
as you would think it would be but i did have to have to hire a safety baby to just like enter in
rooms before i do and to like open any drawer that i need to like access for any reason because
you never know there there might be like uh i don't know like a naked man and it's uncomfortable
it's like an uncomfortable situation or you open up the toilet and there's like a human head in
there or he'll leave his door slightly jar so you think it's okay to go in and then you'll find him
in flagrante with a young hollywood starlet how is that a prank what he looks up he looks
up from the act of love making and says gotcha because that's what they that's what they said
wait just to be clear just to be clear ashton kutcher looks up after his prank and what he
says is gotcha yeah that's what he says that's what the name of the show gotcha punks hey let's
do another question uh my wife always chides me in the way i carry groceries from the trunk of
the car to the kitchen counter i take as many bags as i can carry so i can make the fewest number of
trips she calls it the lazy man's load but i completely disagree i feel like it's the opposite
it's the strong man's load since my arms are way down to the max am i being truly lazy and carrying
only one bag at a time as opposed to being truly lazy and carrying only one bag at a time what say
you brothers that's from shooting in chicago i i'm 100 with the question asker yeah absolutely i
don't have much i don't have much opportunity for strength training in my life so i need that i mean
it's it's good because it gets the job done quick but also i feel like macho man randy savage
carrying all those bags there has never been a time when i've come in from the car with bags
weighing down my arms when i haven't looked at my wife and like expected like a whoa look at how
many you're carrying i want i want some sort of sensor embedded above the door so that whenever
i come in carrying a big old arm of macho man randy savage groceries i want the john cena theme
song to play like just trumpeting me in the room look at his arms look at the definition look at
the tone how could he carry so many bags whenever i'm carrying the bags in from the car i wish that
there were like big stair steps in front of me so i like the judges could judge how many stair
steps i get up before i quit and like the lithuanian competitors that i could only do the
three steps like that what was that it was a lithuanian accent griffin read a book you can't
hear accents in books audiobooks uh i just love every part of it i love just being one and done
i love like when someone gets in my way and i'm like get out of the way because i'm carrying so
many bags and like that was rude but oh never mind he's got he does have a lot of bags i like
the inspirational moment when my arms are completely weighed down and i've got two 12
packs of soda and there's no way i could carry a single bag and then i realized i am not gonna
walk all the way back out here to close the trunk no way on earth am i making another trip and i
just dig deep digging that well that 127 hours well and just flex all my muscles available to
me and like somehow fling the 12 pack up and let it use its weight to carry the trunk back
to its closed position i'm also gonna be honest i also really like the moment when you're carrying
those 12 packs and one of them like the handle starts to rip a little bit and you're like oh
this is 24 now now the clock's a ticking i've only got like 30 seconds tops to get inside
before all these cans go everywhere whenever i see whenever i see somebody with those new fangled
cars or you kick the back bumper and it opens and closes the trunk i see them get their groceries
out and just give it a little a little punt to shut the door i just look at them and i think you
cuckold i don't think you're using that word correctly and i think i'm using it exactly
correctly you cuckold shut it with your hands i once uh was uh pulling this trick helping uh
my in-laws loaded some groceries in and uh my father-in-law is an an actual strong person
and he was carrying a bunch of groceries so i thought well i'm gonna you know i want you to be
impressed by the the the uh you know the spouse that your daughter has hitched her proverbial
wagon to so i'm gonna haul in like a ton of groceries too and i had a 12 pack of diet sun
kissed that the strong man's beverage i had 12 well it was theirs full of protein it's like his
fave to drink and just bustle down and uh and i picked it up and i held the top of the 12 pack
and it like ripped i had open as i was holding it and it was amazing because they have this like
very steep driveway and the the kansas sun kids were just like and falling out and exploding as
they hit the ground my strength potion how could you i need that strength potion to lift and he
turned to dust before you're very hot no i can already feel my knees trying to lap so well my
muscles are atrophying now i'm all noodly my strength potion my diet strength juice
let's go to the money zone so i can buy my own street
before we start this nature zone um in which we're talking about nature box griffin was
telling us about the uh mouse sounds he edited out of our tortinos sponsored episode griffin
did you save those tell me that somewhere there's an audio file on your computer just chained
together uh uh eating noises no i did do that once when the three of us all this is if you're
eating don't anymore ever again after hearing this but the three of us all had colds all at
the same time and oh my god oh gee i edited them all together and it sounded like one of those like
wind tunnels that they create for science to like test out the the you know strength and
pliability of like industrial strength walls it was a oh man what a bad bad thing i don't know
why i edited that together i used to have a strong fuck that was an evocative metaphor yeah nature
box offers lots of snack choices like mini belgian waffles strawberry lemonade fruit stars and sweet
and salty medley last night you know what i did i was watching sharknado 3 and getting drunk
and i had some mini belgian waffles that i dipped in nutella yeah i know flavor pioneer oh sorry
neighbors nature box is full of flavor but it doesn't have any of the chunk oh it does if you
dunk it in nutella you okay you can add junk to it no inherent junk no inherent junk and you can
try your first boss nature this is our first time talking about nature box you have to forgive
justin you can enjoy your first box of nature box snacks on them if you go to nature box dot com
slash my brother i just polished off a bag of the honey macadamia uh pretzel pops wow what a
satisfying crunch i uh i'm a big fan of these blueberry figgy bars damn they're like fig
newton's on but they if fig newton's got diesel see i prefer like the the the saltier more savory
snacks i like the guacamole uh crunch bites and uh asiago and cheddar cheese crisps those are my
favorite those are my those are my jam i like parmesan garlic pop pops so you've just eaten
a bunch of parmesan garlic pop pops and asiago cheese crisps and now your beard is full of cheesy
dustins oh no not cheesy dustins what am i gonna do about this what am i gonna do hire
a bunch of birds to peck the dustins out of my beard no not in this not in this economy
i i said o economy there on purpose thanks obama because of because obama anyway i think this
beard's gotta go and i know the best way to get it off my face and that is harry's.com and as
luck would have it my brother my brother is this week supported in part by harry's.com
so did the stars really aligned on this one huh guys
these uh these these ads whenever they say supported in part by harry's.com i always
find that very confusing because the if the inverse were true like that would be a really
dependent lifestyle to lead if like my entire support system is an online retailer of shaving
products like i go to them for everything we are supported in whole by harry's.com
they're your mr financially yeah uh there there are everything harry's razors offer a high quality
shave that's better for your face and for your wallet the starter set is 15 it includes a razor
foaming shave gel or shave cream and three razor blades plus free shipping that's bonkers that's
give me 33.3 repeating off okay i don't know why you're so angry uh all i need to haggle it's the
only way i can feel okay well uh no need to haggle just go to harry's.com and you can get five dollars
off that starter set with the code my brother all one word so ten dollars you get a razor foaming
shave gel or shave cream and three razor blades and they're really really good blades and it's
it's it's an awesome shaving solution and ten dollars is like cheaper than just regular blades
that you would buy at the the you know the costco or whatever and they're great for everybody
everybody can use them even babies even babies shit baby you've really let your face go time to
shave up you're all scruffy baby i got a message for isaac beachy from andre who says isaac can't
decide what i'm more disappointed by the fact that you'd be willing to blow a hundred dollars
to have some clever assholes that was been endearingly read your incomprehensible message
on the fake radio or the fact that i'm dominant to respond in kind love andre p.s thanks for
introducing me to my bim bam they're funny and stuff just see just so people listening at home
you can call us whatever you want to if you pay us a hundred dollars like i you can cause any name
in the book just don't call me late for dinner good lord how about this message for brady and
it's from mike uh and mike says two things number one friendly reminder that you promised kristen
and team something rap lyrics your required rhymes were home free sweet pea whoopee and morning tea
maybe the mackerel brothers can help you out here try to get this in before your birthday
number two happy birthday oh you just missed it i think that's sweet i think i did
wrap those i think it's it sounded to me like i wrapped them there wasn't the you know how sometimes
in rap between the rhyming words they just like throw some other words in there to like form
complete sentences and coherent thoughts and stuff that's not my style i do slam rap
maybe you can buy them like just like home free sweet pea whoopee morning tea that's pretty good
is that rap oh you forgot to say my name is justin and i'm here to say okay okay
my name is justin and i'm here to say that i love fruity pebbles in a home free way
there is a flavor called sweet pea whoopee morning tea but to get the fruity taste i got a trick fred
is that pretty good is that rap was nailed it
it we're dave and graham and we host stop podcasting yourself we started this podcast back
in 2008 before podcasts had to have any kind of concept so we don't really know how to describe
it it's kind of like going to the barber shop if your barber knew all about the first season of the
show elf it's like a 90 minute massage where the masseuse is two people talking to each other with
a third person it's like the monsters of metal tour only quieter no music and just talking it's
like a makeout session but without the lips touching they just talk a lot download stop
podcasting yourself from itunes or maximum fun.org uh do you guys want to yahoo yeah oh i'm gonna
stretch first get a good stretch in zoe kinski sent this one and thank you zoe it's by yahoo
answers climbing that ladder climbing that ladder sent in by yahoo answers user james who asks
ghostbusters question what happens if one of the ghostbusters dies and becomes a ghost
holy shit here's a question i always had what happens if one of the ghostbusters
dies and becomes a ghost do the other ghostbusters suck him up like they do with the other ghosts
okay i would say that if they've made an arrangement with a ghost that's literally named
slime yes that is defined by its sliming that that he can just like chill at their house yeah
which is like by the way by the way okay if i just say okay just give me a second yeah by the way
by the way by the way if i'm going in to procure the ghostbuster services which i'm assuming i'm
doing at a premium once they become the toast of new york if i'm going in to procure their services
and like i'm talking to janine i'm setting up a time for my uh consultation an estimate which
i'm assuming they'll do for free uh i and i'm like setting that up and out of the corner of my eye
i spy slimer like just jamming hot dogs down his throat let's fucking equate that if you were an
exterminator and like people came in to hire you and there were just like rats hanging out on the
floor that's not a good look not just rats hanging on the floor like a giant rat emitting green goo
and eating hot dog and you were just like oh that's our rat that's ratty the rat he's our buddy
like the grossest rat was slimer a pet or like was he sharing the office space like what i never
quite understood because he had to be like the embodiment of a human being who had died like
that's how ghosts work but he didn't seem to like speak english or have any human characteristics
except that he was just kind of hungry all the time and terrible and yet he was the ghost that
was allowed like free reign of the place yeah sure not like ghost around not like einstein
or like gondi but slimer two things number one slimer was like on the cover of the ecto cooler
box right and he was like right and the the juice was green are we to like i'm thinking about that
now and i wish i'd never let that beverage cross between my lips and slip down my throat
i always assumed it was slimer blood is it slimer milk
did someone grasp his teats firmly but also ghostbusters themed jelly that was green
green probably at some point i feel like there was ecto jelly they had teenager ninja turtles
fruit pies that were green in them oh they were pudding pie green in the middle i guess just
ground up turtles yeah i guess turtles i had two points and i did my first one and i forget
what the second one was don't it always seem to go um uh do you okay slimer we can all okay let
me ask this as a setup slimer was nasty right give me like like a headless ballroom dancer or
something anything anything anything okay so i was nasty anybody anything right do you think
there was ever a moment when one of the ghostbusters was using the bathroom and they
just saw slimer's face like peek in expectantly like just wait because here's what i'm was there
a moment when they were using the bathroom and they had to deal with slimer watching them waiting
to go eat their bathroom this is what i'm that's what i'm what i'm wondering aloud that why would
you wonder that internally why would you wonder that in any assets now everybody has to wonder
okay good i think maybe this is i remembered my second thing if dogs do it there's no reality
which dogs do it please do it even as the little ghost do it everybody's eating bathrooms you meet
a nice girl or guy when you get one of your rare off nights from ghost busting and you go uh uh uh
and up to the room things are going well and what is that mid coitus bursting through the like flying
through the wall it's slimer and he's there to watch you fuck um i remembered my second point
thank god maybe it's like michonne on the walking dead how she carried two two zombies around with
her and so no zombies would mess her like ghosts would come by more listen simon's the worst
aesthetically and um just sort of just sort of having him around it gives you a sense of unease
and also there's all the slime that you have to deal with that's like a full-time job taking care
of slimer um but he's not gonna he's not going to kill you he's not gonna he's not gonna you know uh
he's not gonna inhabit a wolf and attack you right he's just slimer he's just gonna slime around
so so a more malicious spirit a lesion comes by and is like what's up time to get spooky
oh slimer you're already here sorry dog this one's yours later takes off oh so he's the devil you
know yes is he the devil hold on i'm not saying the slimer is the devil but he's definitely of
the devil it's never addressed in i don't think in any of the ghostbusters extended universe
that there are ghosts that are not malicious except for slimer it is like the one chill ghost
but no i would say that slimer is at least one percent malicious because like he eats your food
and gets his detritus leavings all over everything so he's not exactly like benevolent
but they don't seem to ever bust a ghost and then have someone say you busted my grandfather
i didn't i didn't want that you turds there's one in the movies just a jogger he's just he's
just trying to lose a couple ghost lbs and they bust him yeah they do they do and it's hard it's
hard he's working hard out there because when you're a ghost your metabolism doesn't exist
because you don't have a physical body yeah and in the song i always got so sick there's an
invisible man sleeping in your bed who you're gonna call ghostbusters why it's an invisible man
not a ghost too he's just napping he's a sleepy bag he's not bothering you he's not messing with
your shit he's taking a fucking nap and you're gonna bust him mid nap mid nap you jerk my dog
jumps on me sometimes when i'm sleeping and bust him setting bust that dog bust my dog
goes murdering dogs makes you feel good i wish we could i wish you could see that moment when
the ghostbusters are just circling your bed with their proton packs all loaded ready to blast then
one of like egon looks at vancom and it's like does this feel wrong to you i'm having a crisis
of conscience like i'm just gonna bust him like why he's not should we wake him up and see if
he's like a jerk or something yeah should we try talking to him maybe just explain that like
it's not his bed and he's like oh sorry i don't have eyeballs i'm invisible yeah hey by the way
we um we have we have back at our house a living fart that emits goo everywhere do you think maybe
the invisible man could stay with us like it probably wouldn't be that big of an inconvenience
yeah oh so you're suggesting that there can only be one ghost at a time it goes
busters hq so fucking vinkman dies and slimer's like well shit writing's on the wall yeah like
if you want to keep one ghost mascot like wouldn't you upgrade to the invisible man who you don't
have to see or think about you just know he's there at most he's napping in your bed at worst
yeah for sure and not shitting his green slime all over your lunch i hope that there's some
story joke in the new ghostbusters movie where slimer's like smokes weed or something
why why would that be a thing it would be fun that'd be pretty funny it would be good
i would get that on a t-shirt man i love slime i love slimer too i take back every mean thing i
said about him i can't stop thinking about slimer it doesn't make sense do you think they tried to
bust him and it just he was too fast they did justin in the first movie they bust him he's
their first victim right and then they take him back and then he's just there and then he's like
driving a bus what the fuck you professionally bust ghosts and he escaped he's the stupidest
goat he's like he's the least he's the least of them he's the most trappable most trappable most
he's the most travel and then he's driving a bus and rick moranis is just like okay cool what the
fuck oh like after your entire city is in the thrall of vego and mood slime like do you really
want to leave open any window to the paranormal like wouldn't you just insatiate like listen
we've had a lot of fun with this ghost slimer but i think we really need to get serious about
but there's not even a scene where they're like playing checkers with slimer going on a beach
vacation with slimer he's like catching a frisbee in his mouth he's just there he's just a shitty
roommate although i do i do not want to see a scene where everyone's like having fun with slimy
right then they all leave the room and he just turns and looks in the mirror and his eyes like
blaze red as blood like drips from his mouth and then he smacks my knife and he smokes a huge pile
of weed maybe slimer is the only one of the ghostbusters team that knows where to get
weed well hold on let's not be too hasty i've got i've got my uh my uh chronic vego ain't
gonna smoke us out gozer ain't gonna smoke us out slimer he's not a great roommate he's a
gatekeeper not the not the weed haver what do you think oscar's gonna get us some weed he's a baby
does he make sense he's in school right now he can't get us well actually he probably would
have to hook up schools today it would be a really nice call back if they cast the baby
that played oscar as slimer in the next movie don't you think that would be a nice call back
do you think slimer i'll have kids in the next movie he's been sliming all over town justin
you know what i mean you gotta pay the piper wear a condom slimer where where would he put it
on his everything what happened to sliver didn't you guys used to have a ghost here uh this is a
scene for the next movie okay what happened to sliver did you guys used to have a ghost to live
here well he got too old and he died that's what happens to ghost and then sliver like peeks up
through the floor just kidding ah it's me slimer i can talk now i sound a lot like harvey feisty
slimer what a character what a what a great what a great character slimer is
do you think he had a room or do you think they just like made him float
like just like he probably doesn't sleep so what's he doing during the night just
sitting down in the office by himself just waits he's like the the dog in
futurama just waiting for them to wake up i'll see you guys in the morning i guess
anybody want to sit around play this is a sad lonely existence for slimer because he loves
them right and they love tolerate him right at most at best can one of you can one of you guys
turn the tv on just so i can have something to watch some white noise or something just leave
on in pr my big so lonely my big mushy fingers can't work the remote so lonely so cold so dead
i i was married when i was alive i had kids i was i was the mayor it's like the dread pirate
robber it's every night they're like good night slimer sleep well uh would like to bust you in
the morning like he he's on concert if he leaves the refrigerator open one of them might get a
wild hair and just bust him i would like to bust him often and then just let him back out to be
like just remember we could leave you in there anytime fuck i fly right turn it around right
the ghostbusters obviously it's insane that they have a ghost that lives at their house
it's crazy this is a debate team that point has been executed that that point is what's wrong
with slimer that of all the world that he could haunt he haunts the building full of people that
could kill him it's like he's got stockholm syndrome at this point it's real it's really
what it is he should haunt anywhere else like where people are exclusively devoted to busting
him on some level slimer believes he deserves to be busted he does he wants to be busted it's his
fetish it's the only way he can feel he's been a ghost for 453 years right in my fan fiction
and the only way that he can feel now is to be busted 50 shades of close to being busted like
dancing the razor's edge of being busted yeah so that's why he's being such a shitty roommate he's
not a bad guy but he needs to antagonize him just enough so that they bust him a little you maybe
could say that busting makes him feel good exactly maybe he likes the smug sense of superiority he
gets every time they drag in a trap full of another guy he's like a bitch he's out there
he's got his ear to the ground he's their confidential informer he's got his ear to the
ground his his ectoplasm ear and then he's like i hear there's a ghost down on 53 in maine who's
jogging and they're like we'll get him slimer and that's how he stays out he is a traitor to his
people maybe the reason he can't like he has to stay with him is no ghosts will have him no
he burned those riches no those bridges are gone maybe it's just because other ghosts would beat
the hell out of him like he's a he's not safe there he can do he can listen if you need a
prank done slime is your guy oh what if it's like what if it's like animals like if you feed the
like wild animals and they become like oh now now they'll starve to death because now they're just
so used to people like feeding them cheetos that they don't know how to hunt anymore slimer has
become like domesticated he wouldn't survive out in the wild he doesn't know how to haunt anymore
like he just he doesn't have the chops he couldn't spook anybody couldn't spook a fly let me hit you
too with this idea ashton kutcher and slimer in prank house and they're roommates and they live
together and slimer comes home from work and ashton's bedroom door's open so slimer goes in
he opens it up kutcher's making love to a young hollywood starlet he looks up and yells gotcha
and then slimer says oh did you and then ashton kutcher looks down and it's not a young hollywood
starlet he's making love to it's a big pile of slime roll credits roll credits roll title screen
directed by martin scorsese it's coming soon turner and hooch too it's it's prank house
it's called prank it was called prank house the show is called prank house and it's on usa we've
got a character before royal paints it's before and during burn notice
if you see psych you have watched too long
it's it's it's in the bottom right corner
prank house is our new series
it kind of looks like in the burned in like you left an image on too long
just catching about three percent you'll see some some spy stuff if you look closely it's
on in the background it's in every tv it's on at midnight when it's raining you turn
your tv off and you can see slimer and ashton kutcher it's called the midnight prank house
so this has been our um our ghostbusters fan cast my brother my brother and me
shit um and i hope you had a good time thanks again to our sponsors usa a nature network
thanks to nature box you can order hundreds of great tasting healthy snacks go to naturebox.com
slash my brother to sign up for a free sampler box of great tasting healthy snacks yeah right
yeah somebody else say something uh we're really excited we have a huge announcement uh we're
going to be performing at la pod fest this year september did you guys look at the rest of the
lineup for la pod fest yeah i know i'm late to game year what are we doing here it's sick um and
now here's another exciting thing not only were we doing a live my brother my brother and me we
will be doing the first ever and possibly only live adventure zone um if you go to la pod fest
and here's the most exciting part y'all i know a lot of people are like la we i can't get to la
i i don't live anywhere near la good news you can watch it live they're going to be live streaming
the whole weekend and you can do it for just 20 if you go to la pod fest.com and use the coupon
code either brother or zone on checkout you get five dollars off and you can watch like all of
the shows live streaming and it benefits and stuff to that if you want to just direct route
the season remember if you go to mbnbam.tumblr.com the top post there is is all about this explain
has the codes and and and what all so we're doing a show and we're doing adventure zone we're doing
my bim bam uh but with that streaming ticket you can watch all the shows so girl on guy the aisha
tyler podcast indoor kids never not funny thrilling adventure hour thrilling adventure
hour wtf with mark maron like there's there's there's so the giant bomb cast is doing a show
there which i'm very excited to catch like yeah there's so much stuff you should know just make
sure you use the coupon code either brother or zone uh so they know that we sent you and it
gives us a couple bucks in our pocket yeah that helps too um we got other live shows too coming
up in portland seattle and vancouver seattle or uh portland is sold out unfortunately uh they the
shows are the last weekend in august uh if you want tickets there's still some available go to
bit.ly slash mbnbam seattle and bit.ly slash van mbnbam i also want to say thank you we've gotten
some really awesome stuff in the uh in the p.o box at least in the west coast one uh ricardo
sent us some awesome coasters a while ago i use mine every time i record i want to say thanks to
knoll who sent me a board game that i cannot wait to try out he said it's one of his favorites
and i'm on a huge board game kick right now so i'm really excited to try it i want to say thanks
to jill who wrote me a really long really lovely incredibly nice letter and i really appreciate it
uh and ryan sent me an awesome t-shirt from his uh martial arts studio and i am wearing it right
now is it helping you kick is it helping you it is helping me kick it is helping me head butt it
is helping me chop um we got a uh postcard in the east coast p.o box p.o box 54 high into west virginia
25706 got uh some cheese coupons from dana and sean got a postcard from serbia from adam and
shelley franklin uh got uh let's see got another postcard here from uh boston and sailor steve sent
us one a beautiful save the date uh from john and julie doherty on their upcoming nuptials same to
uh christy and eric who got married back in may so thanks for that congratulations on your uh
graduation to uh sarah poppus who graduated and sent us a an announcement of that uh similar
congratulations to robert william ashley his bachelor of science degree uh anna and david
got married and invited us thank you all so much for that and uh you are all the uh the best so
thank you if you have something for us you send it to p.o box 34 1769 341769 los angeles california
90034 or what was the east coast one again juice i already gave it i don't want to give it a gift
okay fair enough fair enough um also if you would like to have a message in the money zone you can
go to maximumfund.org forward slash jumbo tron but fair warning at this point we're backed up
a couple months so it's better if you just accept that it may be a while before we get to it but we
will get to all of them we will do all of them we promise we're going a little bit long here but i
just want to leave a note here that you should go check out all the other shows on the maximum fun
network uh there's some new max fun shows there's a show called we got this with uh hal lublin and
mark gagliardi uh and travis you are involved in a new podcast project can you tell me about it
yeah uh i'm producer and you will occasionally hear my voice on the show as well it's called
can i pet your dog with renee culvert and allegra ringo and it's for people who love dogs love
talking about dogs or just like love the idea of people who love dogs and every week we talk about
dogs that we met that week we talk about uh dog news sometimes we have guests on on our first
episode uh we had lynn manuel miranda on to talk about his dog and how they found their dog on a
beach in the dominican republic which is insane and also uh you can follow us on twitter cipyd
podcast or just search can i pet your dog on facebook enjoy the facebook group because people
are constantly sending us and posting pictures of their dogs and it's like becoming my favorite
thing yeah it's like the best so i'm gonna burn through the rest of shit justin has a youtube
series called things i bought at sheets i wore the shirt for things i bought at sheets yesterday and
it's very comfortable and the show's very good travis send me a picture of you wearing that shirt
you still don't believe that i bought it huh no i just want to put you to the show i see uh uh travis
has a podcast called trends like these eight does with his friend brent uh and you can find that on
itunes and pot and wherever podcasts are i don't have any other things going on right now i've got
a lot on my plate that's frankly none of your business watch the monster factory videos that
griffin and justin do on youtube oh shit you can also we gotta do one of those tomorrow dude it's
been a long time you can also check out a bunch of my brother my brother and me videos on youtube
just search mbnba him we have a whole channel animated stuff shareable shorts uh go on itunes
rate review subscribe to my brother my brother and me and all the other podcasts you listen to
uh and also thanks to john roderick and the long winters for the use of their theme song
it's a departure off of the album putting the days to bed that election his election for seattle city
council is coming up so if you live in the eighth district look them up think about it
think about your options final yahoo sent in by ira ray are you ira ray who wants to know thank
you ira ray it's by yahoo answers user dumb blonde whoops who asks is cowabunga a cuss word uh i'm
slimer i'm rick moranis i am the pile of slime upon which ashton kutcher is dedicating his love
this has been my brother my brother me kiss your dad square out of lips
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
hi i'm lisa hannawalt and i'm emily heller and if you're not listening to our podcast baby
geniuses you're missing out on stuff like camille nandiani solving the zodiac murders
oh who's like would you ever go to a friend and you're like hey could you
lick all these lick all these envelopes for me you'd be like you're a serial killer
definitely i'm leaving right now guy brandom talking about ruth bader ginsburg um and it was
it was just a great moment of like oh no i'm here boys like i'm on this side of the bench
megan amram talking about intimidating baristas just feel like they're always in character
like they're always in character as like cool hipster girl and i just want to break through
that barrier plus every week we explore a new wikipedia page and talk to a crazy expert in the
field of nonsense well any any hack can make you not have a boner i mean that's it's about how you
do it right and we're the only podcast with regular updates about martha stewart's pony
or your money back we're not gonna give them their money back are we no let's keep it yeah
listen to our show every other monday on maximum fun yay