If you change your mind, I'm the first in line Honey I'm still free, take a chance on me
If you need me, let me know, I'm gonna be around If you got no place to go, when you're feeling down
If you're all alone, with a pretty verse
Carve another notch in your bedpost, you've done it, you've made time in your week for us
My brother, my brother and me
This is an advice show for the modern era, I am Justin McElroy
I'm Travis McElroy, I'm Griffin McElroy
And this has been my brother, my brother and me, the end
Have a great week
Have a great week, it's the beginning, don't worry about it
Can we address?
Okay
Just right from the get
I'm addressing it
We fucked up
Take it a head on
Fucked up
We fucked up
We done fucked up
We done y'all wrong
This show is like two weeks old, it's like a two week old infant
And we went ahead and we done skipped a week
Done skipped a week
Can we assign blame?
Memorial Day, what's up?
So we're blaming Memorial Day for our malfeasance
Memorial Day caused us to forget
Yeah, we forgot to make the show for you
Right
Yeah, I'm eternally sorry
I want to apologize because I expected like we skip a week
And then all the love falls out the bottom
And we lose all the love
But I did a Twitter search for the title of our show yesterday
As I want to do
And still just a lot of people support
A lot of questions, not a lot of anger
Mostly just sorrow
And I want to apologize
A deep hunger was the theme
I want to personally deeply apologize to little Badkins
He's a way fish young lad who lives on the streets
He was heart broke
He was, I'm so sorry Badkins
We'll send you some new matchsticks
Can we just say, make it official
Episode 008 right now, official decree
We will never miss another week ever again
Until we die
Until we die, and even then we'll get two more shows out
Yeah, ghost shows
Here's our first question
Comes to us from FormSpring
FormSpring questions are anonymous
If you want to send a question to us
Listen to the end of the show and we'll tell you how
I've been seeing this girl lately
And every time we have plans to hang out she bails on me
If we don't make plans
And I tell her I'm just going to show up
She's cool with it
Is this a case of plans are meant to be broken
Or is it something more
Oh my friend
I didn't know that was an idiom
No dude, plans are meant to be broken
No actually, that's kind of counterintuitive
To what a plan is
They're actually meant to people do things
If plans
What's the difference between making plans
And telling her you're going to show up
Is that not a plan?
Is that not a thing?
That seems like an awfully narrow distinction
I think it seems like if you and I
Should go somewhere
Okay cool
I'm not going to do that
I'm going to be at a place
Are you going to be at that same place?
We'll see
I think maybe she's just not
Necessarily
Into this relationship right now
Or maybe she just loves
Scavenger hunts
Have we considered that?
Maybe she likes to pretend it's serendipitous
She doesn't want to meet you
She wants to find you
And a lot of the times
We try to tell ourselves with stuff like that
Maybe she's just the type of person
That breaks plans
And she's all willy nilly and crazy
No, she just doesn't want to hang out with you
She is the type of person
That doesn't particularly care for you
So much anymore
Plans are meant to be broken
Hey they are
My GF
I'm a different person now
She's always wanting to go out to dinner
But she expects me to romantically choose
Where to eat and pay
Despite the fact that she pretty much
Always eats steak no matter where we go
Also money is tight
Should I cave to her demands?
My suggestion
Plan on a really fancy dinner
And tell her about it and then don't go
And she'll look at you like what?
And you'll be like plans are meant to be broken
Can I just say how much I love
The concept of romantically choosing
Where to eat dinner
Like baby girl
I've been thinking about it for a long time
But I think
Golden corral
Golden corral girl
You want to get some of them hot buttery rolls
Sensual rolls
Um no
She wants you to be in charge
Like a man say this is where we're going tonight
Steco
Also start calling your
Call your GF Steco
She'll love it
Yeah and also
Don't let your girlfriend eat steak everywhere you go
What's the matter with her
It's not healthy
Take her to a vegan restaurant
And see if her head implodes
Next time she buys steak just cough
And be like please choose another option
Cough
Please choose the chicken
She'll have the chicken
Are you dating a caveman maybe
Or a feral wolf
Maybe you should romantically order for her
She'll have the chicken
Thank you Garcon
As dry as possible please
Another form spring question
Does my best man have to be a man
My closest confidants
Are all female
And I have just casual mostly
Uncaring relationships with the majority of
Guys in my life
His closest what
Confidants
That's how they say it
In France
I don't
I don't know that's awfully progressive
I don't have a problem with it one bit
Yeah
No you wouldn't
Well I have a lot of female friends
Right but we'll never have to deal with this
Because we've already agreed that we're going to be
Each other's best man
This is correct
We've signed that blood pact
I forget how it breaks down
Alright
What if like Steve Gutenberg
Rolls up the day of my wedding and is like
Hey I've got like two hours to kill
Could I do it? That's fine
Would you understand Justin?
Oh what if for the Goots?
Yeah when the Goots in there
The only thing I would wish is that we could be co-best men
And I could go to things remembered
And have a co-best men
Necklace made that would be broken into
Two parts with two separate chains
So it would be like a dead hooker
Or a death stripper
And one of you would get one part and one of you would get the other
And when you link it up it shows
It shows
That you are co-best men right
Also I want to kill a hook with Steve Gutenberg
Once again we've created
The greatest movie idea ever
The new Steve Gutenberg
Vehicle co-best men
That sounds like
An Adam Sandler movie
No it's Steve Gutenberg and Dave Coulier
Kevin James and Adam Sandler in co-best men
Hey guys
You can do it
Can we give this guy some real advice
Yeah
I think it's okay
Yeah it's fine
But make her wear a tux
Hey can I say this? It's your wedding so tell everybody to eat a bacon
Yeah
In this scenario would you
Have to refer to her as best man still?
I would say best woman
I think I would still go with best man
I was kidding about the tux
But I think
Talk to your fiance first
Gender switching
Is not that
Sydney had
Guys in her party but they weren't bridesmaids
They were bridesmen
Can you have groomsmen?
I had to walk down the aisle
With one of them
It may be best maid
Best lady
You should probably marry your best lady
You have to realize
That's what's going to happen
Day of the wedding
Right before you get cold feet
Your lady friend
Confesses her
Your wife might have a problem with that
That's what I'm saying
Talk to your fiance first
My official advice is I don't know
Is your best woman going to be
Jennifer Lopez?
If so you're definitely
Going to switch over at the last second
Hey you know
Guys I have this problem
Every time I talk to some stranger on the phone
They mistake me for a woman
What can I do in the future to prevent this?
I don't drink whiskey or smoke so forget about that
Yeah are you 12?
That you don't drink whiskey or smoke?
Maybe pick up one of those and we'll meet you halfway
Could I suggest
Either saying your name
But what if your name is like Aaron
Double A Aaron
And that doesn't help the matter at all
So to cut any confusion I would say
Just call a person up
And they say hello
And you say hi this is Aaron
Man can we
Hi this is Aaron I'm a fella
And let's keep going
I'm known dude Aaron
You should do
My name's Aaron got a wiener can we talk?
My suggestion would obviously
Be to talk like Christian Bale
From the Batman movies
You reach Aaron's residence
I'm a Russian chicken
I want a chick
I'm gonna wear an
Augie Paz
Or just go with it
That's not your problem if they think you're a woman
That's their problem
And their embarrassment when they realize
The faux pas they've made that's a power play dude
Some people are paid
Big money to live life as a woman
And they get the full taste of it for free
If you could do
You could leverage that if you were
In the
Telemarketing industry
Leverage it in the sense that
I think female telemarketers
Probably are more successful than dudes
Cause they can call up lonely dudes
And you know
Get a foot in the door
Telemarketresses?
Telemarketrinas
Yeah just go with it
I've known a girl for a while
And since I got back from college for summer
We've been hanging out a lot
But I'm not sure if I can make it a relationship
Because we go to school 100 miles apart
Advice
100 miles ain't nothing
100 miles is a
Pretty long distance actually
No it's like 2 hours
I say don't date a girl
Who lives farther away from you
I was gonna say that you could walk
To but that's
Probably better
Could you throw in a pinch
I could throw a shot put
100 to 150 yards
That's why my wife lives with me
In my house
How far do you think you could throw a baseball?
About 5 feet
50 feet
You think you could clear it from the mount?
I'd get it at home play
Oh yeah I'd get it at home play
Funky of the year and they'd hire me on
Funky butt loving
Funky butt loving?
What?
Here's my advice
Would you give him a high stinky cheddar?
Yes I would
This young person has already
Answered their own question
You don't think you can make it a relationship
Guess what? You're not gonna
You would know
He's unsure
Yeah but he would know
If it's a cross country trip
If 2 hours isn't worth it to you
Then I think you've already answered your own question
Real life
Is gonna work really hard
In every relationship
To try to tear it down
If you're not sold on it from the jump
It's not gonna pan out
If she's the one
You wouldn't be asking us this question
If you were sure about it
You wouldn't trust us to the reality of a long distance relationship
Is way harder than you think it would be
100 miles apart
You know where I live 100 miles from?
Kings Island, I don't get there
And you love Kings Island, that's the relationship
I do, I love the Viking
Fury, I wanna make that relationship
Beautiful boat
Let's do one from Yahoo
This one comes from Chris D
Chris R?
Not Chris R, Chris D
Please help
Where should we make out?
Well, me and my girlfriend
Are both going into 9th grade
We're both 14 and she wants to make out
Where should we make out?
And this is my first make out
So any tips would be great, thanks
I heard like during a movie
In the theaters, but I don't know
Any places would be great, thanks
Easy 10 points
I think if any places are great
You should stop worrying about it so much
Dude, you can't
Has it been so long
Since you went into 9th grade
And we're about to have your first make out sesh
That you can't recall the mortal
Terror that is involved with
Finding a locale for this
To go down
This is hard, now it's suddenly hard
Yeah, cause I can recall
Exactly, and I also recall
The
Unorthodox
Solution that I came up with
Oh Christ
It was in Ritter Park
Which is a park
That was a few blocks from my house
In our hometown of Huntington, West Virginia
And there's a
There's a little
Concave, like a little
Circle
A little stone circle
Of benches that's kind of hidden
Beneath the shady trees
But
I think that that circle was
Constructed as
A monument to
AIDS
Yes, it's the AIDS circle
Which is probably
I don't know
Disrespectful
Maybe not romantic, maybe not the most
Romantic thing I've ever done in my life
But you have to get your make out on
And you have to do it in a place where your folks won't catch you
Did you wrap it up?
Cause that would have been disrespectful
Yeah, definitely, I played it smart
Even at 14
I find dens
Dens and basements
Dens and basements are awesome
Friends tree houses
Parents can't stay up forever, dawg
They're old
I'm almost parent age, trust me
You can't stay up that long
You'll outlast them
I don't think I've
I never, ever, ever got fresh in a movie
If I see you making out in a movie
I'm gonna fucking smack you
If you're gonna do it
Sit in the back
Cause people paid so much money to go to that movie
They don't need to hear you're smacking
But it's in 3D
Here's the thing
Right now you're paying 12 bucks
To get into a movie
15 bucks, don't waste that money
Watch the damn movie
That's 15 dollars
You're halfway to a cheap hourly motel
Unless the movie
Is really bad and you can add
Some humor to it
You know, like
Train my dragon
If you're in the middle of it
I like that one
There are people like me that will sit
Uncomfortably close to you
So that you are not able to do that
On the note that I just brought up
I wouldn't do it in like a kid's movie
Don't go to like a generated movie
Some of us have
Made out during Toy Story 2
Yeah
It was creep
Flubber
Dear podcast
Okay, kind of inhuman
Last night I went to my friend's
21st birthday party when suddenly his girlfriend
Who was very drunk told me
She had feelings for me
I don't feel the same about her
So my question is how do I or even
Do I tell my friend
Okay, hold on
You're at
Your friend's birthday party
His lady tells you
She has feelings for you
You don't have feelings for you
Guess what you got buddy
You got a little something I like to call a non-problem
You do not have an issue
That you need to address
Here's the important
Little segment there
She was very drunk
Doesn't matter
I say things
Say things you wouldn't believe
It's astonishing how many questions we get
Where my answer is just pack up
And move away and never talk to anyone
Involved in a scenario again
Because that's literally the only
The only solution I have for this
Maybe that's why I've been such a globetrotter these past few years
You keep messing up social
Situations and you gotta move
In my mind this is unfixable
And you have to get out of there
It's called a global reset
You can either stick around, don't say anything
And then have it be awkward forever
Or you can tell your friend and he'll get mad
At you and
You know
Here's what I'd do if I was you
Don't
Don't say anything
But frequently
Ask your friend how his relationship
Is going and then when he answers
You say oh yeah? Cool
I guess
Can I suggest a honeypot
Scenario
Where you tell the
Friend and then if he doesn't believe
You'd be like no no no check it out
And then you
You get the friend drunk
No well no that's exploitative
But you know
You were gonna suggest a baiting situation
Yes get her to confess those feelings again
I like that
Like you're wearing a wire
Or your friend is like hidden in the closet
And ask her about the new package
And ask her where Omar is
I assume that's a joke
Cause we haven't washed the wire
Yeah
You need to talk to your friend's girlfriend is what you need to do
No you don't need to tell
Oh shit people don't want to hear about things
They don't want to talk about them
Your two options are honeypot or move the fuck away
Change your name
I'm gonna switch these gmail
Gmail questions cause these people have their names on them
Ender
I know right
Ender writes tons of people I went to high school
With are already about to get married
Or are married and I've only been out of high school
For two years what am I missing here
A girlfriend
Yeah let me throw in a little side note here
This email comes to us from Utah
I don't know if that changes
Your outlook on this but it does for me
So they get married
Like six years earlier than
Probably the median age in the nation
I think that's a fair
Figure
What you're missing is a partner to go through life with
And you are going to die alone
Ender you're not missing anything
You're 20 years old
You're kicking it living it large in Utah
Yeah
Going to jazz games
Listening to jazz games and
Listening to jazz and
Going to jazz basketball games
Just jazzing
In general
You need to stop all that jazz and get yourself a girlfriend
I don't
Are you going to college
Well he didn't say he's going to college
He said he's been out of high school for two years
Just pair up quick
Cause your options are dwindling everyday
I'm probably the only person from Huntington
Who's not married
And I
I'm so fucking lonely
All the time Ender do it just find someone
Anyone
You know one of my friends once told me
Who was married he said marriage isn't a goal
Marriage isn't something you work towards
It's something that happens
So
It is a goal in the sense that if you don't cross it
By the time you die then you've failed it
Yes
Whatever it's a goal if you don't cross it by the time you're 30
It comes out
Speed it up Ender
Matt writes to us from gmail
Says myself and my friend
And my brother and me
That's not true just myself and my friend
Myself and my friend recently went for the same job
And he got it ahead of me
Do you have any advice for how to
Deal with this
Yeah keep your mouth shut Matt
Move to a different town
Just move away dude
No I mean that sucks
That sucks pretty royally but
You gotta ask yourself what would he do
If the scenario was switch
And it sounds like he's a really good friend
And that he wouldn't
Cause a big stink about it
I think in any situation even if he would do that
You gotta be the bigger man
And if he's really your friend you gotta be happy for him
You know what I mean
Yeah
At the end of the day what is more important the job you went for
And the friendship with this kid
Well the job
Probably
It sounds like a great gig
With a nice big salary and lots of benefits
And also Matt
He's probably more qualified than you
He probably got it based on merit
He deserves it
He earned it What did you do
Wow
Good jobs Matt
Can we give Matt an internship
At NBNBAM Industries
Matt is the first intern of NBNBAM Industries
What's he gonna do
He's gonna promote the show
Is it paid
He's gonna sell tribes and away slavery
Can we scrounge some money together
To give this guy a salary do you think
If I get any money I'm gonna spend it on a Facebook
App for our show
Yeah that's true
6x9
Who's a known gmail user
Asks I've recently moved
To the states from Australia
And I'd like to find a low calorie
Beer to drink I have no problem
Sampling from your wide selection of microbrews
On occasion but I'd really like a nice beer to drink
Regularly and I don't need the extra
Calories I'm looking for a taste sensation
But something that tastes better
Than brackish water would be nice
Any suggestions PBR
He asked PBR
Get out of this website
Get off the podcast
I mean you can't go wrong with an MGD-64
How about I slap both of you
In the mouth
That's the only low calorie beer I mean
No okay let me
Hip you guys because you're
Like children you're like an infant
Tickling yourself with a razor
Number one
Is your an
Infant tickling yourself with a razor
The best low
Calorie beer is Guinness
Which clocks in at
125 calories per bottle
That's high calorie
That's not comparatively high
Calories the idea that beer
Has calories in it
Is astonishing to me
I don't know why I've never been able
If you drink too much beer you get fat
My brain has never been able to
It's a liquid
It's not a food
Have you tried pork chunk
Ale
I don't think it's real
I would say that
Your top three
I think Guinness is good
Right after that I think the
Two best light beers you can get
Are
Sam Adams Light and
So if it has light on it
Then that's what that means
You would be surprised
I would actually check calorie
Comparisons
A lot of those light beers
Are not as low calorie
As
Like a Guinness or something like that
Guinness is low in calories
I'll tell you what I had a lot of
When I was up Shytown
Is that light?
Would you say that's light
I would say that's probably
Ripping with calories
It felt airy in my mouth
It had an airy quality to it
I would say go with that
And don't worry about the calories
Because you deserve it
Girl
You're worth it girl
130 calories per bottle
Not bad at all
Also
Jack and Diet Coke
It saved you a bunch of calories
Dominic
Says I'm trying to be more outgoing
And looking for more venues to meet people
And possible relationships
Would church groups be a good start?
Even though I'm not particularly
Churchy
Or do you have any other suggestions?
Okay Dominic
That won't be a great conversation starter
Hey what's going on
Mallory
No I'm not particularly churchy
I'm not churchy
This is apparently working for you
I think so
I made a lot of good connections
In
Church
My old church
I actually went out to dinner last night
With old Alex White
Good people
I don't know if he's thinking
About love
Relationships
I think maybe he's just talking about friendships
And if that's the way to go
Now if you're looking for someone
Who's going to give up to pussy
God
Well
There it is
Speaking of
Speaking of not particularly churchy
This yahoo answers question
Comes to us from Dick
Oh man
Dick asks
If there is no oxygen in space
Then how does the sun burn?
Answer that atheists
Christians 1 Atheists 0
What a sick bird
He's got you there
Game over
Fuck
Ah shit
I don't have an answer for that
I know you don't
Hey do you guys see what Dick said?
Fuck we're all ruined
There are
Like 300
Theology professors across the country
Who just like
Exploded
Oh wait a minute
Dick just solved it for all of us
Everyone knows that the sun burns cause the devil lives inside
Yup the devil lives in the sun
Duh what's up
It's your first night at the rodeo apparently
I have to thank
I did a little bit of
Crowd sourcing that question
Was actually sent to me by
Godly is the person's name
Who sent that to me so thanks Godly shout outs
Shout outs
I've been having problems
With expressing my anger
Says Sean from Gmail
And I was wondering if you could help
I'm a 17 year old New Zealander and over here
Any showing of anger to anyone
Will often result in a physical fight
I have the problem that I seem to
Either bottle it up
I've been meditating late
And it seems to help a little in thinking about things
Or completely fly off the handle and hurt people badly
I was wondering if you guys could help
Hey Sean
Hi
Sean
You're a
You're talking to three guys
Who are raised Baptist if you're looking
For guys who are telling you to not bottle
It up you've come to the wrong podcast
Keep it inside
Or get to your bottle
Breaks and then you get a bigger bottle
I don't
I don't know
I can't I think the last time
I got angry was when I was
I was
Making a left turn onto
The interstate and someone behind me
Was upset by the fact that I was making
A left turn so they passed me and gave me
The finger and I just wanted to get out
Of my car and
Just
Hurt them
I'm so bad at it see
Would you rather be Sean the guy who
Expresses his
Feeling in a healthy way or Sean
The guy who at any second
Could fucking flip and fight somebody
I kind of like the last
Sean yeah right
That Sean's cool that Sean's crazy
Like Sean's crazy
Nobody knows what the fuck Sean's about to do
What's Sean doing now
Sean's drinking everybody stops
Looks at Sean real slow
And maybe this time Sean laughs it off
But next time fucking Sean
Is basically a human
Version of Kerplunk
Yeah only the marbles are his
Rage and every time you
Scuff his pumas you're pulling a stick
Out
And once you step on that
Poo that wrong time you're sunk
Also Sean in real advice
You're 17 dude you're a wash of hormones
And emotion yeah completely normal
You will calm down as you get older
Meditation's the best way to go
Just think about everything someone's
Scuffing your pumas not a time
To pull the stick out no if you
I mean if he's 17
If you don't let that anger out
Then you'll get really bad acne
That's where
Those hormones gotta work
Them out of your body little anger volcanoes
I actually saw
A dermatologist when I was 17
I had really bad skin she said
You got lots of anger volcanoes on your face
Thanks
What's Sean
Don't hurt anybody Sean
Everybody
Don't follow our advice ever
Dude have you guys heard about Cody
From Gmail where he's going
Next weekend no
He's taking a trip up with his
Family up to Canada
Oh Canada I like it up there. Homeland of
Rafi
I love to drink
And I'm 19 years old which means
I can drink in Canada however
My mom hates that I drink
How can I get shit faced in Canada
Without my mother getting upset
Cody
I have great news for you
This is a wonderful
Time
To start practicing the art of
Flaskmanship
She don't need to know anything
She turns away for 30
10 8 seconds
You got that flask out you pound it
You're done
I would say also that it sounds like
Laws aren't keeping you from drinking
So much in the US of A
So what's the concern
Well there's a difference
There's a difference between
Our laws
And statutes and mama
Law mama law
I think he might be afraid of
Transgressing
On mama laws
Which I understand
Maybe what he's saying
Is the reason he's excited about drinking is because
It's legal right what I'm saying
Is it doesn't seem to be slowing down
Although I'm sure the beer in Canada is so
Dope
Cody why do you need to get shit faced
As you put it
Can you not just
Have a beer or two
Do you have a
Do you have an eye opener Cody
Do you ever have an eye opener do you ever drink alone
Again I
Would you say your mom has a problem
With it do you mean she keeps having interventions
For you because that's a different thing altogether
I've got
A Canada fetish so I imagine
Everything is cooler in Canada maybe
Getting drunk in Canada is like the sweetest
Thing ever like maybe a mount he sees you
On the street and instead of arresting
You like he gets off his horse he's like hey go
Ahead just take one around the block
Winnie
Maybe
Getting fucked up and eating poutine
Is like you know
A religious experience
Joel writes to us
From Gmail he says I'm in a bit of a
Predicament I recently moved to a new
Town and I only know a few people I'm not
In college so I can't meet people that way
And I'm 19 so I can't meet people in bars
Can you guys put your heads together and
Give me some pointers on how to meet people and make friends
Joel started the D&D group
That's a really good I'm actually
You're joking but I met a lot of people
That way I'm not joking I think that would be fun
Give a call to Dominic and go to church
With him sometime
He just wants to tell you about a friend of his his name
Is Jesus on the serious on on Justin's
First point there's a website called meet up
You can use that to find groups of people
That have your interest maybe not D&D maybe knitting
Maybe scrapbooking maybe that's
Joel's game you can find a group
And do that thing with them
I wish he had told us what city he was in
And then we could have some MBMBAM
Like friendship connections
Here's what we'll do Joel go to Facebook
Go on our appreciation group
Put some stats
Some things you're into the city you're into
We'll make that connection
Height weight eye color
Basically a match.com profile
But put it in our Facebook group
And then see if you can find any
People should be using our Facebook group for friendship
And love connections I know
I wish more people were doing that
I want by our next show to have at least one
Piece of verifiable evidence
Of two kids who found each other
On the Facebook group got together
And fucked
What kind of verifiable evidence
Are you looking for? Kicks
Jesus
Here's one
Yahoo answer also sent
To me by Action Allen
Thank you Action Allen this one comes from Kyle S
He asks
I need a list of the
Most practical kicks
What?
What? Oh just you wait
I want a list of kicks
All must be practical and where they would land
So far the obvious ones
Front kick to groin
Mid area head
I'm sorry
Side kick to groin
Mid area I personally don't like
This one because it's hard to see
Round kick
To lower leg back of knee
All suggestions are welcome
I'm about to kick the spirit
Yeah how about
Below to your subconscious
Hey listen
Why do you need this list?
Sean what are you doing?
Guys can we get
He's got the front he's got the side he's got the round
Have you considered a donkey kick?
A back kick as it's
Referred to it in some circles where
An assailant comes behind you
You can usually kick the front
Of their knee or groin area
And that will completely take them
Out of the fight all together
Have you tried a spin kick?
Spin kick's really good
That's the coolest kick you can do
When the point of your boot goes into their
Butthole
A butthole kick
A butthole boot knocker
A well aimed butthole kick
Have you tried perhaps like a
Ryu style bicycle kick where you fly
Through the air for 10 seconds and squeal
Like a pig? How about an awesome kick
Where you literally take their head off
And one cleans it
Have you tried the mental kick
Where you don't actually kick
But they think that you do
And then in three days their stocks crash
What about the kick where you
Take your foot off and make the guy smell your foot
Like in a funny movie
The Zoans
That Zoan movie. That's pretty funny
Have you tried a taint kick?
What?
A taint kick where you kick them square in the tank
And it lifts them off of the ground and into the air
By about three feet
That one's really hard to do. Could I suggest a kick kick?
Which is where you kick their kick
And disrupt their kick
They're meant to kick
You gotta be careful though because if you don't time it right
They'll kick your kick and then you're fucked
That's a kick kick kick
The triple kick. The KKK
Have you tried a punch kick?
Which is where you take your shoe off
And put it on your hand
And then you punch them with it
Oh god
That's a pretty
Comprehensive list I feel
Yeah I think that's all the kicks
That's all the kicks I know about I guess
What about the junior kick where you kick their kid?
Yeah that's sometimes more painful
In the long run I mean
What do you think? One more question?
Before the last question? Yeah
You got time for one more? Griffin you pick
You pick this time
This one comes from Allison via Gmail
I like a sociable smart
Funny nerdy guy
But I don't know where to find them
Why'd you pick this one? Weird
I don't want to show up at a magic game and be laughed out
Because I'm playing with my merfolk deck
And can't remember all of the rules
Or be ignored because I'd rather watch someone play the horror games
For example Fatal Frame 2
So that I can cover my eyes when it gets scary
How do you suggest I go about finding
These guys without running into the creepy stalkers
On Craigslist? Do they even exist?
Say it
Griffin you are fucking adorable
You can tell me how girls get your attention
Sorry okay well thanks
Well thank you
This one was a confidence booster
For me
A little pep in my step
The pep in your step kick is good too
Yeah
That one hurts really bad
Whoa that has something extra
He kicked me right in my pep
Wow right in the pep
I will say that
In situations like this
I don't think
I don't think ladies need to use their
Their nerd charm to try and attract
Fellas because their usual old
Feminine wiles will
Serve them pretty well
Yeah I think actually you're going to attract the wrong
Kind of guy by being outwardly nerdy
Yeah maybe that's just me
Here's the thing
The nerdy guys they already want to go out with you
Yeah
Because according to your email you're pretty
And they're guys
They're probably lonely
Here's the trick though
The trick is you've got to find the right kind of nerdy guy
Because
God love them you may not want to end up
A lot of nerdy guys can be kind of socially
Eh retarded
And I don't mean that in the
Retarded sense I mean socially retarded
Like slow
Inept just comically inept
Look at our emails
Just pick like the top 5 from the people who
Email us every week and we'll send them to you
No kidding
Yeah not a joke
I think the MBMBAM community is a good
Place for you to cast
Your proverbial net
Yeah that should pan out real good
Just go on our Facebook group and post a
Picture of yourself and say you're looking to meet the eyes
We don't have time to read his question
But we got a question
From a gentleman
We've been debating how to pronounce his name
Khem Lewis
I think Khem
Lewis sent us a picture after we
We mentioned that we got a ton of questions
From people who don't know how girls work
And he sent us
Pictures of himself and his girlfriend
And he looks like a really dope
Like a kind of guy
Like a dude I could be best friends with
Best friends
He's got himself a cute lady friend
I imagine that Khem Lewis
Is the norm
In our little family
That we've built
You live in that house of cards and tell me how it works out
I think he's the coolest
He's the best of us
Don't try hitting on Khem though
Because he's got a lady friend
Khem's not the fan we deserve
She's a cutie
Also
Allison
Opposites attract
Be your classy lady that hides from
Horror games and shows up with her
Merfolk deck
I don't know what that means
And you want guys
That are attracted to you in a
Romantic sense and not a friend sense
So you don't have to appeal to their
Nerdy side
Appeal to their man side
Griffin how does a girl get your attention?
She sends me flattering
Emails over the internet
No she
She goes naked day one
No I very much fit into this
I try to put on air
I'm so cool but
I fall into the group of people
Where if a lady walks up to me and is like
Hey I'm like I love you
Thank you
For giving me this chance
I love you
I promise that I will take this trust
This sacred trust that you've put in me
By saying hi
But seriously sir do you want
A grande or a bento?
Do you ask everyone that?
Let's go out
You want to go to Starbucks?
Damn it
We're already at Starbucks
I want to hear Griffin's last question
But first I want to tell you fine
Folks at home how you can get in touch with us
If you need advice
You can go
Twitter and use the hashtag
NBNBAM we like that one a lot
Because it helps promote
The show you can go
Gmail NBNBAM at
Gmail.com you can use form spring
Which is at form spring dot form spring
Slash emails
Slash show
Slash form spring
If you want the actual link to that
You can go to NBNBAM dot com
Where you can find all this jazz
Um
The Utah Jazz
Also thank you so much we've passed
300 ratings on iTunes
And we're approaching 150 reviews
Really great
Can we just have a solid minute
Where we thank everyone for being so great
Like we missed a week
And people were hungry for it
And I hope that this
I hope that we can somehow in the future
Find a way to make up for it
But please tell somebody
You know about the show
Cause it
It really does
That's the only way we can spread
We're not advertising or anything
You gotta
We're gladvertising
The show makes you happy and then you tell people about it
And here's what happened
We were going to advertise and then we watched a lot of Mad Men
And then we just ended up getting drunk
I can't feel that world
I can't put money in those
Misogynist hands
I would suggest maybe listening to us in your car
Maybe you're doing that right now
Look out! Just kidding
Roll all your windows down
And just blast it
Yeah
And then we'll be like hey people on the streets
Download NBNBAM
Hey everybody
Look at this fresh car
You wanna be like him?
He knows what he's doing
We gave him this car
Make sure you check out our Facebook appreciation group
Allison's gonna be on there
Joel's gonna be on there
Dominic's gonna be on there meeting
Christian girls
That's what he's into apparently
But that's the
That's the whole podcast
But we wanna have something to grow on
Something to ponder over the next week
The ensuing week
We promise it won't be a week until the next NBNBAM
Next Monday
So Griffin why don't you break us off a slice
This one comes to us from
Yahoo Answers user Chuck Boris
Who asks
How many drops of LSD
Should I give a 4 month old to get her to stop crying
I'm Justin McElroy
I'm Travis McElroy
I'm 7
And this is my brother and me
You will never know me
You