The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother, Me,
an advice show for the modern era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy. I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
We just forced our editor to cut out three minutes of us talking about
Terra Cells before we could start the program. It's an epidemic, folks.
Guys, we've got a brand new watch, and I can't stress enough how legitimate this watch is,
and I'm very excited about it. Yesterday, news went out, DuckTales reboot cast, have you seen it?
Griffin, are you losing your mind about this DuckTales cast?
It's an insane DuckTales cast, but I have a problem with making this a watch, boys. I don't
think the small screen can be a watch. I think a watch, if it was Passenger's Watch, if it was
Star Wars, there's a new Star Wars, that's a big blockbuster watch.
Bobby Moynihan, Danny Putty, Ben Schwartz, David Tennant, are you kidding me?
I think it's PewDie because Danny Putty is the fun new holiday toy.
You put it on the newspaper, and yeah, Danny Putty.
It's hot as hell. Is it a watch, though? Another problem I have with it is it's not here yet.
I can't watch it.
How about we're watching the horizon? We're scoping. This is a scope.
Then it's a scope. If we're doing a watch, then I'm sorry, but it has to be. Trolls is on DVD now,
probably. It might be.
Here's what I want to ask you guys. They put out the cast list, right?
Yeah, okay.
It's pretty, like, they revealed a lot here, but there's still some major characters that
they haven't announced the casting for, and I want to throw it to us to make that decision for them.
Here's the characters that I didn't see on that list.
One, the big one jumped right out to me, Magic of Dispel.
Always trying to get that number one dime so she can cast magic with it.
Two, Gyrogear Loose.
You're just going to, sorry, this isn't a segment where you want to make jokes about
the actors and actresses that we think could fill these roles. You just want to sort of spout
lore and show off how many DuckTales characters you know.
Well, I mean, I do want to talk about, but yes, mostly I wanted to talk about. Also,
I had this really great joke that you just stepped on where I was going to talk about
Gyrogear Loose, or it might be Eurogear Loose, and I wasn't sure how it's pronounced.
It was really good. I've been working on it for weeks.
Oh, God, I'm sorry to step on that one.
That's okay. You know, they'll fix it in post.
Okay, so let's start with Magic of Dispel. Griffin, where are you at?
I mean, Emily Blunt, I know she's busy, but not too busy for DuckTales. If David Tennant
is in the mix, then if Beck Bennett, is Beck Bennett still on SNL?
Uh, yeah.
He's busy too. Get in there.
Ooh, Kate McKinnon.
Okay, yeah, I mean, any SNL, let's just make it an all SNL cast.
Yeah, can I hit you guys with a sick Magic of Dispel, and it's Ms. Jessica Walter.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, from downtown.
Okay.
Shit, that's good, Justin.
It's really good.
Is this gonna, are we gonna get a revival of hot cartoons from my kid age? Are we gonna
get, are we gonna get a tailspin starring Denzel Washington as Baloo?
That would be amazing.
Reprising his character from flight with just replacing Baloo.
Uh-huh. He flies the plane upside down drunk, I think. I didn't see it. I saw the trailer,
and I think he was drunk.
Just screaming, wahoo! I see that. It was amazing.
Here's my question. Here's my question. Here's my question. It's 2016. It will be 2017.
Donald. Donald. That's what you're wondering.
Well, Donald's a big one, but 2017, right, is when this is coming out. It's hitting shores,
2017.
What takes, what's taking him so long? You're just drawing funny pictures.
Well, one, that. But two, what kind of dark, gritty elements do you think they're gonna
put in now that weren't there in our childhood?
Guns.
Okay.
His cane has got a poison tip. It is fatal. That's a new thing.
Oh, I wonder if there'll be whole storylines about income inequality in Duckburg.
Interesting.
We'll raise some troubling, it's a troubling visual. Once you realize he's absolutely one of
the 0.01 percenters.
He probably, the series probably opens with him getting picked for a cabinet position.
And I think the first episode, we have to watch Launchpad McQuacks, or nope, sorry,
Robo-Duck's grizzly surgery that turns him, that replaces all of his fleshy duck parts
with cybernetic stuff. So like the lung, the lungs are gone. The duck lungs are gone.
That weird spiral pee pee, that's gone.
He's gotta carry them all in a backpack now.
It's all his organs they took out.
I would like to pitch, if you're listening to this Disney XD, and I know he's super
busy, listen, you can't find a busier man in show business right now, but Fit and
Crack Show, AKA Gizmo Duck, is Lin-Manuel Miranda. Like that would be amazing casting.
That'd be really good.
Please make that happen.
And he could really sell the duck screams as, cause he's awake during the robo-surgery.
And I don't know why they make us look at this and I don't know why, it's a children's cartoon.
Uh, if I could just put it in my hat here for Donald, cause I feel like, um, my Donald
is so nightmare-inducing as I've tried to like replicate it for our child. It's so bad
that, uh, my wife makes me do it on command just to make fun of me because she's that
much in dis-
Hey, break, break me off a, break me off a piece of that football cream.
You guys gave me like a line from DuckTales 2017 that he-
Oh my God, my God. There's duck guts everywhere.
Yeah.
You sound like, it sounds like a, an interstellar transmission from the cataracts, which is
an alien species that's just sort of, uh, based around violence.
You might also be some kind of like the fly hybrid between Donald Duck and the fish from
Pee-Wee's Playhouse.
Yeah.
Do you think when you're trying to get your Donald, you have to sound like that for like
a hundred hours and then it just like gels, like it just comes to you? Do you think that's
how it works?
I don't know, bud.
No, I think you're born with it. I think either you've got it or you don't.
Yeah. Uh, and you, you do, you do. Congratulations, Justin. You, baby, you got it. You got that
sound I've been looking for.
Would you guys be interested in a new podcast called Let Me Hear Your Donald? And it's just,
you talk to new parents or parents who've been in the game for a while, any parents,
and just like, let me hear your Donald real quick. Let me hear the Donald you're working
with.
I mean, if the last year has taught me anything, it's that just we can do basically anything
up here and people will listen to it.
So.
Yeah. Yeah, do true.
Do you want to hear mine?
Yeah, let's hear your Donald.
Hello, I am Donald Duck.
No, that's not anything.
Now I know, I know what you're thinking. That's not it. But here's what I'm planning.
I'm going to read books about Donald Duck to my child long before she ever sees him
in any kind of moving picture.
And so then when she hears that, that person's doing it wrong.
That's how Donald. So no, no old Disney cartoons, no Kingdom Hearts.
Not till she's like five or six. You know what I mean?
I put myself out there actually. Real quick, can I just hear, I'm going to leave you boys
with Uncle Scrooge in your best Donald and not a joke, but like right now, cold.
Give it your best to try to make that classic.
I've got I've got my expense.
Sure. That'll make it perfect.
Even better.
What a nice timber that will lend to your performance.
OK, I'm going to do my best.
Yeah, OK.
Justin, did you do yours one more time as a reference for me?
This is what Donald is supposed to sound like.
No, no, you do yours right now.
Cold, I'm not stalling for you anymore.
Make the sound of Donald with your mouth.
I can't.
I got nothing.
I'm going to leave you boys with Uncle Scrooge.
No, I think I'm just doing Bobcat Gold
Yeah, Travis, I need you to do it for real and not don't laugh through it.
This is serious.
Don't fuck with Travis.
Stop laughing.
This is a serious moment.
It doesn't help that Travis is looking at me in horror.
I'm going to leave you boys with Uncle Scrooge.
No, I think I'm just doing Bobcat Gold.