The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
I never realized how much flossing looks like repeatedly stabbing yourself in the butt and
crotch. Oh my god. Yeah, you're the one who chose to floss furiously. No one, I just said do a dance.
You flossed so hard. I dislocated every bone in my body. Holy shit. You flossed really hard.
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother made advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I am your middle-est brother Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother in 30 under 30 media luminary Griffin McElroy.
And what a thrill it is to be here in Cleveland.
Oh you've heard of it. We are here and we are so grateful to those of you that bought tickets to
make the long journey out. There's like 2,000 of you. This is our community theater production
that just our dad's friends. Thanks for giving us a chance. This is this grassroots live show.
We want you, but there's that and also our families are still at Great Wolf Lodge in Cincinnati so
it's gonna get nasty tonight. We talked about it and we, this is gonna, we want it to be a vile
show. What we want from this show is you know a lot of your friends maybe didn't want to come
because they don't like us and they think we're like smelly or whatever or like terrible or not
funny or whatever and um wait we want you to go back to them and and be like you missed.
Well I won't say missed. It was vile. You made the right choice in not coming because it was
it was profane. We've we've had to not publish a lot of live shows due to like technical sound
issues. Or Star Wars issues. Or Star Wars issues. Star Wars centric issues. This one might just be
too hot for TV. Yeah sure. And if this one goes up it'll be 10 minutes long. Not that they let us on
TV anymore. No not anymore. I mean technically unless you had some way to connect your streaming
device to a TV we weren't allowed on TV in the first place. That's fair that's fair but anyway
we are here. We do advice. We're brothers. We're nasty. We're nasty. No we're not. We're nasty.
We're three top tier nasty boys. We're nasty middle-aged men. Okay that's way worse. That's
so much worse. So much worse. No listen we're three nasty middle-aged men that bring their dad
with them everywhere. We're nasty. We're three dads who hang three nasty dads who hang out with
their nasty dads. Who hang out with their nastier dad. With two musician nasty dads who opened for
us. Listen we're just a big group of nasty dads traveling the country in a band. I thought that
me breaking both my arms before the show started was a bad energy. This is making it actually way
worse. I love this energy. Get comfortable here in the kingdom of the profane where we reign supreme.
Y'all about to get slimed. It's gonna be. We're gonna say nasty words. All right let's fucking do
the show. I'm tired of this. Traveling concepts. Confrontational ideas. Mature situations. Adult
situations. Cartoon violence. Cartoon violence. Mild drug use. Anyway it's a strong language.
It's an advice show. I decided to apply for a part-time job. One job that came up was for
a paranormal investigation group. I jokingly sent an application and I received a phone call from
the group because they want me on the team. Here lies the problem. I'm beyond terrified of the dark
even though I'm an adult. Holy shit this question has now taken two turns. Yes. It is almost back
where it started. I made up an excuse that I wasn't able to go to the interview and they stated that
they still really want me on the team and I need to give them a call when I'm available to do the
interview. How do I get out of this mess? I don't want to hurt anyone and I don't want to be haunted
and that's from I ain't afraid of no ghost. Wait. Yes I am. Are you are you here? Are you here? Are
you present? I'm sorry. All right thank you. Okay let me just. First off let me say I'm sorry about
how dark it is out there. Are you cool? Yeah it's quite dark. Just look at us. It's bright up here.
Imagine being us. I would also say two things. Thank you for. Thank you so much for writing
questions but uh thing one you didn't jokingly submit a resume. It takes a lot of work. That
takes a lot of work. You were like ha ha ha click like you typed out a thing and secondly how good
is that resume and what do you have on it that these paranormal investigators like this is
everything we've been looking for. I was an assistant assistant manager at Toys R Us before
it shut down. I was a safety associate at Best Buy and also I'm an esper who can see. I would be
concerned about any job where the exchange is hey we want you come for interview. I'm not gonna
fucking do that. No please. We really need people by which I mean bodies by which I mean vessels.
Did I say vessels? Damn um have you thought okay here's what you do okay you go to the interview
on pins and needles and you say okay here's the only thing I kind of focus on day ghosts okay
and then if they're like what day ghosts then you say what you think ghosts only come out at night
that's ridiculous and racist yeah I catch when the ghostbusters catch their nighttime ghosts
and they bring them home and then those ghosts escape from captivity while they're on the road
and have nowhere to haunt sun comes up what are they gonna do call a fucking uber no no they're
still just ghosts are always there where do they go during the day thank you yes someone's saying
yes this isn't a joke this is a this is my thesis yeah um I I think that there's a pretty easy
solution is you go in you do the interview crush it of course you're already halfway you're in
you're in once someone says we really need you they can't play hardball with you so you go you
do the interview and as you're standing up and you're about to sign the huge novelty signing
bonus they have for you a huge novelty check you say I just want one more thing I am a ghost
and then see how they handle that because they can't prove you're not right can't prove a
negative can't prove a negative can't prove you're not a ghost and they can't say like there's no
such thing as ghost oh god damn it you are going to need to phase through the door instead of
opening that will be and I have a wiki how article for you that's really going to help you out with
that he was paid 17 to write it and it was worth every penny uh do you all want a yahoo from the
yahoo answer service yeah uh I have one here that was sent in by uh Emma Kant thank you Emma
it's yahoo they're an anonymous yahoo answers user uh I'm going to call them uh Philip which is like
Philip without the h fun I've missed a button I'm going to remedy that very quickly oh no no no
what I tell you sexy no no no no yikes we gotta get raunchy no Jesus okay so
uh that's a no that's gonna be a no for me all right uh pilip asks how to surprise someone with
a horse what's what's the best way to surprise someone with a horse and what's the best time
to do it after dinner or early in the morning why are those the only two options yeah uh this
doesn't seem relevant but btw we don't have a barn and aren't going to keep our horse at our house
this is just sort of a woods a woods horse that comes back and it knows it's needed that is that
is like if I surprised my child with a bike and said now I'm going to put this bike inconveniently
away yeah this bike will actually be across town this one's going to be in the basement at church
it is it's kind of like speed once you get the horse you can't stop with it anywhere you have
nowhere to stop with a horse you have to keep moving okay it's like a chocobo it'll run away
as soon as you get off of it so before breakfast or after dinner and no time in between do it yeah
do it after dinner here's what I would do invite the person to a fancy dinner make sure your table
is near wait hold on what did you think he was gonna say people who groaned in the audience
sorry invite the person to a fancy dinner make sure your table is near a giant plate glass window
after the desserts have been served or may perhaps uh it's an ice cream or that's a kind
of dessert yeah sure crème crème crème brûlée still a dessert yeah uh the all of a sudden the
plate glass window fucking shatters in you come riding a horse whoo you shatter right there this
is yours and it's bleeding to death it's bleeding to death so dad make your peace enjoy it quick
enjoy it quick surprise quick get a picture fuck get a picture quick no not there gross no too much
blood hey that's a good speaking of put a horse head in their bed and then when they wake up when
they wake up it's a great surprise when they wake up screaming you'd be like no psych the rest of
it's right there and then you just pick up the horse head and just right back onto the horse's
body it's like it's fine it's young it's a young horse it's gonna be fine and it regrows and it's
fine you could also if you're still at the restaurant you could have your server come by
with like i don't know a big cupcake and you're like here's a special cupcake for your birthday
and they're like it's not my birthday you know just please please start opening
time is of the essence you must start opening the cupcake right now horses inside oh that's a big
cupcake yeah maybe put a horse at the bottom of a glass of champagne yes but i was your lover
yeah what's it oh rodney and then it's like a very sweet moment you put the horse in like a
big big jewelry like claptrap box and when they reach in to get the horse you fucking slam it
down on their hand also slamming it on the horse killing it instantly it's again this is there's
very few survivable options for the horse the horse isn't making it folks yeah don't make your
part of a surprise i have another question it's still i'm still it still feels like we're we're
beta testing riddle me piss one of these riddles was submitted by matthew the other one i lost
the name how mysterious oh two riddles good double the length i do have two riddles the first one
goes a little something like this what's clear to the eyes made by your imagination
wary weary weary by hurt feelings escapes only by death i literally this frequency you're using it
makes it impossible to remember the last it's shutting down my brain like my brain is like
don't hear this what's clear to the eyes thank you made by your imagination okay weary by hurt
feelings okay weary wait wait stop weary by her feelings that's the wording that's not a coherent
thought escapes only by death can i i want to i you know what sucks about this segment
is that i try to guess what the correct answer is that the riddles.com user said so i'll say some
like wild shit thinking it's right and it's even wronger and what's that say about me right
i'm going to say life close very close dreams okay very close i want i want to remind you
my favorite part of the riddle connected the answer and that is made by your imagination
yeah the answer is your soul
escapes only by death finally
okay bye fucker this okay the second one just it's you're not even gonna let that one
dink around a little bit in the noodle i love this one so much it has the best beginning to
a riddle me piss ever okay and i'm actually going to say it in the voice because the i love it so
much it goes like this i am something oh good i kiss my mama before i die
what am i okay right that's it
it once again the clues you get are i am something right i kiss my mama before i die
what am i so there's just the two clues i am something uh-huh i kiss my mama before i die
correct don't kiss mama before you die from the train um a bit these i hate this
it is anti-joke like it is that if the other things that we do are like comedy prompts
this is a comedy uh sandbag that you drop from the ceiling yeah and poison our show i know what
it is i know you know fucking too i kiss my mama before i die uh a baby a baby i know i don't
challenging obviously the answer is a matchstick oh yeah this is actually good now here's a riddle
it scratches the box which is like it came out of its mommy and it touches it and also it is
something and you know how whenever you take a matchsticks out of a box you're like time to
leave your mommy yeah yeah but you know how after you use a match you say oh that match it's dead
now yeah that's a dead kissed its mommy the box what a wild thing if you throw a match down like
what happened with that like well it kissed its mommy and now it's dead excuse me i know sometimes
when i'm setting up a candlelit romantic dinner at home i'll be like you like this you want some
music okay yeah uh just give me one second kiss your mommy let's go
let's get that question going yeah anything anything i'd rather read my own obituary
i moved i i moved back in with my parents after graduating from college and i'm finishing
unpacking problem is i have a bunch of anime posters and i'm not sure if i should put them
up on my walls no oh that one was so easy no no put up posters of other things what about
cool cards or babes or sports heroes put up posters of other stuff not this i enjoy these
posters okay but i'm worried my family will view me as immature yep if i put them up
it's bad enough i didn't have a job right out of school and i had to move back in here
should i go ahead and put these away or follow my bliss i that's from poster fiend in philly
you should not don't do it i know this is risky to ask now but are you here okay okay
all right no i get it i get it stop wait wait okay just two thirds just dunk i'm gonna say
you should stand your bliss this is beautiful now are you here no okay fine okay what about
a poster of scarface that's now that's a bad a lot of people have that it's like a cool yeah
it's like the world is yours and it says it on there and people come over like this is tommy
montana i haven't seen the movie this is a this poster is a reminder for me to see the movie
i wrote on the wall above it to do and then i put a colon and then i put the poster from
scarface i didn't frame it or anything i just kind of duct taped it up there i'll just i know
two things it's big gun and this dude loves confectioner's sugar i think yeah he eats piles
of it um i say i say you put the anime posters up and then when your parents come in the room
you're wearing like a really cool smoking jacket yeah maybe you have like a cool mustache and a
pipe and you explain to them the artistic values and then if they're like that seems immature then
you say you don't get it and then blow smoke directly right in their face it's time for you
to elevate anime maybe a nice frame is so important and some down lighting oh yes some museum quality
frame maybe like a station with a velvet rope museum quality framing is huge yes because that
is art that elevates anime to art yeah and i think that that would be put a little stuff up here put
a little plate next to it that says like you know printing on paper with the artist's name and maybe
the piece title and the year that it came out and then just stand in front of it like can you two
not name any anime other than dragon ball z yuri on ice that doesn't count
i know you name any anime i've not joked about on a stage with you before gun gundam
all right attack on titan okay paul was talking about that backstage also doesn't count wait hold
on battle angel elita there's one where little kids are detective that's the adventure zone
it doesn't count okay let me say this let me say this i'm all for this right but that's a lot of
posters and you can put up too many posters you can do poster overkill but you can repurpose them
i mean i was sometimes on queer either like i don't want to throw out my dad's old clothes
and then they come back and bobby's like i made it into a quilt and then they have to be like
oh good because i i for sure didn't like them in clothes form bobby that's not overstepping
at all pal anyway make a quilt out of your anime posters make a quilt out of your dad's anime
posters yeah i i um i want to say i love anime i think it's a beautiful art form i'm just trying
to give myself an excuse to quit twitter and i feel like i'm nudging my way there closer man
toxic enough hey let's just swing right onto this good vine uh emma compt also sent this
one and it's from yahoo answers user we who asks how do i buy an anime body pillow without my parents
knowing this is great this is almost the inverse of the last question i want one but i don't know
how to get one without my parents knowing and how can i get it without my parents knowing
okay here's my pet here's the hardest thing to pretend it's something other than what it is
it's so it's so of itself right that if you were seeing carrying it you and then would say what is
it and you had to say what it was luggage it's a dead friend like there's nothing it's a memorial
it's a memorial here's what you do you go to your parents you say listen i've been doing some
research i went on consumer reports.com or whatever and i was looking for the best pillow case and it
turns out it's this one having nothing to do with the anime baby nothing to do with it it is just
hypoallergenic and top quality material the thread count is oh off the charts right it's just one big
thread and apparently and that's what we've been looking for it hides stains like you wouldn't
believe and that's oh we're getting the light that's our time thanks no i love anime okay how
can we get an anime body pillow in this fucking house without their parents knowing sarcophagus
now we're talking now we're cooking with gas sarcophagus how what like a shot of turin kind
of thing what are you talking about no you idiot that's a wrap i'm talking about a beautiful museum
quality sarcophagus if you can find the anime body pillow on amazon you should be able to find a
sarcophagus to fit it that's what i'm saying jeff bezos yes of course
you could always say it was a shipping mistake from the amazon factory i was trying to get one
of a cool car maybe the car from cars that the wilson brother plays i can't remember which one
does it and it's dad it was supposed to be the car car and believe me i've been on the phone
with amazon every freaking day trying to take care of this and as soon as i can get it corrected
they are going to ship me out a beautiful owen wilson yeah what was the car car call can you
get an owen wilson pillow lightning mcqueen that's good they're gonna replace it with an
owen i'm pissed off too dad it's supposed to be owen wilson i'm the one who has to sleep with it
yeah oh fuck dude hey if you had to get an owen wilson body pillow would you get owen wilson from
royal sand and bombs or owen wilson from um the holy shit hold on hold on owen wilson from royal
sand and bombs yeah or thank you drill bit taylor it's the one and only time i will accept audience
participation when it's trying to help me remember the name of the film drill bit taylor thank you my
friend but let it be law from now on because i don't want this to be a bad habit established in
this or any other audience if we ever ask for a question if we ever ask for advice if it's we
don't know a rule for dungeons and dragons we can't remember some arcane name of something
just yell drill bit taylor every time right that'll always spice things up i think i would
take the drill bit taylor pillow yes because it would be uh far more inexplicable yes if anybody
saw it there is no justice i could just be like i don't know griffin what which uh owen wilson
pillow would you yeah mine would be dupree and i could act pissed off every time i came in my
bedroom like this fucking guy's still here justin marmaduke fuck that wasn't an option
i think outside the box uh i decided to apply for a part-time job one job that came oh i got that one
i work children's birthday parties take another pass i think we could one more again i work
children's birthday parties at a local family fun center as it is known a big part of my job
is doing magic tricks for the kids here's my issue i absolutely suck at doing magic tricks
i've been doing working this job for almost two years and my boss thinks i'm great at it
i managed to convince her i'm really good by pure luck even every time i do a party though
the kids are unimpressed and often see right through my tricks they'll literally shout out
how i'm doing the trick it's frustrating and embarrassing what do i do and that's from
mediocre magician in cleveland are you are you here all right
whoa a thousand doves just flew onto the stage whoa thank you they're all on fire oh shit i
cannot think of anything more demoralizing than having an eight-year-old just yell out like
the balls under your armpit dumb ass i mean okay maybe try theming it for something the kids like
like fortnight just like i you put it instead of a bunny rabbit and just rename it their favorite
fortnight stars are you literally reaching what's inside the hat and then it's your phone and you're
like your favorite guys just streaming just watch this for 20 minutes i'm gonna sit in silence and
smoke cigarettes while you kids enjoy this fortnight video um maybe work on your pattern
yes i get less of a you know there are a lot of like uh comedian magicians out there whether
the tricks are either like really basic or sometimes even really bad but then it's actually
about like the comedy they do yeah you could do that and just like full on dunk on the birthday
just roast on the birthday boy yeah but like here's two rings whoops anyways fuck you josh
yeah i mean probably more subtle than that yeah what's in i'm not you what's in the hat let's see
it's for you josh huff my shorts if you're listening to this later griffin just did a flip
off it was rad oh look at this i got two hats josh it's two these are yours two flip offs um
um are you hold on i'm running some mental calculations okay are you prepared currently
to do any visual magic right now oh my god be quiet i can't hear them i can't hear them
agonizing over this question are you prepared to let us judge your magical prowess right now this
is not acceptable are you prepared to let us support your magic support your magical prowess
right now if not just say no real loud does anyone have a deck of cards if anyone says yes they're a
plant now everyone be quiet do you have a deck of cards listen we've never had magic in a show before
one magic trick is not gonna kill us
i guess come on magic come on down i guess come on down let's get that down and let's pass that
deck of cards forward let's get that deck of cards up here you'll never get it back
i don't know how you get up to the stage paul i don't either can we get a little bit
hello hello welcome hello come to this microphone hello adonis god we've never had magic i'm so
excited at this point in the show adonis does a badass magic trick but their microphone wasn't
working so it's just like three minutes of us going whoa no way so now we take you to the
end of adonis's magic trick all right bye adonis thank you you're great you're a great magician
that was incredible that was amazing see that's much i keep telling you guys that's much better
than jokes um i mean i just want to know how they cheated yeah i mean uh i know how they did it
the worst hey i got a yahoo okay perfect cool uh this one's from adrian cowles thank you adrian
it's uh it's an anonymous yahoo answers user i'm gonna call uh adonis asks should scientists
give octopi bones
and a lot of other podcasts a lot of other podcasts would turn and just run away from
a question like that five words each one so vitally essential should scientists give octopi
bones i will say that the word that most troubles me in there and if i have to pick one is give
because that makes it sound like you would hand the octopi bones and they would just absorb them
in oh thank you finally someone gave us bones travis it's up to the scientists to figure out
how to give the bones to the octopi i think the problem would be that's why they're scientists
if if you did this i think that the it would be really hard for the octopus to walk
because its legs would now just be locked in a straight position and it'd be like like a tripod
it doesn't have to be one bone per leg travis your imagination has failed you make me so
fucking mad sometimes i mean again with this shit even if it's every fucking show you give it like
a like a human and it's two bones with knees two bones that's still gonna be hard to walk
i think that it would be a lot of bones in each one how many eight
eight so it would have seven knees no not every joints and knee you dullard so it would have
knuckle oh wait now hold on are the legs the fingers there's 50 bones in one big skull and
think about that last one for a second because that's the worst fucked up bone of all the last
thing yeah what if they give him the skull no that's just attractive squidward never mind listen
my fear is this we give the octopi bones we're loving it we we don't i don't know how to the
scientists are gonna do this i just give them boats at first they're not crazy about it right
they don't love it their pants don't fit they can't squish through little holes they can't
squish through little holes oh no my door's only this big gig into my ding-dang house now they're
mad at us but they do have bones oh no my fear is this you give an octopi bones and they'll
want a glass of milk eventually they're gonna eventually they're gonna look up from the
beautiful briny shimmery shiny sea yeah they're gonna look up on land and they're gonna say
jerald i'm going up to take what's theirs that's the big mistake you make with octopi is you give
them bones and they're gonna come on land and want our shit yeah that's what happened in finding
dory and i know what you're saying they can't breathe well we gave them bones like lung bones
like lung bones why why no why stop there let's give them gills and get them up here let's give
them gills and then let's give them skin and then let's give them emotions and then let's give them
a car alone let them have sex and then there'll be bicentennial octopus yes let's give them bones
let's give them gills let's give them training and coding my bicentennial man joke didn't go very good
nobody octotennial man no let me ask you that i think that this listen science has come a long
way we know that we've maybe been to the moon you know don't do this we've done a lot of stuff
where's the pelvis going an octopus they don't have to have all the bones they just have to wait
where would you stop give them a spine you give them a skull you give them some legs you give
them a pelvis maybe some ribs now they're a person now let me let me ask you this does the octopus
wear pants with four legs or a or is it four legs and a shirt with four sleeves i would actually
think uh two two sleeves two pants legs and then just when they lift their shirt up just four arms
oh yeah nice fun at parties why would they wear clothes they're an octopus oh well because they've
joined the fraternity of bones you've got to wear clothes if you got everybody at least that's my
platform for 2020 if everybody else can run i can fucking run with if you got bones you need clothes
i'm polling at two percent wait ribbon has the biggest donations of all time
ah i've never used this in self-defense before but
so
this is the munch squad it's a podcast within a podcast and it's waning years
still still that's what hold on i need a little sip of my cab before we move on
wet the comedy whistle
this and thank you book house brewing um this okay paul's just gonna keep okay
okay uh i'll just keep doing my jokes thanks paul this outrageously you don't have to do that
hey you guys did really good yeah y'all brush it paul and storm yeah it's so good
do you guys want to come back out and finish the show
okay all right this outrageously kinky ice cream store is coming to victoria in july
wow i don't like any of that none of it's good none of it's good this is from cat thank you cat
for sending in this outrageously kinky ice cream store coming to victoria in july i've been on the
internet a while it's gonna take something pretty wild for me to qualify it as outrageously we used
to we used to advertise for a sex toy company for many years so this is the the extreme no
there's a fun life hack i still follow them on twitter so sometimes i'll be scrolling like
oh bad news bad news oh cage for a boner i'm just saying if this ice cream is not going inside me
not mouth-wise warning this store is not suitable for children and adults who aren't down to get
dirty it says that stop looking at my jokes victorians will finally that's what they call
themselves in victoria okay it wouldn't be safe victorians will finally be able to get a taste
of provocative vancouver-based ice cream store perverted ice cream by july 2019 store owner
susan serwatuk confirmed to victoria buzz they'll be opening up a new location at 604 it doesn't
matter all the flavors featured in the vancouver shop ranging from classic and premium perverted
to royally perverted sure what could that be very very perverted delivering this ice cream will go
down on you in a theater delivering delivering on the owner's promise to serve delicious ice cream
with a twist and that twist it's jizz it's not it's not jizz i told you this would be a dirty one
i told you this would be a dirty one i just think maybe that was a family miscommunication where
like the grandpa was like let's open an ice cream store with a twist and he meant like two flavors
twisted together and his pervert son was like oh i know exactly twist and dicks right i love it whoa
no we just wanted something that was unlike any other ice cream shop out there mission accomplished
perverted is a beautiful word that can mean so much a sexual meaning is just a tiny bit of that
oh so your ice cream is the different kind of perverted yeah got it hey everybody i'm a pervert
that means i like uh listening to music because it has lots of meanings we're not here to king
shame at all but also you can't say that the sexual meaning of perverted is just a tiny bit
of it when i would argue it's a good 85 yeah it's a it's a yeah this this one ice cream they have a
picture of um actually is a big ice cream uh in a uh and with chocolate on it and it's got a condom
shoved into it not a joke oh yep uh-huh yeah so that you are definitely going for the sex one
on that the perverted is definitely the sex one y'all y'all y'all y'all news update the condoms
in a wrapper yes thank you explore the seductive side to some of your favorite sweet treats some
of which are served with a condom as one of the toppings no glove no love right wrong yeah but
incorrect you've used it incorrectly it's not supposed to refer to a condom shoved into an
ice cream treat no condom no ice cream is nothing that's nothing besides being finger licking
delicious no ass hard pass hard pass i i have never had a press release make me want to wash
my hands before besides being finger licking delicious this ice cream shop works with a local
company that supplies the sugar and other simple base ingredients that staff mix in the store every
day with fresh local high fat milk oh sorry we that was from a different place no this is this
place it's perverted but like don't get it twisted it's still great at shop local think super horny
all the time they're also known for avoiding fillers for for what and chemicals as much as
possible to create the closest possible natural soft serve is that sexy i literally don't know
anymore i'm i'm afraid of the caveat as much as possible we avoid chemical oh no some got in well
we do our best they're cool quirky ice cream flavors aren't the only things that'll make you
scream this summer pop some of their um no pop some of their uh signature salty balls in your
mouth for a delicious surprise don't don't gratify that no don't worry we're only talking about their
soft caramel covered chocolate balls with malden sea salt good job you made it have a fucking
paragraph being cool yeah you had to be boring don't get it twisted we're not gonna put testicles
in your mouth no fucking duh ice cream company oh i thought you meant you were gonna play some real
human testicles in my mouth oh thank you for clear i was aghast i'd made it this far in the
advertisement but i was confused by that because i didn't want stranger's human testicles in my
mouth but now you've clarified to me that perhaps you made a confectionery treat oh thank you so
much ice cream store fuck you perverted perverted ice cream also sells t-shirts sweatpants candles
lip balms baseball hats and of course perverted condoms so you can rep this new favorite in style
imagine that scenario hey cool condom what's it from
um it's from my favorite ice cream that i like and you got the condom to keep us from having
a child or an std uh at the ice cream store so let me get it fucking straight you pulled the
condom to protect us sexually from the ice cream that you ate earlier good i'm going home goodbye
wait wait don't leave don't leave it's a perverted condom i'm actually out no i'm actually done
who would say who wants to say that let me put on my perverted condom
and anyway that's perverted ice cream cone to victoria in july if you're in the area check it
out or don't don't or do or do i do want to know what the flavor is
hey everybody this is griffin uh flying flying solo got my pilot's license so you're on board
my plane of advertising money zone stuff and i'm gonna take good care of you if you look out to the
right you'll see the blue ridge mountains i want to tell you first of all about casper casper is
not a scary ghost and not a scary scary monster of any kind it's not a frankenstein it's a bed
specifically the mattress part of the bread the bread okay cut that make sure you cut that one
terry they make beds but mattresses they've got these new hybrid mattresses that combine the
pressure relief of their award-winning foam with durable yet gentle springs uh we all have casper
mattresses some of us i think more than one i've got one up in my guest bedroom whenever we have
folks over to take a slumber or take it to slumber town and snooze the day away uh then we always get
compliments they said oh wow that must that must be a million dollar mattress and then we say uh
we're not supposed to say the price of the mattress in this advertisement but it's super affordable
and uh it's got luxurious comfort and resilience we say all of this to them uh they've got the
hybrid collection with lift support increased airflow for cooling durability for all body types
and enhanced edge support uh and they also have that 100 night risk-free sleep on at trial so
get one i'm still saying all of this to my friends get 100 towards select mattresses by visiting
casper.com brother and using brother at checkout that's casper.com brother and using brother at
checkout terms and conditions apply and then uh that's all i say to my friends and they leave
we're also sponsored in part this week by me undies me undies is a really slick place that is
here to change your underwear uh but not actually like even though even if you have made a mess down
there they're not that's not what they do they supply you with new underwear uh they believe
that undies should be soft fit every booty and offer fun patterns that give you the freedom to
express yourself uh i have replaced my entire underwear collection at this point with me undies
it uh has changed my life i'm wearing them right now everything feels so nice uh makes my butt look
like a fun fiesta because of all the fun prints that they have on it and they also just introduced
the feel free collection for women me undies size tested these five new silhouettes on every body
type with an ultra soft feather light waistband that provides zero restriction these undies are
dedicated to being the best thing that has ever been on your body in sizes extra small up to 4xl
and as always they have new prints that drop every tuesday uh i love them love them love the love the
underwear love the lounge pants love the onesie comfort suits it's all so good and right now they
have an offer for our listeners for any first-time purchasers you can get 15 off and free shipping
and a 100 satisfaction guarantee uh by going to uh me undies dot com slash my brother that's 15
off your first pair free shipping and a 100 satisfaction guarantee by going to me undies
dot com slash my brother that's me undies dot com slash my brother uh that is it for the jumbo trons
thank you all so much for everybody that came out to cleveland i feel like we were kind of bratty
about ticket sales for cleveland uh but y'all showed up in a big way and it was a real fun show
that's what you're hearing right now uh we are super super slammed this week uh and last week
all the the rest of the fam was out on a beach vacation so uh this is this is us filling in but
we should be back next week with a new installment in the macaroy adventures in the macaroy trials
and you're gonna hear that and you're gonna be razzled and dazzled go check out all our new
merch we got backpacks we got fanny packs now covered in sort of macaroy brand iconography
uh we got new pins we got new kinds of everything all at macaroy dot family uh we still got some
live shows coming up but i think they may all be sold out but you can also check on that at
macaroy dot family and uh yeah i think everything else we do at the end of the show so i'm gonna
let you get back to it bye have you ever watched a movie so bad you just needed to talk to somebody
about it well here at the flop house we watch a bad movie and then talk about it yeah you don't
have to do anything we'll watch it and we'll talk it we do the hard work featuring the beautiful
vocal talents of dan mccoy stewart wellington and me america's rascal elliot kaylen new episodes
every other saturday at maximum fun org or wherever you get your podcast dude bye bye bye
hello what's your name hi um my name is uh morgan hi morgan that's quite an instrument
you got there morgan i love it why thank you i appreciate it so um my uh my uh seeking um for
advice comes from a recent promotion that i got at work which uh requires me to uh talk to a lot
of executives at a corporate office and kind of make relationships with them so oh thank you share
some of your like hobbies and everything like that we get it my hobby is yucky ice cream from
a sexual no i don't want to go there ever no thank you um coward put our ice cream in you
who uh my biggest hobby is magic the gathering yes which uh very cool you all among my friends
and family clearly but uh i don't know if i want to tell a 50 year old man that i play a card game
for 13 and up uh sure most games are for 13 and up don't worry about that true true i don't know
of a board game that says like for 50 years old and older uh not a board game but golf golf yeah
yeah okay i'm pretty sure that you just came up so you love magic the gathering and you came up
to drag golf is that what we're doing okay good oh 100 okay good good it might not be magic the
gathering that's the only thing keeping you separate from 50 year olds they might also be
your junkie okay um but my question is uh how do i uh make that sound cool
oh my passion is cards oh do you play do you play cards i've been known to get down to vegas
from time to time okay okay would you say that this is the end of our conversation yeah i would
excellent this has gone very well here's a great option lie you could lie what are you into i love
football i also love football excellent who's your team though the plane walkers is that a
no here here's the thing real world real the thing is is like a lot of people have um hobbies that
when they first started out like hundreds of years ago or whatever were all so weird and the key is
now when you say it like i play magic the gathering don't explain it they don't if they said like i
love to play golf they wouldn't sit there like but golf's fun it's cool you know like they wouldn't
explain that's a dumb thing to say though because everybody knows that golf is yeah
that would be ridiculous imagine that fucking thing you just said with your own mouth here on
stage like i play golf it's um have you ever seen a very small white ball yeah but that's what i'm
saying if you say like i played a magic the gathering for fun and they're like what's that
i'm like oh you don't know um and then with that tiny phrase oh you don't know you've just gained
dominance in this situation oh yeah oh you don't know okay uh and then you explain it to them well
i got a starter deck for you to borrow let's just uh let's just throw down right now and see now you
got them whoa and then if they beat you they're a natural and you take them on tour and you milk
them for everything that's your bobby fisher right there yeah uh you could say oh well uh i play yugioh
and they're like what you're like just kidding i play magic and they're like oh thank god
i thought we had a nerd on our hands shit whoo scared me um could you and then you play your
trap card and then dragon eats him or something can you travel around with a starter deck and say
i play magic the gathering and now so do you and hand them the deck and and see and say like if
you really care about getting to know but you'll learn to play this card game and anyways i don't
know what you do but do you want to buy a car or whatever i don't know who your job is do you
do you have any expensive cards any of those fancy ones i have a few nothing like in the
thousand dollar range or anything like that get some of those step one step one is you need to
get a lot of those until you're very wealthy with card money i guess and then you just show
you play magic the gathering oh that's uh that's the nerd shit right you're like i guess you tell
me and you fan yourself with a bunch of cards and then your boss is gonna be like i don't know what
he needs these are these are very valuable and they always will be i have a printout of how these
are good hold on these are worth 560 dollars oh good that's good for you does that help uh yeah
my wife usually just tells people i'm a magician though so there you go it's not wrong yeah thank
you i love it hello hello hi what is your name my name is billy hi billy billy hi how are you
thank you you can adjust that mic if you want uh just point it right up at the yeah yeah
so i was running a little late i had to run a conference call telling people a lot of boring
things so i got to my house uh had maybe five minutes to get ready so as i am peeing you know
how you have occasionally have an itch on your head okay yeah i'm aware yeah yeah well so as i
was itching my head my glasses midstream fell off yeah and you caught them oh yeah i caught them
with the toilet and you never yeah and you never once peed on your glasses oh this is the first
time i peed on my glasses okay yeah i don't know about you guys but the pee breaks did not stop
they just kept going wait wait wait wait wait wait wait you just kept peeing on the glass sorry
what was your name again uh that my name is billy billy so billy the speed at which you accepted
the scenario was zero seconds yes um well i mean i don't know how far we want to get into this but
not only did we're pretty far i didn't understand what that press release meant when it said that
pervert doesn't have to be a sexual word until literally you're welcome just now yeah i see the
light thank you billy i am curious we don't kink shame on the show but we are allowed to
kink question to find out more information this is not mine uh how much of a part of you telling
a bunch of strangers that you pissed on your glasses is part of the kink is this part of it
for you or is this just billy i would just throw them in the dishwasher that would but then the
dishes huh yeah what about the plastic you could boil them how would you and i know what you're
saying that would ruin my glasses but bad news billy we're past that yeah we passed that station
about 25 miles ago we passed that when you looked down at your piss covered glasses and said that's
not a reason to stop some piss is the same as all piss really it's a fair question in that you can
do it you want me to go step by step muscular okay i want to leap to billy's defense for a
second okay no one ever says i just pissed on my glasses a little bit right i mean you pissed on
them or you didn't are you are you wearing them right now okay okay now listen now listen you
knew he was you really was you rinsed him off you used some sort of cleaning product on him
right okay and then you felt okay and you put them on well i need them okay right you need
them to see uh i actually think you're in the clear as long as you don't tell anyone oh no
does that help billy we might help it helps thank you one one last question promise
so i shit on my watch no no this is nothing that can i give you guys pens no no don't get anywhere
near us billy billy no billy think about this for a second if anyone for the rest of our life
ever tries to hand us anything and we're like no thanks and they're like you took pens from the
piss glass guy yeah they're pretty amazing listen i believe you and normally we say don't follow
advice but i'm going to give you one piece of actionable advice next time lead with the pens
just put them right there on the edge of the stage if that's okay thanks billy thank you billy
hello hello what's your name my name is heather hello heather um my question uh is
well there's a little bit of my husband loves tourist traps uh and i am a vegetarian so
so we how do you make it work yeah it's a real darman greg situation they're related
strangely okay um so we honeymooned in gatlinburg tennessee yeah you are a lot of beef jerky stores
okay and my husband airsoft airsoft airsoft guns beef jerky stores that fudge and laser tag
yeah it's lit down there we went into no less than three beef jerky stores and my husband is
is incapable of not telling the employees that i'm a vegetarian okay unprompted yeah
have we not gotten vegetarian jerky yet it seems like we would have gotten there yeah it's called
kale chips portobello mushrooms that's not bad they do not sell it at the beef jerky stores at
gatlinburg tennessee okay they do sell shirts that say uh people eating tasty animals okay pita i
love that that's fucking funny i get it yeah so uh inevitably the uh employees will then like
unload on me so i've had to stop going into beef jerky stores with him because he goes into this
fugue state right he can't help himself like half and i've asked him like why did you nobody
nobody asked like nobody even offered me jerky and he was like i don't know when you say unload
do you mean like they give you shit lots of shit wow i don't understand like you don't you don't
you don't like my dry animal what it's trying oh but you this un-chewable beef you don't like
my hard crispy tooth-breaking beef but you you can eat jerky right except jerky though right
jerky is not even like meat it's old it's just like beef paper so how do i get him to stop okay
um is your husband here he is okay hey cut it out yeah yeah stop it fucking stop you can get
your jerky on amazon stop going into these stores i think they yell at your wife now listen now if
you want the better question that we can have more fun with yeah cover your ears cover i'm
watching you cover your ears cover them for real the real question is how do you get back
and the answer is you take him to whole foods and you're like this one has tasted the flesh of the cow
and then someone's gonna fucking kill him
so you're gonna have to find a new path for yourself yeah now listen it's gonna get real
messy after that you're gonna have to change your name probably move get a new job part of
your journey though respect the journey you got it it's part of your journey and your new identity
might eat meat yeah and it's gonna be a cover yeah they'll never suspect if you're gonna start
don't start with jerky holy shit no it makes a bad first meat impression some meat is wet
and that's okay that's a griffin mackerel guarantee does that help extremely excellent thank you
hello hello how's it going i'm good how are you good good thank you for asking so uh some kids
moved in next door which is fine i guess it's not what's your name stephen by the way stephen hey
so um i have like a pretty tall fence and you can't really see through it from my dog
um and i can't normally see the kids which is a good thing but then they got a trampoline
and now they keep jumping on it and they keep staring at me when they jump
yeah yeah and it looks like michael meyers isn't the george lopez theme song okay
it's a beautiful mental image you've painted for me steven
um are you asking us to help you sell your house how do i feel peace of mind in my own home um
see i want to i want to take it it wasn't seaman yes okay um i want to take you back to the first
thing she said which was some kids moved in next door which is amazing this idea that a bunch of
blank checks we got a camp nowhere situation we got a real camp nowhere situation a bunch of kids
just moved in and bought a house together i also really like when you said that you had
a fence you couldn't see through for your dog which i imagine your dog just is really private
like this space it's uh it's the taco bell dog we don't want paparazzi
um could you next time they go out to trampoline you're already on their trampoline
yeah wait wait your turn idiots i'm having fun up here this is how adults do it and you're smoking
you'll never see that coming and you always put it out on the trampoline
and maybe lower your backyard so no matter how high they get they still can't cavernous cavernous
very good raise your fences build an extension on the trampoline side just right in front of
the trampoline goes up another eight feet nothing maybe seal their trampoline and burn it no come
on it's not even a joke can you somehow and i'm i'm not a scientist i'll be i'd be putting bones
and fish and stuff but if i was a scientist i could tell you some way to weaken the springs
just to affect the height not enough to hurt the kids not enough to hurt the kids lawyers when they
jump on it it just goes lower and then doesn't raise back up that's a net so you're talking about
a huge round hammock kids would love that they'll appreciate it when they're in their 30s and they
need a license to chill that's true they'll appreciate that giant round hammock that steven
made for them steven i have one very good piece of advice but it depends on if you have one
particular item and it may be uncomfortable uncomfortable for you to tell me whether or
not you own this item is that okay okay do you own a baba duke costume
not yet not yet not yet ebay's open late ebay's open late kids hate this guy okay yeah i think
the problem there is if i jumped and i saw my neighbor like my neighbor was baba dude i'd want
to like i gotta double check this maybe try they jump over they see yours in your backyard doing
your taxes really frustrated and they're like oh they go down below the fence and they come back
up your baba dude they come back down they come back up you're doing your taxes oh yeah i like
that yeah it's like muscle confusion but for kids it's just kid confusion it's regular kid confusion
steven does that help yes excellent excellent thank you bye baba duke costume
we can lower the house lights now it's getting a little scary honestly to see all those people
out there uh thank you so much cleveland for coming to our program i want to say a huge
thank you to paul and storm you can go to their website i'm assuming at paulinstore.com that's
right paulinstorm.com that's the first time you've ever said it correctly that's fair uh
we still have some merch out there i think the pin sets might be gone there may be like
buy it before since that it can get their grubby mitts on yeah uh we have the poster the poster is no
joke one of the most amazing posters gorgeous there's also paul and storm merch out there
please go buy that uh uh thank you again for for doing that that was very special also listen i
know we made a lot of jokes about like people not buying tickets or whatever but you all coming yeah
it was all good you're a great crowd thank you so much and we will obviously despite my jokes
we'll obviously come back to cleveland we'll just we'll just do it in a building that is 30
smaller than this building and then it'll work no but actually the people in this building have been
amazing thank you so much this place is wild yes you're so sweet thank you there's literal can
there's one single piece of confetti falling from the sea of which considering the ticket sales
does seem apropos this is all you get this is all you get uh thanks also to john rogerick and the
long winters for these for theme song it's a departure off the album today is the bed yes
thank you to amanda thank you to our daddy thanks to maximum fun thank you sam thank you sam let's
have and thank you to our families uh our families for hanging out in great wolf lodge you don't have
to thank them uh here's the final yahoo is simon by simon by imacom wow a hat trick oh oh oh sorry
oh oh oh shit we have to travel uh very early in the morning to get back to cincinnati tomorrow so
we won't be able to hang out after the show yes uh so right now we're going to take a second to say
thank you all of you oh no you're great yeah you're fine i'm signing and uh so we won't be
able to see you after the show yes but hopefully you got a sign poster we did a bunch of those
before and if not uh maybe next time so also there's voter registration outside paul is just
testing go do that yes okay final yahoo this one is centered by imacom thank you emma it's
emma can't thank you it's are you here are you here no i've just fucked it up oh you know her oh
cool thanks say hi how is emma okay stop imacant con no it's can't can't emma can't it can't be
caught it's from yahoo answers user shawn who asks shawn asks can you milk gushers to make
fruit juice my name is jessica mcroy i drive is mcroy my brother my brother may kiss your
dead square on the lips maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
hi everybody my name is justin mcroy i'm sydney mcroy we're both doctors and nope just me okay
well sydney's a doctor and i'm a medical enthusiast and we create saw bones a marital
tour of misguided medicine every week i dig through the annals of medical history to bring
you the wildest grossest sometimes dumbest tales of ways we've tried to treat people throughout
history lately we do a lot of modern fake medicine because everything's a disaster but
it's slightly less of a disaster every friday right here on maximum fun.org as we bring you
saw bones a marital tour of misguided medicine and remember don't drill a hole in your head