The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how
cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
Oh, hello.
Did you start the thing?
Yeah, no, I started the thing.
The thing is going.
This is it.
We're in it now.
We're in the shit.
We're in the part that the people paid the money for.
Chilean miners emerging from the ground.
We are here with you, the podcast viewing public, to sell our wares.
What's on offer today?
Podcast.
Podcast for sale.
And honey.
I made honey.
I figured it out.
He made it himself.
Welcome to My Brother, My Brother, Me, and Advice Show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I tickled you, huh?
Because it's the name of the shit and then it was your name.
I'm your middle brother, Travis McElroy.
And I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
All right.
That's fine.
We get it.
Thank you all for joining us here live at the PlayStation Theater.
That's the name of the place.
It's the name of the theater.
It's the PlayStation Theater.
That's not a clever bit we came up with.
We do have some stuff.
We're super excited to be here.
It's a nice place, centrally located right across from Guy Fieri's shit store.
His whole thing?
His whole...
As Fieri watches overall.
His chubby museum.
But it is the PlayStation Theater.
I thought it was a museum of the swang.
No.
It is the PlayStation Theater.
All right.
We got some stuff out of the way.
And just the first thing is...
Yo, fuck Xbox.
Right?
Yeah.
The whole fucking family, man.
The first Xbox, Xbox One.
You can't call it Xbox One again.
Xbox 360.
Sounds like you skipped 359 of them, idiot.
Boom.
Cameo.
Suck my dick.
Blink's a time sweeper.
Fuck off, Blink's a time sweeper.
You got nothing.
Suck my dick.
I don't know any platform exclusive games.
But yeah, fuck them.
Halo.
Reach around my butt and grab my balls.
Yeah.
Fuck Xbox.
Uh-oh.
Who's that?
Over the horizon.
It's Nintendo.
Fuck you guys, too.
Yeah.
Luigi can suck my balls.
Okay.
That's good.
You know what Nintendo thinks.
Now, I will say this.
Thank you.
I will say this, though.
Yeah.
Backstage.
I got smoked out by Crash Bandicoot.
That dude fucking rules.
He's so cool and chill.
He's so fucking cool and chill.
And who lit the spliff?
Spyro the dragon.
Spyro the dragon did it.
Of course he did.
The reason I broke up...
Did I say lit the spliff?
How old am I?
The reason I broke up when I was introduced to myself is I was thinking about how just
a second ago Griffin told us, as he has told us before every live show we've ever done
in our lives...
Okay.
This is gonna make me sound terrible.
This is...
I told you that in confidence, obviously.
Okay.
What he said was, aw, they horny for this one.
Now, there is...
Listen.
Now, listen, though.
No, listen, though, for real.
Listen.
It's mind over matter.
I'm extremely nervous.
I get so scared back there.
Well, that's the old saying.
If you're nervous, just picture everyone in the crowd horny.
Just for this...
Just for this one.
Just for this one?
I believe you also use the term wet and wild.
That's just in reference to this dance that we're gonna be doing up here.
Okay.
That's a lot of fun falls we've been practicing.
I want to say you all are very, very special tonight.
Not just because you're here, but because you will also be the first human beings to
hear us say out loud that we are doing a television show in the near future.
Yeah.
So here's the thing.
That's good.
The house lights are good.
You can bring the stage lights even down a little bit, help me out with the glare.
Here's the thing.
It's coming next year.
And here's the other thing we're...
This is true.
We're filming it in Huntington, West Virginia.
So I guess my question, and I can't see you guys right now, but I'm trusting you're still
there.
My question is this.
Are you all horny for this one?
So that is gonna be available on CISO TV, who we are of course big fans of.
Thank you so much.
Don't wait to subscribe to CISO.
Do it right now.
They got so much better stuff.
You could right now leave the theater and I think go watch Hidden America, which is
probably gonna be better than whatever we put on up here.
They're also the first company that we went to and they didn't immediately see what we
look like and we're like, no.
Absolutely not.
No.
You can't.
Not on TV.
No.
Wait.
With your face and everything?
You realize this is the bigger screen, right?
Not the computer one or the iPad one, the one that people hold.
And we looked into that truth about cats and dogs technology that they did in the movie
where I haven't seen it.
I'm gonna let you fucking hang.
If you think I'm gonna fucking Tarzan to your rescue with cats and dogs.
Here it goes.
Oh, here we go.
Janine Garofalo turned Uma Thurman into a human puppet.
I think.
Nailed it.
I'm a dude who loves to walk around the apartment in my underwear.
I step in the door and boom, my clothes are off.
Now my roommates don't mind this, but one of them is Airbnb-ing his room while he summers
in Chicago.
Ruh-roh.
While he summers in Chicago.
He has rented the room to a nice couple and has asked that in his three month absence,
I reframe some semi-nudity so he doesn't get a bad review.
I hate the idea of giving up on my freedom.
It's not my problem.
Or is it?
Am I the asshole here for wanting to continue a clothes-free lifestyle that's from nudists
in New York?
You're in boxers.
Are you here?
Yeah!
Are Ozzy Osbourne, is that you?
I was fucking running a list of things I hope you don't sound like in my head.
Welcome to the apartment!
Check out my dick!
Dear Airbnb review, this was a cool house, centrally located.
Great neighborhood.
Great neighborhood, very affordable.
The other thing about it is I can draw Chris' penis from memory.
Are you curious about every nook and cranny of Chris' penis?
Do you have an hour?
Okay.
Sit down.
He's got a lot of them.
Act one, the shaft.
Five star, ten out of ten.
Would recommend.
It was great.
No, it was great.
The penis?
Great.
Good stuff.
How is this not a criminal crime for criminals?
I can't like bounce on my wife who I live with and be like, someone else is gonna be
here for a while.
I'm going to eat all the fruit by the foot later.
No, it's cool.
I'm going to get like 150 bucks.
It's totally cool.
Do you have to put that in like the Airbnb description?
There might be a God in you.
Do you think there's like coded language of like, open air plan, you know what I mean?
Derrick.
Open Derrick.
Public Derrick for use by all.
Why not?
I don't know.
Wait, I was about to make a joke about the guy's penis.
What is the name we settled on?
Chris Derrick?
Hey, Chris Derrick, let me see you erotica.
Now I lost the joke, but I do remember his name is Chris Derrick.
And something about his penis.
That's just comedy math right there.
Name plus penis reference equals audience disappointment.
Six years of podcasting, apparently.
Hey, do you guys want a Yahoo answer from Yahoo Answers?
Can you take a moment, though, and game recognize game Rachel Rosie for me real quick?
Thank you, Rachel.
It's about Yahoo Answers.
User Brian, who asks, can cops pull over other cops?
Let's say a cop was breaking the law, driving down the street for something like speeding
or not using a turn signal.
Can another cop get behind him and pull him over?
Got you.
Arrest you.
Good.
This time, Derrick again.
Derrick's been spelled differently.
You saw on Twitter over there on your phone?
What?
I thought we were supposed to tweet.
I wanted to tweet about the show happened, and I thought you guys could handle it.
Cool.
Already big time Mr. Hollywood phoning it in.
TVs were the real money.
You know, the first time we talked about this question, I thought of like plain clothes,
like a dude in a car who was like, I'm actually a cop.
But now I'm picturing like someone pulling over another cop car with a uniform on top.
But then what if-
Do you know why I pulled you over?
Yes, fuck, I know why you pulled me over.
What if to catch that cop car, the second cop car had to speed, and we got a whole human
centipede situation?
They sewed the cars together?
That seems cruel and unusual.
That is what happened in that movie.
Which one?
The human centipede.
Oh, I'm with you now.
Someone's got to stop him from doing like, I mean-
Who watches the Watchmen?
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
That's a good- Why has nobody ever thought of seeing if cops are on the love learn?
There should be a cop for cops.
Cop cop.
Do you think- Cop cop, time to go to jail or work.
Time to come to work with me.
You're in jail now.
Cop cop, making arrests, but no friends.
You just said top cop, I think?
Top cop.
You got to make it to the top to arrest other cops.
Yeah, you got to be the king of cops.
You can't arrest from the bottom up.
You can't be first day on the job arresting the chief.
First off, okay, two things.
First off, coming this summer to TLC, top cop.
America's next top cop.
America's next top cop, and secondly, do you think they would have to get the best cop
to catch the other cops, right?
How do you want to think a cop with the best cop?
Not the worst cop.
It was like, I don't know.
What do you even do?
Is President Barack Hussein Obama, and a lot of people forget about the Hussein, it's important.
I've never done that one live, and it was like, I didn't know how it was going to go.
It's okay.
You only said half the syllables.
Yeah, you kind of farted the last- Does President Barack Hussein, and a lot of
people forget about the Hussein, but it's important, Obama, is he the top cop?
Because the buck stops here, is that what that means?
The crime stops here, and I'm it, like if Joe Biden's speed, and he's like, I got you
and I'm the only one, dog.
Bad luck.
I was like right behind you in traffic.
I saw you turn left without the signal.
Joe, that's a bad beat, dude.
I'm literally the only dude.
It's me.
Why'd you do it in front of me?
I'm top cop.
You know this.
It's all checks and balances, because he can arrest Joe Biden, but who can arrest Barack
Obama?
The lowliest, the criminals.
Only criminals can arrest the president for speeding.
I love the world where the president's A, driving himself, and B, just like burning
it.
Just like pedal to the metal, see you bitches in Arlington, bye.
Him and Joe Biden have a famous series of pranks that they do back and forth on each
other.
And this is the end game.
Do you think that cops, I was thinking about when we were saying come with me to jail,
I mean work.
Do you think cops, if the money's ever tight, just like decide to live in jail?
Cut down on the commute.
Just like there's no commute.
It's like, do you think it ever occurs to them like, well, I could just go home, or
I could just live in jail.
Do jail, I think.
You got beds and everything?
You got beds.
Somebody can scoot my desk up close to the bar so I can do work and stuff.
I'll come back at the end of the day.
You let me out, I'll come back.
I got nowhere else to go.
Yeah.
I mean, you should lock me in for security's sake, and it's really locking out.
I can't be trusted.
Who knows?
I'm a wild man.
And then if you do get arrested for real, you're like used to it a little bit.
It's like, you know, I'm just back at work.
I'm just really, really busting my ass.
I'm really spending the nights at the old office.
How about another question?
Here's another question.
What?
Tell me how to live my life.
A few weeks ago, my girlfriend and I splurged on a fancy meal in an upscale restaurant.
One of the courses...
Already loving it.
Oh, shit.
Wait.
Was it you?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, hold on.
The only information you got is someone wrote in about splurging on a fancy meal, and only
one person in the audience went, I think that's me.
One of the courses was a Sunchoke dish garnished with dainty purple flowers.
What dish?
A Sunchoke dish?
It's a type of fish?
I believe it's a fish.
Fish?
Hey, is it a fish?
What was that noise?
Is it a fish?
It's like an artichoke?
I want one person to answer wherever I'm pointing into the void.
I was pointing there.
What is it?
Okay.
You don't have to fucking yell at me.
Yeah, we're on stage with you.
Okay.
What's the demonstration?
I got internet.
You know what we were doing while you were learning about types of fish?
We're at podcast school, getting our degrees in podcasts.
Hey, this is like ginger.
Nice try, Sunchoke.
You're ginger.
Got them again.
It was a Sunchoke dish garnished with dainty purple flowers.
I ate some of the flowers, and I thought they were okay, but I didn't eat them all in case
they were just decoration.
However, when the server cleared our table, he asked, sir, would you like to finish your
flowers before I take your plate?
So then I felt obligated to eat the flowers as he watched.
I suddenly felt inexplicable shame as I chewed.
I can't imagine why.
His gaze seemed to suggest, yes, little fancy boy loves eating little purple flowers, doesn't
he?
I'm no stranger to public shame.
I did magic in a talent show when I was six and later went on to play Oompa Loompa in
a community theater production of Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
Tick tick boom.
My main question is this.
Was this dude fucking with me?
Am I wrong to feel like he was shaming me for being a fancy flower boy?
As from Blossom Binging in Brooklyn.
Yeah.
Hey, whoever you are.
I feel like I know you better than my brothers.
Sometimes we finish a question and have to say like, we don't have enough information
to answer this.
That is not a problem.
We totally see what's going on here.
I take some of that information, put it aside, save it for the winter.
You could have just written a question, I went to a place and a bully made me eat flowers.
A bully made me eat a whole bouquet.
What do I do now?
But you are here though, right?
Oh, you're real close.
Okay.
The flower eater.
How do they taste?
How do they taste for real?
Why are you yelling at him?
I'm really excited to find out.
Compare it.
What?
Savory.
Well, I can tell you where the floral element of it came from.
No fucking root word.
No pun intended because apparently this is a root vegetable, the Sunchoke.
Is it possible that you weren't supposed to eat the flowers, but the guy had counted
how many flowers are on the plate when he put them down, and he came back with five
and he was like, do you want to eat the rest?
You know what you're supposed to eat?
Anything you could swallow.
No, you've had a baby for too long, that's not actually true.
Fucking markers, crayons, dice, it's all good in the hood.
My brothers played, I was trying to get my baby to eat while still buffering was on,
my brothers played restaurant with her backstage.
What kind of wild and crazy rock star shenanigans do we get on?
Good question.
And then 45 minutes later, I said the sentence, oh yeah, they horny for this one.
So it all balances out.
We're very complex individuals.
That's how I come at you, hot and cold.
Let's say this, though, they got her to eat some chicken quesadilla, so what's up now?
Mission accomplished.
You ate the flowers, though, and that's great.
There's no part of that that doesn't make me very, very happy.
I like that.
This is to any other living person, I don't want to put you on blast, I'm saying it's
a beautiful thing you've done here.
Eating flowers is an in for a penny, in for a pound situation where you either don't eat
the flowers because they're plants, or you eat all the flowers because it's like, hey
when in Rome, nom nom nom nom.
You can't rule out plants from being eaten.
Right, but like, the point he's making is, if they're decoration, you're not off the
hook by eating some.
Yeah.
Like, no, I just ate some of the decoration.
Is this an ice cream bar or a candle?
I'm going to take six to seven bites out of it.
No, you've committed.
You're eating the whole candle now.
You need the waiter to come back and go, where is the candle, and you go, yum yum.
Yum yum in my belly.
Might I suggest the next time this happens, should this happen again or happen to anyone
out there, you eat two flowers, the person says, would you like to finish the flower,
and you go, no, they're not the best I've had, and you big time them right back.
I've had better flowers.
I will say this though, I've got a super pretty tummy, and you show them your tummy.
They'll love that.
They love that.
That's what restaurants do.
You want to do another Yahoo?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oops.
I lost the name on this one.
Dang it.
I'll find it.
Here we go.
It's also from Rachel Rosen.
Game Recognized Game.
Fuck.
It's a lot of game recognition going on.
It's from Yahoo Answers user, they're anonymous, and you're about to know why.
This anonymous user will call Derek, yeah.
Got it in one.
Derek asks, help me add to and improve a standup I'm writing.
Most of it's observational humor.
Buckle up.
We got you.
Ideas so far.
Let's just run through some of these bullet points.
Some standup comedy ideas.
Should I stand up and just deliver something?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If we didn't have any of you, we wouldn't stand up.
Let me get that spotlight.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Our phones fall and we panic, right?
Our friends fall.
We laugh.
Hey, guys.
Phones, they're getting bigger.
Our laptops are getting smaller.
The best reaction you get from that is someone going, yes.
There's no laughter at that standup show.
Phones getting bigger, laptops getting smaller.
Yes.
Agreed.
They certainly are.
I noticed.
Uh-huh.
Hey, guys.
If there's no talking during the movie, isn't it then a silent movie?
No, it's fucking not.
But hold on.
They played into the bit.
Think about it, because it's not.
Oh, that's the joke.
Yes, yes, and no?
No.
Vin Diesel's saying words up there in Fast 7.
You can hear them.
When a guy likes a girl, he looks her in the eye.
When a girl likes a guy, she looks away.
Again, you're just, it's patently untrue.
But also, what's the punchline there?
Just, the sky's blue.
Hey, guys.
Why does chicken, why does chicken mean wimp?
A chicken will peck you to pieces.
So a little bit of that.
That's how I lost my brother.
That's a rural Seinfeld.
Okay, like, we're all having a lot of fun here, but let's all agree.
If we saw a human being, like us, you know how we're humans?
If we saw a human being stand on stage and say these things as jokes, it would be literally
the funniest comedian I've ever seen in my entire life.
But not, I would argue, for the right reasons.
Right reasons.
But if, hey, guys, right reasons.
The word none, though, this one's real, is just the letter N doing a cartwheel.
You have to think about that one for like 45 fucking seconds, but once you get there,
it's good.
Hey, no word, no word in the English language rhymes with month.
That's another one.
That wasn't just some weird non sequitur that I did.
Let's just punch these up real quick, guys.
Do we have to do other jokes other than these jokes?
Our phones fall, we panic.
Our friends fall, we laugh.
What if your friend is like playing Angry Birds on your phone and like asteroid lands
on both of them and you lose both and you're just, your reaction is just.
I'm neutral.
I'm completely neutral about this.
I don't know.
All those two events, they both canceled each other out.
My friend is dead, but my tiny phone is also dead.
It's very funny that my friend died, but very sad that my phone died.
Derek, oh my God, you're just standing there doing something.
Can I still get my numbers?
Are those in the cloud?
I'll tell you who is in the cloud.
James.
Now see, that's a bit.
We did do the shit.
That's a tight five.
Thank you.
That's my time.
You want to hear another question?
Or do you want to punch up some more of those bad boys?
No, I've literally, I can't anymore.
At the grocery store line, the clerk got to my last item, a large bag of cherries.
Okay.
I love this crowd.
This is the second time in a row, somebody's like, oh, here comes my shit.
Everybody listen.
Shut up.
Here comes the drop.
Here comes my jam.
Okay.
At the grocery store checkout line, the clerk got to my last item, a large bag of cherries.
They looked at the bag, then at me and said, you know, these are expensive, right?
It's such a fucking, that's like a nuclear bird from like deployed from orbit.
So fucking good.
Asking them to clarify might have sent the conversation to a super judgy place.
But in the future, too late, too late.
How should I handle egregious displays of fiscal judgment from cashiers or other service
personnel that's from swimming in subtext?
And that was you who laughed at it.
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Somebody was just like, yeah, buy some cherries.
Are you here?
Hi.
You are here.
How are the cherries?
Moldy.
Moldy?
What the fuck?
Are these your artisanal molded cherries?
Did you take them back after like that?
You were a real shithead to me and look at your garbage cherries.
At these prices, maybe they, did they kind of, were they patronizing when they said it?
Like, did you?
How could they not be?
Yeah.
Like.
You know these are expensive, right?
Good job.
You did great.
Did you, did you mean to get grapes?
Come on.
Come on, sweetheart.
Hey, why don't I put those, why don't I take those back for you and get you some grapes?
You know grapes.
You ever have raisins?
They're like dope raisins.
Pre raisins.
I call them.
Come on.
Super wet raisins.
They're good as heck.
You're going to love eating these.
Grapes are like your cherries.
You know what?
Hold on.
Why don't you eat one cherry?
Just so I can watch.
This is going to be adorable.
Oh, it's sour, isn't it?
Wait, let me.
A little bit sweet.
Oh, there's a hard thing in the middle.
Let me find this.
Hold on.
Oh, that's cute.
Look at him go.
Look at him eat that cherry for the first time.
What a sweet boy.
That'll be a hundred dollars because that was a fucking cherry you just ate.
They put those as the symbol on slot machines for a reason because you're rich.
The problem is if someone asked the question, you know, these are expensive, right?
There's literally no way to like come out from under that burn.
You can't say yes.
Like, and sound like an adult.
Okay.
Here's the old, like there's no cool way.
You're right, Travis.
Because what, and one answer is, oh no, that sucks.
The other answer is, hell yeah, let it ride.
This was just for me.
I had a good month.
Hell yeah.
I know they're expensive.
I love cherries.
I earned this shit.
I promised myself.
He said one day I would walk in here and I would buy the cherries.
I saw the rich man when I was a kid and I said one day, that'll be me.
I've earned this.
Just say no and like ask if you could have someone help you back with them because you're
worried you'll drop them and you can't afford it.
You know there's this, I do.
Could you pretend to put them in the bag, please?
Just don't let people see you put them in the bag.
My boss is here.
Yeah, do put grapes in there.
Yes, of course, of course, of course.
Of course I fucked up.
Thank you for asking.
Thank you.
They look super duper similar.
Okay.
You're going to understand how I slipped up, but of course I want grapes instead.
Can we get-
Yeah.
Can we do our special-
No, no.
I want the one.
You've been teasing with it for two shows about the TV question.
Okay.
All right.
We've got a wonderful-
Type two.
We're going to do a type two about this Yahoo that's sent in by Aaron Keyes.
Thank you, Aaron Keyes.
I'm sorry-
Remember, you credit me for whatever happens in the next two minutes unless it's bad.
Okay.
Thank you, Aaron Keyes.
It's from Yahoo.
Answers user lalizard who asks, in home improvement, are the sons related to Tim Allen?
They look so much like him.
In the series Home Improvement, Tim Allen has three sons, Brad, Randy, and Mark.
Two of the kids look exactly like Tim Allen.
I'm frustrated.
Which two?
I have to know.
Are they related in any way?
Maybe not as actual sons in real life, but maybe his nephews or something.
You're already backpedaling.
They just have to be related.
Can someone please help?
It's killing me.
I think about those sons from Home Improvement so much.
If they're not related, I don't even know what to think.
Which two look like Tim Allen?
It doesn't matter.
Are they related?
That would be weird, though, if they got two of his sons in their neighborhood friends.
Stupid Reggie.
We wanted three.
Do you got anybody else?
We got stupid Reggie.
Stupid Reggie are friends of mine.
We only expected this to go a season.
Yeah, he's a doofus.
You want him for the acting?
We can get him.
He's cheap.
I always did assume they were the love child of Tim Allen and Richard Karn.
They-
Those are Richard Karn's boys.
Yeah.
Oh, the Karn boys?
Oh, the Karn boys.
Yeah, I love those guys.
Karn boys are at it again.
They experience Karnal pleasures and they-
Shut the fuck up.
I'm just saying-
Go to prison.
Oh my God.
If he ever had a late nights and weekend R&B show, that would be like the greatest time.
Like he's a DJ.
Karnal pleasures.
You're listening.
We talked about this on the show, but he does host a celebrity golf tournament called The
Carnival.
That's legit and real.
And you can buy tickets to just like go to it.
And I guess just hang out with Rich.
Rich.
With Sweet Rich.
But no, they definitely junior'd each other, Tim Allen and Richard Karn.
Did you see that movie Junior where Tim Allen had sex with Richard Karn?
I haven't seen-
It must not get blue.
It was romantic.
Tender.
Yeah.
They meant it.
I heard full penetration.
I didn't see the movie Junior, but the best scene in it was when Arnold Schwarzenegger
and Dane DeVito, I assume, may love for 30 minutes tenderly-
30 minutes.
It was a third of the movie.
Yeah.
They went from, cover your ears if you don't want to hear this, from fully soft.
Like you saw every act, every part of it.
Like them coming in the front door and putting their keys down.
Like how was your day?
Like I'm feeling it.
You feeling it?
Yeah.
Fully soft.
Well, not right now, but like maybe in two minutes.
Okay, great.
Let's eat some pasta.
We got to carve up.
This is going to go long.
That was all you.
Just want to go ahead and put that disclaimer back on there.
Folks, we hate to break into the action here, but we want to take a second-
This nonstop thrill a minute.
Chill a minute.
Action.
Disaster.
Chill a minute.
Hey, why don't you chill for a bit?
Let us sell you some shit.
The first shit that's not shit at all, it's actually pretty great, is Squarespace.
We're supported in part by them.
The simplest way to capture your passion with a beautiful website.
If there's an idea or a project you're itching to show the world, you should.
Don't keep that locked inside you.
Create something that the whole world can share in your mind's eye.
Squarespace has simple tools and captivating templates that showcase your hard work is
the easy part.
That wasn't a sentence.
Let me try again.
Showcasing your hard work is the easy part.
That's more of a sentence.
That's like a sentence.
Now, if you're itching to try Squarespace, you'll be shocked at how easy it is to use.
Even if you never designed anything, try it out.
Give it a shot.
Start a free trial today when you visit squarespace.com slash my brother.
You should Squarespace.
Now how good is Squarespace websites, you ask?
I'm glad that you did ask because I made a website inside of which I trapped my brother
Travis McElroy.
Yeah, kind of a Phantom Zone type thing.
It's like a Phantom Zone place where I've trapped Travis and now he spends his days
surfing the web helping teens solve mysteries and cyberbullying a lot.
Is he doing the cyberbullying or is he stopping it or what's up helping the teens?
He's doing it a lot and he's very good at it because he is cyber.
He is cyber.
Hey, goofball.
By the way, Travis is in the cyber dimension.
That's right.
He's not here.
He's also at MaxFunCon, which I didn't fucking know he's going to.
That's cool.
Have fun.
I guess we don't tell each other things.
We're not really a unit, huh?
Kind of fun.
We're a package deal.
Interesting.
Kind of broke away from the shark pack, huh?
Tell me about Bowlin Branch.
Let's tell you about Bowlin Branch.
Bowlin Branch is the place to go-
My name's Bowlin Branch.
Okay.
Hi, Bowlin Branch.
My name's Bowlin Branch and I want to sell you some sheets.
Yeah, that's what they do at Bowlin Branch.
No, it's just Bowlin Branch and what they do is they send you nice, nice sheets.
They have streamlined the sheets buying and sleeping upon process.
You got some Bowlin Branch at your place, right?
Yeah, I love it.
We say this all the time on Sawbones.
We do not sleep on other sheets.
When those sheets are dirty, we wash those sheets and then put them back on the bed.
We have other sheets.
We don't sleep on them.
It's just Bowlin Branch.
We're talking about luxury at a sensible price.
Sensible but luxurious.
You want to see how good they feel?
They're going to let you try them risk-free for 30 nights.
You don't love them?
They'll let you send them back.
You got nothing to lose.
It gets better if you go to bowl, that's B-O-L-L and branch.com today.
You get 20% off your entire order when you use the promo code MYBROTHER.
It's not just sheets.
I got towels, blankets, duvet covers, everything.
Plus you get free shipping.
It's all so good.
Go to bowl, branch.com.
Use the promo code MYBROTHER.
That's all one word.
My brother.
Oh, so luxurious.
How about a Jumbotron?
If you want to get a message on this show, a personal message to a friend or maybe for
a small business, just go to maximumfun.org.jumbotron.
They'll help you do that exactly.
This message is for Poopsie and it's from Moopsie.
Got it.
Who says, happy birthday six months ago.
Well, was that worth the wait?
Since this is halfway late, it counts as halfway early, so you're welcome.
Love you muchly and even though I know part of your heart belongs to three other dudes,
they are brothers and married and that's gross.
Get it together, Grady.
You're still always numbers one through five with me.
Smoot.
Wait, that might be the beginning of the word smooth, but I do very much like, here's the
thing.
Slang term for smooching.
Right, or salutations or my condolences or best regards.
That shit, it's done.
Now?
Over with.
When you're done, when you send an email?
Smoot.
I love that.
So we got another personal message here.
Another sort of, I think you could call it an e-smoot from Claire Winnick and sorry,
it is for Claire Winnick and it is from the sweet baby Nichols brother, Jake.
And that's her name is pronounced Nichols.
So I got it right.
Yeah, you did very good.
No problem there.
Happy 30th birthday.
It says, there seemed to be no greater gift than immortalizing you in the intricate mythology
of the bim bamma verse nestled on the shelves of an Indiana Jones-esque warehouse somewhere
between the lost gushy tapes.
They're never getting out.
Stop asking.
And I literally, I don't have, they were deleted.
Do you not, do you guys understand?
When I delete, when I edit something out of a podcast, I don't take that audio and then
put it in a little folder and say like for savesies.
It goes to hell.
It goes to deleted hell.
Between the gushy tapes and Willem Dafoe in a handmade green goblin costume, your name
will live eternally in semi-obscurity what you've always wanted and that is for Claire.
Happy 30th birthday, Claire, and that's from Jake.
So thanks, baby Jake.
Thank you, Jake.
Jake from State Farm.
Magic baby Jake.
I like anytime anybody says Jake, I like to say like Jake from State Farm, like the commercial.
Well, it's worth asking because one out of a million, the person's gonna say yeah, in
fact.
Yeah, that is actually me, Jake from State Farm.
That's me.
I'm Jake from State Farm.
Anyway, that's gonna do it for us.
For the ad portion of our program, we got a lot more jokes for you, lots of jokes.
Thank you everybody who came out to all the live shows in DC and New York.
Thanks to John Hodgman.
Is he out there yet or did I just ruin the surprise?
I don't know.
We gotta think of him at some point.
I'm gonna thank him right now.
Thanks John Hodgman for your help with the show.
And we had a great time.
Hope everybody who came out did too.
Boston, we're coming for you, dawg.
Those shows sold out.
Thanks Boston.
Thanks Beantown.
Watch your butt.
Watch your butt, Beantown.
Smoot.
Hey guys, this is Adam Conover.
You may know me from my true TV show, Adam Ruins Everything.
Well guess what?
Now we're doing a podcast version right here on Maximum Fun.
What we do is we take all the interesting, fascinating experts that we talked to for
just a couple minutes on the show and we sit with them for an entire podcast, really going
deep and getting into the fascinating details of their work.
And Adam Ruins Everything wherever you get your podcasts or at MaximumFun.org.
So we do our, we have a thing.
Okay, so like a couple weeks ago.
I have the thing here, the OG.
Don't read the OG, but do read the OG story.
Okay.
My Brother, My Brother and Me episode 304, a very recent one.
We had, we do a segment in the middle of the show called The Money Zone, which is where
we get paid.
And in episode 304, we had a very special part of The Money Zone where somebody sent
in a message that was unfortunately the funniest thing that's maybe ever happened on the show.
They are, what are their names, Griffin?
Their names are Avital and Rishi.
And who put who on blast?
Rishi put Avital so fucking on blast that they were like pushed 10 feet into the ground.
And it was so good.
And the first off, let me say they're here.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Avital and Rishi, you guys here?
Just stand up real quick.
Perfect.
Thank you.
Oh, front row, center.
Hello.
The best.
Thank you for, this is the fucking funniest thing that's ever happened.
Now it's a message about, it's a message of, I mean, it's about Coldplay, but it's really
about Rebirth.
Rebirth, I guess.
And it was a, we should set it up a little bit more, a live journal message that Avital
wrote a while ago about Coldplay and how transformative seeing Coldplay was.
We read some of the message, but there wasn't enough room in the Jumbotron to read the whole
message.
So we have it in its entirety.
And we debated back and forth about which one of us would read it.
And the answer was none of us.
So without further ado, we'd like to welcome to the stage, John Hodgman.
Coldplay.
Keep it, keep it up guys.
He really needs a, okay, wait, wait, hold on, time out, time out.
Coldplay comes on.
My God.
When they had started up in my place and I saw him on stage and he was singing to heaven.
I swear his arms were outstretched.
He was just so at peace with himself and everything, just so free.
Are we not done?
I started crying.
Not just crying, sobbing.
I dredged everything up and everything melted away.
But it was me and the words.
I cried for everything bad that had happened to anyone.
That people live in fear, that there is injustice and cruelty.
And that I take what I have for granted.
I cried on behalf of everything.
Oh God.
And he sang.
No one ever said it would be easy.
And I, I knew what he meant.
It was so meaningful.
It sounds dumb.
When I was momentarily at peace myself, Coldplay is so awesome.
All I needed was yellow.
And I'm okay again.
Yes!
Ladies and gentlemen, John Audrey.
Brilliant.
John, would you like to stay on stage and help us answer some audience questions?
Yes, please.
Yes.
Is there a chair?
May we have a chair?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
John, he's going to read some dope shit I read about train.
This guy.
No, I didn't write anything about train.
Seriously, thank you for letting us read that.
Thank you.
Stand up again.
Another big round of applause.
No.
It's so wonderful.
That was so, so, so good.
It was beautifully written.
It makes me so sad.
The funniest thing that's ever happened on our show has nothing to do with us.
Let's say I love you.
This is life.
Hey, thanks for doing that, John.
Oh, it was my pleasure.
We're going to take some audience questions.
And the way this works is this, you raise your hand, you get called on, you come to
the microphone, you ask us, all four of us, my brother, my brother, my brother, and me,
all four, for advice, and we help you.
There is one rule.
What's the one rule, everybody?
No bummers.
That is correct.
So, who has a question that is not a bummer?
Oh, my God.
The pressure is so on.
I saw the gentleman there in the light blue shirt.
Come on up.
Yeah.
The mic is actually behind you.
The gentleman there in the light blue shirt.
While he's walking to the mic, may I just say one thing?
Yes.
Sure.
I was very moved by your description of Arnold Schwarzenegger and Danny DeVito having sex.
The weird thing is that it wasn't, like, romantic.
No.
They were just like...
It was purely of convenience.
They were porking for science.
It reminded me that when I was a young person here in New York City, my friends and I had
a would-you-rather game with one specific question.
Would you rather cuddle with Danny DeVito nude every night for the rest of your life...
That one.
...or have Danny DeVito call you every day and have to talk with him for an hour?
They're both really good things.
Yeah.
I mean, they're both good outcomes.
You're the centerpiece of my day.
Don't make me choose.
I know.
And we talked about it for a long time because we couldn't decide.
And I understand you want to ask your question, sir, but I don't care about you.
In the year 2012, I took my family on a vacation to London, England, and we stayed in a hotel.
And I took my children, who were very young at the time.
They're approximately four years older each now, but at the time they were younger, by
roughly eight years.
It was a weird thing.
Anyway, we went up to the pool of this hotel in London, England, and because it was London,
the pool was about the size of a postage stamp.
And we were there, and there was a weird old man there doing exercises.
What do you call these?
Bicep curls?
Bicep curls.
Yes, exactly so.
And it took me a while to realize.
Why was I the one to get that?
You beat me through.
You jumped.
It took me a while to realize that that man was Danny DeVito.
Nice.
Getting some gains.
And I was like, how about that?
There's Danny DeVito.
Well, children, it's time to leave immediately.
And before we could go, Danny DeVito caught my eye, and he said, daily show.
I'm like, oh, Jesus, kids.
You were physically putting yourself between them and Danny DeVito.
And I went over, and I'm like, hello, Danny DeVito, who, by the way, is a hero of mine.
But Danny DeVito, all I wanted to do is take my kids back to the room so we could get on
with the day.
And Danny DeVito just started talking and talking and talking about his love for the
daily show.
And then he took his shirt off.
Nice.
To go swimming.
To show you his John Stewart tattoo.
No, no, no.
He was just going to go swimming, and it was this profound, weird moment where I realized
both versions of my dream are coming true.
And with that, your question.
Your question.
I hadn't thought about that.
It was a wonderful life you've led.
Also, I love you, Danny DeVito.
All right, go on.
If you're listening, please, you're welcome any time.
I'll cuddle with you or talk to you every day for the rest of my life.
What if this guy, like, what's your name, and this guy's like, my name's Steve DeVito,
and I'm not entertained.
Could be.
What is your real name?
My name's Tim.
What?
Tim.
Just a disclaimer, you've got to eat that mic.
Yeah.
The sound just disappears.
Levels?
Levels.
You're great.
We're going to shut up and let you talk, too.
It's just a dead room, they told us.
I should be teaching a first aid course.
One more question, Danny DeVito.
Yes.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
So I should be teaching a first aid course this weekend, but when I saw the opportunity
to come see you guys live, my best friend stepped in and said he would teach the course
for me, and how do I pay someone back for a treat like this, and I don't count John because
you weren't part of the original deal.
Fair.
No, he's only sweetened it.
Amazing.
I was going to get him an Xbox, but in light of recent events-
No, fuck it.
Are you kidding me?
Xbox.
Not so much.
So I just don't know if you have any ideas.
Commencer it for the amount of appointments.
Have you thought about a PlayStation 4?
Yeah.
It's a good one.
It's a solid get.
Have you considered a subscription to CISO?
What was the-
There's a lot of great programming on CISO.
Beautiful.
All good.
What was the course you were going to take?
I was going to teach a first aid course.
You were going to teach a first aid course.
Is your friend qualified to do this?
Super not.
All right, here's the thing.
The heartbeat is super important.
You got to keep a bunch of blood in there all at once.
If you see blood outside, bummer.
That's bad.
Okay.
Were you going to be paid to teach this course?
No.
Volunteer.
Then you should have just not done it.
He's giving up a weekend.
Just don't come.
Just don't go.
Just don't arrive at the time you're supposed to.
But now I'm on audio and they know I'm here.
What are they going to do?
Not pay you?
Well, you're fine.
Just don't go.
So I figured I'd say thank you on the mic to him because I'm going to play this episode
for him to say thank you.
Oh, so you're just fucking losing yourself.
We're going to edit this out.
We're going to edit this out, Tim.
No free ride.
It's a fun arrangement.
You got to buy a Jumbotron.
By the way, if any of you are thinking about going to that Saturday night volunteer first
aid course, I would say don't bother.
The party courts they call it.
Let's do this.
How many people are going to be at the first aid course?
How many people?
About 40.
40.
Jesus.
That's a lot.
This bit may not work then.
I was going to say just give...
There's like a thousand people here.
Just give them like a little nug, like a little first aid nug, like the first like most important
like keep the blood inside.
Right now.
So no bleeding.
Right.
It better not be a joke.
I want to learn something.
First, don't bleed.
Don't bleed?
Right.
Okay.
But if they're already doing that, then like...
Oh, then stop it.
Stop it.
All right.
There we go.
Great.
Tim, everybody.
Tim.
All right.
Who's next?
I see this hand.
I saw this hand go really fast front row.
Come on down.
You did it.
Okay.
My name is Allison.
Hi, Allison.
So John, I have to tell you, I have a really good friend who used to work at The Daily
Show.
Come on.
It's our show.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Do you...
John.
Hi, Allison.
How are you?
I'm fine back here.
I'm going to tweet more about my TV show.
John, do you know my friend Jocelyn who used to work at The Daily Show?
Sure.
Of course I know Jocelyn.
Yeah, we're good friends.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, fantastic.
I hate Jocelyn.
Yeah, she stinks.
Boo.
Jocelyn is made of farts.
Let me tell you.
We're all making a big mistake because she's a lovely woman.
I bet.
Made of farts.
She is.
And my whole point is that you were very nice to me.
I met you before once.
You probably don't remember, but it was...
I don't.
It was great.
It was great for me.
Were you with Jocelyn?
Yeah, I was.
Yeah, I still don't remember.
I bet you're regretting not pointing your question at us, huh?
We would have remembered you.
But anyway, nice to see you again.
Oh, it's great to see you as well.
My question...
Is there something for our desk that we have here?
We have an inbox.
It's empty.
We have an outbox for trash.
I think she's transitioning to the question.
I am.
I am indeed.
So my question is, I was introduced to my Bim Bam about a year ago by a guy, and I'm
about to turn 31.
And it's fine.
It didn't work out, but it was cool.
I'm totally mature and whatever.
It's fine.
Mature people usually do say stuff like that, so whatever.
But I'm totally great and successful and whatever.
It's fine.
My life is great.
I'm doing great.
It's fucking sick.
Yeah.
You're doing great.
Hey, can I ask you some advice questions?
But I introduced one of my really very good friends from college to my Bim Bam, and he
loves it.
However, his wife, who also happens to be one of my best friends, is not as interested.
Cool.
By the way, this is quite an emotional journey.
I agree.
Yeah, this is like, I'm going to need a flow chart.
So some people like us, some people don't, and you're doing great.
Yeah.
So honest, we're like 50-50, you're 100% rad, and also you have a friend who knows John.
I have picked up all the details.
The key to writing a fantasy novel is world building.
Sorry, did you say your name was Griffin McElroy's Twitter mentions?
No, but for real, are you asking us like how to get your friend on board with our brand
of comedy?
Yeah, because there's two of us now, and we have good taste, and we're strong, and we
believe in ourselves, but this one other person outlier is not into it.
How do we convince?
Who is the person?
I'm confused.
Who's the person?
No one.
It's not Jocelyn.
It's no one you know.
No, no, no.
Everyone loves you, John.
Don't worry.
Yeah, don't worry.
So this is your friend's wife.
Yeah, who happens to be also my very good friend.
Like do they try?
They don't try.
Are they unaware?
Are they trying?
They're like, eh, eh.
Do they know we have a TV show now?
Yeah.
We're like multimedia.
Maybe they'll prefer like a visual medium.
To be fair.
Probably not.
I've tried.
I've tried, but her husband like walks around the house like laughing to himself, which
is not very cool.
No, that's not it.
No, no, no.
That's not really how you sell anything.
What are you laughing at?
No, you can't hear it.
Be quiet.
Listen, I've spent a lot of time with baby Charlie over the last two days.
To get someone interested in something, you have to be withholding of it.
So what has to happen is your friend has to laugh at it, and when she's like, what is
it like?
It's not for you.
No, no, no.
It's only for cool, mature people.
This is just for cool, mature people who are doing great financially.
It's not for you babies.
Babies wouldn't appreciate our show.
It's a grown-up podcast.
You do that enough, and pretty soon you'll catch her listening to it.
I'm like, I had to find out what all the fuss was about.
I'm like, welcome.
Yeah, welcome to the family.
Come with me.
Do they live in the area?
Yeah, we all live in New York.
Is she here?
No, she's not.
I had to take it.
That would have been a great onboard though.
If they live in the area, it's probably pretty good they didn't get into the show, because
we ain't got no more seats.
What's up?
I've had a TV show for 30 minutes, and I fucking lost it.
I'm an insane person.
Is her husband here?
Hey, you did great.
You guys are together.
Oh, that's fantastic.
Okay.
Here's a solution.
You leave your wife.
Jesus.
Oh, no.
John, John.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, hold on.
John, John, John, John, John, John, John.
And you guys- John, John, John, John, it's your first time here.
Justin's literally covering his ears like a child would do.
John, John, no.
Not about John.
No.
We have samplers on YouTube.
There are easier ways to go about this.
Please try our samplers on YouTube.
Please.
Maybe get her a t-shirt.
They're great.
You guys know this is where this is going.
Just go.
It wasn't.
Justin is shipping our audience who are doing her best up here.
Who's next?
Let's get someone from over there.
I see somebody in a white jacket over there.
Yes, you're waving your hand.
Yes, yes, yes.
The one who applauded.
Come on down.
The one who applauded when we picked you.
That's wonderful.
Hi.
What's your name?
My name is Dani.
Hi, Dani.
First of all, I'm wearing a Kung Fu Panda 3.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah.
Have you seen it?
It's so good, dude.
I was interning at DreamWorks when that episode came out.
Holy shit.
They must have been...
And you played it for Jim DreamWorks?
They must have been so excited to hear us buzzing.
I almost got fired.
No.
So my question is, I have had a childhood friend since we were in second grade.
Unfortunately, it has kind of turned into a hate kind of thing.
Okay.
Cool.
But this is a long journey, but...
You're on the razor's edge of Bummer County.
No, no, no.
No.
I got this.
Okay.
But I really love his mom.
She's like a second mom to me, and she is trying to pay me to tutor his little brother.
Layer upon layer.
This is an onion, Dani.
Go on.
So what I'm trying to figure out is how do I avoid that guy while getting paid?
You don't.
You rub it right in his face.
You are getting paid to be in his house.
He is there for free.
You are the grim specter that haunts him for all his days.
What's...
I shouldn't ask what the friend's name is.
That's probably a little too personal.
Let's just call him Chad, and he'll be like, hey, Chad, you got any little debbies like
you usually have?
I guess your mom doesn't have money for that anymore.
Wonder where it went.
Flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip, flip,
flip, flip, flip.
Your brother can do math now.
You Chad, I'm out.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, we did it.
Cool.
Yep.
Fucking fixed it.
Got it in one.
Wait.
You pick.
Right here in the middle, because we never do in the middle.
Right here with the pink hair.
Yes.
You got it.
Here with the cool hair.
Come on.
I feel like you didn't get a hand on that ball, the Tudor ball.
You okay with that?
I'm just fine.
Okay.
Hey.
Hi.
What's your name?
I'm Jessica.
Hi, Jessica.
I'm Justin.
So I discovered Maximum Fun while I was pregnant with my second child.
Really?
Named Moxie.
That's cool.
We're now-
I saw a few people nodding approvingly.
I think the ship has sailed.
Did Moxie sponsor your child?
Because they didn't sponsor my goddamn podcast.
Moxie did sponsor your podcast.
Oh, no, no.
Don't.
Go on with your question.
Yeah.
We sent you some money.
So how can we help you?
Or did you just want to talk to John like you're crazy?
So John helped name my second child.
Okay.
So the second one-
I need you guys to help name my third child.
Hell yeah.
Have you considered-
It has to start with an M.
M?
Okay.
How about extreme restraints?
What about just mmm and you call them mmm for short?
What about Mbembe?
Yeah.
Yeah, you really set us up easy for that one.
McElroy.
What McElroy?
McElroy's such a good name.
I figured you guys would have enough M names to suggest.
Macklemore.
Shit no.
Have you-
I've never met a person with the name money, but I kind of love it.
I'm money.
You know me.
You know my style.
I'm money.
Are you quoting swingers?
No.
Here's my driver's license.
I'm 115 years old.
I'm Benjamin Buttoning out.
Have you thought about Mark, but said with like a fun way, like Merck?
Like if somebody's having fun with a guy named Mark, they're not just going to say, hey Mark.
Never.
Hey Mark.
I would have to say that's a winner, but we already used that one.
Son of a bitch.
What about Mark all caps?
So it's like this is Mark and this is brother Mark.
Wait a minute.
This is for your third child.
Number one is Mark.
Yeah.
Number two is Moxie.
You have to stop that.
Might I suggest these are, these are human beings.
You understand that they're not your craft project.
Come up with something else.
You can maybe combine the two older boys names and call him Marks.
Yeah.
That's good.
Marksy for short.
Or mock.
I am mock.
I'm excited for school.
Thank you for the PB&J mother.
Mock desires applesauce.
You will bring mock applesauce.
You are mother.
Do as I say.
You do as mock.
All are become mock.
Hey Modoc at some point.
Hey Modoc.
Hey.
Modoc is very good too.
What about, hey.
Hello for babies.
Kill those were the real gay much play brought to you by play station.
I hope that answers your question.
Wait, wait.
You have to decide.
Well, Mr. Mr.
Manzy, but taken Maraites Mandy.
Mattington.
I like Manzi a lot better.
Mustin.
Mustin McElroy.
Mavis.
Mustard Gas.
Mustard.
I didn't know what I was getting into when I asked.
Yeah, you're just getting into a fucking free association.
You guys literally aren't here right now.
We're just doing a free association.
We gave up on words that start with M
and we're adding the M to other words.
That's a bad job, huh?
That's not even humor.
And now you see my problem.
My words, my words.
Just love, love large numbers.
I think the name was in there somewhere.
Somewhere. Thank you guys.
Glad we could help.
Thank you.
Let's do one more.
One more?
Yeah.
Right there.
Yes.
Red shirt.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right under, under shirt.
It says Goosebumps.
It's clearly a Goosebumps shirt.
It is a Goosebumps shirt.
That's so rad.
Excellent.
Which one is that?
It's Night of the Living Dummy.
I actually, I used my alcohol money on this shirt.
Because I.
You are going to be fantastic.
Yeah.
I'm going to say you don't drink enough.
So to answer your question, yes, I budget.
And yes, I'm great at it.
I have vodka in my freezer.
I couldn't bring that with me.
You could have.
I have to confess a sin.
Oh shit.
I murdered.
Not to, I murder a bunch.
No.
You know murder?
I bought an Xbox.
Oh, that's a great name for your baby.
Murder.
Yeah.
Okay.
What did you do?
So last year I made my friend listen to all of the Haunted
Doll Watch segments.
Okay.
Sure.
And she got really into it and started selling dolls
on eBay.
Hold on.
It's becoming Ouroboros.
It's a snake in its own tail.
One day we might do a Haunted Doll Watch of your friend's
Haunted Dolls that we learned about from Haunted Dolls.
Let her finish because I'm worried.
See that's the thing is that she hired me to write a couple
of doll stories.
You traitor.
You wrote Haunted Doll stories for eBay?
She paid me.
Wait.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh shit.
I'm all about that dollar.
One of them actually sold and she paid me 25% which amounted
to $8 consisting of a pair of socks.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Kind of a garment based economy.
Yeah.
It's kind of the barter system.
So I just, I needed to confess that I did technically.
I prodded you.
Yeah, you're fine.
I technically prod.
You're exonerated.
I still have those socks.
They're really, really good.
Nice.
Guys, two Hawaiian shirts.
That's the trade.
And we'll fight over.
I wish.
Hawaiian shirts are expensive.
I know.
For sure.
No.
Thank you all so much for coming.
Thank you, John, for all of the hard work that you've done.
A big thank you to the PlayStation Theater.
Yeah, seriously.
Fuck Xbox.
Fuck Xbox for real.
Blink's the time sweeper.
I can't even say your name.
Good sequel you did.
Oh wait, did he do a sequel?
He did.
He did one sequel.
Nerd sequel you did.
Nerd trap.
You all fell into it.
Yeah, you all fell directly into it.
Thank you to Still Buffering.
Yeah.
New to Groundwalk.
A big thank you to Sawbones.
Hey.
For real?
Thank you to CISO for real, though.
Thank you to CISO for taking a chance on us.
Please tweet about that.
Help us spread the word.
Tweet at CISO TV and say good job.
Good job.
You nailed it.
Yeah, don't say good job.
No, well.
Say great job.
We'll see how the show turns out.
Anything else?
Oh, thanks to Billions who booked
without whom this show would not be possible.
Yeah, thank you.
Thanks to Billions.
And.
You want to thank anybody, John?
You want to get some thanks out there?
Yeah, you want anything else?
I want to thank all my brothers for having me on the stage.
Aw, he's a sweetheart.
And so are you.
We got one final yahoo.
Wait, hold on.
I also want to say thank you to our wives and stuff.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you, Rachel.
Thanks to my baby for being so chill.
I was also going to thank all of my wives over there.
How about this final yahoo, though?
I just want to send up our level 9,000 Yahoo Juju
to have important support.
Whoa!
So we have our answers user.
Sorry, something's gone wrong.
It certainly has.
Who asks, is Wario really all that bad?
Asking for my children.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
I'm John Hodgman.
This has been my brother, my brother and me.
Kiss your dad square on the lips.
God bless you.
Kiss your family.
God bless Ur Geld drones.
Just say and I'll run.
Just say and I'll run and I'll run.
Maximumfun.org, comedy and culture, artist owned,
listener supported