The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to my brother and my brother mean advice show for the
Maginera. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I be your middlest brother, Travis McElroy.
Yo, g'day. Hail and well met. I'm your youngest, Harold.
Don't love this.
Griffin.
I don't love it.
We're high in the fantasy spirit, because we've just returned from
the biggest nerd event of the year, good, gentle folk.
Folks, the rumors are true. The meek have inherited the earth.
Oh wow.
These nerds, they're running the show.
Oh, I see.
I looked for a solid week for someone to talk to me about sports.
Yeah, you remember that poster that was hanging up on high school walls?
It's like, if you get made fun of now, don't worry, you'll be Steve Jobs.
Oh, I saw hundreds of thousands of Jobses here.
Everyone was a Steve Jobs.
Yeah, Jobses, Jobses everywhere, but not a basketball to drink.
Did you guys make any new, you know, big celeb friends?
That's why you go to Comic Con for the connectiones.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, you brush your elbows with arrow.
You brush your shoulders with flash.
I met Spider-Man, got a photo with Spider-Man.
Spider-Man came to our signing, and he said,
thank you, it's such an honor to meet you.
And I'm like, are you kidding with me right now?
After all you've done?
You're the web slinger.
After all your good work.
I left, here's how, what's cooler than being at a cool party?
Ice cold.
Leaving a cool party.
I left Comic Con's most exclusive event to go home and eat a muffin top.
A chocolate muffin top and a drink of vitamin water
in my hotel room while I play Dragon Quest Builders.
That's kind of the most exclusive.
The most exclusive party is the one you leave.
It was, I've never seen anything like it before my entire life.
There were famos littered, strewn about.
I stepped over the corpse of Stephen Amell.
He was just there, there's like 30 arrows there.
I was playfully pushed into the pool by Taye Diggs,
but then I bounced off of Cuba Gooding Jr.
who was in the pool to land on the other side
without getting wet, so many famoses.
And you're over there and you got caught by John Cryer.
And John Cryer said you safely made it to the other side.
Actually, that's not a joke, he was there.
Yes, and you can tell that when John Cryer said
the thing about making it to the other side,
he meant both literally the pool and figuratively
to the other side of fame.
To the other side of fame, and now we're all famoses.
You know what people won't tell you about red carpets?
And this is probably not for everyone.
I've only been to one red carpet event in my entire life.
Well, the Margaritaville was a blue carpet,
but this was a red carpet event.
We've only been on one side, yes.
You only are there, you could just walk in.
So there was a door that you walk,
this is Entertainment Weekly thing.
And it was an honor, wow, what an honor.
Wow, what an honor, H-O-N-O-R.
So anyway, we went.
And you go in, and they're like,
well, there's the entrance, and then over there
is where the red carpet is.
To go on it, you have to wait in like a line.
And this line is like, there's some people
from the new Spider-Man movie in this line.
John Cryer is in this line.
We were ahead of the Spider-Manzes.
The Spider-Manzes was behind us.
Not a Spider-Man, but like some cast member from Spider-Man.
Legit, I mean, top tier talent
that I honestly, earnestly suggested
we should let them go in front of us.
There's no way that we should be.
But you could just go into the party,
which is what a lot of people were doing.
There were five minutes less of canapes
for the cast of Spider-Man because they had to wait
for us to finish getting our picture taken.
Strange but true.
I did enjoy making good, good friends with David Harbour.
Now we didn't, we didn't talk.
Yeah.
And we were only in the same place for like half a second
as he got into a car as we got out of a car.
But I felt him like register
like my celebrity Musk on the air.
And like I registered his, and I think he was like,
there's another like big bearded man here.
Sure, yeah.
I saw it Travis, he was getting in the car
and you guys like met eyes and just walked by each other
and he tickled you real fast.
He tickled you real quick.
Real quick, he and I took a second
to bully Tom Hiddleston for being a nerd.
It was so fast, it was so fast.
Yes, but like that was the only connection we made
just real quick, me and David Harbour
bullied Tom Hiddleston and then David Harbour had to go.
But he did, he kissed me on both cheeks
and said, now the power is yours.
We were standing outside this party
waiting for the person that was supposed
to get us into the party.
And we were waiting there feeling like we didn't belong.
And as we're standing there feeling incredibly uncomfortable
and really not of a place where we should be there at all.
Tom Hiddleston, TV's Loki walks out of this place.
TVS's Loki.
TVS's Loki walks out and walked past us
and to get into his car.
And I asked Griffin, I said, I hope he didn't eat
all the free hot dogs that he had
because he had that sort of self-satisfied grin
on his face that he always had,
which I'm assuming is because he ate all the free hot dogs.
And he kept patting his tummy and saying,
yum, yum, hot dog tummy.
Yum, yum, winter king.
And then I did a fun accent where I was like,
they got split up buns, they got brioche.
They got a new topping only famos know about.
They got hot dogs too.
The sequel to dogs.
Yeah, that was fun.
Fun time.
It wasn't fun.
Maybe for Travis it was fun.
Maybe you had fun.
It was way fun for me.
Good, I'm glad you all received energy from it
instead of having it depleted from you like a vampire.
I expected to be arrested.
That's where I was at as I was walking around this party.
I fully expected a helicopter to swoop in and arrest me.
They wouldn't even send an officer.
They would just kind of scoop me up with a big claw.
They would lower one of those things that they use
to rescue people who have been injured in the desert.
Yes, except it's got a trapping claw on it.
It would swoop down and grab me.
And as I flew away, Darcy Cardin would wave
to the helicopter and be like, thank you.
Thank you, you ate all the hot dogs.
He ate all the hot dogs.
We saw so many, guys, this was a wild one.
This was a wild week.
I hope this doesn't come off as bragging.
No, we did not belong.
We did not belong there.
We were like the kids in the mix of files
of Mrs. Batesley, Frank Weiler.
We were hiding in the museum just hoping the security guards
did not catch us as we ate from the vending machines
to stay alive.
Dad added a fun layer of difficulty to it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, we played hard mode.
Dad, we did play hard mode, new game plots,
because Dad has a tic, which makes him, legally,
whenever he sees a famous person,
he has to loudly announce their name
or a role that they're well known for.
And there's fucking Ducky!
Yeah, right, yeah, Dad's four feet away from you.
Now, to our credit, and I think that this is a testament today,
did not say there's Ducky.
He said, I wonder if he's still bald
because he played Lex Luthor.
Yeah, that's what he said about John Crier.
And then John Crier turned around and said,
yeah, that's great, Clint.
And then once we got inside the very crowded party,
Dad would just go somewhere.
That would just tell what they're off.
And we would have to find Dad,
because he can't, y'all, he can't party anymore.
He can't party like Ducky do.
I will say this.
So Dad introduced himself to Brandon Routh,
one of the Superman's.
And then later in the evening,
our friend Sarah Benincasa introduced me to Brandon Routh,
and Brandon Routh said, oh, that was your dad.
And like, remembered our father.
He gets Sarah for you, and there's two places
where Travis is known as Max Kidd.
It's Huntington and Brandon Routh's house.
Oh, yeah, you know my friend, your dad.
Apparently, Dad told me later that Brandon Routh said to him,
like, are you an actor?
And Dad explained all of his stage work
in Huntington, West Virginia.
Fuck, yeah.
Yes, see, that rules.
I wish I had the spiritual confidence of my father.
But I mean, like, the whole thing was weird.
I guess it's all thank you to everybody
who came out to, like, all our signings
and bought our new book, The Avenger Zone,
or on the Rockport Limited,
and came to all our events and shows.
Like, that's the, you're the, you are our only,
you're like our cool friend that gets us into parties.
Like, I don't know, a bunch of other people know
who these guys are, because we certainly don't.
So we appreciate it.
Thank you for making all our lives so strange.
It feels increasingly like a dare,
but holy fuck.
They haven't chickened out yet.
Let's see, I don't know.
Maybe we'll invite them to, I don't know,
another party with, like, two John Criers
and see if they get the hint this time.
Just want to say this world is bullshit, you know?
This is the world of fame?
Fiona Apple, I just wanted to get out there
and say, like, it was a fine party.
The hot dogs were just scrumptious,
but this whole world is bullshit,
and don't let anybody tell you who to be,
like Fiona Apple said once.
Wow, that's beautiful.
But Griffin, what if I want to be,
like, a hobnobbing celebrity?
That doesn't, that's, then you're bullshit.
Oh no, ow!
When John Crier came over, he was like,
hey, I met some of your families.
I hear you do a podcast.
That sounds really interesting.
You know, I used to play, and I'm like,
bullshit, dude!
Bullshit!
Hey, somebody come get Ducky.
Brandon Routh is like, hey, me and your brother
are literally going out for hamburgers.
Bullshit, bud!
I've seen through your lies, Superman!
And when Melissa Fumero was like,
oh, it's so nice to meet you,
I was like, yeah, it's nice to meet you as well.
I'm a huge fan, and you're super nice.
See, he's bullshit, Justin.
Not like us.
He's falling in.
Sheep and wolf's clothing.
I, when I met, when I met Ashton,
I said, who are you in Lion King?
And he said, I wasn't in Lion King.
I said, then what fucking good are ya?
I wandered away.
No, that was good.
And he knew who had the power
in that relationship, for sure.
That was a good one.
That was good.
I asked everybody what they thought of Lion King
or if they were in it.
That's the only people I wanted to talk to
is people who had seen Lion King
or performed in the film Lion King.
The guy did Moana, the musical guy.
He came over and I was like, were you in Lion King?
And he's like, Justin, we've been friends for years.
It's like, I don't have any friends
that didn't work on Lion King.
Yeah, that was true.
He started crying.
Yeah, he was hurt.
Because actually, I was like,
Lion King's the only part of this whole,
and I pointed to everybody at the party,
world that isn't bullshit.
It's the only legit one.
And then Seth Rogen was like, I was in Lion King.
And that's when dad started screaming,
are you Nathan Lane?
Are you Nathan Lane?
Like in his face over and over again.
And they pushed him over the balcony.
I do want to say one other thing about this
before we move on for this intolerable section
of the podcast.
At a separate after party event
that was not really a party,
but was just a bunch of us sitting around at a bar,
Griffin did, during a particularly heated round of Uno,
hadouken an entire beer onto Lin-Manuel Miranda's pants.
Which I mention only because
it's the exact thing you're worried about
happening at these other parts.
Like, you're not gonna do something worse than that.
Like, the worst thing had already happened to you,
which you spin kicked an entire beer
onto this poor gentleman.
I didn't, it wasn't a hadouken.
It wasn't a hadouken.
It was a closed fist punch into a beer glass
because I got excited about a card I had to play.
And there it is, there's the truth.
And like, we squashed that beef right away.
We traded pants.
Okay.
Okay, moving on.
This is an advice show.
It's not just a San Diego Comic-Con recap.
A famous.
Nothing you just heard was a brag.
It killed all of us a little bit except Travis.
Even, no, even I was not bragging.
I have been in a cocoon for the last like three days.
Yeah.
Just recovering from having to talk to so many people.
Travis did force himself into a picture with Kristen Bell
and came back to us and was doubled over
with the exhaustion of the effort.
It took all of his power.
Or maybe Kristen is a Shang Tsung
and just got a little bit of that soul.
Just got it, pulled it right in.
If so, she's welcome to it.
She knows she's given us all so much.
Eat my soul, Kristen Bell.
Yes, it's an advice show.
And we help you, the listener, with your queries.
You can send those because I don't think we've mentioned this
in a couple of years.
You can send those to mbmbam at maximumfund.org.
Real queries for advice only, please.
I'm a pizza delivery driver.
And every time I deliver to a certain bar in town,
they tell me I have to dance or they aren't going to tip me.
I really need the money, so I humored them the first time
and now they ask every time.
And I deliver there twice a week.
How do I get them to stop asking me to dance?
Is there any way I can get a tip without dancing?
And that's from Ben Vereen.
No, mine would have made a lot of sense.
That would have made a lot of sense.
It's from Two-Stepping in Texas and not Ben Vereen.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think this is the wildest and worst bar.
This is a bad bar.
That's what it says outside.
It's a two-step bar, so they probably play it off
like they're chill.
Like, hey, come on in.
Now honky-tonk, ba-donk-a-donk.
And step this way and then this way.
And that's apparently dancing.
Now you do it or else we will suspend your ability
to pay bills this month.
It seems like this is like one step removed from like
the outlaw gang in town firing their pistol at your feet
to make you dance.
Yeah, it's a lot like-
You want this $3, you're gonna have to dance.
Let me ask you a question.
Every time you pull up to this bar,
do you knock over all of the motorcycles lined up outside
and then you do it as a sort of distraction
to save your hiney?
This makes sense.
I've seen this before.
Yes, that makes sense to me.
I just don't dance, like the next-
Listen, you gotta pull that bandaid off
and then we're like, you got a chance for this tip.
You say, no, I don't.
I'm an adult.
And then just-
That doesn't sound like the kind of person
you want to party with.
Yeah, I want to be able to party with my pizza delivery.
Or maybe just say like, my boss said
I'm not allowed to dance anymore.
My doctor said I'm not allowed to dance anymore.
I have a condition where I'm not allowed to dance.
John Lithgow said I'm not allowed to dance anymore.
In town, if you want to leave the town, I can go.
Or if you know Kevin Bacon,
I could probably make some arrangements.
You could wear your cleats inside.
Ah, fuck.
The cleats.
I can't.
Oh, I didn't know.
Ah, shoot.
I just came from my big game.
And before you ask, I won the kick.
And yeah, I did have a pretty special touchdown dance.
I did for-
Ah, damn it.
Okay, fine, you can see it.
Yes, let's go outside.
I'll do my special touchdown dance.
And then you've made it worse.
At that point, it's worse because now you have to come up
with a special touchdown dance outside in your cleats.
Maybe you get the first move.
You get the upper hand and you say,
do you want this pizza?
You're gonna have to sing for it.
Ah, okay.
And then when they're like, that's ridiculous.
I'm paying for it.
Then you be like, yes, thank you.
Now we're on the same page.
You take the pizza and give me extra money, please.
Just like I gave you extra cheese,
you give me extra money.
This is obviously untenable,
but I am very glad that you mentioned that it is two-step,
which is a fairly harmless dance.
Because if you hadn't included the genre of dance,
my worst fear would be like,
yeah, go make it clap out on the floor.
And then we'll see.
Then we'll see.
This is a miserable tip.
Make that booty clap.
Fucking tip everyone.
Tip everyone.
100% of the price of the meal every time.
This is the new rule.
It's rough out there.
Tipping rules are easy.
Now you just have to put exactly what the thing cost
for everything that you purchased and every service,
you tip 100% perfect.
Easy.
Easy to remember, easy to abide by.
It's the same number.
It's just the same number.
And then when the revolution comes,
it's all gonna work out, baby.
Don't worry about it.
And listen, this is just a helpful tip from me to you
who I've been a delivery driver at different places.
Tipping cash because they have to pay for their own gasoline.
Yeah, baby.
But then once the revolution comes,
that cash is just gonna be stinky, dirty paper.
Right.
Correct.
Then you're gonna want to start paying with credit card.
I have a Yahoo here.
Can I read it?
Yeah, bud.
It's from Graham.
Roboc sent it in.
Thanks, Graham.
It's Yahoo answers you.
They're anonymous.
Chelsea asks,
how do I remind myself to eat more kale?
I blank, I'll fill it in here.
I fucking used to love kale.
That's it.
What happened?
What did happen?
I've had situations.
When I was a kid, I stayed at granny's house
and I had myself a bean lunch
and then I got sick in the toilet.
A wet sickness.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Yes.
And then I didn't eat.
Yes, sir.
I didn't eat beans for like, no joke,
six or seven years after that
because I thought I was allergic to beans.
People would ask me, do you have any allergies?
And I would say, well, yes, I do.
Beans.
And they would say, are you positive?
And then I would tell them the story
that preceded this explanation.
Griffin, that's wild.
Yeah.
That's wild.
If you have a bad food time,
you don't want to eat that food again.
That's what I'm saying.
But that's not the same as being allergic to a food.
No, I know.
I was wrong.
I'm not allergic to beans.
Now I bean it up all the fucking, all day long.
Yeah.
Get off my thing.
Get back onto the question.
Okay, so you're thinking that this person
ate a kale lunch and had a bathroom, uh-oh.
Had a wet sick, yeah.
And that made them like stop eating kale
and then they just went like,
oh man, I should eat some kale again.
But every time the opportunity for kale arises,
they just forget.
They eat something else.
Oh, they forget about kale.
Well, you can't look at life through the lens
of every meal is an opportunity for kale
because you will absolutely just wear yourself down
to the bone like that.
Yeah, you miss 100% of the kales you don't eat.
That's, yeah.
That's what Brinsky said.
And that's why he was so fucking yoked all the time.
Yeah, also regular as shit.
A little too regular maybe even.
Couldn't make it through a game.
Yeah.
This person fucking-
That was his undoing.
I fucking used to love kale.
How can I remind myself to eat more kale?
Tie some kale around your finger.
That's a good one, Trav, thank you.
That's pretty good.
Kale shirt.
Can't get into bed wearing that.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe like hang some kale from the ceiling
that you have to walk through to get to bed
and then just-
They should have kale barriers on stuff.
Yeah.
Like if you had a kale rope tied around every toilet
that you had to gnaw your way through
before you could use the bathroom, I love that.
Just a big sheet of kale over the bathroom door
that you have to eat your way through
like you're in Metroid.
Yes, hire a company to kidnap you and bury you in kale
and you have to eat your way out.
It's good too.
If Mark Summers would just put the flag
in a big pile of kale
and you had to eat your way into the pile
to win double there,
I feel like that is something.
Welcome to super healthy, super clean double dare.
First, you're gonna go through this bath
and then you're gonna eat some kale
and get in some jammies and go to bed.
Now listen, it's gonna get-
Point of order, it will get super sloppy.
Just not during the show.
Yes.
Post-show is going to be an unfortunate sloppy situation.
Yeah.
At double dare after dark.
Double dare nights.
I wish there was such a thing
and bear with me here, fellas,
because it's gonna-
As double dare nights,
detective show starring Mark Summers.
Yes.
Looks like this one got a little too sloppy.
He shoots someone in the head,
he's like, I'm sending you to space camp.
This is gonna get kind of cerebral.
Okay.
I wish there was such a thing as an edible tattoo.
Well, I'm getting comfy.
Okay, go on Wonka.
It is kind of Wonka-esque,
but if you like kale,
if you were to ask me,
Griffin, sit down in front of a Google doc
and type out every kind of food that you like,
I would get the easy stuff first.
Pizza, taco, meatballs.
But then if you asked me to keep going,
I like broccoli, okay.
A list, a ranking even of my favorite foods,
I couldn't do it.
And so what if every time you tried something
and you were like, oh my God, what is that?
And somebody's like, that is ceviche, my man.
I'll be like, get out the pen.
And then I would tattoo it in my arm.
So anytime I got hungry, I could look down
and be like, ooh, what is that?
Oh, that's right, ceviche.
What did ceviche taste like?
And then you give it a little.
I think you're really close to auto cannibalism, Griffin.
No, you don't eat it.
You don't eat it.
You lick it.
You understand.
You understand that you have gone into human evolution
and have basically replaced memory,
our ability to remember, with a fun fruit snack
for the whole family.
Not a fruit.
This is what you're saying.
You're trading memory for the ability to eat your own flesh.
No, I'm saying you trade off.
Now I don't have to keep my favorite foods inside my brain.
I keep that on my arm.
Now my brain has more room for the 800 Pokemon that exist.
And we can get super hyper concentrated flavor ink, right?
And you'll be like, yeah, let me get ceviche,
but do it in ceviche flavored ink.
And so they would do it
and it would be really fucking concentrated.
So it lasts a long time,
but you will have to get a re-up every like three months or so.
Now, how do you decide-
We all assumed flavoring, Griffin.
I mean, we all assumed that.
That was obvious.
Yeah, how do you determine,
like how much do you have to like a food
for it to, is it like the more you like a food,
the bigger the tattoo is?
Does every food get a spot or is it like-
I think it's gotta be quick, right?
I think every restaurant has to offer the tattoo service.
Oh, but that's awkward.
They're gonna come over and be like,
so do you want a tattoo of our world famous fries or not?
But you didn't like the fries.
I didn't.
The truffle oil wasn't, no.
So no tattoo for me, you think?
No, I think the tattoo would be extremely rare.
Somebody eats these truffle fries and they go, yummy!
Hey!
And then they just bring out the whole cart
and get them going and get it on the arm.
I think it doesn't have to go on the arm,
but it does have to go on a lickable body part.
Yeah, it can't be the elbow or like the ear lobe.
Yeah, or your own butt.
You can't lick your own butt?
Haven't tried.
Do it now.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
Well, I can't eat ass while I podcast, Trav.
Fucking eat ass while you podcast seems like a t-shirt.
It should have a big fucking eagle on it
and you a rad thumbs up.
Or it could be like the keep calm and carry on,
which says eat ass and podcast.
Big Dogs is back with a thrilling new line.
Oh, shit.
That's our new podcast merch is just gonna be
Big Dogs inspired collection.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Should we do one more little question?
Yeah, I got one here for you.
My partner and I are out for dinner at a local pizzeria.
This is our second pizza themed question.
Listen, sometimes I put together a question list
when I'm hungry, okay?
We don't need to identify that.
Okay, so the place is somewhat trendy
and caters to young hip clientele.
We've already ordered
and we're told it might be a 30 minute wait.
The people at the table next to us just left,
leaving behind three untouched slices of pepperoni pizza.
No, next question.
My partner and I are both quite hungry.
It's a busy night.
We would almost certainly be seen by other diners
if we went for it.
Should we grab the pizza
before someone comes to clear the table?
And that's from Pining for Pizza in Little Rock.
And they have decided to solve this immediate problem
by sending an email to a weekly podcast.
And I salute you for that.
Now, first and foremost,
I wanna go ahead and get out of the way.
Food waste is a real issue in our country.
Thank you, yes Travis.
Why is it weird to eat that pizza
that no one else is gonna take on the table?
It's not suddenly,
like if they were still sitting there
and they picked,
like the people who are at that table,
picked up one of those three slices,
no one else in the restaurant would be like,
ew, but if you reach across a two foot gap
to grab that piece of pizza,
you're a monster.
You have to assume,
okay, I wanna take the social thing out of it.
I always, everyone is always assuming
that they're fucking up.
And everyone also assumes,
the assumption that everyone makes
is that everyone else knows what they're doing.
And it's a faulty supposition,
but it's one we're constantly making
on a subconscious basis.
You have to work extremely hard
to make people think you don't know what you're doing.
If you walk over and you pick up some za off a table
that was abandoned by some other people,
everyone will just assume you're doing it.
Assume it was agreed upon beforehand,
like they texted you,
they're your cousin,
it could be anything.
Everyone will just take that aspect out of it.
So then we're left with like a hygiene question, right?
That is, that I think is more debatable.
No, I mean, hygiene is not a question for me.
Hygiene is not a question.
This is good pizza, folks.
It's not like they slobbered all over it.
Maybe they did,
but you gotta just sort of play the odds
when you're doing stuff like this.
Food waste is a problem, Travis, yes.
And we are basically,
we're all basically already a bunch of just dirty dogs.
So just go for it.
Go for it.
Go eat this.
And if somebody gets on you,
just like throw them a newspaper and say,
we're all already dirty dogs.
So it really doesn't matter anymore.
Are you throwing the newspaper in like a fetch kind of way?
It can be a joke like that, yeah.
But they do need to read it
and then read it front to back.
And I don't know where you live,
but you're gonna make it to the end of that newspaper
and be like, damn, we're all dirty dogs.
So it doesn't matter if you eat the scraps, does it?
Well, I think the only concern would be
that you might get asked to leave the restaurant,
but I also don't think anyone working at the restaurant
would want to do that.
Like they'd have to walk over and say,
did you eat the pizza at that table?
And you would say, no.
And they would say, okay.
And then they'd leave you alone
because that is as much confrontation
as any human being ever wants.
Now, unless they, unless,
sorry, I gave you the window.
Oh, unless.
Justin, you're still there.
You gotta leave.
You can't leave me with unsatisfied.
Unless they wanted to eat that pizza in the secret back.
Now that is the thing.
And that's the thing.
Juice, when you worked at the OG,
were you snarfing down soup salad,
bread bowl, breadstick, whatever?
I got hired at the OG as a dishwasher.
So yes.
And I went back to meet the man who would be training me.
I watched him pick up a cup of minestrone off a plate
and fucking jam it like a shooter.
And then he asked, what department are you working in?
And I said, I'm a line chef.
Yes.
Because I couldn't study under this man,
even though I celebrate him for that.
I couldn't live up to this person.
So I lied and said I'd been hired as a chef.
And that's how I got to be a chef at the Olive Garden.
That anecdote I've told probably 30 times.
I've never gotten more than a polite chuckle.
But I submit that if I did become a chef in my life,
after that, it would be an extremely good story.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm just saying the value of the story is diminished
because I worked there for a month and quit
because I was tired of stinking of garlic.
You smelled so bad.
You smelled like fucking Van Helsing.
You smelled so much of the garlic.
I would like to pitch a new idea.
I recently, while in San Diego, went to a breakfast place
and I got some pancakes and as is always the case,
they brought me three huge flappy jacks
and I only wanted one.
And I kept thinking I should have asked around first
to see if anyone around me was thinking
of ordering the same pancakes.
And I could have just like, I don't know,
ride shared these pancakes with people sitting around me
and said like, I only want one of these three.
Does anybody else just want to go ahead
and eat one of the other ones?
And then I don't have to feel bad about ordering them.
I'm saying maybe we ride share pancakes from now on.
And pizza too, something that comes in easily dividable.
You know, like, let's, hey, when you're here, your family,
let's treat it like family and share fucking pancakes
and pizza, but just that.
Let's take a break from this.
Thank God.
It's all very good.
I love this.
But let's take a break to talk about the money.
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
Who's there?
Whoa.
I should have let you do it.
Yeah, were you calling yourself?
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
Don't answer it.
It's him again.
No, it's him again.
Oh no, this is a, sorry, this is a doorbell.
Well, they're just ringing it in a pattern
that makes it sound like a telephone.
Okay, try it again.
We'll get it.
Yeah, we'll get it this time.
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
No, thank you.
We're good.
Thank you.
Why don't you look at the app and see the camera
and see who it is?
I did.
And it was you.
So you were dismissed.
We sent you straight to voice mail, which is the modern sort
of fun, kinky way of saying we didn't answer the door.
All right, well, I guess I'll take this big briefcase
full of money and cereal somewhere else.
Ooh, I use the ring.
Ring is a magical doorbell that goes in the front of your door.
And no one knows how it works and no one knows how it works,
but it has AC video and two way audio.
You can set motion detection.
Someone showed up in front door.
You're not only going to get a notification that they're there.
You're going to be able to pop the camera open and see like,
what do you want?
What are you doing?
Who is that right now?
If you're out and about, I've answered my door from across
the country before and said, just leave the weed under the map.
One thing that I like about it is that if there's,
I'll just say shit going down in your neighborhood,
there are these neighborhood safety alerts where you see like,
hey, a bunch of people are getting robbed over here.
You should try to stay cool.
Try to be cool about it and not tell the cops.
No, you can't tell.
You should tell the cops.
But like, you get those sorts of neighborhood safety alerts.
They got a deal for our listeners.
If you go to ring.com slash my brother,
you can get a special deal on a ring starter kit,
which is the video doorbell and motion activated floodlight camera.
You can get that starter kit and save like 50 bucks,
which is awesome.
And if you want to get some more equipment,
you can also save more at ring.com slash my brother.
I use the thing literally every day.
It is the best.
And it is available for you now at ring.com slash my brother.
Gonna tell you about Blue Apron now.
So here it comes.
This is the cooking box.
It's gonna have lots of stuff in it
and you're gonna be confused by it.
Why did I just get a big thing of asparagus and meat?
Don't freak out.
Look at the box.
It says Blue Apron on it.
That's how you know that the payload has been delivered.
It's not a threat.
This is what I'm going to do to you.
It is a box that gives you that,
those ingredients exclusively meat and asparagus only
and then it teaches you how to use it
in all kinds of different ways.
That's one of my favorite things about Blue Apron.
It gives you all the ingredients you need,
none that you don't.
There's never like, what?
There's just a zucchini in here.
What do I do with it?
A fucking golf ball in here.
Zucchini is neither meat nor asparagus.
And those are the two things that are available
in every Blue Apron box and only those two things.
Now here's what's going to throw you.
They have started offering the Beyond Burger,
which is a plant-based patty, right?
So you're going to be like, wait, is this the burger
or is this the asparagus?
And you'll never know.
Yeah, yeah, it's confusing.
So anyway, they make cooking a sustainable part
of your weekly routine and all their meals
are carefully designed and tested
by the Test Kitchen chefs.
Boy, I bet that's a good job,
snacking around on these good burgers and stuff.
They use unique specialty ingredients
to bring chef quality recipes to your dinner table.
We've all used it.
I learned how to cook from it.
It's really, it's the jam.
It's the shit.
Here's some recipes.
Cajun shrimp and corn pancakes
with sauteed summer vegetables.
Don't mind if I yum.
Steaks and sauteed vegetables
with cheesy mashed potatoes.
Can't guarantee that those are asparagus.
I'm looking, they're green and long.
So maybe, maybe.
Anyway, if you want to start making delicious
brag-worthy meals at home without-
They also have stuff that are like non-meat based,
just too, just throwing that out.
You know, yellow tomato and zucchini pasta.
Griffin just chose to list off
two of the like eight different options
that both contained meat,
but there are non-meat options.
They look badass.
You can check out this week's menu
and get $60 off when you visit
blueapron.com slash my brother.
That's blueapron.com slash my brother.
Blue Apron, a better way to cook.
Hi, I'm Dave.
Hi, I'm Graham.
And we're two house DJs
who have been trapped inside our drum machine.
We love it here and we'd love if you stopped by
and visited us every week
on Stop Podcasting Yourself
here on MaximumFun.org.
We're just a couple of doofuses from Canada
and listen to our show or perish.
Stop podcasting yourself
on MaximumFun.org.
My lord.
I, yay verily, want too much.
Huzzah!
It's a Ren Faire version
of the Munch Squad theme song.
It's a podcast within a podcast.
Usually I read press releases
before I do them
and I'm gonna roll a cosmic dice here
on this episode of My Brother, My Brother, Me
and tell you about Taco Bell
revealing spicy details
of its new pop-up hotel.
Oh my god.
Okay.
So yeah, so they're getting in the hotels
with, it's called the Bell.
Now we've definitely not talked about this before
because god that's weird.
Yeah, no.
I mean we may have mentioned it
but we didn't have these fucking spicy details,
Trav.
The Bell.
Okay.
A Taco Bell hotel and resort
opening in Palm Springs in August.
It's a limited time experience
but as this press release certainly reminds me
all things are limited time
and this is a great application
of the time that you have on earth
is to go to the Taco Bell hotel
which is called the Bell.
Available for a limited time.
What is gonna make the Bell
such an incredible experience?
Is that what I hear you asking?
What are your top questions about the Bell?
Are you asking us?
Oh yeah, no.
Hey, it was kind of rhetorical
but I was also curious.
Are there on-site restaurants?
Yes, thank you.
The food, yes.
Yes, here's what's gonna be the best Taco Bell
and there's also an unexpected take
on a resort poolside menu.
I guess unexpected when you're staying
at the Taco Bell hotel means not Taco Bell.
So there's the two things you could do there
at Taco Bell and not Taco Bell.
So you're looking at maybe a toasted cheddar club
with hand-breaded crispy chicken, jalapeno, bacon, avocado,
sharp cheddar, it doesn't matter.
Or an avocado tostada served on local multi-grain toast
with avocado breakfast radish.
So this press release is bold enough
to imagine a world where I would be the sort of person
that would go to the Taco Bell hotel
and then say, excuse me, is this spread local?
Mm-hmm, excuse me, is this local multi-grain toast
from the region?
But it also implies that there is a person who's like,
I'm gonna go out of my way to stay at the Taco Bell hotel
but I don't like Taco Bell food.
It's just closest to my convention.
Think outside the bun, purchase local.
So there's gonna be a Baja Blast birthday freeze
celebrating the 15th anniversary.
It's gonna be served in the first ever freeze lounge
to keep things chill.
So I guess this is a very cold lounge,
perfect for enjoying the Baja Blast.
I would argue we already have those
and they're called Morgues.
But there will be an onsite morgue perfect
for enjoying a Baja Blast.
Fantastic, here's a quote, I got a quote.
All right.
It's from Rene Piscotti.
He's the executive chef of the Bell.
They have one of those?
Hell yeah.
Let's be honest, let's be honest,
food is the best part of traveling.
A lot of effort and homework goes into finding out
the best places to eat near where you're staying.
What is this accent?
I love it.
It's Rene Piscotti.
But with the Bell, we thought of everything for you.
You mean Taco Bell food?
From welcome beverages to room service
to build your own breakfast tacos
and surprises throughout.
What?
Whoa, wait, hold on.
You can't just say surprises throughout.
Surprises without.
Many of which feature local ingredients
like our horchata date smoothie.
We're curating the ultimate Taco Bell food experience.
So the Bell is a hotel that has the bravery
to look at the Taco Bell menu and say,
well, certainly not this.
Certainly you didn't intend on consuming this.
Do you guys know what a,
I think it's pronounced Hallow Klein is?
No.
This is when usually in like an underwater cave
like really salty salt water and fresh water
like refuse to mix.
And so it creates like a visible surface
from one water to the other that you can see.
And I'm wondering if there's one of these
at the front door of the Taco Bell hotel
because of how many farts,
like concentrated condensed like fart air
is in there that you literally can see
like a visible air surface.
Yes, welcome to the hotel.
I do have to warn you, our air is flavor blasted.
So you're going to need to wear this special diving mask.
It's local farts.
Farts, locally sourced farts.
These are farm to table farts.
The fun, the fun you ask?
Well, they've got the fun.
While daytime DJs play jams,
this is basically someone's nephew hooked up Spotify.
surprise performances will kick off
after the sun goes down for guests at the bell.
Fans can bring home the same vibes
to their own summer plans with curated playlists
from Feed the Beat artists, a Taco Bell program
that has helped more than 1,600 artists and bands
discover new fans.
And ladies and gentlemen, coming back to the stage
for the fourth time today, Eddie Money.
Eddie's back.
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, they asked me to do it again.
And I said, so here I am.
I said, do you got any more Crunchwraps?
And they laughed and laughed.
Anyway.
I've got two tickets to paradise.
They didn't answer my question,
but I'm assuming they're out.
I want to go to this place with a desire
that I'm not sure I can quantify
with the sort of linguistic tools
that we trade in on this show.
We very rarely get into sort of poetry
or epic narrative at all.
And I feel like that's what I would need
to sort of communicate the desire
with which I really, really, really, really
want to go to the bell.
Yeah.
If I may, Justin, it seems to me
to be a bit of a siren song
drawing you into the cheesy ocean
to crash upon the nacho rocks.
Like, you know it will be your undoing.
Yeah.
But you're drawn to it.
Let me remind you, you're going to have to sleep here.
Yeah.
That is hard.
The other thing that I'm struggling with
is I've eaten at Taco Bell many times.
My reaction physically and mentally
after that is always never again.
I swear to myself, never again.
But now I'm sleeping in a place
where they make it.
I'm sleeping at the belly of the beast,
as it were.
That's hard for me.
That's tough.
Can I read a Yahoo?
Yeah.
Yes, please.
Yeah, there's a Taco Bell gift shop, by the way,
where you can buy, it's got,
I'm looking at right now,
a Taco Bell is life tie clip,
which imagines a world
where you would be someone with a Taco Bell
is life tie clip,
but also have any use for a tie
at any point in your life whatsoever.
Well, I can think of a couple.
Okay.
CEO of Taco Bell.
Court date.
Be at bail, bail arrangement.
Okay, here is a Yahoo.
Gosh, these are all kind of food related.
Graham Roebuck also sent this one in.
It's a hungry app.
It's from Yahoo Answers user Ernesto,
who asks,
which food awakens the beast inside you?
Oh, yeah.
Which food awakens the beast inside you?
Let's get this out of the way.
I have, and this will just be a blanket
sort of crude humor joke,
but I do have irritable bowel syndrome.
So you can make an argument
that you're describing most foods.
More like irritable beast syndrome.
That makes it cooler for sure, for sure, for sure.
You've got an irritable beast in your system.
It feels like it sometimes certainly,
but let's not go down that route
because I feel like the Taco Bell one
used up all of our resources.
For me, it's kale.
Okay.
When I eat kale, I feel like a wild beast.
That's also true when I eat sticks of cinnamon or rocks.
Here's a, this is gonna complicate things
maybe a little bit, but are pills food?
Do pills count as food?
Do they unleash the beast?
In a manner of speaking.
I see.
A beast who's not as anxious as a non-beast is.
Ah, yes.
Compared to what the non-beast is,
I am currently and have been for a while now
beasting the fuck out.
That is true with Travis, anxiety Travis and sad Travis,
who is now doing okay, Travis.
The regular Travis, yeah.
The fucking beast.
Oh, a wild man who can focus on homework.
Yeah, I can get out of bed.
I'm the beast.
Whoa, I care more about the needs of others.
I wanna hear more about Travis's pull of homework.
That's relevant to your day to day.
Dude, that's all that work is now.
You know, I work from home.
It's all homework now.
Dang, that's great.
That's so good, dude.
But what food makes you go wild with power and fury
and you can be stronger because of the food?
If I eat the right amount of boneless buffalo wings,
I feel that way.
The problem is I don't know what the right amount is
and it changes every time.
It's a moving target.
One too little and I'm still hungry,
one too many and I instantly feel like death.
Have you guys tried vegetables?
Yeah.
Yeah, every show we've ever done for the past few years,
we request that they put some vegetables backstage
and then at the end of every show,
we like to take them and float them on the nearest body of water
and then shoot a flaming arrow into them
and watch as they sail off.
And then we say,
maybe next show we'll definitely eat these vegetables.
I mean, if it was a bigger tray, we would have eaten it.
I mean, I tried one of those orange ones
and I didn't care for it one bit.
Oh, the crunchy boys?
Yeah, the crunchy orange ones are no good.
I got sinus surgery last year
and while I was going home from the hospital,
they had given me a little drink,
a little nutritional drink of Boost
and I drank one of those and I was like,
I feel incredible.
But I think it might be because I was still high
a little bit from the surgery,
but that Boost made me feel so good.
So I bought like a 12 pack of Boost
and it didn't, it wasn't that good.
You know what I like?
What I enjoy, which gives me my own Boost TM
is I enjoy a strawberry and walnut salad.
It always hits the spot
and I find it crisp and refreshing and filling
and gives me the energy I need to get out there.
You are so not the beast right now.
This is the not.
But my beast allows me to finish doing the dishes
and maybe stretch a little bit.
You know what, I'll tell you what does me right,
what makes me feel like I'm getting it done
and brings out the beast within.
Sometimes if I have a really healthy cereal in the house,
I'll pour a really small bowl
like they do in commercials
and I'll kind of like put my leg up on a thick,
sort of prop my leg up on a nearby banister
like they do in commercials or a big rock
and just kind of eat it with my puffy vest
and a self-satisfied look on my face.
And I really, I like to live in that moment a little bit,
this world where I'm just having a small bowl of healthy cereal
and I'm about to use this energy to hike.
I mean, a big bowl of Mama Freddie's turbo spaghetti
will get there for me most days.
Most days, if I have like a big event coming up
or I'm about to go on book tour
or I'm about to have like a Comic Con Fred Savage encounter,
I will just like,
I have a little can of Mama Freddie's turbo spaghetti with me
and I will just, I'll cram it and be ready for the day.
I just assume, I assumed that was a given.
Like I would have said Mama Freddie's turbo spaghetti
if I had known like that wasn't just assumed.
Like, yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, I edited out the part
where I at the beginning of the question,
I said, we're all gonna say Mama Freddie's turbo spaghetti.
So let's just pass over that.
Is there, this is slightly changing the question.
So the inverse.
Well, there's Mama Freddie's come down spaghetti.
That's the only thing that can undo the turbo energy
or else you'll die.
And then there's Papa Cannoli's turbo ravioli,
which is basically the same thing.
This is kind of the inverse,
but like, do you guys at this point in your lives
know of food, perhaps specific restaurants
that you know 100% if you eat at them, you will be sick?
And not like a, if I overindulge,
but like 100% if I darken the door there,
I'm going home sick.
Do you have places like that?
Places or meals?
Fazzolis.
Fazzolis, yeah, it's not great for you.
Yes.
And Long John Silver's.
If you're gonna go in there, you're gonna leave back.
I thought you said restaurants.
That's fair, that's a fair burn.
On the Long John Silver's brand.
But that's the thing is, I will say,
I love quick service food, love it.
I can't remember the last time.
No one who loves it calls it that.
What?
Fucking nobody.
That's the ultimate fake test.
But I can't remember the last time I ate
a fast food hamburger and walked away like, yes.
Now I'm ready.
I really wish I could help make jokes with you guys,
but all I can do is sit here
and try and think of other members
of the canned pasta family.
The best I've got is Grandma Tanya's power lasagna.
It's not bad, it's pretty good.
It's not bad.
It's so full of protein,
but not in the places you would expect this power lasagna.
So do we leave, for the format of the joke,
do we leave turbo, turbo?
No, this is power lasagna.
The turbo, this is a different,
this one's more about gains.
Oh, I see, okay.
Turbo lasagna is speed.
This one's about gains.
There's probably a smart one.
Yeah, like maybe like Cousin Joni's meditative rigatoni.
Yeah, okay.
That one's about inner peace and mindfulness.
That one's about focus.
Here's one, Cousin Jim's good sauce.
Ah, so close.
Almost nailed it.
And then for adults who need a little bit of help
revving their engine,
we got Papa Pocky's horny gnocchi.
They're little, and it comes in a discreet can.
Delivered to your door in a brown paper package.
It does not say, it says not Papa Pocky's horny gnocchi.
Mr. Jim's nice food.
It's good, Justin, you're getting us better than that.
It gets better than the last one.
You're moving in the right direction.
Thank you, that's very kind, thank you.
Folks, that's gonna do it for us this week
on My Brother, My Brother and Me,
a show that we make just for you.
We hope you've enjoyed yourself.
Sorry that things have been a little bit scattershot
over these past couple weeks and the two weeks to come.
It's kind of like wild, wild time
with like the book and book touring,
Comic-Con and vacation and everything.
Speaking of which, thanks for hanging in there with us.
Speaking of which, next episode will almost certainly
be a live show, we have not talked about this,
but yeah, there is a, some of the McRoy's
are going on vacation after the book tour
and all the touring and stuff, and so I doubt
that we will have time to record an episode,
so yeah, I assume next one will be a live show.
But it'll be a funny one.
Yeah, you'll like it.
Or you won't, you know, like it's a free world.
Yes, so thank you to John Roderick and the Long Winters
for the use of our theme song, It's a Departure,
off the album, Putting the Days to Bed,
which is really good, and thanks to Maximum Fun
for having us on the network.
Shit, we have the biggest announcement.
Oh shit.
Bean Juice is dead.
Oh God.
Okay, yeah, not dead.
Well, but it's a new-
Bean Juice, as you know it, is dead.
We talk, we fucking talked about it.
I'm sorry, sorry, sorry.
We're not spinning it, like a fucking debacle.
It is a new era and a fresh face
that all our loyal bean heads are gonna go wild for,
and it's a benefit for their lifestyle,
and it's gonna be more relatable to them
and their friends and their families.
It is not, we did not take a bath on this.
We are making so much money that we wanna cash in, okay?
Start over, start over, start over.
Have we got an offer for you?
You're gonna be so excited about it.
Finally, a mug that keeps up with it.
Listen, you loved Bean Juice,
but you couldn't take Bean Juice on the go
because that Bean Juice mug
just wouldn't keep up with your lifestyle.
But now, with Bean Juice 2.0,
the new, latest, and greatest version of Bean Juice,
you could take Bean Juice with you wherever you go.
This is a portable mug, not like our first mug,
which you felt weird taking with you on the go.
This one, you're like, what if I did this?
It's just functionally, it's the same mug.
Can I take a swing, let me take a swing at it.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, please.
You're still drinking a Bean Juice 1.0 mug?
Okay, grandpa or grandma.
Don't think so.
This one, this is you.
Ah, time to sit down with my Bean Juice mug
and pour some of the brown stuff in it.
And you lift it up with your old arm.
Gonna put it to my mouth.
Hey, what's this cup say?
Bee-een Juice?
And while you've read that, while it takes you
the time to read that, I did a stunt over a vape shop
and got one already.
And when I landed, I was holding the 2.0 mug,
which you can read much faster.
And the 2.0 company, it's a rebirth for Bean Juice.
It's still pronounced the same way,
but the company is now spelled B-N-J-C.
It's so fresh now.
I know you were saying that our stock ticker symbol
is B-E-A-N, and so that's gonna be very confusing
for the investors, but they don't know that vowels ain't it.
No.
We don't care about the investors.
It's never been about the money.
It's about profits.
Yes.
That's the only thing that is different from what they
don't seem to understand on Wall Street when they're like,
we're foreclosing, et cetera, et cetera.
Unpaid bills, blah, blah, blah.
If we don't traffic in money, we traffic in lifestyle.
And profits.
Profits.
And profits that were supposed to be,
according to DFTBA, fucking bulletproof, my man, on mugs.
The margins on these things were supposed to be outrageous.
People use mugs, they said.
That's why Hank and John blowed a bunch of smoke in our face
at the same time and said,
these mugs are gonna make you guys fucking rich.
And when they blew the smoke, it formed the word mugs,
and then they turned the S into a dollar sign
by like, it was so cool.
It was cool.
It was so cool.
And we gave them our life savings to make those mugs,
and now they're in Tahiti, and we're left with the, no.
Bean juice 2.0.
It's the new cool for the cool kids.
Wait till you see this new design.
You're gonna shit.
Anything else?
Can we wrap it on up?
There's a whole bunch of new stuff coming to the merch store, too.
You can go to mackerelmerch.com.
None of it matters.
I'm going to be at Gen Con.
You can check out my Twitter.
The banner at the top of my Twitter has all the dates.
Dad's gonna be there soon.
We're ruined!
You can go to TravisMackerelRite.com,
and it's gonna be there as well.
And I will see you at Gen Con.
Here's a Yahoo that was sent in by,
oh geez, the hat trick.
Graham Roebuck, well done.
Thank you, Graham.
It's anonymous.
No, it's Yahoo Answers user, BearThePolarBear, who asks,
why is Peter Gabriel's voice nice?
My name is Justin Mackerel.
Travis Mackerel, you caught me drinking on that one.
I was taking a sip on that one.
Coach Billy's football fusilli.
Is that anything?
It's close.
This has been my brother and my brother and me.
Kiss your dad's square on the lips.
Maximumfun.org.
Comedy and culture.
Artist owned.
Listener supported.
Hey, James.
Hey, Nneke.
What we doing, girl?
We are inviting the awesome listeners of Maximum Fun
to join us at Minority Corner.
Ooh, fun.
But you know how we go on Tangent City.
We're the joint mayors.
We're not gonna do that, okay?
Soup's focused.
Okay, so Minority Corner is where you can all come
and get your pop culture takes.
Plus social commentary, news, and TV movie reactions
like Avengers Endgame.
No spoilers here.
Ooh, snap.
Sometimes we dig into the vaults
and we review and recap those movies you missed.
Good at you, Halle Berry's Kidnapped.
I love how she always gives 1000%.
Like Beyonce.
Did you see Homecoming on Netflix?
She was burning it down like the Mother of Dragons.
Have you seen the latest Game of Thrones?
So good.
Only thing missing?
More black people.
What you think about Mayor Pete?
Wait a minute, James.
We went on a tangent?
Yes.
Ah well.
Join us every Friday for more tangents.
On Maximum Fun.