The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to my brother my brother made advice show for the modern era. I'm
your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I'm your middle brother Travis McElroy. I am your sweet
baby brother and 30 under 30 media luminary girlfriend McElroy. Speaking of babies, yes,
they done did the thing they had another there's another royal baby who I saw a lot of uh news
outlets just simply referring to as second boy which I thought was really funny boy you're the
second boy second boy can be third boy yeah yes you can be the third boy you can be best boy key
grip three boy me who me three boy I love this new baby I can't wait for him to reign over all us
yes I can't wait to follow this baby's every command die in his beautiful army I like second
boy I question their decision to have invoiced by will arnett it's a little much who even wins in
the fight between the boss baby and the king baby right amazing yeah because I think boss baby would
make you know goo goo gaga hand me my briefcase but king baby's like die in my army kick boy boss
baby I also think that the crossover when they added the minions to work for a second boy that
was what are they even little yellow babies I don't even know they look like tic tacs what's
going on there what's up I do love that they call the future king baby they named him Ralph I think
hysterical and the way prince the prince of him the bad prince yeah lowered his sunglasses
when he said it is like the baby oh he'll be king ralph and then he liked and then the
banners dropped which I thought was pretty cool it's so good when I was getting my haircut
the person cutting my hair talked to me completely unironically I thought you were just gonna stop
there no completely ironically at length about the new baby second boy and it seems like that
should be against the law because it was a lot of like you could tell like comments like you could
tell that they really love each other and I think it's really nice the baby is being raised in such
a loving environment and I mean a lot of different things that I had a lot of comments that I had to
ingest about the baby king and it seems like unfair cut in that position right I can't I'm
captive I'm a hair so sorry Justin I'm sorry I just want to clarify please king baby because
baby king sounds like the king of babies might be I think that might be how it works baby is a
Kate Beaton book that I don't want to I don't want to step on Kate's trademark
what have you all brought for the king baby I thought maybe we could take a moment here
present him with our it's our new segment hold on what's your tribute all right oh sweet baby
happy birthday welcome to earth you're gonna make such a special impact I brought you something
that you don't have over here across the pond a fishy ships but I'm so sorry for that king
baby but anyway here is my tribute for you please do not dragoon me into your crusade
but I did bring you all my old tech decks and you are gonna love these maybe maybe daddy can show
you because of harry harry harry you remember harry you remember griffin harry's the uncle
who's the daddy that's william bill king bill king bill you remember doing the flips because harry is
the prunkle prince uncle now oh you're right okay let me take it again okay uh bill you remember
oh you swallowed him you swallowed all the tech no oh his guts are skateboarding around doing vert
ramps off the big intestine oh shoot guys I'm so sorry I shit it up real bad travis what's your
tribute um my tribute is myself I have been um working out um I so that I can defend uh king
baby what a sweet boy oh happy birthday you know justin he's here what did your what's your tribute
can you do the can you do the jingling I can't remember what's your tribute mine's mustard and
yeah because if the baby may be young for mustard now but if we start the baby on mustard at 12
months uh maybe it's actually six months we can start with mustard because it's not solid food
if we start the baby with mustard at six months then by the time he has reached fluency with
adulthood you know what I mean then he'll be the one that loves mustard and I might
have a shot at telling these fucking people apart when I am being told about their various
exploits and so the mustard it can all be in reference for me at least I'll have one fucking
king touchstone where I can say is that the mom of the one who loves mustard is that the one who
loves mustard's cousin is that the son of the one who loves mustard at least I'll have something
that can help me decode that explains the t-shirt when they presented royal baby to the crowds the
t-shirt that said I'll be your anchor point or king baby is your constant that's what my constant
royal family could that apparently people over here are just gaga for even though we we threw
off their shackles of their rule they are now ruling our social media and what have you through
these extremely important babies that everyone is just just gaga over if you'll pardon the
did you not hear me earlier when I said I say I uh thank you I'm reinforcing your bet oh thank you
thank you so much oh king baby oh what if dastardly first baby then decides that they
also like mustard just in your whole plans got no one else can have mustard okay period the end
good luck enforcing that Sydney brought something out to me that I the only thing I think is
interesting about the royal family besides the one who loves mustard the new baby who probably
does have a name um prince mustard prince mustard did you realize that every time they crank out
another one it kicks harry down another notch in the lineage boy that's got to be a mixed bag of
emotions huh you know I thought about that's cool so I'm six now huh okay cool so it's just the one
baby boy and then the baby girl and then this other baby and then great y'all too nice I'm not
the duke of uh north North Shenshire anymore cool that's the babies now great can't wait to see how
they run it so I guess I'll just hand over the paperwork great here's my scepter baby enjoy
enjoy that scepter uh excuse me erry could you scoot down please could you scoot down but there's
no more there's no more bench uh-huh we'll just pull up a folding chair for you harry at the end
there harry thank you make some room for me to put this fucking uh car seat that I pulled out
I'm just gonna sit here at our very fancy uh uh secession table I think that maybe like there's
but there's benefits to it too I maybe like every time there's a new royal baby prince harry like
things like oh I'm one step closer to being able to get that face tattoo I've always wanted you
know like oh yeah no chance yeah it's no chance oh yeah yeah oh finally oh I'm so close to just
being able to retire you know what I mean because like right being a prince for life isn't bad but
if it's like oh no you're the you know you're gonna get the call man you're on call that's a
lot of pressure to be ready to king at any point you know just take over it at any point it's it's
terrifying too much and that's it okay shoo 10 minutes we did it everybody got 10 minutes out
of the royal family not get it twisted that is gonna end up being a tight five and a half by the
time okay well we have recorded for 10 minutes and honestly that's all I can do uh that's as far
as I can that the whole episode that's that's basically the entire no we got all all kinds of
fun stuff I live on the third and top story of a walk up with one other neighbor sharing the
landing outside my door I do not know these neighbors well but I've seen them passing
sometimes they will put a bag of trash outside their door to be taken down later this does not
bother me because I know they have young children it would be difficult for them to run the trash
down every time it's full thank you occasionally when I'm taking my own trash down or taking my
dog out I think oh I should just grab that and run it down for them then I stop and think no don't
do that they will go crazy trying to figure out what happened to their trash is that too weird
or just something a nice neighbor would do what should I do that's from Waste Bag Weirdo in
Washington first of all they're not the stupids so they're not gonna think somebody's stolen their
trash and you need to perish that thought nobody on earth would ever be upset at their trash going
away and in fact if you did that to my house I would name my next child after you it was gonna
be Prince Mustard but I will name them Waste Bag Weirdo in Washington if you did this for me to
never touch that trash again this is such a bad thing because you put out your trash and you set
it down but not in the can and it's like oh I got a date with you later don't I stinky bag
I think maybe maybe you take the trash bag and you leave a quarter
and you start to develop like a whole mythos about like the trash trash fairy yeah I think that
yeah a fairy can lift a tooth the tooth is quite small I don't think they're gonna have the you
know the guns to lift up a full bag full of probably diapers which are the heaviest the
heaviest substance on earth is diapers trash gremlin trash gremlin could be fun but then
it couldn't be a quarter it'd have to be like a little buggy worm or something yeah a little
grubbing I think you're creating behavior with this that it that will be damaging to this person
in the long run uh because if if one time I put my trash outside my front door and it disappeared
I would never ever ever carry my trash down again never you've taught me that some that somehow
it's getting down there so I would not go through the extra work of taking it all the way down for
the rest of my life your mind is so good at filling in gaps especially when those gaps involve
touching the trash ever again or doing any work ever I would just assume that like the police
have started doing this for us like oh yeah the police have a new service so they'll come into our
walk up and then go up to the third floor and they'll just grab the trash out of there thanks
I sure am glad we elected that new mayor yeah really taking care of the church I will say
that the problem here is if you do this consistently to Justin's point if you do this
like four times in a row right and then on the fifth time you don't and they open the door and
the trash is still there they're gonna be like oh no is neighbor person mad at us I am incapable of
not just taking the trash to the can and putting it in there because 100% of the time a trash bag
is gonna have chicken juice in it and I don't care if you're a vegan and it doesn't have chicken
juice in it I don't care if it's just if it's just lawn clippings that you did from your apartment
where you have inside grass and you put that in a bag and you put it out on the floor outside
you're gonna have a big chicken juice puddle it is just the default state of trash they gonna
they're gonna find the bones and there will be raccoons that are gonna pull bones out of it even
if there's not bones they'll find a bone in there there's a bone in there somewhere and they're
gonna find it raccoons I was just gonna say that I've been running a long-term scam on my trash
guys where that I bring my adorable children out to thank them every time they come get the trash
and that is one because it's just a nice thing to do it's probably kind of a thankless job all the
time so I like to go out there and say thank you and you know leave a nice tip around the holidays
you know I like to take care of them so I can throw progressively weirder things away not just
weirder but bigger like every time I don't like like I'll send Charlie out there and we'll kind
of like wave because I'm afraid to go out by myself because I hate watching their reactions to
see what they think about the things that I've tried to throw away because I'll try to throw away
a lot of things that I probably should take somewhere where grown-ups will handle it for me
and when they do a double take at it when they do a double take there's only so many times you can
say I know right before you just have to stop doing it my Christmas tree is the one that I feel
juice just yeah because it's like there's certainly a place those are supposed to go
but I don't know where or how so I just put that out there it's lucky that it comes right after
that good old Christmas tip yeah because hopefully that's still fresh in their minds when they think
I'll just throw this dead ass tree in my truck do you do you wrap it up like Laura Palmer you just
like leave it out there wrapped in plastic okay uh how about a yahoo there's bang go ahead in the
percolator uh it's from merit palm it's from yahoo answers user uh they're anonymous so I'm
gonna call him bob asks oh no that yum you're like asks yes is yahoo a good stock
sorry where is this from when is this from oh that's a good question a week ago a week ago
you're hard no are you kidding 1999 sure buddy let her rip but keep your finger on the on the
escape hatch because it'll be good forever um so we never talk about the you know the
the bull and the bear that we like to wrestle with sometimes that we call the stock market
because it can be so exciting and you put your money in and then you see what happens maybe good
nothing ever goes wrong sometime it goes wrong uh pets.com went bad um oh shit did not work out
pets.com did i be honest i haven't checked in a while i put a lot of money into pets.com
all right well check actually do see oh you know what it just bumped back up
you just made a million dollars and that's every day you did put in a billion dollars though
that's every day that's every day on this market that we call stock because it's so exciting and so
this person either has many dollars invested in yahoo and doesn't know how to read the little
ticker uh which i don't blame them for it's like i don't know what the symbol is for yahoo um if
it's any indication of like what their service is actually like it's just farts it says like farts
negative a million percent no money left but knowing what we know about this service is yahoo
a good stock well it okay here's the thing if you think about it isn't everything a stock market
you know because you're like you're choosing to invest in friendship or you're choosing to invest
in like fandom or you're choosing so maybe we should look at this as like if am i is as yahoo
answers a good thing for me to invest my time and brainwaves into which is no but then again
we we invested in it 404 episodes ago real hard and it's paid off it's paid off big dividends for
us but i do love the idea of a friend stock market because you just be like how's terry doing like
actually that one thought it was a blue chip way in the red on that one farted right in my car and
so it took a big downturn the terry stock sell sell sell get rid of terry sell terry anybody
looking to pick up some terry i got i got terry for dimes on the dollar come on i used to think
hey do you want to hang out today todd oh i can't actually chuck bought up all my terry stock
stock i'll tell you about my terry stock i gotta i gotta go and uh divest but i heard he got uh
recently some butt surgery so this one's looking real good uh a lot of upswings in the future
you know how you always see the people running around all higgledy-piggledy on the the floor of
the stock market whenever people are talking about it that's like the image that you see like
everybody going buck wild out there with all like papers in hand and they're yelling about stuff
until a an upsettingly recent point i thought that when they sold a stock they had to find
someone to sell it to i thought that they had to find someone who would be like yo buy that
i thought that's why they were running around so wild because they were trying to find somebody
who would buy the best i got i got like 100 chiquita shares anybody like bananas i've got
kids i like bananas i got you good price do i'm doing trades if anybody's got one of the
walt disney world commemorative pins from the like 87 debut i got a pikachu anybody need a
pikachu for chiquita i got 100 chiquitas 100 chiquitas for like a bulbasaur maybe i don't
know how this works got a cadabra i'm looking for 10 shares of google this dude's gonna evolve when
i trade him so that's that's a that's a money earner right there justin if it makes you feel
any better i'm 34 i still don't 100 know what this could be fun so they run around the stock market
floor and they got the pieces of paper that i guess have either the stocks on it or an
amount of money that they have and it's just a way of sort of really thin pieces of paper
because i think they can't afford like thick paper yeah yeah they're famously uh unwealthy
so let's go around and just sort of describe how we think stock market works uh and justin maybe
you can start with it i well i feel like i described how i i did think that that it went
yeah um uh you roll up you show up you you get out of your fancy car and you walk inside you
have a few slips of paper that i guess say like you know uh yo play yo play basketball and eggs
these are my three stocks i want to get in the stock market yeah i call this is how i understand
i call somebody who knows somebody that lives in new york and that and they will go there to buy
the yahoo for me yeah and they'll say like justin wants to buy yahoo who's got yahoo who's who's
hitting who's got yahoo to sell and maybe nobody wants to sell theirs and that's how stock prices
go up because everybody wants to have some yahoo uh-huh and then and then oh no things have taken
a downward no one wants yahoo no one wants yahoo and then it's very easy to find it because
everybody's they're just dropping it on the ground like it's a racetrack i thought legitimately that
the papers in their hand were the shares i thought that that was like when people talk about shares
in movies they open up old boxes and they're like what this is a hundred shares of telephones or
whatever right i will say how i always thought it worked okay travis please um because you see them
and they're like yelling kind of up into the air like i'll take whatever i always assume there's
like one person who's like writing all that down who's like slow down slow down what did you say
how much did you okay i'll see if that is a bit wait what did you hold on who who said it first
everybody get in line or something what if i go to stock market and i have a slip of paper and i say
y'all is a hot one i'm looking for a lot of money like 500 like 500 dollars and you can get
all my shares in apples and then they see the slip of paper and it says apple in big letters
they're like yeah sure here's 500 and then i say thanks and i take all the bills away from them
and then they look at it and it does say apple in big letters but then there's a small s at the end
of it because i've just sold them shares in apples the fruit and then now i'm 500 richer and nobody
eats fucking apples anymore is that legal yes yes i gotta go then uh here is another uh question
for one of our beloved readers so my girlfriend goes to college and she is very into geology and
rocks at her school her geology teacher tried to get her set up on a date with his nephew who was
a geologist she said no thank you i have a boyfriend to which he responded is your boyfriend a geologist
didn't think so brothers do i need to fear these rock experts stealing my girlfriend
must i become a rock expert to keep my four-year relationship intact that's from demolished in
detroit yeah yeah yeah you're gonna have to get super into rocks yeah learn about rocks and we
can help you with that limestone i get bag it big gray geodes heavy small brown concrete
concrete volcano rock some of the hardest rock there is salt is a bunch of delicious rocks
tasty rocks melt in your mouth rock candy candy is not well rock candy yes thank you also those
pebbles that kind of look it's candy that looks like fruity pebbles the rock the rock is another
one rock and roll yeah the music blue dream maui wowie magnets how do they work different
strains i think this helps i did yes here's the thing no one actually knows anything about rocks
how would you even look into a rock so you can say anything is inside of a rock and no one knows
that is such a good point travis thank you yeah so like i'm so fucking glad you said that dude
because it was fucking good so like you could like take your girlfriend out on a date to like
a canyon or whatever and point and be like see that that's full of dead fish or whatever and
like who the fuck knows you can't see through rocks no one's got to find out what's in that
rock so you can say whatever i think you gotta show up to the school and i think you gotta pick
up the biggest rock they have and i think you need to take a big bite out of it and then you
chew it up talk about how big and strong your hands are you chew it up and you swallow it and
you look at it and be like this is the stuff you guys are into okay and then you shred on the
guitar and then you leave and then go immediately to the hospital oh time is of the essence right
away um that that fraggle rock flavor is such a power booth and they're gonna love it so good
though it always looks so good i get really excited when i'm like down when i'm kayaking
when i'm hitting the yak and i find a rock that has like a fossil in it but do you think when
a geologist finds out they're like fuck this rock is ruined yeah so let's go let's walk through that
step by step if you don't mind travis um just parse it we're learning a lot this time while
you're hitting the yak uh-huh and you see a rock big enough i guess to stick out of the water and
there's half a tyrannosaur just sort of poking out of it um you see that often well you know
it's more like you you you pull your boat over you pull your yak over to the side and you skip
rocks for a couple hours and maybe one in like a thousand has got like a leaf imprint on it
or a little dinosaur or a little dinosaur yeah and then you think well i should hold on to this
and then you don't yeah i mean what if you pull out a diamond you're like i was looking for
limestone and you throw that away because you're such a fucking idiot or one time i was eating
some oysters and i found a pearl and i don't know what i did with that i lost that shit that's a
good story am i a good geologist one easy way to make it seem like you know more about rocks than
you do if you're wanting to to maybe not put the time in is try to more frequently point out when
something isn't a rock oh you're walking down the street you see um a fire hydrant or grass
yeah maybe a big rock oh no okay don't do it to rocks don't do it to rocks no wait is the
statue a rock good question travis statue of liberty big green rock yes or no who knows
now that one's metal i do know that one but what about like you know that david statue that's made
a rock is that a rock oh all right they gotta come up with a better name for that david statue
by the way i know right what about that 70s show you know what i mean just name it something even
if it's like david presented by pens oil or something yeah it's like just give me some
kind of name for it what about what about dave's real proud of his dick dave's wiener
peep peep dave's ween don't cover up dave's ween fucking peep it peep this way keep your fig leaf
which is not a rock in case you're curious what if you had a dog made of rocks is that a rock or
is it a dog oh god that's a good question i'm just saying geology's hard i respect you geologists
we're finally getting into some smart stuff which i've obviously been wanting for a long time
it's so nice to give us some science on this one y'all let's get into this when when michelangelo
was carving the statue of david uh-huh probably took a long time right right like probably several
weeks most of that's been on the ween well that's the question okay okay he finishes arm torso head
hair face legs did he save the ween for last i'm not saying he was like grossed out by it but did
he know like his friend leonardo was talking to him like what's what do you got going on tomorrow
did he have even the thought of like well tomorrow's tomorrow's the weener day like he had
to have some sort of was it in his google calendar like or did he just do it and it you know
perish the thought not a second thought about it or he had to at least for a second be like this is
the thing that people are gonna be arguing about for a while i really gotta nail this dingus i'm
gonna bring one actual fact into this discussion and then we can go from there i know david
david according to google according to a quick google took two years working constantly
jesus get better jackhammer dude hey dude you're working really hard on this just to make it out
of cheese did you lick did you lick it and erode it with your spit what's your deal michelangelo
realistically it took two years to make was there a weener month
one i'm saying how long do you think he spent on the was there a whole month where he's they're
like come to dinner and like i can't i have to keep working i wish i could i wish i could but
i want to make this penis look very good tell you what you come over you stare at this penis
if you think it looks done then i'll come to dinner but otherwise let me go back to the lab
and let me keep getting this penis with a tiny chisel and the bush and the and the bush too like
he had to how do you the rest of it i get i want this torso to look fucking cut and it is ripped
awesome nips perfect everything's great weiner i think he just did it he probably look at his own
wiener just be like all right that's a wiener but the bush he had to have a moment and again
i'm not stigmatizing i'm not saying he was like oh gross a bush but he had to make a judgment call
at some point like he had his chisel this was probably an entire this was a week he had a week
where he just kept moving his chisel up and down the pubis like where does it where do we begin
i've done some quick math yeah the david statue is 17 feet tall so 17 feet what that's much larger
than i how much of that though is the fucking pedestal it's standing on yeah well but it's
17 feet tall divided by 24 months means that every month he crafted 0.7 so like about three
quarters of a foot right so nine inches so yes i could say that just statistically speaking there
was a wiener month okay so how was your september michael angelo it was it was intense do you think
he had a moment after he finished the belly button and i assume that this is the way statues work
where you just sort of start at the top and work your way down uh-huh do you think he had a moment
after he finished the belly button where he thought i should just put shorts on this motherfucking guy
i should just give this guy so much easier if i just get some fucking shorts on the do you
do you think he ever had a moment when he was working on the penis and it got very challenging
and irritating after like a couple weeks in where he's like i'm just gonna knock this fucking thing
knock this fucking thing off and draw some shorts on this guy i'm just i can't do this right now i'm
just gonna put some fucking shorts on it or maybe just like got shorts it's just like how do i get
these shorts i'm just gonna buy shorts and put them on this way that's why it took two years
because it only took him a year to carve it but the original version had shorts and everybody came
in going i don't know about the shorts and he was like chisel those off another another possibility
is that he knew the statue you wanted to make didn't want to like waste a lot of time on it
so he tried to find a big rock that already had a dick on it oh so like when you whittle and you're
like oh this is the perfect shape of like a bear and a log or whatever yeah this one is he looked
for this was probably one of the years him wandering around probably like greece or something
looking for the perfect the perfect rock right dimensions uh easy density to carve into
a fully formed dick just kind of hanging off the side and now we're now that's what i call a statue
and it's good that the it wasn't like it probably wasn't way out on the inside or else david the
final product would be like a dude like leaning backward arching his back with his wiener stuck
way out there like come at me which may be a better statue i i would like i would like someone
to now carve a companion statue of goliath just kind of like hey do you need a second um i'm ready
to fight you but if you wouldn't like put on shorts or whatever i don't i don't know if you're dressed
for battle my man um on this same uh website uh there's a uh uh there's a fact that the david
currently you can see he sits under a skylight that was designed just for him in the 19th century by
amelio de febree i bet his friends never stopped hearing about that fucking window yeah i mean huh
so like well it's sort of a collaboration between me and michelangelo if you think about it because
like lighting is so huge in any form of art so it's like kind of our step we know amelio we know
yeah it's kind of like it's kind of like you know he took it to the one yard line right and i kind
of ran it ran it through with my great window so it's kind of like it was my touchdown you know
if you think about it michelangelo and amelio's david is one or maybe if you want to go alphabetical
amelio and michelangelo's day they're still looking for a name for this fucking thing
they should call it amelio and michelangelo's david or amelio's amelio's david featuring
michelangelo and pitbull because that dude is just on everything listen they don't tell everybody
this but did you guys know that he just found the penis i don't know if that denigrates us
so really it's amelio and god's michael and rv david with michelangelo with special guests
and introducing and introducing michael
um
oh crap so anyway yeah learn about rocks that'll be good for your relationship uh let's take a
break and go to the money i've got about 25 david dicks on my monitor right now
yeah i have been staring at this picture far too long can i say beautiful statue a great
it's a really good statue is the one thought that i've had seven times we've been doing this like
man that was really i'm having a lot of fun here sort of dunking on people that are not here anymore
to defend themselves with a great statue but it's like a very good statue it's like a really good
statue it's like i don't know how you did it i'll come to art appreciation with my brother my brother
me this week michelangelo's david a very good statue super detailed bush next week next week
starry night too many stars maybe or not or not enough the hands are just so good how do you do
it all right next week penswell presents starry night uh okay now it is actually time for our
first sponsor this week is texture the only app that offers unlimited access to over 200 top
magazines including people the atlantic time and vanity fair with texture okay you love magazines
right but then they you get them they clutter up your house you got to find a place for them you
feel guilty about throw them away if you haven't read anything you can forget all of that once you
have texture it's got over 200 top magazines and their back issues in a single app so anytime you
want to explore one you can do they have issues of yakking weekly i it's impossible for me to say
travis if you sign up right now at texture.com slash my brother you get a seven day free trial
how many magazines can you read in that seven days i don't know you tell me probably a lot to
start your free trial go to texture.com slash my brother to start reading the latest issues of your
favorite magazines today that's texture.com slash my brother you don't want a bunch of magazines
around you can just have them all in one app and read there's a lot of great writing there's a lot
of great journalism and photography happening in magazines today uh and i don't think that you
should have to have them stacking up around your house i think you should just be able to look at
them on an app and you're gonna get pissed on the real physical magazines thank you yes finally
somebody said it so texture.com slash my brother you piss on your ipad you just wipe it right off
yep not a big deal one of steve's biggest priorities on that product pittsburgh not even
a big thing um my brother my brother and me is also supported in part by away makers of first
class luggage at a coach price i have an away suitcase and i adore it it has solid sort of
metal body uh you put stuff in there it ain't going nowhere it's got those cool things where
like you can zip to close one of the interior chambers completely and like hold your clothes
down and there's like straps to help keep your shit organized there's like a little bag like
that sort of floats around on the inside that you can roll up and put all your toiletries in
and that's nice and it has a little uh usb charger thing that you can slot in it's it's really slick
they use high quality materials while offering a much lower price by cutting out the middleman
and selling directly to you the interior features a patent-pending compression system helpful for
overpackers away carry-ons are able to charge all cell phones tablets and anything else that's
powered by a usb port a single charge of the away carry-on will charge your iphone five times
there's a lifetime warranty if anything breaks they'll fix it or replace it for you for life
for $20 office suitcase visit away travel.com slash my brother and use the code my brother
at checkout that's away folks there it is okay i want to tell you about we'll get it right next
year an adventure in cinema so is we brought a zoo about the mafia versus the fbi a love story
between matt damon and a scarlet johansson gorilla scientologists versus zombies and a dystopian run
by by big funeral who are we to say what happens we've never seen it michael and ryan hosts of the
podcast we'll get it right next year spend a year guessing what happens in a movie using bi-weekly
scraps of info from reviews and quotes surprisingly hard to avoid spoilers and we respectfully ask
griffin to stop referencing the movie i mean if it makes you feel any better i definitely
fucking haven't seen it either so i don't think i'm gonna be able to spoil anything but i can't
say one thing gang i think it is a movie about purchasing sort of a homebrew zoo and if that
comes as a spoiler to you it's it i i don't know what to tell you it's in the fucking name of the
movie so that's we'll get it right next year an adventure in cinema it comes out every other
saturday on itunes stitcher or wherever you get your podcast it's just like the movie ratatouille
you know it's about a rat at one point he's gonna fucking make ratatouille and they try to
tweet it let's treat it like a big twist ending and it's like no y'all it's the title of the
fucking movie i mean there it is uh i have a message from rob and it's for sarah and the
message says hi lovely hope you're having a wonderful birthday i'm thankful every day that
you've chosen to build a life with me and our little rat looking dog baby issie uh please know
that you're better than star wars and one day we will wrestle may fourth back from them in the
meantime let's go eat burritos and watch an anime you want to show me that's the most beautiful
generous message that i've ever seen happy birthday to sarah um i have a message here this
one's for joey and it's from sam who says hey joey happy 28th birthday slash congrats on receiving
your phd it seems like just yesterday you were driving me to school and forcing me to listen to
will smith's greatest hits you should be so fucking lucky um now you are married have two adorable dog
children and can give professional advice from your sweet baby sister who is still waiting on
her birthday gift i love you uh just jumbotrons are probably sold out so never mind that's the
only gift that's worth a shit these days um and so you you miss the boat on that one and don't
know what to tell you but maybe uh you know a fitbit hello are you looking for a new comedy
podcast in which case can i draw your attention to the beef and dairy network podcast it's a
fictional industry podcast for the beef and dairy industries it won best comedy at the 2017 british
podcast awards and it features wonderful guests such as greg davis to my knowledge it's the only
cow circus has ever existed in this country in rural russia every small town has a cow circus joe
seed long you should have a beef have a beef with them i have a beef with you i will have a
beef with you come around my house and i'll have a beef with you and andy daly that virus never
existed there was never any such thing as a mad cow disease that was all an illusion that uh big
lamb came up with that's the beef and dairy network podcast find us at maximumfund.org or wherever you
get your podcasts from and i would recommend starting at episode one bye if i invest in yahoo
stocks and then through this show talk about how good yahoo is to try and get it doing better and
then i sell it once it's made more money because i did a good job talking about it is that okay
is that a legal thing to do griffin that's not yahoo answers question that's just a scam you want
to pull that's me that's that's my whole thing right now just i think is that wait i was gonna
call that insider trading but you don't work at yahoo so is that outsider trading i don't know
what any of that means okay is that what they got martha stewart on that's what i got martha on
that was actually cocaine wait what lots and lots of cocaine um this is yahoo that was sent to us by
stacy trombone which is fantastic it's from yahoo answers user question mark this website's fucking
falling down around my ears asks what are some things you would tell your younger equestrian self
here's my own list one just because the ponies you grew up riding were difficult it doesn't make
you a horse trainer wow set your goals small stop thinking of the ability to jump in big shows when
you only jump small courses at home yeah man wake up patricia don't waste money on bling think
matchy matchy gear and spend your money on lessons i like that one a lot i like that one a lot no one
cares how much you know shiny metal you and your horse are wearing and matching if you you know if
it you know poops during a run you got to train that shit out of them pay attention when the
horse acts up instead of immediately considering it to be training issues what's the problem i'm
listening plan ahead whenever everything is going well be very cautious something not only can go
wrong but will go wrong yes number six is a good life lesson number six you don't need a foal seven
you don't need a wild horse just eight don't invest in that timeshare eight take the harsh
advice other people give you and learn from it rather than crying about it patricia no matter
how good you are at riding people will always be better than you and that's okay ten don't fall for
the cheap prices horses sell for you will end up spending so much more time money and tears than
you would if you had just bought a regular horse wait i want to hear some hundred dollars can we
chill down on the tears we all have ones we want to focus on here because i want to focus on the
idea that there will always be someone better at writing than you statistically that is not true
there has to be someone in the world who is the best horse rider uh it's why not you um yeah it's
me so i can go ahead and say like i've got another you know few decades to kick it on this world so
don't even fucking try it um so you don't need a foal you don't need a wild horse don't buy a cheap
horse because the rate the quote regular horse is going to cost you a bigger upfront investment
but you're gonna cry way less because if you get a cheap horse you're gonna have to spend so much
money fixing it up you know what i mean it's gonna be in the shop more than it's not yeah
just get a new horse don't buy used um but as soon as you walk that whole you that new horse off the
barn it's gonna lose a lot of value especially if you walk it off off a barn it's gonna lose
a considerable amount of value and so are you i want to go back and say that i actually think well i
think sea biscuit was a used horse and look at sea biscuit yeah but okay yeah sea biscuit one
but that movie specifically how much fucking time money and tears did tophor have to and that may
have been tophor was it tophor no it was not tophor grace no it was what's in it no i think
it was spider man on that one so spider man could have gotten i think it could have been spider man
right and he could have gotten a regular more wire tophor mcguire could have gotten a regular horse
and then won the race way faster and not had to worry about how many tears he was gonna have to
produce but would you and would you rather have one expensive horse or 10 cheap horses that's a
good point did you know when that when tophor was filming the movie tophor tophor was filming the
movie did you know that he that he thought was about him he was very surprised when the movie
came out and it was called sea biscuit because he thought it was about a movie about a guy who was
so good at riding horses that they made a movie about him you don't think he was actually very
s very surprised that they would make a movie about a horse you don't think when he showed
up and the horse's trailer was bigger than his that he didn't like figure that out well i mean
that one you gotta chalk up to just physics oh that's right yeah yeah the horse has got to have
enough room to run around so what things would you tell your younger equestrian self i think i'd
start out just saying like don't just try as hard as you can to make your fingers look less like baby
carrots yeah that's pretty good um i would say like hey that horse is three people in a suit
i've been hurt too many times yeah i'd rather know that ahead of time and go in eyes open
rather than find out after five years
i mean i got one if you're this if you're this froze up i'm frozen i don't have any i'm sorry
well justin we all haven't all been perfect equestrian since birth like you yeah um i was
just to go back i just don't learn i just keep doing it the same way when i started you know
i would go back and i would say listen i know fast and furious movies are really hot right now but
don't put nos in the horse it just doesn't work like that you think you knew where to put it and
i think in your defense you put it in the best if you are going to install a nos a nitrous booster
system in the horse i think you probably did it about as good as you possibly could but it's just
a sort of fundamentally flawed idea i okay i do have some one piece of advice don't don't get
frustrated with your horse and try to put him on your back so you can show how it's done and loudly
announce like let me show you how it's done and then call over friends and family to say i'm
going to show this horse how it's done and then let the horse get on your back um it's not it's
not going to pan out the way that you would would like it to go um i would also say to young equestria
me like yes a talking horse seems like a good investment but after a while like you and the
horse will grow apart and you will find his stories no longer interest you and you've heard
the same stories over and over again but legally you are still required to take care of that horse
yeah it's not even worth it just get a regular whispering horse that you can ignore whenever
you need to listen young griffin it's so important that you don't actually choreograph a dressage
routine to kid rocks um i'm gonna be a cowboy baby because the judges are gonna find it pretty
distasteful and in the future you're gonna find kid rock sort of politics also pretty distasteful
so that's just a heads up uh also sell your yahoo stock depending on how far along ago i was i guess
it's like what a decade so we said 10 years whatever however long it was sell your yahoo
stock younger justin and this also applies to both equestrianism and stocks buy apples
i like that joke hey thank you hey yeah can i ask you guys a question yeah is apple still also
called macintosh no hold on was the company called macintosh and then they just named that
would be like if mcdonald's was just like we're called burgers now we're called french fries come
to us for or was the computer called the macintosh hold on the computer was called the macintosh
because of the apple thing i would assume i do i i think you would assume it's called the that
because you think that there was somebody when they were like we're gonna call the company apple
there were people were like that's gonna get fucking confusing what do you guys sell apples
do you think that when they came out there and steve was like our company's name is apple
do you think there were some apple companies that were like ah fuck that's shit
wait i wish fuck i wish we thought of that can you imagine we would just just why do we call
ourselves sweet crunch that is not a good company name and you know i'm really glad that they did
all that focus testing or else their like original desktop computer would have been called the apple
granny smith and i just don't think that would have sold as well as the macintosh this is the
this is the apple this is the apple sweet crunch it's the most powerful computer known to man
apple red delicious i could do a fuji i think that would be a good line the fuji the apple
pink lady all right how many apples is travis no name how many other apples you know don't google
i'll know if you google i'll hear it nobody google i'm just and you want to know about
apples the sweet edible fruit produced by the malice pumila well i know this is my brain from
school we grew 84.6 million tons of apples in 2014 so when you say we you mean like the planet
it no me okay a lot of work planting 84.6 million tons worth of apple trees now you're trying to
sell them i got so many apples y'all i would like to be the first to apologize for this dumber than
usual episode my brother my brother okay yes even for us this is a pretty dumb one yeah sure
uh how about we do one more question because we had a long piss break in there and uh okay
and we'll make this one real smart oh no i figured out why these are dumbest episode
why because this episode 404 so it's not working it's an error code so my girlfriend goes to
call it at least that was funny so my girlfriend goes to college and she is very did this one
travis what what do you mean travis i he distracted with the 404 thing and then i
forward the link to the question i have a i real quick this one's sent in by merit palmer
thank you merit it's an anonymous yahoo answers user so i'll call him dougie asks
has the human body evolved for fist fighting a lot of people sent this one in is the human
body designed by evolution for fist fighting let me think let me pose
uh yeah well that's pretty your body has some smooth action i've never done a fist fight so i
can't really be a voice of authority about this um but my gut said my gut says yes i think we
probably either we had different priorities throughout the ages one was just sort of hiding
and survival and then using rudimentary tools and then we kind of peaked and then it was like
like i don't know fist fighting it would be pretty cool to be very good at and so our
fists got bigger arm got stronger bodies got better at taking the fist punches um i don't
know my i'm a beautiful machine of fury and violence well that's when i look at my body
i'm looking at my body for the first time just thinking i'm a beautiful machine of fury and
violence i didn't know it until this moment i'm thinking about how every every piece of my body
is designed to be better at fist fighting yeah so break it down bite bite for bite for me well i
have the beard which protects my jaw yeah it's like natural armor um my glasses which of course
grow out of my face that protect my eyes well your eyes got bad and that was evolution's way
of saying you need some sort of covering on here for people with you know sharper knuckles yeah and
then i turned 22 and started packing on the lbs to protect my guts yeah you know what i mean so i
got a little extra padding there so if someone tries to punch you in the guts they're like oh
i can't even get through it and i remember that travis on your 22nd birthday we got in a fist
fight and i beat the snot out of you dude yeah and you said i'm making the decision today to
you know add some add some some padding and i did and he did also my fists are three feet wide
travis just got the ever long hands he's got ever long hands in this one i've got ed for long hands
and so they let me punch better and punch like six people at a time it's tough to know this
personally right because that's not how evolution works you don't you don't use a leaf stone on
yourself and then turn into venus or it's like you can't see that but um i have a son now and
when i look at his beautiful fists all i can think is wow we're really moving in that direction huh
we're really moving in sort of a fist fight and i don't want my son to ever get in a fist fight
but i know that his body because of evolution how it works is gonna be just crazy and wild in the
in the ring or the you know wherever it is he has to fight with his fists do you think glass joe from
punch out was like the last evolutionary link we had to that line of humanity like he was the last
one and you just punched him out because we evolved past it obviously i haven't seen anybody
with his particular malady you're right yeah it's kind of like the evolution of man of like seeing
the monkey turn into the person which is like science is still out on that one it's a fun it's
a fun theory but uh still waiting to hear back on that one but you can sort of follow the same
trajectory going from glass joe to king hippo you see king hippo and you're like perfect specimen
king hippo punching of punching his body his body can do nothing else he leaves the ring after
punching so good because his body's been perfectly tuned for that purpose and he walks out of the
ring and like tries to open a door and can't because his body just so he punches it right
open and of course that works and you know punches spaghetti into his mouth you know i've never seen
the wrestler but this is what i assume the wrestler is like yeah it's mickey roark v king hippo from
uh punch out and it's just like mickey roark wrestling food into his face to where we're
starting a new podcast about us guessing what's in the wrestler it's called we'll get it right next
year and it's about us guessing about that it's called i'll get it right next year too the sequel
to the podcast that paid us to advertise them i'm gonna google real king hippo because i need to know
if king hippo but real king hippo versus prince mustern is the thing about king hippo what
evolution told us is like your instinct would be the perfect puncher would have
few places to punch but what king hippo does it's his he says there's many places to punch
so that he can take more of them you know what i mean if you think about like you have more body
mass so it's like there's more space for you to store punches yeah probably probably king hippo
is god played god played a joke on him well one problem juiced and that is his huge weak point
designated by an x-shaped bandage that he has over his belly button and i guess that's because his
body got so crazy that and so perfect for fighting and so crazy that he needed something to hold
his you know punching guts in and that is this bandage and it got hippo did you not even think
about making it like flesh colored at least or just not an x shape yeah you could have made it
any shape power in that shit like 45 degrees you got a plus sign if he just hiked his pants up
nobody would have any fucking clue what to do with him just pull your pants up king hippo
pull your pants up king hippo and then no one will know oh um i will say thank you wikipedia
for clarifying that king hippo is a fictional boxer from nintendo's punch out thank you for
clarifying that wikipedia um that folks that's this is the ideal male body come on uh thanks
for listening to our show uh we are going to be next week this is your last movie man before
this this happened no sorry this week when you're hearing this we are going to be in detroit and
saint louis or more accurately saint louis and detroit uh we really hope that y'all come out
to those shows they are going to happen on thursday and friday this week thursday saint
louis friday detroit both their shows start at 7 p.m um the saint louis peabody opera house detroit
masonic temple theater you can go to bit uh sorry uh mackleroy shows dot com slash tours
to find links to those we really hope you'll come out there uh uh we got some good seats we're also
going to be in columbus i don't think you said that but is that one sold out it's sold out oh
sorry columbus but um this is almost sold out so maybe it's not 100 oh no nope website says sold
out just sold the last ticket while recording this thanks derrick if you can get to those shows
we really hope you do because it's going to be a fun time and don't forget to send in your
questions both regular and yahoo and be sure to put in the subject line detroit show saint louis
show or columbus show um i want to thank john rogerick and the long winters for the use of
our theme song it's a departure off the album putting the days to bed it is a very good album
we're very grateful that we are allowed to use it as our theme song and i want to thank max fun
for having us on the network you can go to maximumfund.org and check out all the great
shows there shows like stop podcasting yourself and tights and fights and the beef and dairy
network and so many more at maximumfund.org and if you want to hear or see other stuff that we do
you go to mcroyshows.com also um in case you missed it last week we are going to be on the
joko cruise this year on the joko cruise 2019 and those cabins are selling really quickly
um so if you'd like to join us on the cruise it is incredibly fun uh joco cruise.com is where
you need to head to get those tickets before they sell out joko cruise.com um also i don't know if
we've mentioned in a while but we are releasing a graphic novel uh of our first arc of the adventure
zone here there be gerblin's you can get that at the adventure zone comic.com um we have a lot of
merch for the shows with a lot more coming out you'll find that at mcroymerch.com and justin and
sydney are writing a saw bones book that you can pre-order now yes that that we just put those
pre-orders up if you go to bit.ly forward slash saw bones book if you've never listened to saw
bones if you have listened to saw bones i think that's all the people on earth yeah that's
everybody please pre-order that it's got uh sydney and i wrote it are writing it are finishing it
it's got illustrations by taylor smurl her sister who's who's very gifted and uh does a great job
with it and it's gonna be it's a fun creepy read with no swears so it's great for kids and non-kids
either way again everyone here's a final yahoo that was sent in by anna davis thank you anna
it's yahoo answers user question mark hey guys the fuck's going on with this website
sell your fucking yahoo stock now buy apples uh i i'm gonna say this one was sent in was
asked by mcintosh who asks what is that one movie where jidna z lohan switched bodies with
jamie lee curtis not freaky friday the other one
i'm travis mcroy i'm griffin mcroy my brother my brother and me kiss your dad square on the lip
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
judge john hodgeman ruled in my favor judge john hodgeman won the case of the
judge john hodgeman podcast i hear their cases i ask them questions they're good ones and then i
tell them who's right and who's wrong.
you're hearing the voices of real litigants real people who have submitted disputes to my
internet court at the judge john hodgeman podcast i hear their cases i ask them questions they're
questions, they're good ones. And then I tell them who's right and who's wrong.
Thanks to Judge John Hodgman's ruling, my dad has been forced to retire one of the worst
dad jokes of all time. Instead of cutting his own hair with a flow
bee, my husband has his hair cut professionally. I have to join a community theater group.
And my wife has stopped bringing home wild animals.
It's the Judge John Hodgman podcast. Find it every Wednesday at MaximumFun.org or wherever
you download podcasts. Thanks Judge John Hodgman.