I need help and I don't know where else to turn I've got a problem deep inside me and
I'm feeling quite concerned It's an issue and I feel I need some input
and insight Into if it's something serious or if I could
just might be overreacting Got the problem I'm having and it's really
no big deal and I should probably be laughing But I think I better talk to someone wiser
than I Get a second opinion just to be on the safe
side
You know what?
An opinion's three and four Cause I know just who I need
I need the brothers McElroy Three sages from the past
Dispensing wisdom for the ages The greatest modern minds
Mending hearts like magic mages I could write pages
About all they've done to help me Like when I caught on fire
Or that time I lost my house keys I will never tire
Of the way this show delights me Advice for the modern era
It's my brother, my brother and me
Just give me a big bottle of pee
The bed you supplied us with is quite loud And we're afraid that our noise-making will
be a ruckus So what bed might be quieter that you could
accommodate us with?
And also, where can I put my oversized duffel bag
With the words, you need your bags
If you change your mind, I'm the first in line Honey, I'm still free, take a chance on me
If you need me, let me know, I'm gonna be around
If you got no place to go when you're feeling down
If you're all alone, when the pretty birds have flown
Then let the money run free Take a chance on me
Finally, being the one to recognize that the true sound
Of my brother, my brother and me is rap
It's the sweet sound of the streets
We all agree that we are urban
We are nothing if not street
Hip-hop
R&B
Most of our episodes are about hip-hop and R&B
I draw most of the things we say from the recordings of Jay-Z and Missile War in Hell
Is it sad that for the better part of my entire life
I thought R&B stood for Rap and Beats?
What?
When did you discover otherwise?
I thought it stood for Rap and Beats
This is My Brother, My Brother and Me
And it's an advice show for the modern era
We also will teach you that R&B does not stand for Rap and Beats
What does it stand for?
How well do you enjoy that Rap and Beats music?
She's the greatest Rap and Beat singer of all time
Aaliyah is the new princess of hip-hop and Rap and Beats
God bless you
Hello Brothers McElroy, this is Michael from California
And I am wondering, how do you learn better?
How do you learn to dress better?
Sorry, got cut off a little bit
That's not your fault, Michael
I'm wondering, how do you learn to dress better?
I'm tired of just wearing nerdy t-shirts all the time
And I have no idea how to start learning how to dress more mature
Thank you
Griffin's got a great answer, watch this
I do?
Well, I was going to suggest that you need to watch a hit web series
Oh, that's right
That's called Put This On, by close personal friend of the show
Jesse Thorn and Adam Lissagore
Well, they are sort of friends of the show
If you're here, thanks to our friends at Maximumfun.org
You have probably heard the name Jesse Thorn
Put This On, there's not enough episodes for my taste
It's at PutThisOn.com
There's just two right now about jeans and shoes
That blog is chock full of tips
What do they say about jeans?
This is a discussion I've been having a lot lately
Their conclusion is that jeans can qualify as fancy dress if worn properly
You should watch it, Travis, you'll get into it
Because it's all about finding a good pair of jeans for you
And then how to maintain those jeans
I was talking to Teresa the other day
And I made her promise that when I reach the point
That I'm too old to wear jeans
That she is sworn to tell me
So she can just kill you
Yeah, and then it's just sweet, sweet death
Let's get back to Michael's question
I think you need to expand beyond nerdy t-shirts
Because those are inherently undressy
Find yourself a nice polo shirt
A nice button up
It's not that hard to dress better
Yeah, just start at the ground up
I would also say that you should
That you could get a t-shirt that's not necessarily nerdy
Maybe something more universal
Something everyone can relate to
Like, for instance, a My Brother, My Brother and Me t-shirt
Available for one day only
This final day at MBMBAM.com
It may even be too late
It may be too late if you're listening to this on Tuesday
But still go look, we might work something out for you
Or just plain t-shirts
Plain t-shirts, that's a classy look
Just a plain, tight fit
You know what I like? A nice corduroy jacket
You know what? A jacket is a good pro tip
Because I could dress up anything
I wear a nice tan jacket at trade shows and things
Because it classes up the look without having to buy a whole new wardrobe
Corduroy is good too though
Go to Target and look at their jackets
They have nice jackets for $20-$30
And you'll wear those things for months
100 years
I finally found out, this is from Michael
I recently found out that my wife and I are expecting a baby
Mazel tov
Congrats
This will be our first
So we're a little nervous about what to expect
Immediately things changed my mind about priorities
I'm also a little listener to the Joystick Podcast
I love my gaming time
How can I balance my new child and keep the trophies rolling in?
First, that sounds dangerous
If you're trying to balance a baby
While at the same time trophies are rolling at you
You may already be a bad parent
Is the baby on your head?
Is this where you're balancing him?
Like a book?
Like a hilarious silent film starring Buster Keaton
There's a baby balanced precariously on your head as trophies roll at you
I think the most important thing about being a parent
Is knowing where to turn for advice about parenting
It's definitely us
You've already cracked the case with the first biggest problem
Which is where to turn for parenting advice
I've seen 3 men and a baby
I've seen 4 men and a baby
I've seen 2 and a half men
I've seen babies stay out
I've seen...
Dunstan checks in
Dunstan checks in, which isn't exactly about parenting
I've seen most viable primate
I've seen air bud
I've seen most vertical primate
We got off the subject right now
I saw Milo and Otis
Land Before Times Part 1, 2, 3, and 4
Land of the Lost
Listen
Michael, the truth is
The truth is, I think
Fire, rain
In order to be a good parent
You have to not do the things that you used to like doing
I think that there's a
I think there's a ratio, an inverse
Ratio between the sacrifices of your fun time
To the relative health of your child
Let me give you a trophy
To reach for
An achievement to try to gain
And that is
Didn't raise a serial killer
100 gamer score
100 gamer score for not raising someone who murders you in your sleep
The way it works is when you grow up
When you have a child
You've been doing cool shit your whole life
Now it's your child's turn to do cool shit
And it's your time to do bummer shit
It's like the Highlander
There can be only one person who's
Enjoying their life at one time
And guess what friend
It's not you anymore
I'm 30 years old
And have recently made a friend in World of Warcraft
Who I've been playing with regularly
Last week I found out he's a 15 year old boy
And when I told my girlfriend
She freaked out and said it was weird
And that I should stop playing with him
What do I do?
I can't tell you the number of times my wife has walked in on me
With a 15 year old boy
And she's like oh no I'll call the cops
I'll leave you blah blah blah blah
It's like chill out lady
He's our neighbor
How am I gonna get better at recording pop music
Well pop
Pop influence by rapping beats
Like Michael Jackson
If I can't play with 15 year old boys
Someone's gotta teach this kid to shave
It's not gonna be his deadbeat dad
You gotta be in front of the mirror
With like whipped cream on his face and a spoon
It's easy it's just like this
It's real good slower
Slower
So much slower
Daniel
This is such a problem of the modern
The modern age
Yeah it is
You know I imagine someone
20 years ago reading this question
Would think it was written
In a different language
I think
When we talked about the question about
Kissing your dad's square on the lips
If you don't think it's weird then it's not
Weird
It is pretty fucking weird though
It's weird though
I assume you guys are just like rating
Whatever people do on that World of Warcraft
Jam
There's nothing you can do
In World of Warcraft with a 15 year old boy that doesn't make you sound like
A gay pedophile
We were just rating
We were just pounding the dragon
On our sewing
We were just teaching him some leather work
We were grinding
We were just grinding
I was grinding with a 15 year old and my wife
Flipped
This is
This is something where
Just pretend you don't know it
Are you sure it's not Chris Hanson on the other end
Saying he's a 15 year old boy
That's the future of To Catch a Predator
Why are you hanging with him?
Maybe find someone your own age
Also playing World of Warcraft
Or switch to Second Life
Because that place is just
Just ripe for the harvest
Of just sweet
Sweet succulent teenage fruit
Just hanging
Hanging low on the tree
You know there's Marshall in Second Life now
Yeah I saw that
Marshall University, my alma mater
And Justin's alma mater
Now has a virtual college
In Second Life
Am I allowed to
I haven't discussed this with my wife
Am I allowed to go to virtual Marshall
And do the things that I did at real Marshall
Without fear of repercussions?
Is that how that works?
Well give me an example of some of these things
Like
If I go to Second Life
Can I set a
Dumpster on fire and then blame it
On a pizza guy that walked by earlier
Is that okay?
I mean it depends if the programmers
Have enabled that
Option for you to do in the game
How's your tech?
How is the tech on this if I can't burn
A dumpster?
I don't know
I would love to see if I could get kicked out of
Second Life Marshall though
I would love to see what it takes to do
When you do you have to walk out screaming
That's it I'm starting Third Life
On one hand
You have it as a recruitment tool
That's what they built it for
So that they can take students on a virtual tour
So I'd love to show up as a prospective
You know student
And walk around that group
And cause all kinds of shenanigans
I'd just like to sit on the quad
And play my guitar that's it
Just don't bother me
Just run into the middle of a group? You guys trying to sack?
You guys want to sack?
We're going to sack over at the student center in 15
Meet by the John and my 15 year old friend
We're just sacking together
We're going to do some disc
You guys like Dave Matthews?
It's a crazy game of poker
Today right?
Allen writes from Gmail
I'm starting my senior year of high school
And my parents are becoming increasingly pushy
About telling me I need to decide where I want to go
To college
Have you considered Marshall?
Have you considered virtual Marshall?
Have you considered VMU?
I'm at the top of my class and should have no problem
Getting a scholarship the problem is
I have no idea what I want to do
I'm equally good in all subjects at school
But I don't like any of them enough to devote
48 years of my life to studying them
Furthermore I cannot think of any real job
I would enjoy
How can I find out what to do with my life?
Oh Allen
Allen Allen Allen
That's a great question
I mean you're asking
Maybe the only person who
Really can provide
Well I guess Travis and Griffin are both better at this than I am
I went to school on an acting and directing degree
And I
Now I write about video games so
I don't know
I think I heard someone say that if
That if
College only teaches you
What you want to do with your life then it's
A good investment but I don't know
What do you guys think?
I think that there's two kinds of people
There are people that have known what they've wanted to do since they were 8 years old
There's people that are going to figure out
What they're going to do when they're 22 and like
Are handed a diploma
And you know both of those people
End up knowing what they're going to do
And there are people like Allen
Griffin
You were saying?
There are people like Allen who will never find out what they want to do
And will die purpose
You know I'm glad you were
Trying to cut Travis off to tell
Allen that he was going to die without
Purpose
Not completely without purpose
But a great use of the
Without a fulfilling purpose
Do you think he'll be on his deathbed and he'll look back and say
I wasted it
I wasted it all
You were right Griffin
Excuse me Travis can I cut in on what you're saying
To remind one of our precious listeners
That his life is a shell
Allen listen
I hate to add to your burden but this is
The most important decision you'll ever make
So you need to spend the last
Few few months
You have left in high school
Doing as much shit as you
Possibly can
Extracurriculars
Join the
Theater community
And choreograph their upcoming
Production of Oklahoma
Go join your
School newspaper
Play some football do some sports
Commentating
Anything you can to try and find
Your calling because it's out there
You just gotta stumble upon it
I would suggest Allen this is such a hard decision
Because it's a weird system we have where we
Ask people to choose what they
Want to do with their lives before they have a chance
To actually do anything
If I might be so bold
Why don't you try talking to some people
Pick some careers you might be interested in
And talk to some people who are currently
In those careers and see how they
Like it because that's a
Pretty good barometer of whether or not
If it's making them happy then
I actually made my decision to go into
Journalism because I did
It a bit in high school and I enjoyed it but I was a
Theater major in high school but I watched
Justin in
College go from
Having this theater degree that he didn't
You know want to use in his
Professional life and making a
Last minute change to journalism
And I was like man I don't want any of that
I don't want to do that
I don't want that life that's for certain
Sir that is great I am so
Glad that my life could serve as a negative
Example for how not to live your life
No not a negative example
That trailblazing guidance for you you piece
Of shit
Forum spring asks is it considered
Cheating if I make out with a gay man
Assuming that you're a
Man okay wait there's so many people
You gotta give us enough
Context to answer these questions
Are you dating the gay man
No then it's not cheating
Are you dating a girl
I think it is a she there a girl
Who is dating a guy is it
Cheating if she makes out with a
Gay man god that's such an answer
Is the answer is yes
Of course of course it is
You know do you know how you know what's
A sin would you do it in front of jesus
Not kind of masturbation which
Is a problem because I would
Totally do that from jesus
So if you're okay so if you're a girl
This is the whole thing this is how
You determine cheating right would you
Do it in front of them if you
Wouldn't do it in front of them then it's cheating
If you would do it in front of them
Then they're cool with it and you're fine it's one of those
How would you feel like if you
Have to ask then
It is yeah
How about it's not cheating if you make out with
That gay man if I go over here and make
Out with this lesbian that cool yeah
We cool nice
This is a real healthy relationship we got going
On here with Portia de Rossi is
Are you are you cool are you cool
For you because it's
Fact it is stone cold
Fact that every girl
Freshman year of college is
Going to make out with a gay man that's that's 100
Percent I think it was actually part of
The marshall plan you couldn't graduate from
From three of the
Twelve schools at marshall unless
You had made out with a gay man it was
A prerequisite and that same
Gay man will flamboyantly
Squeeze one or more of her breasts
If they honk it was
Just one gay man
It was marshall's marshall's gay
Man and everyone had to make out with him
In order to graduate college his name actually
Funny enough marshall gayman
Is it cheating is really easy
To answer because it's all about
Your partner's perception if they think
It's cheating
It's cheating if you can't
Ask them like is it cool that I made out
With a gay are you asking me if you should feel guilty
I don't know guilt fades are
You going to do anything about you're not going to start a relationship
With this guy so
I don't think you should tell the person
Like especially if it's going to create
Well let me I mean if you can let
It slide then don't
Tell them because it's just going to hurt their feelings especially
Because that's not
A sexual preference like girls who
Are into gay dudes it's not like
It's not maybe it is I don't know
Maybe it is well let me ask you this turn
Around it's probably a katherine heigl movie about it
Is a straight girl asking this question
If she makes out with another straight girl
Is that cheating
There are so
Many layers to that question no it's
It's irrelevant it has everything
To do it has nothing to do with what
The
Planets leading advice podcast says
And more about
What it has everything
To do with what your dude thinks
So if he's cool
If he's like this doesn't bother me at all
It's not cheating if he's not
Cool it's fully fully
And also be prepared for him to say he's
Cool but he's probably not just don't do it
How about you just don't make out with gay dudes
Anymore you already did it
Didn't you but using that metric like
Any any like
Your boyfriend could think that splitting a pizza
With another dude is cheating like
There has to be
But if you
Presumably if you're asking what is
Cheating you're doing it because you're
Worried that your partner will
Dump you
If if they
Think you've been cheating so
It has everything to do with what they
Consider cheating and I mean
Like if they're the sort of person if
They do consider splitting a pizza with a dude cheating
You need to break up with him
You need to break up with him be are you sure
That's not the name of some kind of crazy new sex thing
Kids today
With him
With him gross and I kissed
You I just kissed you I'm gonna go
Vomit and then cut my tongue off
I think just as a
Good ground rule don't make out with anybody
That's not your significant other
Just to be on the safe side
Probably don't make out with anybody else
Unless they're famous
Unless they're famous and that's always
Just for the story
Yahoo answers user Jake Sully
Asks would you book an international
Flight on 9-11
Some people are superstitious
And won't what about you I wanted to book
A flight to London in September and I see
On 9-11 some flights are a bit cheaper
I am wondering why
Jake Sully
Was not as you might imagine
Booking a flight to Pandora
He would do that on 9-11
If that was the only day it was available
Is that international travel flying to Pandora
On 9-11
Is that the guy from I still haven't seen
Pandora is that yeah Pandora
By James Cameroon what
No it's called Avatar
Oh right again
Was that a
Was that the 3D one
It's the one from
And he goes to the core of the earth
And then he finds smurfs
And they're giant giant smurfs man eating
Smurfs and he and
Native Americans
Fight to defend the core of the earth
Justin how did you get into my dream last night
Now that's a movie James Cameroon
Either that or T4
That's what I want from you
Or is it T5 I guess
Jake Sully listen
Jake Sully
Lightning don't strike twice in the same place
I think I would
I would only fly on 9-11
That is the safest day to fly
Everyone knows that if there's one thing
Terrorists are afraid of it's cliches
9-11 been there done that
I was in the 9-11
Yeah I was in the 9-11 before it was cool
9-11 was so 2001
Ever since
Ever since they used 9-11
In that episode of the OC it was like
Everybody was in the 9-11
I was like well kinda over it
9-12 I think
Is what you need to be worried about
9-12 is the day man
Or 9-10 where everybody is just getting psyched
For 9-11 and then it's like what happened?
Doing some pre-gaming
Actually what you need to be afraid of
3-12
Just trust me I've got a bad feeling
Really?
3-12
I have a question I hope you can help me with
In 2012 you mean
My wife and I have two kids
A two year old girl and a five year old boy
Ever since my son could speak
I've been discriminating about one thing
What's called his private area
My wife, I would just call it his bedroom
But my wife being a traditionalist
Refers to it as his penis
I being a little more hip call it his junk
Now when he refers to it
As his junk
My wife cringes and gives me dirty looks
What do you guys think?
Where do you stay on the matter?
I think you need to think about what's creepier
That or a little three year old kid saying
Excuse me papa my penis
Eww
What happened to wiener?
Why can't kids call it their worm?
You know what, yeah there it is
Wormy was my option until
The sophomore year of high school
Which got awkward
Once the intimate times started up
Like at a high school dancing
Can you feel
My wormy poking through these
These Jess pants
Here comes the wormy
These fashionable slacks
The early bird gets this wormy
What do you girls think is going to be the early bird?
I think you should teach your son
To be ashamed of his sexuality
And not refer to it at all
Yeah, just every time he brings it up
Hose him down
Have you considered my shame?
My shame, my evil, my pants evil
Now what is
What's going on in your five year old's life
That this is a
Recurring problem for you
Yo pops, what do I call this thing?
What's the deal with the dangle?
Can you talk about my junk?
Jimmy kindergarten says
To call it my cock and balls
Teach gets mad when I call it that
What do I calls it?
Well Ali G
I don't know how you got in place
With my son, can I suggest
Maybe you let him name it
I just came up with a bad name for it
His wiener machine
What about something nice and
Non specific like coach
Coach is good cause he like
He tells you what to do
And plus he's got a whistle
He's got a whistle
Do you guys not have that?
Don't gatorade on him
Call yours coach and call his assistant coach
And then one is your special teams coach
Special teams coach, that's your b-hole
I think the real problem you're faced with is
Your two year old girl will eventually need to have
The same conversation
And my advice to you is
You need to get out of it
There's gonna be a house word for this
And you've gotta be careful because someday
Your little girl is gonna be married
And she's gonna be
You see the problem here
This has gotta be a nice non specific word
You know what I mean
Like vagina flower
Don't call the penis the vagina
That is not gonna teach him anything
How about
How about this
What about penis
I think your wife is right
I think if everybody's calling it a penis
You're gonna take the power away from that word
And plus you set up that really great moment
In sex ed in high school
Where she just slowly raises her hand
She's like um
I'm very confused
What about pistol
And tell your girls hers is called a stamen
It'll just really mess them up
I have
That one was from Scott by the way
We didn't say his name
We don't want you to get confused
That was from you
If somebody else had written it
We might have given them a different answer
What's our final decision on this
Coach and pistol
Or coach pistols
I have conflicting views about pornography
Says an anonymous writer from gmail
I love it
But I realize in most of its forms
It's degrading to women okay
Also my girlfriend commanded I quit watching it
And I hate to have to lie to her
Because I still watch it anyway
Quit watching it
Should I try to resist these animal impulses
And live a life of celibacy
Only jerking off to my imagination
Or am I blowing this out of proportion
Should I try to find feminist porn
Does it exist
Um
I'm sure it exists
Are you listening to it right now dude
Turn it off and let's just talk
For one second
No off don't just mute it off
Thank you
If there is foot crush porn
There is probably feminist porn
I don't think that's up for debate
Um
I think you could probably google it
Though I
Be careful
Um cause you could end up with
Femma piss porn that's not good
Or Femma mist porn and that's
Really weird
And listen buddy we understand where you're coming from
And we know you better than this
But the next time you have this conversation with someone
Leave out the phrase animal impulses
It sends
A bad message that I don't think
You wanna put out there
Listen anonymous here
Is hungry like the wolf
For sweet internet
He's on the lookout
I think he just wrote us to get recommendations
On sites
What are the hot sites you guys are into
These days for feminist porn
First off thank your girlfriend
For
Porn can so quickly
Turn kind of stale
So thank your girlfriend for making it dirty
And elicit and sexier than ever
By foreboding
You from looking at it yes
The danger
The trick is something he brought up
Which is his imagination
Let me tell you something
The scenarios
You can invent up in your noodle
Up there way better
Than anything on the net
Well hello Ms. Ellen DeGeneres
Except
This is me
But
To answer your question really
Don't be a sicko
Shit's unhealthy
There is nothing sick about watching porn
Throwing it out there
Yeah it's not good you should never watch porn
You guys
I'm trying to make it dirtier
I'm trying to make it dirtier for him
My brother and me and my girlfriend
Listen here naughty boy
It's so bad
Oh god it's gross
Take off those dungarees and let's get you punished
No
Get that one out
Oh no
Benjamin
Benjamin writes to us from gmail
Um
Good luck
Can you put this in here
That may have been me
Okay
This one's for you
I love your show
I'll be 13 on August 20th
Griffin is my favorite person on MB&B AM
But I love Justin and Travis
I would really like it if you just randomly said
Pick chicken rules
Thanks oh yeah
I also follow you guys on Facebook and Twitter
And I'm dry as a popcorn
Okay
I imagine that says
Popcorn fart
But I can't be certain
It's hard to say
His 12 year old hotmail account
Automatically censors that word
Benjamin
Pick chicken rules and thank you for listening
Pick chicken doesn't fart
Yahoo answers user
Duke power hand
What
My whole day is about that name now
What is it again
Duke power hand
That sounds like the greatest peripheral ever
He asks
Obama implements a
White only tax?
Uh
He explains tanning beds
Doesn't this tax fall disproportionately
On Caucasians?
Yeah so does the mayonnaise tax
I don't think they flip it out
This Kenny G tax
Is killing me
This is killing me
I gotta tell you guys I was on Yahoo today
And it was a hotbed
Of political and religious discussion
Was it?
I can't like
Just people going back and forth like
God doesn't exist God totally exists
Obama
Is a Muslim
And he's taxing whites
Actually it's such
It's you know
People helping people
That's the point of this website
Today it was just
I don't know it really brought me down
People waging war on each other
I can't say it enough
When you want to have an important
Political and religious discussion
Yahoo answers
Is the place to go
Is the place to be
Yeah it's a hotbed of learning
Philosophical growing
I graduated last year
And I've been working for the past 10 months
And saving most of the money
This is from Jen's via Gmail
I'm 20 years old and I've been planning to go traveling later this year
Mostly in Asia
My problem is that my friend I was going with
Bailed and is going to start studying again
That's what most people might soon be doing
After getting anxiety for not doing shit and just staying at home
Note to yourself Allen
This is you in 5 years get your shit together
So what do I do?
Because all my other friends are either studying or just out of cash
It's basically impossible to get one of them to come
So I either go alone which is kind of scary
And not as fun or I find some random person
On the internet to join me which seems weird
And you might get sick of him or her
Pretty fast yeah it is weird
You know what's scarier?
A random person on the internet traveling with you
Yeah I've never seen Hostel
But this sounds like how that
Movie plays out
Imagine that moment you wake up in the train
Car and they're just staring
At you
With your own eyes that they've pried out of your head
You sleep so nicely
I just love it
Gents don't travel
What? No
Just don't travel
Think of all the things you could spend
That money on that you've saved up over the past 10 months
That you could keep for longer than
The duration of your travel
No Griffin you know what never goes away?
Memories
I'm not taking off Ginkgo
You can easily lose that shit
And then it's like oh man I totally should have
Spent that 2000 dollars
On a scooter
And then you die
I just need a lifetime of buying Ginkgo
And then pump it directly
Into my brain
So there you have it gents
I guess
My advice is travel by yourself
It seems scary
But think of it like a vision quest
You know what I mean you'll get more out of it
And you'll feel more
Self assured and independent or
You'll get knifed in an alley
In Hong Kong
At which point you learn something else about yourself
And that is that you are vulnerable
You could go on a real vision quest
Just
Go into the desert with some peyote
And then
It'll feel like you're traveling in Asia
Because the sky around you will turn into
Artwork from Asia albums
Um
You
Yeah it's hard
I would say maybe
If you got this money socked away right
Just um
Just keep it socked away like you can
Always just keep adding to it
And soon you'll meet someone who
Would be down to go with you
I don't think going by yourself is a great idea
First off you're going to need someone to talk
To or you're going to go crazy with jungle madness
Second you
Want someone to be able to take pictures of you
And or because without pictures
It didn't happen
Gosh this next email we're running along
But this next email is so good
Okay let me just read real quick
I'm 16 from Vancouver Canada and my
Grandmother moved in with my family a few months ago
Recently she's been trying to connect
With me which in her mind
Means going out to buy gangsta clothes
Baggy pants and lots of Ed Hardy
Bling and lots of rap
Music now she follows me around
Asking what's up J-Dog
And blasting 50 cent
From our home speaker system
At first it was easy to
Ignore but now she's talking like
This G-Ma thing as she calls
It outside and even approaches
My home dogs
When we're at the mall and stuff
What's even weirder about this whole situation
Is that I'm more of an alternative guy
Or even hipster myself
So I have no idea
Where she got this scheme from
It's terrifying
Help me I'm so confused
As to what to do
Should I mock her or something
James from Gmail oh christ James
I have to ask
James would it be better if your Grandma was a huge hipster
Like
Dressed up in like one of those
One piece tunics and it's like hey did you hear that new
Animal Collective album?
That sucks nothing's good anymore
Well I think James' bigger problem is
He's trapped in the Tyler Perry movie
What
Tyler Perry movie is that Travis can you come up with the name real quick?
What's your favorite one?
Madea but I haven't seen any
I've never seen a Tyler Perry movie
You choked
There's Madea Goes to Jail or Madea's Family Reunion
I think you just love
I just think you just love
You need to love your G-Ma
Love her as much as you can I think that's fresh
That she's putting in the effort
I think you should encourage her to just be
Yourself
Unless she's a racist and a lot of people
I hope people are
So
It's a tough call to make
I say you cherish it because I think that's badass
I think you cherish it because I think it's awesome
I think you need to have interviews pictures taken
With her she can be big on the net
On the web maybe you need to turn her into
An internet celebrity I think that's your first
How about this my podcast
G-Ma on me
Oh my Jesus
I'll put her on I'll take Griffin
Off put her on
I want to hear Griffin's last question
But first
I want to
Well
I want to read you an email first and then we'll get to the other stuff
We got this email from our buddy Tristan
The Marine
And it's a little long
But Tristan's a real close friend of the show so I
Want to read it he says
Hey brothers McElroy
And hello to all you amazing good looking
Listeners Tristan The Marine here
I'm writing this email with a heavy heart and a frown on my face
Because it pains me to say the following the next
MB&B AM will be the last episode of
McElroy goodness I will get to listen to for three long
Months see I'm leaving for boot camp at
Recruit Training Depot Paris Island
August 8th other than occasional
Letters I will have no contact with the outside world
For 13 weeks I wanted to
Write to tell the three of you and again
Those of you listening
That what an encouragement you've been to me
And how much joy you brought in my life
In the time since MB&B AM launched
I've had a wild ride getting ready to go to boot camp
While I will never doubt my commitment to serving my
Country and protecting our precious freedoms
There have been times when the light at the end of the tunnel was very very dim
Over the last
I'm going to skip ahead a little bit
Over the last few months MB&B AM has reminded
Me what I'm joining for I'm joining for the people
Of this nation like Justin Griffin and Travis and all the
Listeners who care more about quality of life
For other people than themselves
The people who are always willing to tell you straight up that you need
To pack your shit and get the hell out of your situation
Because it is the only way
I'm proud to serve my country and even more proud
To know that I'm serving for amazing people like you
Again thank you from the bottom of my heart
Now seriously pack up your bags
No one wants you around with all the pride and
Gratitude Tristan the Marine
And he gives a special
Shout out to Bob Ball
For the encouragement and all the listeners for
Encouraging him and he says
So
Tristan
Much much much love
Safety continued safety
And I hope
That once you get a taste of
Killing you're still able to find
Humor in situations like our podcast
And you don't turn into a murder automaton
Though that is a distinct possibility
So thanks
So thanks but
Always make sure you murder for America
Not against America
That is so key
So important you cannot
Enforce that enough so we love you Tristan come back soon
Good luck Tristan
Get me an ear
I don't know a lot about the military
I think boot camp is pretty sick
I still want him to bring me an ear
Bring me a necklace
Of ears
Tristan I want a necklace of ears
Carved from your enemies
I don't care who they come from
Yeah
I do
I want you to be the people who
Say ill words about our show
Make sure you play it for them
On a boombox held over your head outside
So I want to hear Griffin's last question
A couple quick notes
Today is the last day
You can pre-order a t-shirt
For my brother my brother and me
After that after today
You may be able to order them
We have no idea of how many are going to get
Made
Other than our pre-orders
If you want to guarantee yourself one in the size and style
That you would prefer
You need to go over to my brother
Go to nbnbam.com and click on
Buy stuff and you can buy that
So do that
Today don't wait don't hesitate
Don't contemplate don't debate
Just do it
Don't masturbate well just not to
Porn it isn't wicked
You can also
You can also buy our iPhone app there
If you want it it's two bucks if you don't want it
But you listen to all the shows
From there you can ask questions from there
We have a little bit of bonus content
Maybe we should put that rap
That rap tune on there
That rap tune
Yeah rap and beat song
Rap and beat song
And
Everything you want to know
About asking us a question is available there
nbnbam.com
Thank you guys a lot
We had our biggest download day last week
And thank you to Maximum
Fun for that really awesome review
Thanks to everybody who bought
T-shirts and the app
It's really nice
We'll promise to spend the
Money on microphones and stuff
Just a little bit of blow
Just a
Not an excessive
Amount of blow but just
I just want a pile of it on my desk
I don't think anything
Is going to make the show
Better
More better than a quick pregame
Bump before each episode
Maybe just a bumpette
Just a little bump
Just a little
Snoot
Griffin
What is our last question?
I'll be honest I've got like three
I'm just going to have to
Think about this Griffin
This is Tristan's last episode of My Brother My Brother Me
For months
You've got to
Nail it
I'm Justin McElroy
Travis McElroy
I'm Griffin McElroy
This has been
My Brother My Brother Me
You will never know me
Because your dad's square on the lips
Music