The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, welcome, my brother, my brother, me, and advice show and cereal roundup,
Wrap Gap for the modern era. I'm your little brother Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-aged brother Travis McElroy.
I'm your babiest baby brother Griffin McElroy. Let's get to the wrap gap.
Yep, it's that. No, it's a wrap cap. It's like a wrap up and a recap.
Okay, this is your official cereal after show.
So where we look at the latest episode of true crime special cereal and we discuss where the
clues are leading us. I have to say I think it's pretty obvious at this point.
What do you think Travis? What are your suspicions based on the recent revelations
that the the Best Buy was a front this whole time? Well, I'm gonna say two words Justin,
fugue state. Fugue state. I think the reporter entered into a few state and did it and now
like 15 years later is like reporting on the crime. Huge twist Shyamalan.
I will say that is a fucking awesome cover-up is like I'm gonna get to the bottom of this,
but I'm having trouble getting to the bottom of it. Are you having trouble getting to the
bottom of it or are you the bottom? Well, she doesn't know because it was a fugue state. That's
the twist. It's like she's gonna like find out and be like oh my god it's all pointing to me.
If she wasn't forgetting what happened every day whenever she fell asleep, it would be so much
easier for her to catch the criminal. Series finale is just gonna be her like
all of this discussion of trying to remember where these teens were makes me try, makes me
want to try and think where I was. Let me think oh my god I can't believe oh my god I'm covered
in blood still. Probably the craziest thing about Serial to Me, a podcast that I listen to,
is where is this lady finding all these teens? Yeah. She seems to know where a lot of teens hang
out and I swear to god I haven't seen a teenager in three years. And if you did, how the fuck would
you approach them without scaring them away like some sort of- I want to talk to you about a Best
Buy parking lot. No! I don't get teens to talk to you. The craziest thing about this show,
as long as we're talking about Serial, is that the events in it happened 15 years ago.
And there are people on this show that talk about what happened at a certain time. I have four
pictures in my entire mind's eye from my entire freshman year of high school 15 years ago. And
one of them is me sitting in sweatpants listening to DC Talk on a portable CD player in the band
instrument closet. And in your head it's just subtitled Coolest Day Ever. Justin where were
you? Where were you on February 20th 1995? I can tell you exactly where I was motherfucker. Check
the DC Talk. Check my DC Talk? Let me get- let me open up my dismount and you check the memory.
But then you see I was listening to Jesus Freak on that exact day. Then he opened up the Walkman
and there was no DC Talk. It was Newsboys. Murder solved. Fugue State. I think that I
have only listened to half of an episode but I'm starting to think that maybe this is fiction.
This is a work of fiction. And I know that you can google it and like find the news reports
saying that this this girl was actually murdered. It's an ARG. They play with those. But maybe it's
a fucking ARG and maybe I think that somebody is using this to sell us all Pringles. I think it's
a Pringles ARG. That does explain why they keep talking about Pringles at the scene of the crime.
Exactly. Jay is like I- he called me up and he was like I'm gonna murder her today.
Sir I'm gonna have to- I gotta ask you to stop eating those Pringles while we're taking your
testimony. I'm sorry now that I popped I just can't stop. I just cannot stop. The most frustrating
like experience of serial listening must be for the guy who used to run Circuit City. Because
every episode is an extended commercial for Best Buy. Like they don't need the exposure. I bet that
guy is wishing on every star he can find that someone would get murdered in the parking lot
of a Circuit City 15 years ago because he needs that heat. Yeah. Yeah. Do you know what I think
the most confusing thing about serial is? What's that, Travis? I've listened to nine episodes and
they have yet to mention Cinnamon Toast Crunch. Okay come on. Low hanging fruit is the sweetest
of fruits. I think we're like we're more than 200 episodes into this thing I think that we can hold
ourselves to a higher standard than that. Okay but I will say- French Toast Crunch. In Travis's
defense I have had at least three experiences in the past couple weeks since Sydney and I started
listening to serial where she will say to me I read the craziest thing about serial today and
I'll perk up like oh that is a that is a favorite topic oh mine did they bring back they brought
back oops all berries it's called ah fuck all berries I might have killed the girl all berries
ah shit all berries odd dunk where were you when all these berries happened what if it what if it
ties back to that Jay is like yeah I totally remember he was eating a bowl of oops all berries
nope sorry oops all berries is out of circulation then check the calendar it is it was not being
made then oh I'm sorry he was eating a McRib no he wasn't no it was not he was not eating a McRib
he was listening to DC talk was he or was it Switchfoot ah shit all berries let's do a question
yeah that sounds good by the way sorry can I apologize to everybody that this is what I sound
like it you can hear you can hear my slimy vocal cords just slapping together forming each consonant
and vowel and I apologize like a drunk seal we had to alter Griffin's voice because he doesn't
want to be identified I don't want to be identified I'm actually the guy from the serial show I need
to listen to more of it my wife won a car a while back and firmly believed it had something to do
with a lucky crystal she bought I'm quit ever since then there has been an increasing number
of crystals appearing around the house am I good god damn you ah fuck you can't make me laugh like
that when I got the the consumption you actually sound better I feel like the crystals healed you
oh fuck thank you oh it was the topaz mmm it was the lustrous topaz on an episode of uh
Penn and Teller's bullshit they say this phrase like everybody's got a gree-gree or something
along those lines so like everybody's got a thing that like they cling to it's like they're special
like and I feel like this is a case of that I think if everybody were to look deep within
themselves everybody has a thing where they were like oh yeah when this really good thing happened
I was wearing this t-shirt so like this is my lucky t-shirt and they always kind of say it like
jokingly like I'm using a tone of voice that shows that I don't really think this is serious
but I said it 20 times today it's so serious but here's the thing can I tell you two something
I've never fucked with crystals and I've never won a car yep Justin gave me his Oldsmobile Cutlass
Sierra um when he upgraded and I guess that was free and you are and to be fair you were on
crystal meth at the time okay I was on that lucky crystal meth I was on that sweet crunch um that
oops all berries and I did get a free car so I take it back crystals are legit they resonate
at a frequency that human beings can't understand but the Silurians can I think that if someone says
they have a lucky crystal you should tell them they have to eat it because think about it if
it's so lucky that should go fine if it's so lucky you should want it inside of you powering your
body yeah like uh like that that like krang in that weird exoskeleton you should want this stone
this crystal inside of you if it's so lucky so eat it already you should start fighting crime
or something it's like I have a crystal that protects me from all harm like cool you need
to leave here or we're going to shoot you to death yeah go ahead and try check out my amethyst
motherfucker I want a car with this shit I want a car with this and it also makes me unkillable
I might be leaving the conclusions I might be leaving the conclusions here but just try and
shoot me through the topaz you cannot sir this story is distinctly American it we find one
crystal that has the magic power to give us cars and we what do we do are we thrilled that we found
them no no we start trying to scam crystals from every which way we can exactly you did you exhaust
the charge on that like why don't you just roll with the one lucky crystal that you found it sounds
like the reporter from serial could use a magic topaz and somebody would hand it to her and she'd
be like oh it was Jay oh god of course the whole time it was right in front of me it was Jay the
whole time I am so sorry I just wasted everybody's time for for for a dozen hours trying to figure
this thing out I could have just touched this topaz and the answer would have revealed itself
to me do you think maybe it's like a ring of keys where this is her lucky car crystal and then she's
got like a lucky job crystal and she's got like a lucky like the food order I made came back
perfect crystal do you think she has a crystal that helps her find sweet crystals oh this is
my crystal crystal crystal yeah this is my crystal gale crystal that I'll crystal gale vinyl I think
that if this is her thing if this is like your wife's thing there there is a saturation point
where I think you get to say like honey the crystals they're everywhere we don't have money
for food because you bought crystals but I think I think that that line is the first time you step
on one yeah like the first time well not so lucky it seems it seems this one might be busted
check the energy on it somebody call a ghostbuster the energons in this one aren't quite matching up
maybe we go a different way do you want to yahoo yeah hit me this yahoo was sent in by sarah benson
thank you sarah you send in a lot of great yahoo's this week sarah so the I feel like we should have
a new segment on the show called game recognized game where people just like crush it with yahoo's
um game recognized game sarah benson great job it's asked by yahoo answers user whoa fuck
before I and then there's a check mark and then you are you and then it's slash and then 18
that probably means some sort of sex thing before I check you this random string of gobbledygook
asks before I check you are you slash before I check you are you 18 that's what it is all right
gross cool history you must have a back cool backstory that you have contained in a single
username this horrible goblin asks in the truman show do they film him when he's in the shower
in the toilet or making love topical because they film every second of his life but those
things are pretty big parts of everyone's life it is certainly a big part of mine
and I don't think they'd show the whole world that it's a pretty big plot hole okay I don't
good morning good evening and in case I don't see you again good night be right back
and then he has diarrhea for 45 minutes I'm gonna I'm gonna say that this is the most frustrating
yahoo answers question we've ever had and I'll tell you why in the movie the truman show when
he is about to make love they deal with that and the camera pans to the curtains it's a whole
fucking scene and they deal with it okay but but but but but but but but but but but maybe a sweet
sweet oh and maybe he wants to show full penetration maybe the camera operator is asleep
at the wheel and they show full jim carrey penetration wouldn't be a great scene in truman
show if they pulled back and the whole time there was just a camera operator standing pretend like
i'm not here what a way to boost it is an artificial way to boost ratings of hey guys
this week it's shit week we're not gonna pan away when he's shitting we put x-lax into all of
truman's meals enjoy why am i shitting so much every week right before christmas every year
it's the truman show christmas special come around gather around the log kids as truman
shits his brains out liquid liquid waste it's a nightmare it's beginning to look a lot like
christmas how does it all end well he's probably gonna shit himself to death because you keep
poisoning him that's what i think i tell you uh i i i don't know if this policy extends to
self-pleasuring but if i had been the star of the truman show the years between middle of middle
school and the end of high school would have featured a lot of pants a lot of camera panning
that go ahead and secure that better homes and gardens sponsorship now top because you are going
to get some prime placement for your curtain top of the credit roll will be courtesy panner and
it's just like from from from 12 to 19 just like that dude is gonna earn that paycheck mom why are
my curtains now covered with the pepsi logo well well because of money because of your sin because
of your sin you did that how much of it there is do you think that if truman had just turned out
to be like a really boring dude and like the show had gotten cancelled they would have murdered him
we should ask the stars of utopia who are currently living through this exact thing oh
god guys on utopia first of all i'm sorry that i cancelled your television show by talking about
it on our podcast um this podcast is basically the indian in the cupboard of reality shows by
which i mean if i say something happens then it becomes real and it becomes extant i i have to
be fucking careful with this power with this crystal power that i've developed and not like
say any shit about survivor or amazing race because i how could i live without those truman
other what other activities would the camera not be able to show if true like what would
you not put in the show what if he was super racist super racist and it was just like hey
can we get like some good influences in there we've tried like the teachers system the parents
who said i don't know where he gets it from i don't know super racist his whole life has been
artificial we've controlled every single element in his life i do not know it has somebody been
sneaking him blue collar comedy has somebody been smuggling blue collar comedy into the biodome
we never yeah we don't really deal with like truman's super excited when he gets out if i
found out that people had filmed everything i had done until i turned like 30 god
woof that is going to be a hard nap for me i'm gonna have to lay down for a little while and
just sort of process that would have been way better in any of that movie if he was like so all
the jerk offs yep every single one because i did 3482 and the audience loved each and every one
and also truman we need to let you know there's a thing called the internet and people have been
tracking these obsessively there are several tumblers devoted to your jerk off schedule
how about another question i do my laundry at the laundromat sometimes when i go to bump my
clothes from the wash to the dryer all the dryers all clothes in them some of the jars won't even
be in the process of drying the clothes clothes will just be hanging out in the dryer taking up
space what's the appropriate amount of time to wait for the owner of the clothes to arrive and
remove their dry clothes before you just get up fed up and take the clothes out and put them on
the counter somewhere so you can use the dryer that's from ornery in oregon when i think about
this i think this just says a lot about me in that i just if i encounter this problem i think
man i'm losing at laundry today i'll wait like i just feel like the other people got there first
they did it better and i am i am losing it well they didn't do it better if they just leave their
fucking garbage in the dryer for six days is that not a worry for other people i mean movies have
made me afraid that people are going to steal my clothes out of out of the dryers can you imagine
it take it took me a long long time to develop my look you guys know this sure yeah me of course
um my look it took me a really long time to discover that my um weird body shape can only
really truly be accommodated by v-neck t-shirts from old navy so maybe not like a lot of work
maybe a lot of initial like investigation but then i just know to buy um chunky midsection
t-shirts at old navy yeah um and i spent a lot of those like high collared t-shirts yeah and it
looked bizarre it looked bizarre it was like a melting marshmallow on a rotten stump it was
bizarre that was my whole body was just all very stumpy and rotten just bad all over just sour and
then you put on the old navy v-neck it was like oh that's like a neutral okay that's like a neutral
where where did griffin go um and i've spent a lot of money on these three dollar t-shirts um
can you imagine just being like i'm gonna leave my entire look and i'm gonna go down the street
to chipotle for four hours and just like good luck clothes just stay right there don't get stole
it's it is it is that's like my baby you know what i mean that my look is everything to me
and you're just you're just potentially sacrificing that it would take so long
to rebuild that look from the ground it would take you could 25 minutes to remember the colors
of shitty v-neck t-shirts that i got from old navy that lasts for about four weeks i just like
i couldn't do it man i couldn't do it this week's episode sponsored by old navy navy their t-shirts
will hide your grotesque thorax protect yourself from the prying eyes of a cruel cruel world with
old navy's chunky midsection v-neck t-shirts become instantly invisible with old navy's
utterly forgettable line hey how come all the parts of your body are super little except for
that one part of your body that's weirdly super big doesn't matter throw on this v-neck
it's pullover season for all the freaky bodies in america hey hey are you fat ish come on
come on down come on get it on one more game we got that weird dog still and that weird old lady
you love them do you remember how much you love them it's buy one get six free at old navy
is this what it'll take uh y'all want to yahoo uh yeah i do griffin this yahoo was sent in by
rachel sperling game recognized game thank you rachel it's by yahoo answers user brian who asks
why is peepaw so rude so today i was at my peepaw's household and he sneezed in my face
it's really good then laughed about it yeah he's always doing rude things like this and tripping
me and my boyfriend when we walk by and spitting on my ferret the other day he even picked his nose
and wiped his booger on my clothing travis patrick mackerel good these are solid how can we get him
to stop being so rude why spitting on the ferret is out of control that's some next level rude
grandpa technique you think your grandpa's rude talking about the war and and just incessantly
and talking about his friends and their sacrifices so rude my grandpa spits on my ferret fuck you
you don't know shit these are all good goofs if i was watching this happen i would i would lose it
why is this ferret caked in grandpa's spit i'll tell you why it's because my my jeeps i i if
if i uh god willing live to an elderly age i'm doing this i'm hitting that point
what are you gonna say but like this is your kin yeah shouldn't you be nice to your to your kin
don't you want them to remember you i know how angry i am at people who are younger than me now
i can only imagine that's going to be compounded in the intervening decades yeah don't even be
young around me you want you want your your grandchildren to wear old person makeup when
they walk in the room like spike jones style yeah i think one of my favorite memories of pa pa is
like him sitting there and just whoever else was talking in the room talking at a level that only
you sitting next to him could hear and he would just be like making fun of them or saying shit
about him like yeah just keeps on talking and nobody's really listening and i don't know why
she keeps talking like that like i'd like to talk but nobody else is gonna let me because
she's in there talking to a lot and it was the best thing it was a very subtle burn he had very
subtly spit on your ferret he used to like i remember one time with pa pa we rolled up to
like a taco bell and he just kept saying like i want an apple pie ask them if they have apple pie
and then looking at me and winking like you dick and then mom would try to explain like no no dad
they don't this is talking about it but i want an apple pie wink you dick that's bit commitment
that's the one thing that old people have in spades i think it's just the ability to say i
don't know if this bit's funny or not but i'm gonna lean into it because how many more bits
am i gonna get i don't have an answer to that i'm just gonna go for it i'm gonna go do you think
that pa pa is the reason they started carrying empanada yeah this old dude just keeps coming
through and he just keeps coming back these apple pies i'm missing a whole market i just
thought about like getting home from pa pa's house and like changing into my pajamas and looking on
the back of my shirt and there were boogers on it and not knowing where they came from and i got
like really really really genuinely upset people damn it on this on this episode of cereal we
checked the time on the bugs we checked them for crusty lists and also old hairs listen
i don't remember it i don't remember the books i mean who remembers every book they ever
had 15 years later another clue was uncovered yeah there were bugs on her shirt how did we
overlook these bugs no if there had been bugs the cops would have checked for books right
like they wouldn't have just let books we didn't have we didn't have book check technology 15 years
ago it was the 90s we were all doing a lot of speed there's no way he could have booked all
those cell phone towers maybe your grandfather's allen font he misses that camera game and he's
the best goose he can cook up maybe your grandma and grandpa's allen font and you never noticed
maybe your grandpa's carrot top mom did you notice how grandpa got really ripped like 12 years ago
a poor carrot top he's been ripped for longer than he hasn't been and it's still any all anyone
could talk about actually i had it i've talked about so many fucking other things i have completely
displaced that mental image from my mind and now it's right back in there so thanks you two chuckle
fucks lots of important stuff in the news today but first carrot top still ripped 12 years later
ripped isn't that silly all right oh shit the boys are back in town don't call it a comeback
extrema straits is your place to get fuck fuck fuck up fuck down fuck any way around
fuck right put your penis in another penis in another penis put your cock in your butt can't
you do it there's a tool for that extreme restraints is basically the old navy of fucking
extreme restraints has the best fucks at the greatest values it's the neem and marcus of
fucking i think they're the brooks brothers of fucking we want uh uh you to experience
extreme restraints.com uh here are some of our favorite products there's been there's silicone
kegel balls put these everywhere there's silicone bagel balls step one put them everywhere how much
how much would you pay for these well uh they're free what the fuck free silicone kegel balls
they got internal weights that cause them to swirl and shake as you move that's guaranteed
to spice up any funeral if you're walking around with kegel balls in your vagina or butt or ears
but or throat everywhere or just your pocket probably not your throat can i just say it's
been a while since we checked in on extreme restraints still one of the most fun websites
to just browse let me check let me see the absolute best if you want to just go check it
out it's the best my net nanny actually locked me out of it now that i live in la i'm gonna go
check out like their warehouse and their showroom and i'm so excited i want you to do like an
infomercial from there where you're just walking around shaking people's hands do you like to put
stuff in your butt sure we all do hi i'm travis background the stuff on extreme restraints.com
is so fucking crazy that you i i whenever i comb their webs i just pardon me i just realized why
i've been cooking this uh goof up in my head i've been staring at a picture of the dick for 30 seconds
but uh anyway uh the the things are so weird that sometimes i think that not weird i should say
varied let's go with that because everybody's gotta have their gree-gree uh sometimes i think
that if i click on one it'll say that's not a real one like when think geek does their april fools
thing like what you disgusting monster that's not a real thing there's not really a uh remote
control cock ring or it's like they put it up and it's like well that's been out for three years
and no one's clicked it we didn't think we'd actually have to like uh okay let's see it's a
thing i don't know give us some time to workshop it so i i have i sword fished my net nanny and
accessed the world wide web to go to extreme restraints and right now i'm looking at the
oppressor chastity device which is on sale it's 119 down for 150 that's fucking huge value just
in time for christmas just in time for christmas and this device is it looks crazy and i couldn't
understand how it could be used until i am looking at it on a dick now uh put your dick in a cage
and that's essential for this chastity device stay in there you did a crime and then there's
like a little containment zone that your balls go in because you they gots to be contained but then
hanging off the back of the device is a rod with a ball on the end of it and i guess that's for
your butt so it is an all-in-one device sort of like the magic bullet for your dick and your balls
and your whole butt and i wore it when i won a car so now
oh there's a urethral plug too every hole is catered to every hole what do you need what do
you have we got this is an item and it's iphone compatible so here's an item i've never seen
before single locking shower suction handles oh you get these wet you put them in the shower and
you look like mission and cruise in the fourth mission impossible movie what did i say mission
and cruise mission and crew together again together again no you look like tom cruise
and they're like you suck you stick these onto your shower wall and you fuck there it's weird
i'm looking at the subcategories uh on the side of the page which includes bondage gear electro
sex gear dildos and insertables there's a there's a a subcategory called fucking machines and i
clicked it and a picture of tom woe pat popped up just with two thumbs pointing to himself just
pointing at himself it's this guy just a good old boy and here's the thing that moves right now
monday to monday starting today till next monday 30 off everything at extremerstraints.com
fuck yourself 30 off with the coupon code brothers friday all one word and even if you
miss that even if you get this after next monday it's 10 off for the rest of 2014 guys i know that
we highlighted some of the more extreme of these restraints including the oppressor and tom woe pat
but there is a lot of fun stuff on there basically for every interest level you're
gonna find something that's gonna find something really spice it up gonna be dirt cheap so go to
extremerstraints.com and use the coupon code brothers friday to get 30 off please go buy
this stuff so that we can keep doing these spots they are the best sponsors still they the prodigal
son hath returneth and make sure to send us pictures of what you know no not while you use
it pre-use right out of the box right out of the box brand new load up our inbox don't please put
us on watch lists don't do this thing so you fucked out you fucked yourself out i'm out of
guys i just checked i'm out of fluid what do you turn to when you're done watching uh you're done
fucking yourself with tom woe pat while you consume your power bar and you drink your
gatorade you put the bag back over his head and you put him in the closet he's done for now
see you tomorrow tom poke some holes in there for tom woe pat or he won't be there tomorrow
no put a twig and a leaf in his container it's so important that you recreate tom woe pat's
natural habitat he's gonna be scared he's gonna be a cross-stitch pillow hanging off your bedroom
closet door that says tom's place well well there's a good reason for that tom woe pat is my
fuck prisoner and my constant and my constant i love him so much uh so hulu plus is the best way
to spend your time after you have sex with tom woe pat whatever you want to watch however much
time you have like if you have days to kill hulu plus is going to be there for you there is an
insane amount of content on this website uh whatever shows that you've been missing that you
want to catch up on they have a blue million of them you want to watch all of sybil including the
episodes of tom woe pat they're there you want to watch the illegal banned episodes of sybil
the too hot for tv episodes that involves sybil turning tom woe pat into a fuck prisoner they're
there they're all there they're not there they're not there but my favorite thing and i like every
time i turn on hulu i find something on there that either i've forgotten it existed or i just
assumed wouldn't be out to watch yet because it was too new and it's there yesterday i found
garth moran's dark place which is it's hilarious it's like a six episode spoof on like 70s and
80s like horror shows it is the funniest thing i've ever watched and i haven't watched it since
it was on tv and there it is on hulu every episode of the season and like that's all i
did for the rest of the day i was like well this is what i'm doing so i guarantee you it's it's
like 7.99 a month and the greatest value for that money because you're going to find something new
on there every time you look um i guess we could do an antm check in although it seems like they're
fucking calming it down a little bit like they've actually been modeling and not like doing dna
tests and dressing up like uh native american robots um although they did make them act and
that should just be banned from the show from this point on no more acting did aaron sorkin
leave the show it's yes aaron sorkin left the show and now the dialogue has become extremely
heavy-handed i'm embarrassed to say i'm like three episodes behind you dummy you stupid idiot
who i have nobody else to talk nobody else is watching this show except for me and rachel
we have no planet on the planet ty returned to the camera in the last episode said thank
you griffin and rachel and then she made everybody eat ribs for some reason everybody
just started eating ribs at at panel she was like aren't these great if you're intrigued you
can go to huluplus.com slash my brother and get a whole extra week for free there's a single week
free trial if you sign up regularly with us you're gonna get an extra week go to huluplus.com
slash my brother and boys in the house pooch tooch uh i have a special message for sarah and oliver
and it's from sean sean says to sarah and oliver congratulations sarah i love you so much and i'm
excited to be starting a family with you welcome oliver and i've been waiting for months for this
what's up you cool baby oh it's a baby the baby was born probably it's a baby that's a good name
for a baby it might also just be like a house guest he's been waiting for maybe but probably
a baby though um what if this is what if us talking what if this episode of the podcast is
the first thing that the baby hears i mean with our scheduling he's probably like three years old
it's probably probably 19 years old um but what if this baby has grown up listening to our voices
and we're like it's three daddies sarah and sean congratulations do you know sean is the dad
stop with the fucking contextual leaps griffin you're gonna get us in
legal hot water one of these days can't get franklin bash to come bail us out
they're not there anymore for us they said i get real lawyers they said i'm excited to start a
family with you mm-hmm maybe he's her uncle okay maybe he's the wacky landlord who popped in from
time to time belvedere maybe he's mr belvedere did you think about that griffin maybe we're
looking at a full bell did mr belvedere like roll up into the estate and be like i'm your dad now
do you not remember the episode in which he was a sperm donor because they couldn't get pregnant
now now i'm your daddy tv but it's on hulu plus here have some of my fancy jism
sorry sorry i i may have missed the cup of bed streaks on the china and streaks on jism i bet
the secret to getting jism off your china is a little bit of soda water and mustard
fancy mustard grape upon i just on the china
i love that show just scrape a little jism up the china there's a baby waiting for you
you can't go to work like that you're coming in jism
change your shirt i'll launder them honey i think we need to fire mr belvedere i'm too afraid i'm
too afraid i can hear perfectly decades of tantric jisming giving me the ability to hear far beyond
those of mortal men we have ruined this super sweet message that this this person has written
for a baby so anyway oliver welcome to earth it's pretty much like this all the time drab did we
have another message we do it's for sean the bandana mitchell and it's from jen rampage hernandez
fuck yeah there is no chance of this getting to you on time if there is any time left mary jane
loves you and the cuckoo has left the nest you know what to do godspeed hey how come somebody
assassinated joe biden yesterday i don't know uh it must have been uh some sort of weird sort of
activation splinter cell code word oh no the wires got crossed and he just jizzed all over joe
biden oh no no not again yeah yeah he made a biden job uh we don't know what that message was about
but we hope it activated whoever you intended to activate we are not legally responsible for any
activation that happens on usually responsible for any soiling of mr vice president joe biden
co-host of the goose down along with the lovely kimberly clark and we want to invite you into the
comfort and groove of our podcast that encompasses the arts and entertainment you can check us out
at maximalfund.org also available on itunes my girlfriend has started writing a harry potter
fan fiction with two characters loosely based on well hold on okay she has told me that these two
characters eventually end up dating i'm a little worried will her writing reveal uncomfortable
truths about how she sees me or wishes that i was should i stop reading now or am i worried
about nothing that's from confundus charmed in california folks these are the kinds of
questions we need this is a perfect my brother my brother me question thank you and then when
steve the wizard pulled out his wand jenna said sure it's a little small but that's okay i still
love you it's filled honey i want to talk about this paragraph no it's a wand i talked about how
it's phoenix feather and dragon heart string and boy i wish it was thicker just a little bit
um and steve the wizard always chewed with his mouth open and sarah the wizard hated that hey
sarah hey sarah let's talk about this one day sarah the wizard got enchanted dagger and buried
it in his fucking throat because he couldn't keep his goddamn mouth shut and i'm also i'm talking
to you i mean first of all let's talk about the terminology because it doesn't sound like harry
potter fan fiction it sounds like maybe a little bit of extended universe a little bit of eu a
little bit of uh like harry potter tales from the moss isley cantina yeah canon canon g if it's
canon g that's that's perfectly fine because when you say fan fiction i immediately think of you
know a lot of draco's throbbing member and you're thinking of slash fiction right that's synonymous
no fan fiction can be completely uh completely benign and oh yeah have you read a lot of that
well uh no you've read a lot of shadow the hedgehog fucking big the cat's asshole is what
you have read sir i love those uh shadow the hedgehog bigs the cat slash fictions yeah oh were
you laughing because you think that's a thing that doesn't exist or are you laughing because
you know and acknowledge that that is half of all fan fiction no i was laughing because i get
actual enjoyment from reading those it makes me very happy okay good i wasn't i i think that this
question would be more troubling wouldn't you be more troubled question asker if she was writing
two characters loosely based on you who were not dating and instead she was dating like the captain
of the quidditch team that would be more you thought that was you and then it turned out the
capital country has like a weird mole that you don't have wait a minute wait that's not me our
neighbor jerry has a mole though and he's great at quidditch god damn it jerry please don't take her
just because you can i'm sorry i can't catch the golden snitch his snitches are beyond compare
his mole is covered with gross hair
oh jesus with ivory skin and dragons of emerald green okay i this sucks on a lot of different
levels isn't this a great test of like a relationship that first time someone hands
you their fan fiction their manuscripts how you react that will determine the course of
your love forever can i say you guys like i secretly think i would enjoy the hell i write
in fan fiction what universe i would like to enjoy what what universe would you want to dip into
what if i had to write fan fiction in a universe which one would i want to inhabit yes i mean i
wrote a spec office script once which was basically this yeah so that maybe like that
was basically well that was uh that was potentially for a job and it was a good right yeah yeah but
isn't it all fan fiction until someone pays you for it that's a good point yeah i mean when when
jk rowling wrote the original harry potter and the sorcerer's stone that was actually dune fan
fiction not a lot of people know that very little details had to change how house house of tradies
was just house griffin door they just changed the name oh yeah i think i would want to dip
into quantum leap it's so it's such a rich vein god what can't you do i would write the hell out
of some quantum leap oh i want to do one where he leaps into santa claus travis that's a fucking
good idea thank you justin oh and who's i'm ready to meet up with dr who i'm gonna go uh actually
run into the run into the bedroom really quick and grab rachel's laptop and read you guys some
of her quantum leap slash fiction that she's written because that is her favorite show of
all time oh boy yeah i'm leaving i'm leaving i know what you're thinking there's a lot of
hologram sex involved and you know what i'm thinking that you're absolutely right yes
congratulations swiss cheese memory and an ass like gruyere oh my god don't she still manages
to write in a scene where scott bacula gets to sing though because it's in his writer i'll let
you i'll fuck a physical manifestation of ziggy and i'll have hologram sex too but you gotta let
me dress up like the big bumper okay scott that is an iron clag contract when he anticipated slash
fiction yep in case like 25 years from now people are writing on the internet about me having sex
with ziggy i have to sing in those in those stories come on donald belisario you want me
i've talked about this before but how fucking good would like an adventure game series set in
quantum leap be i think about it and i get so excited i could write that is that is that fan
fiction are you about it telltale are you talking about like a video game scenario like yes card
game scenario no no no video game scenario be so fucking tight i would write it for free you can
make any game into a quantum leap game by just having a scene at the beginning where he leaps
like there's very few distinguishing features of it other than the leaping it's not like he gets
super strength or anything cool like that you could do it right now just by editing in like
scenes into video games where like just for one second he looks at the camera and says like oh
boy and then you just keep going you're like holy wait hold on is this a quantum leap game
is gold my a quantum leap game did we talk about quantum loop slash fan fiction enough that will
actually be forced into making some because i really want to write some fan fiction isn't
everyone just looking for an excuse to write some fan fiction like i guess i guess i need to do a
patreon where we just write a quantum leap i gotta do it it's for the donors yeah i don't want to
write fan fiction uh this yahoo was sent in by level 700 yahoo shaman drew davenport thank you
drew it's by yahoo answers user joe who asks chris angel versus santa claus who who is more magical
i don't want to ruin it but i'm going down through the dozens of responses to this question dozens
of people who decided this is going to be worth their while uh it is almost entirely chris angel
almost all in chris angel's corner serious question yeah if it was revealed that chris angel was some
kind of like suck you incubus character some kind of actual like demon person would you be shocked
at all if he was some sort of nephilim yes if it turned out that he was like an agent of mephistopheles
and like had some unearthly powers if it turned out he was an agent of mr mistopheles
if he was a jellicle cat if it turned out that he was a jellicle cat and ascended to the heavy
time layer or whatever it's called would you be shocked let me see i'm going to show you a trick
hand me those sardines i love them i love these things i love them shits now watch this i'm going
to put a sword through my belly look at that sand over there you see how smooth and not chunky that
sand is can you check this out poopy poop poop poop sweet sweet did you like my magic
check out that laser pointer you want to say hold on oh yeah i tell you guys something this is truth
yeah when i was a young child i saw uh david copperfield on tv performing his uh illusion
of flight uh perhaps one of you could wikipedia that to find out the exact year and the name of
that special because it was something amazing but i watched his illusion of flight and in my young
mind as a as a young boy i entertained seriously entertained for the span of a few days afterwards
that david copperfield may maybe maybe an angel i thought wait now don't laugh no i'm going to
fuck you no i thought that david copperfield in his special his flight 1992 perfect 12 that's
exactly where i thought i was i i and what was the name of that special do you do you have that on
hand uh the magic of david copperfield 14 flying hyphen live the dream calm the fuck down david
copperfield name davey so i was so stumped by how he did this trick i entertained that he was an
angel who has was on earth to re-convince the people that miracles can happen i thought that
david copperfield was perhaps an angel and that was the best explanation can i just say like
it being the 90s i'm amazed that that wasn't like a movie or a tv special or something where it's
like you know who's popular right now that david copperfield people love the angels and stuff so
let's make it where he's really doing magic and solving crimes that was that was actually the
finale of the secrets of magic revealed that the masked magician who's like putting everybody on
blast like and here's the secret behind david copperfield he's a fucking angel guys like i
fucking i've looked at that shit through every angle and this guy's a motherfucking angel i have
no idea why can't we see his halo that's the great magic trick he made that shit disappear
he must have linked it with another ring and then pulled it off his fucking head he actually had to
set he had to give up his halo when he revealed his abilities to earth people is that how it works
in my fan fiction yesterday my roommate of five plus years walked in our room and asked to borrow
my nail clippers like it was the most normal thing in the world i had two questions for you guys but
first the but the answers were real obvious is that okay no how do you say no to that no you
may not use my nail clippers the real question at the root of this is how do i figure out what
other weird stuff he thinks is normal and that's from well please don't use my nail clippers in
pittsburgh first off thanks for handling our light work i don't think it's that weird
what what now the nail clipper borrowing sorry what travis yeah i know i feel like i should
but like i think if brent in college had walked into my room and said like hey can i borrow your
nail clippers i wouldn't have thought twice about it i would have just handed it to and said here
you go good friend okay but when i use nail clippers i don't just like clip my nails i get
in there yeah i get i mean i do some work in there some reconstructive work yeah you get
out the the the speculum that's one of the attachments isn't it so is the fear that okay
is the fear like a that their feet are so gross you're going to catch something from like their
fingernails why do i have to spell this out for you like their nail clippers uh-huh it's gross
everything and you're worried about the feet i'm more worried about the hands because everything
you ever touch including your butthole is going to get under there and then it's going to get on
there and then it's going to get on your shit when you touch it what kind of honey pots of items can
you leave around the house just to see if you'll pick them up and utilize them and make yourself
look like a chair as you like document it and being okay use my toothbrush i need to move out
and now you're sitting on me jerked off on my china okay it's not explicitly what that's for
wish you'd jerk off on your own china
why do we have two sets of china in our college apartment i don't know one's real streaky
folks thank you so much for listening to our podcast uh we we hope you've enjoyed recording it
with us weird because i didn't do that no they're all here with me they've just been really quiet
i'm on some meds there all right it's out i'm on some fucking meds all right i've been sitting
on a fucking quill i've been sick for a week and a half i've become like a fucking cough syrup
sommelier i believe this is a this is a generic brand of walgreens dayquil and there's like an
earthy sort of acetaminophen delicious i love it thank you uh thank you for listening to our show
we hope you had fun um listen thank you to people on twitter tweeting about the show people like
roller girl james scotty uh uh peewee scotty mo hillary fink neil louisa heron taylor bear the
doctor diana knock katie shackleford chloe chef rj moore pluto so many others we really appreciate
it we're at nbmb am on twitter if you want to follow us there or tweet about the show or whatever
and just a heads up so you don't miss it tickets from xfuncon go on sale after thanksgiving and
they always sell out and it is always like the most fun time it is a solid weekend of good time
you will never be more exhausted in your life than you are sunday afternoon so make sure to go get
your tickets it's gonna we can't tell you who's gonna be there like we don't even know yet the
lineup doesn't drop till after like long after tickets go on sale but trust me it's always a
solid lineup last year i think michael leon black was there i kyle canane was there two years ago
john hodgeman's like almost always there maria bamford go it's always a solid jesse tweeted jesse
tweeted that uh uh this is max fun uh boss jesse thorn he tweeted that uh you would be well served
to bring some farm wisdom uh with you so take that how you said i don't know what he meant by that i
think camille and emily from the indoor kids were there last year they were and from what i understand
killed it there's classes there's a comedy show there's parties you're gonna make some new friends
you get to hang out with everybody who's there it is like a solid good time we love going so make
sure to get your tickets don't miss out and yeah it's you may be a trek for some people but it's
once a year and it's worth it it's a track for everybody it's at the top of the fucking mountain
it's at the goddamn throat of the world literally it is at the throat there is a high school there
called throat of the world high school not throw to the world i thought it was throw to the world
high school not throw to the world i think it is what is it rim of the world top of the world at
the rim of the world rim of the world sounds good at world's rim i think it's fus ro dah university
um i would like to thank john roderick and the long winters both of them for the use of our theme
song it's a departure off the album putting the days to bed if you haven't listened to that album
in fullness i feel like we still get tweets every week like oh man this is a good cd yeah no shit i
know also why are you buying cds yeah i went to i just went to sam goodie and i'm listening to
this great compact disc oh i dropped my mic we got a youtube channel youtube.com slash mbnb am
we just crossed 5000 subscribers there yeah and we want you to be 5000 and change or whatever
maybe be the 5000 a month i don't know if you like the videos the best way to get the word out
is to like share it on your facebook or tweet about it i i keep seeing people who like like
the videos and say like we're more people watching these because we need you to show them to people
and i guarantee it like there's so many shorts up now and if you haven't watched the animated videos
that tyler crowley has been making they are the fucking best do we have a new one coming up this
week we do there's a new one coming out friday you're gonna love it are we done no also check
out all the other max fun shows they're all great yeah oh hey we're doing a live show in huntington
yeah uh yeah you go to bit.ly forward slash candlelight's live uh and you can get tickets
to see my brother my brother me uh we i know we sold over half the tickets uh they are they are
selling uh briskly i would say i think that's fair to say they're selling briskly so you want
to go pick those up they're just 15 bucks uh saw bones will be opening for my brother my brother
me soon you can get two podcasts for the price of one it's a it's a holiday special titled the
magic of the mcelroy brothers 14 flying live the dream so you don't want to miss we've got people
coming in i just found out i saw a tweet about it coming down from delaware coming down from
new jersey and coming in from hislvania so like this may be the biggest tourism event huntington
has ever had we have people coming in from canada and switzerland yeah so that's pretty cool no
pressure no pressure no pressure just like get there uh and that's gonna do it for us cool one
last uh yahoo question i do chew on this final yahoo is sent in by rachel spurling thank you
again rachel it's by yahoo answers user greg who asks was jeremy pearl jam arrested for the stuff
he did in the video um justin my brother my brother may get your dad square on the lips
so
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
hi my name is dave and my name is graham now what do we have to do to put you in a brand
new podcast today yeah what do you want me to drink bleach i'll do it yeah dave will drink
if that's what it takes to get you to listen to stop podcasting yourself on maximum fun.org
don't make dave drink bleach just listen to the show he will but don't make him stop podcasting
yourself