The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
It's familiar, but not too much familiar. It's a new craze.
And the girls, do you want it? Just say, hey, I want it.
Did I interrupt the flow, you know?
Yeah, well I was kind of counting on the whole thing playing out, because that's the first physical exertion I've done in a decade or so.
It's the most exercise I've gotten. Hi everybody, this is my brother, my brother, I'm in an advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest, most winded brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm a sweet baby griffin.
Guys, I got presents.
Candle Knight's presents.
I got Candle Knight's presents for everyone who is sitting at this table, and nobody in the audience, I'm sorry.
Just this from here, Candle Knight's celebration.
It's our swag from Genesis Today.
Now what do you got there?
I got you the gift of health.
I got you an acai berry shooter.
Okay, I'm not gonna drink that right now.
I got you super fruit omega-3 gummies.
Wow, all for me?
I got you some goji, I don't even know what that one is, never heard of it before.
I think that's what makes you do backflips real good.
I was just thinking.
Tell me.
There's a second back, I was just thinking since we just did another show,
an hour of goofs, and we never tried to do two hours of goofs in the same day,
that we need all the energy that we can get, and these have lots of B12 in them.
So we got gummy vitamins, this is super fruit.
We got five-hour energy drinks, which are not from Genesis Today, but I figure they get the job done too.
Also at the Walgreens, where I purchased some of this stuff,
they have these at the counter, they're called Tropic Chillers.
They're 17% alcohol by volume.
They come in these delightful little spheres.
They're little alcohols.
They're little alcohols, and we drink them.
That translates to 17% funnier for you, the people.
Let's do it.
I really don't want to.
How is it?
That's straight gross.
Wow.
Oh my God.
That tastes like radioactive urine.
It tastes like the bad part of vodka night, like towards the end when it comes back to you.
Mine actually tastes like someone was floating apple slices in gross vodka, and then someone vomited in it.
I spilled Tropic Chillers with a Z all over my paper, so now I can't read them.
Oh, gross.
And we'll combine that with the five-hour energy.
I don't want to do that.
I think the gag was initially that we would jam.
I'm like, ah, look at us.
They're disgusting.
I'm not doing that.
It's repellent.
I will drink a five-hour energy, and I want you guys to have the most pumped up.
Can we start a clap?
Can we start a slow clap for Justin?
Slow clap, people.
A slow clap.
I know that.
Holy shit.
He's gone mad with power.
Don't encourage him.
These are really bad.
They're really brutal, right?
Let's get right into the advice.
I feel like we've stalled long enough.
First bit of advice.
Don't do any of the things from the last three minutes or so.
Just don't do that, and you'll be good to go.
First question comes from The Holiday Hater.
Are they here?
The Holiday Hater.
Hey, everybody.
Hey, hi.
Well, come on, guys.
That turned dirty quick.
We've yet to do a live show where the audience turns on each other before they turn on us.
But we will encourage that behavior.
Hey, everybody.
Turn on that guy.
Just got straight Hunger Games in here.
The candidate from Panama.
Okay, so he says, I'm a Grinch.
It doesn't matter what holiday it is.
Christmas, Thanksgiving, Halloween, Fourth of July.
He did not include candle nights, but I'm assuming.
Or anything else.
Just can't get excited for them.
Want to get excited and enjoy the holidays, but I just can't seem to.
How can I stop being a Grinch?
Like things.
Okay.
Normally we try to cut a little deeper to the bone here on our show.
But I guess like things is a perfectly suitable answer.
Like every holiday?
Like Columbus Day and like Canadian Thanksgiving and stuff?
What about Independence Day?
When we beat all the aliens?
Can you not eat super fruit gummies during the show?
Sorry.
You sound like my...
This is my chaw-addicted brother, Griffin.
He loves two things.
Bad advice and smokeless tobacco.
No, but really.
Independence Day?
Not a fan of that?
It's just fireworks and hot dogs.
How can you not get into things exploding and also there are hot dogs there?
Wait a minute.
Is every day of your life a holiday?
Are you Tim McGraw?
Live like it was...
Like I was dying style?
Every day out there skydiving?
Rocking mountain climbing?
No?
Well, you're here so I can tell that's not true.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I want to say that.
I love the holidays.
Why don't you like them?
Wow.
What do you have against...
Let me say this.
Do you have anything against them or is it just like, eh?
Yeah, I don't feel it.
Mostly good.
Oh, welcome to adulthood.
Guess what?
Nothing's as good as it used to be.
You turn like 16 and people stop giving you candy and sparklers and it's sad from now on.
Yeah, and you have to drink chillers and five-hour energy drinks just to feel.
Yeah.
We have a cure for your problem.
It's called alcohol.
Get on the bus.
They sold these like next to the paydays and three musketeers at the Walgreens.
I can guarantee you carried parents have picked these up as a treat for their young ones.
Here.
Oh, they like this.
It's bright green.
They'll love it.
I'm not even fucking kidding anymore.
This is the grossest thing I've ever drank in my life.
Yeah.
Hey, Frank, I know he's our son and I know how this sounds, but for the first time I
was able to really just chill with Dylan.
He just fucking hung out.
Me and Brian got some serious hang time on the bus.
It was really good.
We went and hit the jukebox, played all the Toby Keith songs, just flipped the table and
left.
What I found in my adult life is all the holidays that I loved as a kid, like Halloween and
Christmas and stuff, I had to give those up to appreciate holidays like St. Patrick's
Day and Columbus Day.
So you're saying sacrifice a few holidays so that the other ones mean more.
No, I'm just saying like I've learned to appreciate I don't have to go to work today
days and I get to drink all day days.
How do you not like those days?
And Flag Day.
What's wrong with you?
I think you're too broken for our help, but sir, I'm sorry, you will be issued a full
refund at the door.
You will not.
I have a Yahoo.
A Yahoo, you say?
Yahoo Answers.
From the Yahoo Answers service.
From the Yahoo Answers platform that was developed.
I can't stop drinking it even though you know you have to stop drinking it.
I know, but it's like an experiment now.
It's like mouth art for your mouth.
This one was sent in by Alethea Eckhart.
Thank you, Alethea.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Nevaeh, who asks, they have it backwards.
Hey everybody, by the way, cheese it with that.
Unless your name's Nevaeh and you're here, in which case it's lovely.
Who asks, what can I get a horse and dog for Christmas?
We're having a Christmas party on this Saturday, and we're doing Secret Santa, and I got a
horse named Daisy and a dog named Bandit, which Bandit is kind of old and only has 20
percent vision, so I can't really get him toys, so what else can I get a dog that only
has 20 percent vision?
Euthanasia.
And what do you buy a horse for Christmas besides treats?
Horse treats, apples, sugar.
Hey, guess what?
That's the only thing that horses give a shit about, those three things, and not being kicked
in the sides.
Those are the four things that a horse is like.
I got you this necklace of roses.
I like oats and not having a man on me.
Maybe you could get him a smaller horse and a smaller dog.
But you know what, even those horses give a shit about holidays.
Just saying.
Hey.
Get it together.
They get a little extra trot in their gallop right around Thanksgiving and stuff.
I don't know what horses like anymore.
In my day, horses...
They appreciated the simpler things, like Smucker's Raspberry Preserve.
I used to have my finger on the equestrian pulse, and nowadays I just feel so divorced
from it.
You know what you could do?
You could get the horse a dog present, and the dog a horse present, and then they swap
them, Gifted and Magi, and they become best friends.
That's not how Gifted and Magi work.
Thanks for the watch chain.
It's yours now.
Gifted the lazy guy.
The Swapperoo.
Newsflash, if you're a horse, you don't fucking know that.
Just take it for granted.
Somebody tells you to run in a circle, you're like, okay, boss.
I guess, thanks.
I hope I get oats for this.
We've gone, I don't know, five minutes without addressing the fact that someone got a horse
and a dog and a Secret Santa.
What kind of fucking Secret Santa is this?
What kind of Secret Santa is there where you draw a human being saying, oh, whoo!
Thank God!
Someone that wears shoes and pants and stuff.
Yeah, I got the short straw, looks like I got the horse.
Good news, you can give the straw to the horse.
He will enjoy that very much.
Why is your response not, this is a horse.
I think there's been a clerical error.
You have written Bandit.
No, I entered the human Secret Santa.
I'm a human and I have a horse.
This is a horse and dog draw names?
What the fuck is that horse going to get?
All I got is these shoes and like an apple.
Do you want this eaten apple?
Steven the human isn't going to like this apple.
Bad news for Dorothy and accounting, you're not getting anything.
Don't even buy a gift.
You're going home empty handed.
How did the horse write their name on the slip?
There's a lot of questions.
Why are horses even involved in the Secret Santa?
The horse doesn't give two shits about Secret Santa.
Someone's having a laugh at the office, I think.
Hey, Kristen, we're doing Secret Santa this year.
The horse office.
The office where horses are.
This whole thing is taking place on Hey Dude, the television show.
Unless this question is written by someone named Steven the weasel.
You're saying that this is an Orwellian animal farm kind of thing.
Right, another animal getting presents for that animal.
On the internet.
Wait, it all fell apart.
Can you get the dog an iPad too?
Everybody wants one of those, the hottest gift this year.
I got you Never Say Never.
Get some Genesis today, super fruit gummies, immunity boosting variety.
For the horse on the go.
Horses need immunity, that's what I'm saying.
I have another question here.
Is Sam Panky here?
Where is he?
Hi, Sam.
Thank you for coming.
Sam didn't create a clever nickname for himself for reasons that will become evident soon.
My name is Sam Panky, and I've been blessed with a pretty wicked last name.
Throughout my life, however, I've received the exact same nicknames and variants.
Spanky, Pankasaurus.
I'm going to call bullshit on that one, by the way.
No one's ever called you that.
Pankinator.
And my personal favorite, Panky Doodle.
These are all great, but I'm looking for something with a little more pizzazz.
And one that might reflect my life as a jazz bassist living and working here in Austin, Texas.
What about pancreatitis?
Okay.
That's a good start.
That's pretty good.
You've got to start somewhere, I guess.
You've never gotten Hanky Panky?
That seems like the most obvious answer.
Every day.
Every goddamn day, huh?
Stanky Panky.
That's not good.
Has anyone just ever called you Sam by your first name?
Mr. Sam.
Excuse me, Sam?
Samuel?
Excuse me, Samuel Panky?
Is that you?
Never that?
What about two in the Pank, one in the Stank?
No, come on.
Jesus.
Whoa, and now I'm the asshole.
Can you not?
Like, can you not?
Could you?
There's a hundred people.
I regret nothing.
Okay.
You've had as much of your tropical chiller as I have.
There's really no excuse.
I'm sorry, Mr. McElroy.
I'm cutting you off.
I'll tell you when I've had enough tropical chiller.
I'll tell you when.
It's exactly when I say two in the Pank, one in the Stank.
That is the specific moment in which I've had enough.
That's my alcohol safe word.
I can't stress enough how bad these are.
Don't drink beverages with Z's in the tile anymore, guys.
How can I have Zima?
Sam, what about doctor base?
Now stay with me.
You play base, right?
You're a medical doctor.
Are you good at it?
What about good base?
Yeah, about average basis.
Then if you have a really rocking knife, you're like, no, he was above average basis.
That's good press.
You can't buy that kind of press.
Set the bar nice and middle.
You can jump right over that with just a few bum bum bum bum bum.
That's what a base sounds like.
Just play the phrase.
I can't see my mouth.
Can we get a nickname started for you that has nothing to do with any of your real names?
Like Burger Master or something.
Now, are you good at making hamburgers, Sam?
I'm sorry.
Do you eat a lot of hamburgers or are you good at making them?
You talk about burgers a lot.
Oh, there it is.
What's up, Burger Master?
Oh, Burger Sam they used to call him.
Nobody loved him.
The Sam burglar.
Take that to the bank.
There you go.
To the panky banky.
You monster.
See you go down to the bottom and while you're down there you find this with two in the pank
and while you're down there you find an oyster, you crack it open, there's a pearl like that.
That's it.
That was beautiful.
That analogy you just weaved.
Get down to the bottom of the oyster and you find a pearl.
It's so unpredictable.
It's like we're with Flea at his prime.
It's hard to know when he's got...
Flea's a bassist.
Do you want a Yahoo to get us out of this?
Wait, I heard somebody...
Did Flea die or something?
I didn't know.
No, he's still cool?
Okay.
Flea's still kicking?
Flea's still cool?
All right.
Go ahead, Griffin.
We're cool on Flea.
Thank you, Flea.
This one was sent in by Nefariosity.
Thank you, Nefariosity.
It's by Yahoo Answers user D who asks, an old woman keeps trying to get into my garden.
What should I do?
Does he mean a secret garden?
I think so.
She is not violent, but she is very persistent.
She seems healthy and of good spirits.
Additional details.
She seems of a healthy stock.
This afternoon she tried again, but she was wearing lipstick this time.
Does this change anything?
It changes everything.
So wait.
Wait, what color lipstick?
Ren is a game changer.
She's obviously trying to get all up on your arugula.
Is that a thing people grow in garden?
Griffin, describe arugula.
It's a purple fruit, like eggplant.
I know I've never eaten it.
Is it a flower?
I can't.
So if I understand the situation properly, this man is looking out his garden window.
Cautiously.
I can't.
He's afraid she'll see her again.
Is she rooting through his vegetables?
No, trying to get in his garden.
She can't figure out the gate.
But don't worry.
She is very persistent.
She'll crack that case eventually.
She'll dig underneath it.
Not violent, though.
She's not one of those violent garden crafters like you read about.
I gotta say, this afternoon she tried again and she was looking good.
Lip-wise.
Really hot.
A real foxy grandma.
Everyone knows that old people keep away crows.
That's just a fact of life.
If you don't have an old people there, a weasel will come and eat your rutabagas.
Have you ever seen Rikki Tiki Tavi?
It's about that.
Rikki Tivi Tavi and my nani.
Nani is our grandma's name.
Backstory.
Ah, the age-old battle of the mongoose and the nani.
A few Yahoo...
There are 53 answers to this question.
Fuck you!
Whoa!
Fuck you, internet.
Because the first one couldn't handle it.
I'm going to summarize the thesis of about 20 of them who say...
Summarize the thesis, though.
They say, um, let her look.
Just fucking let that old fucking lady into your garden.
What are you doing?
What's so important?
Hey, you, get out of here.
Okay, that is a good question.
What's your in-game worry?
She's a carrot thief, maybe.
I don't know.
She's just going to start Godzilla-ing it all over your garden.
Grandma, smash!
I hide all my butterscotch candies in there and she's going to take them off.
She'll find my stash.
I mean, lock your garden, I guess.
Like, what actionable advice can we possibly give this human being?
It sounds like the problem is resolving itself.
She can't get in.
You're cool.
Unless you're worried about...
No, she's like the Velociraptor.
She's checking every point of the fence.
Clever old girl.
She's trying to dig under it.
This is great.
Yeah.
It is really good.
Where's the goat?
Just stick it out.
Wait, wait.
Is it a goat?
Because I get confused that way, too.
This goat in a dress keeps trying to get in my yard.
Because if the goat is wearing lipstick, it has changed.
The rules that you had before are evaporated.
Get the horse and the dog lipstick!
Yes!
Let's get these barnyard animals sexy, everybody.
It's like a key to any garden.
Oh, shit.
Sam Panky.
Maybe the lipstick-wearing old lady.
That's a good nickname.
Lipstick-wearing old...
Lipstick Gma.
No?
I don't like it.
You don't like it?
Hey, one of my...
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on.
Is Leviticus here?
Boom.
Leviticus.
Front row.
This is going to get awkward, but let's just stay with us, okay?
It's nice.
Is that Argyle?
Yes.
It's lovely.
Oh, God.
One of my friends...
We'll talk more after the show.
Don't listen to these neanderthals.
They will, too.
It's not a gag.
One of my friends...
Did you go to my brother's and my brother's show?
Yeah, it was good.
For, like, three minutes, they talked about old ladies and it was funny.
And then for 45 minutes, they talked about Argyle sweaters.
It got weird.
I asked for my $10 back.
They refused.
One of my friends is trying to introduce me to a coworker of hers.
I feel like I should direct this at him.
He's close enough that I can just stare at him.
I should just have him read it.
One of my friends is trying to introduce me to a coworker of hers that she thinks I'm...
Please don't look at him.
I was...
I was actually just looking at you really closely.
If I'm gonna divorce myself from him enough to goof on him, I need to not...
Do you want some acai?
Yeah.
If you could just superfruit me...
You want one of these?
I'm not...
Yeah, cool.
You gotta come up here.
I can't throw.
Hey, everybody, Leviticus, everybody.
Hey.
He's getting his goji on.
He's becoming too real to me.
I can't goof on him.
If you keep your mind to me, he's there.
One of my friends is...
I need to switch seats.
One of my friends is trying to introduce me to a coworker of hers that she thinks I might
be romantically interested in.
I don't know much about her other than that she seems nice and that I think we might share
similar interests.
When asked if I had any deal breakers, I said smoking and it turns out she does smoke.
Should I completely rule her out based on this one condition or should I quit being
stubborn and just accept someone as they are?
I've been single for a long time and I don't want to keep missing out.
That's a really good instinct, everybody.
Minutes, taking away, time to pair off.
My biological clock is ticking.
Yeah.
Noah's Ark style.
One by one.
You have to pair off to die.
Pair off and die, everybody.
Hey, are you sure she really smokes and she didn't just share?
That's a deal breaker.
Maybe she's trying to get...
She's trying to comment.
Did you see?
That was her disappear...
What?
I guess I smoke now.
Yum.
I love these.
Smooth.
This is the fresh baked tobacco leaf.
I love how crisp it is in my mouth.
Picked these up from my buddy Joe Camel.
Yummy.
Thank you, Joe Camel.
Flavor country resident me.
You know, there's a middle ground between being stubborn and accepting her for who she
is and that's changing her to the person you want her to be.
You could do like my wife did.
Start dating a non-smoker and then convince them that they're not, in fact, a smoker.
Three years clean, everybody.
Flip it.
You're saying...
I want to go back to what Travis was saying because it was funnier.
Funnier unless real.
You want to flip it Eliza Doolittle style, My Fair Lady style.
Did you say Eliza Dushku style?
You want to flip it Eliza Dushku.
Is she here?
Eliza?
Eliza...
She was at the 7.
You guys totally missed her.
Ask everyone who was at the 7.
They'll attack.
Striking young auntie.
Who was at the 7 o'clock show?
See?
They voted.
None of them were Eliza Dushku.
No.
She had to go.
If you can't...
I don't think you should try a changer.
I think you gotta change yourself.
No.
This is all it takes.
A couple of those.
You throw like eight of those and she gets self-conscious.
Did you enjoy the date with Leviticus?
Yeah.
He's kind of coffee.
He coughs a lot.
He has rheumatism.
Yeah.
I think he's got rheumatism.
He's got TB.
He's got a touch of the consumption.
He's a lunger.
He was a lunger.
I didn't enjoy the time I spent with him.
We tried to watch a movie and he kept coughing.
I'm sorry.
I'm here and I feel so bad.
This is what's important to note.
The fact that she smokes now is not a concrete thing forever.
Right.
You gotta change it.
It's not like she has blue eyes.
Right.
This is like, yes, she smokes.
That doesn't mean she's always going to be a smoker.
She's going to want to change your taste in podcasts.
It's going to be a give and take.
She's going to insist you stop calling yourself Leviticus.
Yeah.
Right.
There's going to be a lot of changing on both sides and that's what relationships are, people.
Yeah.
Just caving in to each other.
Right.
Finding out what you need to change about yourself.
Can you talk about negotiation?
Can you get her to cigars?
Can you flip it and get her to smoke cigars and then you kiss her and it tastes like grandpa
mouth?
Can you start dipping and then tell her, I'll give up dip if you give up smoking?
That's great.
In between vomiting.
Hold on.
I need a moment.
Can you take up snoozing?
Can you snoozing?
Or snoozing.
Or you just say everything in rhyme.
Can you talk about the secret a lot?
I don't understand.
What?
The secret.
The book.
Is the secret that you do snooze?
Am I saying that right?
Is it an umlaut over the u?
If you snooze, tell him you're going to reinforce.
It's a liquid u.
Snooze?
I don't like how it sounds when you say it.
Griffin.
Griffin, save me.
Here's a Yahoo that has nothing to do with snooze.
It's by Yahoo Answers.
Sent in by Nefariosity.
Thank you, Nefariosity.
It's by Yahoo Answers user question mark who asks, what do angels eat for my book?
How to cook for angels.
I'd read it.
I would.
That Shinerbuck is so good after drinking that orange jizz for 30 minutes.
That's because of my asses.
Made here in Austin.
Guys, you got to stop giving in to me.
I am writing a book and the girl in my book is pregnant with an angel and I want her to
have something to crave.
Help.
Unfortunately, it's a biography.
You're not writing a book.
Let's be honest.
You're justifying to your dad.
Daddy is an angel.
Trust me, it's an angel, baby.
I'm trying to win a bet with my stupid friends.
What do angels eat?
Two different people in the Yahoo Answers platform wrote angel food cake.
Good one, guys.
Quality.
Good goof.
Nobody said angel hair pasta.
Couldn't get another angel-based.
What about devil's food cake?
Can you believe it?
Travis, if you make the jokes that are as bad as the jokes that are in there, then people
don't have to listen.
No, I said it in a tone of voice like I'm mocking them, but it's all I could come up
with.
Can I joke snidely for 30 minutes?
Would you guys be cool?
I think, like, anything?
I guess anything they want to.
Obviously, their teeth are made of metal.
Roman Downey's teeth are made of metal.
Fuck you if you don't believe me.
I had a brief fling with her.
What's the other lady on there called?
Mama Angel.
I don't know.
I didn't watch it.
Angel's.
I'm pretty sure I only eat cloud-based foods.
So like cloud burgers.
Like cloud burgers, mostly.
Right.
Do they eat like tacos?
Cloud tacos.
They can eat cloud tacos.
They're not exclusively towards cloud burgers.
There's a lot of cloud-based foods in this situation that I am whipping up live on stage.
Griffin's out there on a bold new frontier, and he is writing the rules as we walk.
They'll keep challenging me on this goof.
What about cupcakes?
God damn it.
Yeah, they eat those too, but they're made of clouds.
In this situation, I'm creating.
Have you guys ever seen improv before?
This is how it works.
Normally we record for an hour and 15 minutes, and you get a 55-minute show, and these are
the gems you're missing out on.
If you could believe it, you would be robbed of cloud tacos.
This is my brother, my brother, me, face-to-face, three, Tokyo Drift, the cutting room floor.
You at home are not hearing this.
So I could say, fuck anybody who doesn't live in Austin or the surrounding area, or New
Orleans.
Really?
There he is.
Good stuff.
You know what?
I'm done.
Do angels have to eat?
Do angels have to... Do angels... Let me bring it down.
Things are getting too funny.
Slow it down.
Let's have a really intense theological discussion.
What do you guys think about angels?
If I get to heaven, when I get to heaven, and I become an angel, because I think I did
a pretty good job down here, pretty sure that's how it works, I don't want to have to have
the onus of eating on me.
Angels only eat because they're hungry, because then, actually, angels only eat to take food
away from poor people.
This is mine.
This isn't made of clouds, I hate it.
I assume you mean non-Christian poor people.
Yes, yes, obviously.
That's how they punish them.
No such thing.
But it's okay, because they don't listen to our show.
Because they don't have iPods.
What are you talking about?
The horse getting a present made more sense than what you're saying right now.
Our show is the 1%.
That's all we're saying.
Topical.
Jesus Christ.
Shit.
Hey.
Hey, I'm talking to this guy who's on my paper.
Hey, I'm a guy who just went on a first date with a girl today.
She seemed really into me.
So we'll go out again later this week, and that brings me to my question.
What is the Christmas gift giving etiquette for someone you just started dating?
How much should I spend, and any gift ideas?
You could give them a coupon that says they don't have to get you anything.
Yeah, that's what everybody really wants, isn't it?
They don't want to have to get you anything.
Oh, a coupon that says, hey, here's a coupon for let's pick this up in three weeks.
You're talking about a temporary breakup slip?
Yeah, just like, we're going to take a break past Christmas, but we're going to kiss each
other on New Year's, and then it'll be totally cool.
So they're going to be lonely for the holidays?
No, because they have someone else, but just on layaway.
Such an asshole.
Hey, don't start dating people now.
What's wrong with you?
Okay, like November 30th should be a cutoff.
Right, earlier than that.
Earlier than that, I'm saying Halloween.
You don't want to do the- You know what, let's just say June.
If you haven't found them by June, you get their number and say, I'll call you in February.
No, no, March.
March, not February.
After February 15th.
Shit.
I'll call you February 15th.
Remember, remember the Ides of February, because then you can hook up.
But please don't forget my name, girl.
I talked to you once.
Hey, you're a down girl.
I'm enjoying this.
I will catch you in March.
Wait, then you have to text them every couple of days and be like, just so you know, only
a couple more weeks till we can talk again.
Got my name on you.
I like that idea, because I like the mental image of somebody being like, oh fuck, it's
June 25th.
I better get on it.
I'm going to be lonely for the rest of the year.
Who am I going to spend Independence Day with?
Not that I give a fuck, because I hate all holidays.
Monster.
And then we invent a new holiday on June 30th called Last Call Day.
That would be- Holy shit.
That would turn the whole game on its ear.
The whole game of love.
You're welcome, homework.
No, it's not homework.
It's dudes who are like, oh, I got to get down.
It's the 30th.
Everyone's going to be window shopping.
It's the last call day.
Just stand on a mound with some pretty shells and do your mating call.
Don't even do that.
Just walk out on the sidewalk and people are going to run to you like they're picking partners
for Cotillion.
Like, come here.
I'm ready.
I'm ready for you.
I'm the best you'll ever do till February 15th or so, and I'll catch you then.
Just listen.
This is easy stuff.
Just get them something related to the holiday.
Yeah.
Christmas.
Get them like a- Well, find out.
How about the promise that you don't have to meet your parents?
Well, that's a good start.
Christmas, you get them like a stocking.
That's great.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, Christmas, you get them a stocking.
Like one sock.
Yeah, like a sock.
For Hanukkah, you get them a dre- Like a dre-
A dre- A dreidel.
Like a what?
Dreidel?
A dreidel?
That's good, Justin.
Wait, hold on.
What's a dreidel, Justin?
Dreidel?
It's made out of clay.
It is a- A dreidel, actually, is a purple eggplant-like fruit.
How many people know that?
That hates holidays, and is a fine- Justin, can you get me a Kwanzaa and also
a Ramadan icon?
Yeah.
Kwanzaa, you will want to get them a Kwanzaa cube.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I just can't solve this Kwanzaa cube.
I got all the red ones matched up.
It's a puzzle-based cube that you give to someone for Kwanzaa.
That was left there by the Transformers.
The only way to stop the Decepticons- Sam Witwicky, you must take this Kwanzaa cube
to the head of Mount Inotron.
Take it to the peak, Sam Witwicky.
Hold the Kwanzaa cube above your head.
Ignore that Christmas is way better, in many ways.
Stick by your convictions, Sam Witwicky.
Keep an open mind, Sam Witwicky.
It's just as good.
This is getting weird for everyone, Sam Witwicky.
Have some awkward conversations with your school friends, Sam Witwicky.
These are our convictions.
Transformers only celebrate Kwanzaa, Sam Witwicky.
And Ramadan.
Hey, how about a yahoo?
Yeah, please.
Because I feel like we're like- Hey, sorry, everyone.
We're leaning towards unplayable for fun.
We just offended both all humans and autobots.
We're quickly moving towards the fact that Ramadan sounds like a Transformer name, and
then we're going to talk about what kind of Transformer Ramadan is.
It's a smartphone that transforms and it's Ramadan-gle.
And obviously the correct answer is Ramabong.
That was incorrect.
I'm sorry.
Ramabong?
Anybody?
Is that good?
Pretty good?
This yahoo answer was- I don't know what religion I'm offending.
I hope it's not one of the ones that- All of them!
This one's the happy ones, right?
The autobots versus the Decepticons versus the Ramagons.
It's a three-way war.
No one knows who's going to come out on top.
I can't believe you finished your chocolate chillers.
As it turns out, it's Sam Witwicky.
Okay.
Go ahead.
This one was sent in by Jacob Locker.
Thank you, Jacob Locker.
Thank you, Jacob.
Somebody wooed for him.
Good work, Jacob Locker.
It's by yahoo answer's user.
It got cut off.
NYC, trim, eye, and then an ellipses.
I don't want to know the rest.
I don't either.
That guy asks, why are these cows yelling?
Like he's stabbing them and they won't shut up.
I live out in a field close to some farms.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
How do you have the internet?
Not near a field.
Is up on it.
Close to some farms.
It's a full moon outside and these cows are making these loud screaming sounds.
Do they do this on full moons or is it just them being killed by a predator?
Or the predator.
These tropical chillers are strong.
Have you seen that new movie, Cow vs. Predator?
That's actually how The Catch Predator got its start.
Did anybody listen for the screams of cows?
You know, I would like to think that most people when they heard this question are thinking
like the cows are sitting there going, but I said they're going, the cows are going,
stop.
Please help.
Help me, I'm a cow.
I'm being stabbed.
Someone forgot to give me a gift for Secret Santa.
My feelings were wicked hurt.
Did anybody here have the kind of rural upbringing that would be required to shed some insight
on this situation?
Do cows actually scream at the full moon?
Do people, I should fucking hope not, but if you had told me that, I would have stood
up and walked right out that door and never looked back.
And now I have a new crusade to destroy cows.
So wait, so they do scream.
Do they just move super loud?
Jesus.
That sounds.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
One more time.
Everybody quiet.
Can you come up to the microphone and recreate that sound for them?
Get up here right now.
This is for our radio audience at home.
Everybody, this is a howl at the moon.
Say your name first.
Introduce yourself to America.
Kate.
And this is the sound of a screaming cow.
We're going to loop this and sound it as one of those tranquil tapes.
This is a full moon hate cow.
This is the sound a cow makes.
That was awful, the worst speaking sound ever.
Now, y'all, I always wonder things about like, how do we get milk?
How did that start?
And I think if you heard a cow making that sound, you're going to try anything.
You know what I want to do?
I'm going to squeeze these pink things and drink what comes out because fuck, I don't,
I have to try something.
I've always been looking for a way to justify hamburgers.
Yeah, right.
It's our only defense.
You make that sound one more fucking time.
I'm getting the A1.
Well, they're not screaming.
Are they screaming racist slurs, these cows?
Is that how you want to eat them to punish them?
What?
Punk cows.
I was imagining the cow screaming racist slurs.
It didn't make any sense.
I just liked the mental image of it.
Next time, just maybe give me, is there a hand signal we can work out to let me know
you're going down a road like that?
Sure.
Can we jump back real quick?
Because I said punk cows and now I want to make a joke about them standing around wearing
leather.
Okay.
Let's find it.
Do you know how you know they're punk cows?
How Travis?
That sounded like a transformer.
Tell us how now.
How do they, how do they know?
They stand around wearing leather.
That's it.
That's just their skin.
Don't.
Pretty good.
Thank you, everyone.
But are the cows, the question is why are these cows yelling?
It's a trick.
What are cows?
Come out here, Steve.
Steve, we have presents.
We can't.
Be cool, guys.
Be cool.
He's coming.
Steve, what are you doing?
Be cool.
Steve, we can't work the VCR.
Come out here, Steve.
It's just flashing 12 again.
Tell them that funny story you were telling me earlier, Steve.
Shh, shh.
I don't tell it like you tell it.
Come out.
Steve.
When he gets out here, we eat him, right, guys?
Now, that's my problem.
I don't think cows do that usually.
Only on the full moon.
Cows that scream, booze.
On the full moon.
There it is.
Move it along.
Are you going to eat it?
Yes, move it along.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You fucking dare.
Fuck.
We know who the crowd favorite is.
Yeah, two people managed to applaud.
Enjoy your night alone.
I hate your guts.
You're out of the family.
I'm just kidding.
I love you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They're booing you now.
Guys, wait, wait, wait.
Listen, they're still booing.
Let's take a second.
They're mooing.
I just turned Justin into a little girl, everyone.
You brilliant son of a bitch.
You got Mad Libs for us so you can bust out?
Let's just keep this shame train a rolling.
Don't actually do it.
I can freestyle one.
Who's got words?
No, stop it.
How about another Yahoo?
No, wait, OK.
No, no, if you've got shit, let's do your shit.
No, please go right ahead.
OK, fine.
This one's sent by Galiayali.
Thank you, Gali.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Totally Awesome, who says.
Nope.
I don't know what the question says.
I'm going to predict that is an inaccurate username.
But go right ahead.
Unless the question is, how do I stop being so totally awesome?
I'm embarrassing my friends.
Help me, Yahoo.
Is it a sin to have sex with a robot for the purposes of procreation?
OK, I was right.
It's not a sin.
It's just really misguided.
You know how some couples cannot have children?
You know, because of an immune reaction by the mother?
However, the husband could fertilize the wife's egg,
and a child could be born if it is placed in a surrogate mother, right?
Well, what if the surrogate mother is an Android robot,
a robot that is holding the wife's egg?
Could the husband have sex with the robot in order for the couple to have a child?
But what my book presupposes is...
What if it...
Listen, listen, listen.
There's a guy who watched the movie Surrogates and got really confused.
Why do you have to put it...
Why can't you just like fucking put it in a Petri dish?
Why does it have to be inside of an Android?
Or like another human!
Why do you have to have sex with an Android to do this thing?
Griffin, you don't have to answer the question.
I'm so sorry.
Is it a sin?
Obviously, God didn't know about robots.
That's true.
No one knew about robots.
John, Mark, Matthew, Luke, Ringo, no one...
None of them knew about robots.
So it can't be a sin.
That's why...
There are...
There's a lot of shit that God don't know about.
That's what you're saying.
Robots, the internet.
Yeah.
God doesn't know...
You can jerk it to e-porn and the Bible can't say anything about it
because the Bible doesn't know about the internet.
Right.
That's why we...
My brother and my brother and me are writing Bible 2.
We're writing the cyber Bible.
Cyber Bible.
What's the cyber Bible for the digital age?
Thou shalt not robo-freak.
Don't robo-freak.
What is robo-freaking?
Just so I know for sure.
So I'm clear?
How about anything where you talk about having a surrogate baby inside of a robot body?
That's a sin?
I guess.
I like to have that discussion and that the word sin enters into it.
There are so many other things that is before it is a sin.
Is it weird?
Is it wrong?
Is it imaginary?
Is it not real in any way?
Don't...
Don't fuck this robot.
This robot is...
I know how it looks wearing lipstick sneaking around in your garden.
Looks great.
It's got mystery.
It's got intrigue.
Can it even feel things?
Wait.
Is it a sin?
Is it a girl robot?
Oh.
You're saying...
Wait.
Wait a second, Rick Perry.
Wait a minute.
You're saying if he fucks a... if this is a lady that fucks a boy robot, then it's bad?
Is that what you're saying?
No.
Okay.
You just want...
You just don't want a bunch of robo-sexuals running around undermining family values.
Hey, by the way, first Republican presidential hopeful to adopt that platform?
You've got my vote.
I will...
I will switch parties if you come out against robo-freaking.
It is...
Did you get one of those robo-calls?
Yeah, I did.
It was weird.
It was about robo.
It was a robo-sex call.
It was really dirty and there was lots of bleeps and boops.
Put it in my...
Everyone knows that if it feels good, it's not a sin.
Tell that to fuck poor Cyber Dave the robot who keeps getting fucked by a human.
Like, he doesn't care how it feels.
He's a robot.
He doesn't even get to vote.
Which, by the way, that is a sin.
Yeah, it's criminal.
It is a sin.
They've got emotions.
They can decide...
Their logic circuits are better than ours.
Are you saying it's a sin that robots don't get to vote?
It is.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't think robots are advanced enough yet to vote.
Like, I don't...
Like, there are robots...
Whoa!
It's that kind of mentality, Griffin.
There's a kind of...
No, no, no, no, no.
All right.
You're gonna start spewing some anti-robo bullshit.
This...
My Roomba doesn't grasp the subtle intricacies of our government system.
I don't want to think that exclusively...
The Robos are coming here and taking our job.
Yeah.
This thing...
Vacuuming our floors, making our cars.
If that doesn't preclude many of the flyover states from voting,
I don't see why it should preclude robots.
Well, most of the people who live in flyover states
don't exclusively eat the Cheetos that I drop on the floor.
Or maybe they do.
Are you talking about...
I don't think Roombas will ever vote.
Is that what you're saying to me?
That's what you're saying.
You just turned it back on me, how to kill a mockingbird style.
There wasn't a lot of turnout for the 2012 election,
but there was a huge turnout for the anti-dirty floors levy.
I just called that book How to Kill a Mockingbird.
I'm pretty sure it's not an instruction manual.
Use rocks and guns and stuff.
Catch them in a net and then hit them with something hard and heavy.
How to murder a mockingbird.
Just get them.
They're really tiny and fragile.
You can step on them.
There's lots of ways.
It's easy.
What do angels eat?
Mockingbirds.
Feed them to an angel.
Cook them.
Throw fire at them.
This is going to be great.
What's his nickname?
Mockingbird killer.
You got Yahoo or a regular question?
Oh, yeah.
Where's Hesitant Houston?
What?
Hi.
Hey.
Oh, a shadowy figure.
Arises for the night.
Hesitant Houston says,
I have a potential job opportunity in Salt Lake City,
which is where my nuclear family lives.
Whoa.
However, all of my awesome friends
and the whole rest of my life is in Houston.
Should I leave it all behind to join the fam
and advance the career,
or should I stay with the friends I love
and hope for the best?
It's from Hesitant Houston.
Listen.
I don't care how awesome your friends are.
If you have a nuclear family,
they're not going to compete with that.
I've seen ones you want to move there
and focus on your half-life.
Yeah.
We...
That's bad.
I've seen the Incredibles.
Yeah.
Do they have, like,
alien tendrils growing out of their body
because of the waste?
I want to know what your situation, like, here is
that you have to define it as hope for the best.
You know, I believe you should be with your family.
Record a podcast with them,
just hang out with them, whatever.
I don't know anybody in Salt Lake City,
but I'm pretty sure that's where they film Sister Wives.
Is that true?
It's around there.
Can you get to know the Sister Wives people?
Because if you get in that club,
there's, like, 45 people in it
for you to just know and have in your crew.
Well, 45 people, 41 of which are kids.
So if you want to be the guy
who has a lot of little kid friends,
which has worked out so well
for many entertainers in the past,
by all means, befriend the Sister Wives.
Or you can be wife of a five.
You can be the fifth wife in that unit,
and then get all the perks of being
in the Sister Wife unit.
No, because he's a dude, and then it gets weird.
Oh, yeah.
You can be brother-husband.
This is my brother-husband resident in Houston.
I love him very much.
I know nothing about Salt Lake City
except that that might be where Sister Wives is filmed,
and that might not even be true.
Don't they have a sports team?
Yeah, the Jazz.
The Jazzers.
The Jazzercizers.
Pretty sure it's not the Jazzers.
I say family beats friends any day of the week.
Isn't that right, guys?
In a fight.
In a fight, you can get it together.
Yeah.
Unless your family sucks.
Are you moving there from Austin?
Dude, that's in Houston.
Whoa.
You're right.
Listen.
Oh, snap.
No, no, no.
That was a good burn.
In my defense, I've drank like half of a Tropical Chillers.
I swear to...
Now the onus is back on you.
We should have handed that out.
How many Tropical Chillers have you drank?
Repost.
Griffin, you got a Yahoo?
I know someone who's not getting a picture with us later.
Ooh.
You absolutely...
Pretty much everyone,
because we'll be passed out in the dressing room.
We're gonna black out on Tropical Chillers.
Did you go to the My Brother, My Brother Me Show?
Yeah, it's the last one.
It was really funny.
For the first 40 minutes,
and then the Tropical Chillers caught up with him.
Griffin, help me out.
Oh, God.
This one is sent in by Alethea Eckhart.
Thank you, Alethea.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Julia, who asks,
does anyone know where to find a gargoyle nativity set?
I'm looking to find a nativity set in the form of gargoyles.
Any suggestions are helpful.
Thanks.
Um, not any suggestions.
I bet the ones that we're gonna have
are not gonna be particularly useful.
In my nightmares.
Did...
Are there other monsters that are getting their own nativity sets
that I didn't know about?
Does anyone know where to find a werewolf nativity set?
Yeah.
With, like, Baby Jesus halfway through Transformers.
They didn't follow a star.
They followed the full moon.
We brought him frankincense and silver bullets.
I... why do you need a gargoyle nativity set?
You know, we don't take the time to ask the obvious questions
and out here, my brother, my brother, me,
what are you doing with this?
So their gargoyle friends don't feel left out.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
Oh, wait.
They're Jewish.
Well, I guess they...
What?
They don't do that.
They don't do the nativity thing, do they?
No, and I don't think they think it starts...
It starts off right there.
Wait, were you thinking of the golem?
That's what it was.
Okay, good.
I got it mixed around my head.
We'll just edit this one out later.
This is a director's cut goof for everybody here.
Hey, let's say more things about Kwanzaa that we don't understand.
I think anybody can appreciate the Kwanzaa cube gag.
I've been working on that for ages.
Can we help this person out and find monster themed nativity sets anywhere?
This is my problem.
To have a gargoyle themed nativity set, at some point,
some stonemason or carver would have to sit there and go,
I'm sick of all this human stuff.
Yeah.
I know what the people want.
I need a Jesus.
Gargoyle babies.
I need a Jesus with wings and a beak.
Also, he is made of stone.
And he perches high upon a watchtower.
I don't think Jesus wants to be in a watchtower.
I think we've got to stick with the manger or else it's not really nativity.
Keep perches on the edge of a manger.
Yeah, because there's no room for him to perch.
And then they're saying, get back in that manger, Jesus.
Yeah, you're a baby.
That's dangerous.
Watch out for the gargoyle cow, Jesus.
There were no perches left on the end, so we had to perch.
The real lie that this set tells is that you can get gargoyles to sit still for anything.
Because they, you know, you get a bunch of them in a room together,
they're going to start arguing, they're going to start having a political fight,
and it's going to be a real disaster.
Yeah, humans, you can get them to stand around, even cows and sheep and stuff,
but gargoyles, ugh.
I have been trying to reference the TV show Gargoyles for a while.
I've been trying to do it in a way that wasn't just saying,
Gargoyles, the TV show.
Hey, if you guys are at the cartoon, they have gargoyles in it.
I almost said that one of the wise men would have to be voiced by Jonathan Frakes.
Jesus.
But I think that might be, like it's a real deep cut.
So I'm really going out to the boneyard for this one.
I would really love to see the look on your face as you look around the audience,
like, guys, Jonathan Frakes, anyone?
How about that Jonathan Frakes groove?
As the stars at night are big and bright.
Deep in the heart of Texas.
Yeah, it gets you out of anything.
That's our fucking zip line.
Bad news, everybody.
That's the ripcord.
So after this, we are working without a net.
You got anything else, Griffin?
Do you have anything else to say?
I do, but it's a question you hate and you don't want me to read.
Oh, do it.
Don't read this fucking question.
Read it as loud as you can.
It was sent by Lynn W.
Wait, can we just end the show instead of that?
That's by Yahoo Answers user Koopy Koo, who asked.
I am against this.
I'm not here for this part.
For the next 30 seconds, Justin's going to check out.
How do I tell my girlfriend that a thing down there looks weird?
Like everyone else does.
It was the first time I ever saw it on a woman and it looked weird.
How do I tell her?
Hold up.
It was the first time you ever saw it on a woman?
You've seen illustrations and stuff.
I was looking through the tree line and I saw it.
It inspired me like sunshine through the boughs.
Yeah, the first time I heard dubstep, it was weird to me.
You have to get used to these things.
Yeah.
Hey, have you ever seen Skrillex's vagina?
It's like wicked weird looking.
I feel that this is like a whole avenue that Hallmark could go down and just like a series
of cards on the front that says, hey, baby, I love you so much.
And there's like a beautiful sunrise.
And then you open it and it just says, but your vagina is weird.
Your business region is like, what?
Your downtown area is like, what the fuck?
You have to broach it with her scientifically.
You have to say, hey, listen.
And push your glasses up your nose.
Push your glasses up your nose and say, listen, I need to see some of your friend's vaginas
because right now I'm-
I'm going to need you to do a side by side comparison.
Yeah, I have no basis.
This is purely scientific.
You understand.
Clinical, a clinical study of your friend Darlene's vagina.
I want you to read that, just the first sentence of that answer.
Rosie says, you're going to destroy her self-esteem if you tell her.
So find a way to communicate that doesn't involve making her feel gross.
If her entire self-esteem is based upon the beauty of her vagina, she doesn't have a lot-
I don't have a lot of things going for me, but man, is my vagina great.
I would like to formally apologize for thinking we shouldn't read this question
because it's gone great so far.
What a gem.
One for the record books, I'd say.
I'm pretty sure that nobody with vagina listens to our show.
Oops.
Sorry.
We should end this.
Thank you guys.
I want to hear Griffin's last question, but first I should say thank you to all of you
who have come to our show from Austin, the surrounding area in New Orleans.
Thank you guys for coming.
You're like the best people in the whole world.
I love you very much.
Thank you so much.
Sorry about that stuff I said about nobody with vaginas listening to the show.
I feel bad about today.
There's a lot of people.
It's just looking around the room.
There's a lot of-
I can't help but notice.
There's like 30 to 40 vagina people with-
And that is what they prefer, right?
Yeah.
That's the PC term.
Vagina among us.
There's a lot of vaginids.
The vaginids among you.
The vaginies.
I can't say that word anymore for the rest of my life.
I burned them all this night.
Thank you.
If anybody wants to eat super fruit gummies, we got them up here.
We got plenty of extras.
Don't be shy.
Don't eat more than two of the acais.
Make sure you come by.
You will freak out.
We'll be over here.
Come by and say hi and get a picture and get something signed and buy a poster if you want
for 10 bucks.
And we're going to be going-
Where are we going to after we're done here?
We're going to go to the Kung Fu Saloon.
They have ski ball, so-
Free ski ball.
Free ski ball, so-
Drink.
Yeah, drink it in.
Free ski ball.
Were you guys just disappointed that the ski ball is free?
That's how you know it's real low level ski ball.
There's going to be kilometers on it.
I saved my tokens.
And special thanks to everyone who helped out with the show tonight.
To Rachel, Sydney, Bristol.
Thanks, guys.
Justin.
Tanner.
Jordan.
And thank you to Blue Theater for having us.
Yeah, thanks, Blue Theater.
I want to thank the creators of Tropic Chillers with a Z.
Don't tell them about all the mean things we said about them.
Your shit tastes so bad.
They probably don't have a lot going for them.
Except for their beautiful vaginas.
Griffin, go ahead with the last question.
This final Yahoo is sent in by Nefariosity.
Thank you, Nefariosity.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Zoro, who is a top contributor, who asks,
Star Wars fans, can a Jedi use the Jedi mind trick to induce labor?
I'm Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been my brother, my brother, me.
Kiss your dad.
I'm Travis McElroy.