hey folks griffin here it's that time of year again a special special time of year where you
can gather the whole family around the jam box and you can play this most most precious candle
nights episode of my brother my brother and me we promise we're gonna keep it clean cleaner even
than years before when we didn't actually keep it all that clean but this time we mean it you know
we're good for it so listen ahead with virgin ears that was that was gross but that was the
last gross thing that we're gonna say on the show on the whole episode i guarantee it come come
around papa mammy daddy there's two dads there's two dads and one mom in this family it's a great
it's a great and crazy family come around everyone gather around for my brother my brother and me's
third annual candle night spectacular
not too familiar
but not too
over the hill lordy lordy look who's 40 what do you mean it's jesus's birthday oh he's getting
up there i see what you did there one more birthday one year closer to death and then life
again right after it three days afterwards happy birthday jesus hey it's jesus's birthday uh
otherwise it's probably a lot of people's birthdays it's probably a lot of people's
birthdays mainly jesus's birthday here my brother my brother and me candle night spectacular what a
bummer it must have been wouldn't you know the years are counting down to you piecing like his
33rd birthday his 32nd birthday was at one like he had to know something was up now justin you
and i both know that that is not the way that the roman calendar works sure it is it's how it's what
what is it why is it one why is it two what do you guys think is gonna happen in two years
i do want to also note that i i did translate this joke from an episode of dinosaurs
oh what's gonna happen what's gonna happen i see hey i thought it sounded familiar and also
hilarious well that's for dinosaurs so but imagine we have to start do we have to start
annotating every time we steal a joke from dinosaurs because this show's gonna become like
one third longer this is our christmas holiday funtacular otherwise known as candle nights
is when we is a non-nominational non-traditional holiday celebration where the only real rule
is just be yourself no rules just right rules just right and also holiday out and also no cursing
there's no cursing that's i guess the only rule so one rule just right the annual did you guys
know we don't do a christmas tree we just do an awesome blossom and then we decorate that awesome
blossom and then we watch over the span of a month as it rots on the ground exactly boy the dogs are
like uh candle lights at our house when the stink is so bad that you can't be in the same house as
the candle lights awesome blossom then you throw it away and then you have a big party to celebrate
that your house doesn't smell like rotten stinky onions anymore now this of course is an advice
show i'm your oldest brother justin mcelroy i'm your middle-est brother travis mcelroy i'm your
sweet baby jesus brother griffin mcelroy guys i have almost sworn like three times already yeah
it's pretty tough it's like hanging over at nani's house and not dropping them you know it's like
one of those like psychological things where it's the don't push the red button thing like as soon
as we announce we can't curse and then you press the red button and then a random person on earth
dies and then you get a million dollars exactly don't scratch that place there i think that the
thing that is important to know first off if it's your first time listening to us welcome we're so
happy that a family member has turned you on to our show oh wow do you want to do you want to
re-emphasize that while we will not be using curse words in the traditional sense we will
be exploring ideas that are extremely upsetting exactly to adults and children alike no cursing
but you know there was a linguistic shorthand to express some of the complicated psychosexual
ideas we will be delving into we have effectively lowered the letter grade of our of our podcast
rating down exactly one step i would like to take this time to apologize for all the screaming that
you'll probably be hearing on my end i live on a street in austin known for its christmas light
displays and the kids are out in full force and for some reason their gut reaction to seeing a
bunch of christmas lights is to scream as if someone was beating them with a pipe they just
love the holidays i don't i haven't looked outside i don't think there's anybody is it like an excited
scream or like a horrified like how could they scream um it's it's a guttural it's just it's
just like almost like they're having a contest to see who can scream as if their their screams
illuminate the lights even brighter if as if their screams provide the lights with the precious
wattage that they need these are these are families like driving through the street right and
mostly walking we had carolers honestly i had carolers last week i didn't know how to handle
it i just stood on the porch i almost i almost asked you why parents would roll down their
windows to share their screams in the neighborhood but then i imagined the alternate personality
who's like let's keep those windows rolled up and just keep all those for me let's just
bake in those let's hot box those screams you know actually so yesterday when justin and i
did some magic um i want everybody to i'm gonna need i'm just gonna need a quick pause to explain
we did some magic together yeah oh you need more than that like special holiday magic did you make
wishes come true for we did make it snow inside with the love in our hearts and we also went to
great wolf lodge and did magic quest oh and defeated a dragon we did it with little kid
wait we did it with a little kid present wait we did we took a little kid with us wait wait
i gave a cape to a little kid i uh this is true i bought a cape and it was eight dollars
it said magic quest on it i was wearing it to the side like a baron or shazam
it got too itchy for my neck and i i there was this little kid who was helping named ryan who
was helping travis to defeat and by little kid like four years old like four years old helping
me shut up now and i was watching all this happen and i said uh here ryan i think you deserve this
cape more than i do and and then i handed it to him and later we were in the back of the room
we're telling this story to my father-in-law and he said that his mom was there right and i realized
that only then did i realize that giving a magical cape to a five-year-old is probably the creepiest
thing i've ever done yeah well so the point of my story here is i watched so many parents carry
their children away towards their rooms screaming like you know and and the parents just continuing
on with their conversation with each other as though the child wasn't screaming and i imagine
that it's got to be like when you decide you're gonna show your kid something awesome or take
them somewhere cool you have to know that at the end of the day they're gonna end up screaming yeah
guess what you're not a wizard anymore sorry yeah let's go you're gonna go back to being a second
grader oh you don't like that trade-off i imagine so i imagine you have to like build up you're a
wizard harry but now you're not anymore because it's tuesday and it's time to go to bed time harry
harry now it's time to go to grandma jones harry uh so listen you know what this is still
a an advice show we should we should get out there and uh and uh and help some people let's
get our hands dirty with yule yeah my family is a rather boring one in terms of gift giving
over the past five years we've mostly exchanged looks dvd sorry books sorry i got you this look
okay we mostly change books dvds and music my parents own electronic readers and owning physical
media is for old maids now i feel entirely unfulfilled giving out itunes codes or whatever
nonsense lets me gift digital goods should i just settle for disappointing codes as gifts
stick with increasingly obsolete formats of gifts or take an entirely different approach that's from
luddye in lambertville first of all i don't i don't think giving dvds books and stuff is and music
is boring because if you were to cut out those three things it does not leave a lot of like other
pop culture media well no but you can reach outside of the of the pop culture realm outside
of that zone maybe you can get me a colander that's none of those things yeah but you can't
like do you can't do a year of all colanders that's true i guess i can't do that i guess he
got you there i also i'm saying like you wouldn't you wouldn't want to like when you're taking away
your hall at the end of the day just have a like a box full of kitchen goods i mean you have a point
but in my defense um it's it's kind of hard to to like strain pasta or cook broccoli um through your
through your pixar brave dvd yeah well if you only have the one you have to knit them together
into a dvd that's gonna be a i'm gonna tell you right now try that that's gonna be a pretty bad
colander i'm just saying unless you are cooking um i do appreciate that the the hand woven dvd
colander you got me last year but it is not effective what's that there are many sharks
what's that fat pasta it looks like cinnabons tortellini that's the only pasta you can do in
there and that's pretty much that's pretty much its only use did you say torbaloni i said torbalon
i said timber lake um i agree that it's not a great i think as part of a gift package uh like
as part of a suite of gifts you're getting someone a code is probably very good yeah you got the
trick to good gift giving is to mix it up like that right like get me an itunes code because i
spend roughly 450 on itunes every week and you know the more you can cut down that number for
me the more i appreciate it then get me something from the heart you know something you made with
your hands then maybe give me something awful to like temper my expectations for the fourth gift
which is another itunes card so you want to cycle through it's the ups and downs good christmas gift
giving is really all about muscle confusion it's really all about zigging i'm doing gift i'm doing
gift insanity zigging left then zigging really hard right and then giving me an itunes you're
basically suggesting giving gifts like a senile great aunt it's basically you know uh what about
a handmade itunes gift card i love that you just stitch it together it's a post-it note and you
wrote 16 random characters on it and you said just a buck how about it etsy or you just get like a
bag with cut up letters and numbers in it and then you have them pick their own 16 digits out
oh that's that way it's like you make your own code and luck be a lady yeah something to do with
the kids you exchange it and it is actually for luck be a lady but it's actually that awful version
that that guy from the eagles did that's like uh it's kind of like a kind of like a reggae jam
you guys i don't know i i don't know what a code is because i don't do a lot of purchasing online
um is that like you get a code for a specific album or for a specific like it's basically
just bucks usually or is it like a gift card it's so it's so hard to tell i don't i don't know how
to do it this person has a point like everything is going digital but i don't want to give i don't
want to give somebody like i don't want to give somebody like a slip of paper and say this can be
a gift this is a gift voucher you know because then you're basically your doorway to a gift
yeah isn't doesn't christmas exist so that you like i will download the music for myself on
itunes but christmas exists so you can hand me a cd like right i don't think it's about the most
convenient thing anymore it's about well let's be honest christmas is about the merch right it's
about the goods well no but what nobody wait what nobody wants to walk away from canon lights
is just no with a with a with nothing to play with right that's the thing if a nerf gun fight
breaks out you can't fire an itunes gift well you can you can you can it's it's incredibly
dangerous and expensive because you're talking about like 10 apps you're throwing you're
weaponizing 10 apps and you're throwing it and it's very sharp i guess i don't have a good answer
so i guess the answer is you get a book and then inside of it you write the code for the
they want actually you can get the code and they'll use the code to get a gift and cool but
like please don't please don't fool yourself into thinking that you're getting a very thoughtful gift
like don't it's not but if like your family is is very utilitarian they may appreciate that they're
not gonna buy what they're not gonna take your ten dollar itunes gift card and then go buy the
greatest hits collection of billy ocean and then every time they listen to that billy ocean mp3
be like oh man thanks chuck oh man you remember when chuck hooked me up with this billy osh
the worst the worst part about gift cards is you can't impose your taste on other people
right unless you write use this to buy billy ocean on the i swear if i find out you didn't
buy billy ocean's greatest hits volumes one through ten then i am done with you hey brice
do you mind if i get on your computer real quick and check my email scan scan scan can't help but
notice i don't see this oh i noticed you got some new some new biscuit on here but i don't see that
billy osh maybe they're uh maybe you got billy ocean the cloud did you put ocean the cloud
maybe toss ocean the cloud let me check nothing in the old drop box i am confused brice i left
explicit instructions did you burn it did you burn osh to a disc and maybe you have like maybe
an osh like portable hard drive do you have your ocean on a on a jazz drive can i breeze your jazz
drives so we don't know next question next question sorry here here's a bit here's a gift
card thank you move along thank you thanks for playing what would you do next question
okay here's our next guest so don't just sit there up until up until now my wife and i have
alternated spent in the holidays with my family one year and hers the next mine involves a rather
pricey flight out east while hers is a 5.5 sorry five and a half hour drive away we figure we're
at the age where it's time to start our own traditions and want to start spending christmas
at home this what is wrong with me i'm having a stroke here we go i want to start spending
christmas at home this isn't going to be much of an issue with my family since the cost involved
with the flight to christmas is an easy excuse however my wife's family already doesn't think
we visit enough despite the five and a half hour drive being relatively long for me as the only
driver and as soon as we start skipping the trip out east they will surely start asking why we
aren't visiting them instead i thought you might know how we could break the cycle without causing
too much family drama can somebody explain signed seeking silent nights can someone explain me what
this question is asking because it was just a bunch of in my head all i heard was a bunch
of directions it's an algebra problem i was saying two families leave the station traveling in
opposite directions at each other how much do they love each other um basically this person wants to
stop traveling at christmas and i guess the best i have for him is yeah yeah dude sorry so next but
his family every movie that like came out in the 80s and 90s about being with your family on
christmas like that's what it's all about let me reference sorry our friend jonathan taylor thomas
his performance in i'll be home for christmas okay it was awesome it was good is that your
reference we can't move on i need a quote i can't quote it i can just tell you how i felt when i
saw i need any evidence that you know what it's about at all it's about his dad wanting him to
come home for christmas and him saying he doesn't want to and so his dad offers to give him a car
if he's able to be home in time for christmas just jessica biel's in the mix right his gf
is she wants him home real bad except that some some some thugs take him don't want him home with
this gf don't want him to get that car they super glue a santa suit to him throw him in the desert
all of a sudden he's got to find his way home but he doesn't have a card he doesn't have any money
doesn't have any documentation how is jtt gonna crack this nut i'll tell you i was gonna crack
this night with his charms and his wiles well here's the thing okay so real talk of course
of course when you say to your family either side hey we don't want to come home for the holidays
their reaction is not going to be like cool dude drop us a line when like there is no way to do
this right i mean they're going to be if you're asking how to do this without making them upset
the answer is you can't you can't do that unless unless you have a kid there it is that's the
answer you're looking for that's your only get out of jail free card because then you can say i
don't really i don't think he's ready to travel that far i don't we're pretty exhausted we're
just gonna spend it home with a family and you get away with that for two years and pretty soon
you're building your own christmas traditions with your kid at your house now they're gonna
come visit you this step is vital you have got to instill in this child a holy fear of planes and cars
you need to ruin this kid um trans transportationally speaking you need to know how
dakota is about traveling you know if we get dakota near a plane or a cdu or any sort of
a a razor scooter if this kid walks too fast if i once told him that eagles could pick you
up and carry you away and he won't get near birds period he won't even watch the movie planes trains
and automobiles i love that movie and you know that's my favorite movie and i can't even have
it in the house now if he sees the box on the shelf he freaks out i was gonna share that with
my son i know i have to keep it locked in a box in the basement i made a new label for it it's
called uncle buck too it's all forward in the buck averse if you think about it all john candy
movies are in the buck averse no bull crap though the the uh uh the dude in home alone is the same
guy in planes trains and automobiles right i mean he doesn't they don't explicitly say it but
ironically enough the entire movie of home alone was conceived because of the scene in uncle buck
when mcauley colton is talking to the guy through the mail slot so that was like the that was the
genesis of of home alone so you can make the argument that that is in the buck averse and
maybe there was that alternate ending to uncle buck where he they're like what are you gonna do
now uncle buck he was like i don't know i've been thinking about training for the olympics fast
forward fast forward to fast sledding to make a story to go sleds but then they change the title
of that in theaters to air buddy to air buds sled but snow snow buddies snow snow buddies snow buds
snow business just joking just just josh around the ice with my friends who are dogs
the whole title of the movie so have a kid griffin yoni yahoos have a kid on us you know i'm reading
these and i don't think they're going to be good for our for the tone of this show yeah about this
one uh this one was sent by steve lewis thank you steve lewis it's by yahoo answers your question
mark who asks what would happen if you were to drink the water that was from where frosty snowman
melted oh no what no don't don't dodge the question you too um oh no justin are you still
close to travis uh no can you take that fool back to magic quest i'm too far to comfort
oh no travis has a point though with this travis's tears have a great point um which is that frosty
is kind of like the most messed up of all right hollad i think because like no imagine if like
rudolph the red-nosed reindeer had like had like really bad ms just like just like ready to go
you know what i mean like six to eight weeks that is what we're working with with frost even
more troubling is the fact that frosty references it in his song now before i melt away like he knows
his impending death his his heat related death is on the way yeah and he brings it up to some
kids he brings it up instead of doing something instead of like moving to bismarck like do
something about it or visiting his friend bismarck key put me in your cooler
frosty you still got that stand up freezing my man frosty the snowman is a great way to teach
your kids about death while still kind of dodging the question in time because he does he does die
you're just kind of counting on that your kids won't remember the next time it snows yeah like
ah crap okay it also had this combo it also dodges the question about um where babies come from
because you can just say that you just put like a magic hat on a lump of flesh a big sack of flesh
and organs and you put a magic hat on it and then it comes to life well isn't that wasn't there a
nickelodeon show about that with the mannequin and the magic hat i see that's where babies come from
today's special that's how babies are born from mannequins i also wonder if when frosty melts
does he reconstitute is it like if you froze him and then like i that is worrisome to me is if i
drank right the frosty frosty leavings and then he attempted to reconstitute in my body if he would
just burst out like an alien or do you gain his his holiday power or does he do you become frosty
do you become frosty at that point and like the snowman forms around your body and consumes you
okay hey bryce you kind of sound like you sound like burl Ives what's going on in there do you
carry his spirit because then i would think there should be an alternate ending to the hit film jack
frost when his kid is just on hands and knees lapping up his dad i gotta get all of him he's
gotta i gotta carry with me what are you doing philip i'm drinking my dad drinking my dad he's
really bad at driving i got to save you michael keaton get inside me come with me michael keaton
come with me if you want to live was was jack frost the movie that michael keaton did and then
just said i can't do movies i can't be in movies for a while my career is going to take a nap for
a bit jack frost started myself what has he done since then i'm worried about him he's still around
right i mean are you asking is he alive yes okay he's done some some one-offs you know he's been
in some things he was in a show called the company which is tv miniseries he was on that episode 30
rock and he's i think he's in the new robocop or toy story 4 or both it's both is he happy i don't
know when was the last time y'all wondered if uh michael keaton was happy is he safe is he has
anybody what was the last thing you did for michael keaton other than buy jack frost on uh
vhs and dvd and you bought it on vh you bought it on vhs first right when dvds like started becoming
a thing and you felt like such a boob you're like if only i'd waited could have gotten all
those special features if if anyone is listening and they're near michael keaton could you check
on him for me if you're michael keaton and you're listening to this can you just drop us a line
just let us know where you are what if it's something really depressing it was like
michael keaton is the mayor of the safeway that he assistant manages oh no oh no michael keaton has
checked in at the michael keaton museum that he made i would hate to be the weird magician that
came up with the frosty stuff and then try to explain to people why i don't know what good
excuse like first up you have to open and like the first line of your explanation has to be
well not for sex listen i want to be clear on one thing this should be self-evident this thing's
made out of snow and coal there is there is no it's not a weird sex thing i was lonely
and was i open-minded yes i was what he has to really explain ship maybe what he has to explain
away is why make this sentient living thing with the heart and soul of a kind human being
out of the most like fleeting substance that there is i made this hat that you put on a fart
and it turns it into a person oh what was i thinking you know how sometimes you experience
a sort of a niggling fear of death can you imagine a creature that didn't even have the
respite of knowing that that day would someday come and after that the fear would stop i need
something that's perpetually obsessed with its own mortality so much so that upon meeting small
children in this winter town he mentions casually his obsession with his own fleeting lifespan
um a rich my first shot at this was frosty the sort of homunculus i made out of wet sand right
on the edge of the beach right at about like 4 30 right before high tide came in have you ever
noticed how from 10 a.m to 4 p.m every single day you just hear a creature screaming a sandy sandy
scream and terror that's my bad that's right mark my words just move them off the beach you say
that's not a bad idea but then the pelicans can get at them i'll workshop it but i can't promise
anything oh you know it's the pits is that that one unseasonably warm day followed by a week of
just the chilliest winter dude today i was walking around cincinnati in a t-shirt and jeans it was
like 68 degrees today and tomorrow it's gonna be like 22 i think that justin was talking about
from the viewpoint of of frosty the snowman human snowman not as as with most things i had to run
it through a filter of how it pertained to me not as a skin-based human being it also was bad for
me though because then you had to find a sweater later at least you didn't have to face your own
gosh darn mortality while knowing that a life of happiness is just around the corner for you
but at least a week if you think about he puts this hat on he knows like nothing it's his birthday
you know by the by the way a a top hat not even a sun hat to protect him from the rain whatsoever
and and he's just this happy-go-lucky young man and yet for some reason there's two things he knows
he knows how to love and that he will soon be dead he's learning everything else on his own
and yet there is one inherent piece of information in his head oh by the way if it heats up above
say about 32 i'm out of here yeah so you're basically saying he's the epitome of tim mcgroth's
live like you were dying yes he was specifically created to know only one thing and that he didn't
have long to go live like you were melting i told some kids in the neighborhood about how i was gonna
die i tried to try to go skydiving but i just kind of fell apart because i made a snow can't
if a parachute whipped me back it would probably rip me in half please don't throw my chest bones
at a kid i don't think i think his bones are made of snow and then you turn those into snowballs
and he hits everybody with it right how is he ambulatory if inside his snow flesh is not a
nice skeleton i assume it was like various sacks of water and air it's like squishing and refilling
much like an octopus or something along those lines how did you go see frosty yeah i tried
to stand next to him the sound of his body moving maybe that had nothing to do with magic it was
just like the it was genetics kind of genetically made a half that when you put it on like that was
the only response system this is gonna sound weird but could you put your could you put your
mouth on my armpit and blow my air sac seems to have deflated i want to wave goodbye to you kids
oh it's too late watch out for my venomous prongs i have all i have all those to keep the dogs away
oh the traffic cop hollered stop so i inked all over him goodbye i'm nature's greatest monster
merry christmas um i'm a nightmare please end me please just turn that radiator on i will be
out skis in like 10 it does explain why frosty smokes though yeah why he has a pipe all right
first up just want to say a big happy birthday to ethan that's coming to you from seth i don't know
why you got to take jesus's flavor though yeah way to go ethan i mean you guys realize that
this episode isn't even going up remotely close to the day of yes griffin but everyone knows that
he wasn't actually born on december 25th okay they just they just had to delay it because of
air time on tv specials ah get out of here that doesn't seem like that doesn't seem true so have
so even we are so proud of you from seth you know seth didn't say this but i really feel like he
seems really touched by just everything that you've been doing lately and he yeah he's so
proud of you i wish you'd cut back on the i can't say you know okay so seth is very proud of you
but he did mention that one thing um and it would be cool if you could maybe do that less let's just
say seth knows and also jesus knows and also your net nanny knows because jesus installed the net
nanny on your pc all of those parties also know about the album national helium shortage by red
sky phenomenon griffin you're into uh music what what could that be um if you like indie
if you're into indie it doesn't get more indie than this uh this album this album was created
using android apps and also a nintendo ds did you guys know you could even do that they got all
kinds of things what you need a quark sympathize sympathizers they've got that on the ds you can
mix together entire albums that's how celo green got started have you heard the album celo green
made where he makes it on ds mm-hmm it's called it's called pokemon celo green um anyway uh you
can get on bandcamp at red sky phenomenon dot bandcamp dot com for zero dollars if you want
but you shouldn't want that you should want to provide them money with which to continue their
art um and if you very cool i just listen to it it's gonna it's gonna get your blood pumping it's
all straight like it even if i don't know what indie music is um this would be a good way for
you to start getting into indie to start enjoying indie it's a great gateway to indie yeah so you
guys can put these quotes on your website if you want yeah a great indie indie it's an indie
guaranteed you have it for me the king of indie music um guys we have another very special sponsor
this week it is uh it is an app which you can get on your ios it's called uh brackalope which is kind
of a silly name i bet you're wondering hey what are you even talking about well let me tell you
and stop being so impatient all the time uh brackalope is a tournament builder it is an
app that lets you build tournaments not the buildings in which like the olympics took
place or anything like that but uh it lets you build the brackets for those tournaments
hence the brackalope up to 128 players um and it allows you to put in all the metadata that you
need metadata is so important for brackets you guys does it say on there like does it limit the
sport um yes it's only do blood sports it's only for figure hacky sack um so uh no it's for it's
all for all manner of things uh and it's all online it's all in the cloud uh so you can
automatically you know post your results online and stuff and it's free it's free on the ios
um brackalope is getting its start uh it's sponsoring the portland pin brawl 2013 which is a
as you can imagine a pinball tournament in in portland oregon um so yeah if you need to settle
some stuff maybe a super smash brothers tournament um maybe thumb wrestling uh maybe blood sports
maybe blood maybe best maybe best kissing maybe your best who's the best at kissing it's the
sport everyone can get behind then you gotta go to brackalope.com and you gotta download this app
it's free you don't even need to go to their website i know some people hate browsers just
get away that's spelled b-r-a-c-k-e-l-o-p-e that's right that's brackalope go get it and solve your
blood sport problems i want to tell you about our last advertiser extreme restraints.com
um uh it is a it is a diverse retailer all right all right with a variety of goods
that seem to have no discernible theme no it's a general store then you would say it's something
of a general store uh here's an attachment you can put on a drill that it seems to be a soft
rubber tip perhaps to protect you from drilling things accidentally what happens are you jamming
a drill and then you turn it on and you say whoops that's not i didn't mean to drill this
this chair how does how you get into this predicament in the first you trip you trip
you get excited because you're about to drill something so you start drilling and then you fall
or trip okay i guess i think i like everything is illuminated okay good now it all makes total sense
i'm i'm looking at one thing here and it looks like have you ever like been carrying a candle
around i thought like i just takes up a whole hand and i need two hands to do some things
it looks like here they have a belt that you can wear that you can hold the candle on the belt
and then you have two free hands i think that's impressive i think i understand um you know
sometimes you're uh at home you just got back from the grocery store and you pull you get out
the kielbases that you bought at the grocery store and you think man i these sure looked
bigger at the grocery store and then you get them out and you find them unsatisfyingly small
and you think these aren't gonna keep me these are gonna fill me up um they have a special
i'll call it a peripheral and it is a pump and you put the kielbasa inside it and if you
you and then all of a sudden your kielbasa the kielbasa that you bought for eating is bigger
have have you ever said something you didn't mean to someone and you think ah me and my big mouth
when am i gonna learn to keep my what am i gonna learn to keep my big mouth shut
well what if i could what if what if you could put a ball in there all the time that you can't
take out at all maybe a big maybe you put a whole leather mask in front of your face it looks like
a dog and you know ever and it's very funny because you know it's a great gag gift because
everyone's always walking dogs but nobody ever puts the leash on a person you know what else
makes a great gag yeah a gag can this be the rest of the episode please have you ever have you ever
been at home and it's real hot so you're obviously you're not wearing any pants or underpants
and so you're sitting there and um i don't want to get blue but let's say your privates are out
but all of a sudden there's a bunch of wild dogs get in the room and you're afraid that you'll be
bitten uh on your privates well there's a special cage that you can put around it to keep wild
animals away from the thing that you have down there whatever it may be but i think i know what
strength is looking out for your safety it's a hey it's a safety cage like a shark with shark
divers to use you know how sometimes when you turn into a werewolf people chain you up in the
basement uh-huh well what if only your privates turn into a werewolf have you thought about that
underserved uh portion of the population it what if you're the captain of a pirate ship okay go on
i'm following so far how you need something to with which to punish the the shipmates who act up
and we're really uh you can't go to target and buy a cat of nine tails you know what i mean
i mean sure yeah go on this is a whip specifically for non-sexual punishment i can't stress this
enough well imagine this that you're trying to get to work right but you're late and you need to
take the carpool lane but you're by yourself and you got no one to carpool with you but then you're
reaching the trunk and you inflate yourself a friend and you call them into your passenger
seat carpool buddy that's the extremistraints.com you ever look at really skiing cucumber and
thought i bet i could juice that uh-huh extremistraints.com has got you covered
if you had honcho man chronic constipation is a problem that a lot of people run to nowadays
maybe you want to buy maybe you don't want to go to the ballgreens and buy a douche
and maybe you want to buy a special douche one that can get real deep in there you know
chronic diarrhea is a problem it'd be easier just plug it up it's just not nothing you know
swings are great for the kids what about adults but don't you miss the fun of of soaring through
the air not a care of the world well extremistraints has you covered with a fun swing to swing on sure
i you know what can't hey what am i get your hand out of the cookie jar no problem i got a lube for
you extremistraints.com is the if you use the coupon code middlest you can get all these uh
gadgets helpful household items household gadgets at uh at 20 off so that's pretty great go to
extremistraints.com use the coupon code middlest there's um yeah you got another one um i just
found a shirt let me workshop it real quick i just have to workshop it while i talk i need
something to spread on my english muffins and i'm a member of the male sex i can't go out and i
can't use country croc because it's too expensive and i know i can't use girl butter because it's
girl butter because it's not it's not my it's not my given gender fortunately extreme restraints
has a product that is called boy butter so i'll just go ahead and i'll buy a few of those in bulk
so i don't even have to worry about my butter needs anymore it's like the doctor pepper you
know it's just for men right yeah it literally it literally comes in a 16 ounce tub or also a
squeeze bottle which is good because sometimes i've only got one hand because the other hand
is holding the english muffin are your kids harry potter pretending not upsetting enough
well we've got a wand for you
it's upsetting here we go brothers that was 20 minutes that was worth it that was the best ad
ever brothers i've been with my boyfriend for three years not once have i surprised him with
a really good gift he always buys what he wants he's really into video games and a fan of the show
i just don't know what to get him that he'll enjoy but also won't put me in the poor house
can you help a lady out thanks brothers and happy candle nights boy you know uh polygon.com is running
a great series of gift guides oh don't you cross promote listen i think that is that it is a great
suggestion to go to polygon.com don't make bathrooms where you eat justin this by the way
this show is definitely the bathrooms you understand that right the place we eat is the
place we work but this show is the bathrooms this show is supposed to death the bathrooms there's no
question about that um let me ask you guys this okay is there something to be said like i envision
it as a triangle right three different points one point is surprise one point is money spent and the
other point is like just numerical amount of gifts and i feel like you can make up for not having one
of the three present by having more of the other two sure sure because if you're not surprising him
fine but i don't think you can and don't and make no mistake if you buy a gift that we recommend and
he listens to the show you will not be surprising him right no um let me list off my top this is
gonna make things really easy because you say he's really into video games and he's a fan of the show
um my top three presents of all time are the sony playstation the game boy advance and the
nintendo 64 so like just get him a new game thing just get him one of those new game things is it
expensive yes but will he remember it forever probably not because he's not a child but
it's too late to have that sort of impact um what i could recommend is maybe a uh
maybe a book about video games um that's not surprising a book
reading about video games is actually how i kind of got into my current career reading
lennard herman's the rise and pho phoenix the rise and fall of video games i got you a book
i wrapped it in socks to double how awful it is
hope you like reading i got you i got you do stuff i basically got you an unpaid job
i got you a clerkship
um happy apprenticing um god gift giving is so hard isn't it guys
yes it is so hard you know what's hard is was you get to be adults mostly if i want something i
either buy it or convince myself i don't want it well it's really hard to find something i'm not
buying that's not as common as you say justin that is a specific problem that you do right well
that's true what i don't know a lot of other people that want a fushigi and just buy it well
then you don't know anybody that has an amazon prime account yeah that's kind of our thing
oops just bought a second fushigi both my wife and i wanted to buy a turntable i was told to
not call it a record player but that's what we're using it for for some time so we can listen to
some groovy tunes on vinyl we've been trying to cut the brick candlelight season and i'm
rocking my brain trying to determine a good gift for my so so i keep coming back to as a turntable
i really believe she'd be grateful to unwrap it but i can't help but hesitate because it's
something i want just as much oh it's uh as if i'd be receiving one and a half gifts on the
exchange that seems a bit selfish to me brothers what should i do buy something else and risk
possible dissatisfaction or go ahead with the turntable and claim the lawn chair of the candle
lights that's her ep list in seattle such a good question wow that's a good one yeah for sure because
there's lots of things that teresa and i enjoy together and so when i think this would be
something awesome for both of us it always throws in that like tinge of like yeah but
that's not how it's supposed to work can i give you some advice yeah please give me some advice
you you stupid idiot what about me neither of you both of you are no okay just just enjoy it
just say you said that like the devil would say it no yeah can i say it a different way yeah okay
and just enjoy it just enjoy the this this special it's a it's an aligning of the stars
as you should see it as a celebration of the fact that you and your significant other like
the same stuff you know what i mean and also you know something out of it you know what i mean
why not do the turntable and also some records that you know she would like i i bet they'd
probably like the same kind of music though oh yeah or you could just don't worry about getting
her records that she likes but instead only get her records that you hate just understand that i'm
giving something up by giving this to you right and that is my right to not listen to tom jones
all the time on vinyl and just know that she's probably also getting you a turntable
and you're going to end up with two turntables please please don't also
oh god so uh might i also recommend uh a crossley turntable c r o s l e y i got one from sydney
uh last year and it is a fine product yeah they make a really good uh
make a really good turntable it comes in a case it looks very retro and a microphone
all right all right okay
oh travis my son has asked santa for a wii u is it santa or santa my son is
my son is at santa for a wii u this this year my wife and i have absolutely no intention of
buying a wii u for a variety of reasons he's young enough that we don't want to tell him
the truth about santa yet but we don't want to be he be disappointed with the big day comes
we've tried several ways of talking them out of this wii u idea but his conviction is pretty strong
how can we shake him of the idea that santa will bring him this ridiculous gift without ruining
the magic that's from alex why is your kid asking for presents from santa from game of thrones
i don't understand see i thought it was beyonce's alter ego santa fears sure listen uh let me uh
let me talk to your kid you guys have to leave the room come in here little brice come in here
little brice let the let the brothers back right talk to you now parents you do have to leave the
room we probably you know we can't use bad words we've been bound by a blood oath so uh just leave
the room and let us talk to him brice just leave your kid with us leave your kid with us for like
hey kid two minutes kid take this cape hey kid kid wear this cape while i talk to you listen kid
you know santa's gonna bring it to you yeah yeah mom and dad are playing this playing dumb
basically they're trying to be so you know my parents try to play this game oh what a genesis
i'm not gonna get you one of those and then what's that nintendo 64 wouldn't you like settle
for a nintendo 63 uh and then what's that behind the couch oh must be from santa what's that from
nani nani's got you another present this is that it's a secret present wait what did what did nani
get it open oh it's a sewing machine box nani why wait a minute wait a minute feels like there's
some extra space something now rattling around in this box open it up is it close
there's a map there's a map on this sweater
there's a map there's a map on this sweater is that a codex oh my god jesus had a son
i'm not even worried about the we you anymore now i'm off on an international
intrigue i love this i'm gonna go find the pope and kill him while he sleeps
i did not read the division that's basically it um bryce listen bryce you know santa's gonna
bring it to you yeah if you believe your parents are just playing dumb santa always hooks you up
bryce for real have you been good that's the only question because if it doesn't show up
then you know that somewhere along the line you done goofed up somewhere bryce have you been good
and are you a christian have you heard the good news bryce you've got good news wear this cape
wear this cape take this little book don't tell your parents though
bryce we've got good news about the love of christ keep this little book secret bryce
you're gonna be like don't tell your parents this is a book bryce they'll tell you it's all lies
they don't know it's full of good news your parents don't believe bryce that's why they
don't think the we you is coming but if santa doesn't bring you a we you then jesus definitely
is this is jesus is we you insurance bryce doesn't bring you a we you it's because your
parents don't believe in jesus you gotta diversify diversify your we you portfolio
listen playing with you is cool you know what it's cool living forever don't you live forever
bryce and also possibly playing two we use one from santa one from jesus after you hear this
good news you're gonna be like we who because because of the good news nintendo power no power
of prayer power of prayer maybe the real power isn't into the power after all and also nintendo
power of prayer hey bryce jesus does what nintendo just who ever thought bryce chew it over maul it
over parents you can come back wait don't wait it's all sorted right bryce we smoothed it all out
hey listen get do get my cake back from him though that wasn't for keeps that wasn't keeps that was
like a loader cake after he's crying he's crying because he saw something outside the window that
scared him it was a hawk a big hawk flew down we scared it away we freaked it out though
god once you have one year where santa doesn't bring the kid what he wants year you never have
to worry about bad behavior again yeah you know do you want this to be like the one year
the one year that santa really followed through on his seemingly hollow threat to not bring you
what you wanted um just merry christmas bryce's parents it's going to be a great one i can just
kind of be a great one don't listen back to that part you may be tempted just burn this after you
after it's done i mean bryce just flush it just flush this phone down the potty bryce
daddy doesn't need bryce come back that way santa can find it because he lives in the sewers
say no i'm thinking of it i'm sorry one of those three is definitely going to hook you up with
the we you jesus santa or this is important bryce don't go to him let him come to you with the we
you don't he's going to come at you from the sewer like check it out just slide it to you down
here having a fun fun two-screen experience with mario and yoshi come check it out and you say no
pennywise why don't you come up i got a big team up here come up here pennywise they all waggle down
here bryce i'm gonna teach you i've got i've got a lot of space that you can really explore with
that gamepad you're gonna i'm telling you i think it's gonna be way better up here so why don't you
just just not in the sewer if we could hey i know kids love clowns is there a clown in the world that
can entice a child to follow into a sewer how good is this clown he was just so gosh darn charming
he is no he's not he's tim curry and tim curry as we know could tim curry blessed with natural charm
could tim curry entice any child into any space anywhere on the earth above ground or subterranean
for any reason using any means imaginable he could have all the we use in candy in the world
and be standing 10 feet away from the child in an open space i'm gonna make you a deal surrounded
by we use the candy the pony and the balloons right no where's he could tim curry couldn't
entice a child into an ice cream truck driven by a pokemon he could be surrounded by his parents
and police officers come here you're going to love this i'm chilling in here with pikachu and charme
charizard pump the brakes we're all eating push pops
how'd you do i see you met my faithful ghastly
man don't get strung out by the way i look well like what else do i have to go on right now you
are a clown with sharp teeth i would rather not do get strung out very strong i also don't think
tim curry could encourage an adult to do anything well except dance
okay so this has been our very special very tim curry agnostic it right this is an episode where
we make fun of tim curry even though we all really love tim curry yes you've seen clue so
oh man we could keep going like this for another two to three minutes let us
worst witch i mean oh my god that's a great one i wish you'd do a christmas version of that
maybe like worst elf maybe like anything can happen not christmas
okay so this has been my brother my brother and me it's a christmas show oh he was also great in
the shadow oh man what's that man everybody saw that thank you so much for for listening to this
show with a family member uh i'm sure you shared it with them and they can go and uh find it find
it and uh listen to it on their own selves so i'm sure they're so hungry for this what
uh yeah i'm sure they're dying for another taste they're not in any way full uh thank you to people
who tweeted about the show this week uh slim jim fatty andy jackson uh dave your fave bill zucker
geeky lindsay uh moskva mule mule sorry it's a liquid you there in dube uh ryan macklin the rab
everybody oh and also uh just you know there will be no episode next week yeah because it's christmas
you fools yeah we're gonna be you know spending spending special time together um i want to thank
sean rogerick in the long winters for use for a theme song into departure off the album uh putting
the days to bed which would make a great christmas present if you haven't bought it for anyone um it
would make a great hannukah present too but you missed it you goofed you missed it by a day it
would make a good anytime present it would make it yeah it would make a good tuesday present um
so so yeah just consider it and just guys thank thanks so much i you know you know what i mean
yeah we really yeah right this well the world's gonna end in four days so oh yeah we're not gonna
get a chance to talk to you again yeah so we'll miss you yeah i mean the world is pretty much
already over um but but you guys have made these last few years just really just really special
really special and and good and you know do you guys know what i'm trying to say
god i get it i get i do get it god help me i get it we've been in the show for for two years and
like eight months and every year has been more special than the one before well the year actually
the year has actually been worse like things are things are just really going to hd double hockey
sticks you know yeah we kind of messed it up as humans this year but um and get it back on track
i don't even think dogs have done great especially great um no either um but and in spite of all that
you guys just keep me coming back for more by which i mean life i guess yeah so thanks there
won't be a episode uh does that mean we're gonna post an episode on new year's eve yeah okay well
we'll do that then i guess um and uh appreciate you guys then people need to know we end up calling
the next year although really it's a moot point everything's going right in quetzalcoatl's gullet
next week yeah at this point after these last couple months we really closed it down
yeah everyone else will figure it out in four days you know what i mean i think quetzalcoatl
came for us now we'd be like ah you got it yeah go ahead yeah next guy try by which i mean that's
our bad bipedal sentient cockroaches with superhuman strength and brain power maybe neck
they'll have a better shot than we did because we really goofed it up merry christmas everybody to
you and yours and happy holidays if you don't if you don't like christmas but it really is the
best one um this one was sent by emily wall thanks emily wall it's by yahoo answers user jssl 2234
who asks um this holiday themed question is nickelback a good band to listen to while trying
to get rid of a meth addiction happy candle lights everyone i'm justin mcroy i'm travis mcroy
i'm griffin mcroy it's been my brother my brother and me kiss your dad on the lips