The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be followed
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it
Also, this show isn't for kids which I mentioned only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening
What's up, you cool, baby?
Ah, it's better, it's better with you
My life
Ah, ah, ah, ah
It's better, it's better with you
This is true
Ah, ah, ah, ah
It's better, it's better with you
My life
Ah, ah, ah, ah
It's better with you
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother, my brother and me, an advice show for the modern era
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy
And I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy
Took too long
Oh Griffin
We were trying to do like a you're 1995 Chicago Bulls kind of stuff
Travis wasn't on that trick
McElroy, you are in
England
Oh, yeah
And I think it sounds a little something like this
Go ahead, Justin
Go ahead, Justin, what does England sound like?
Around him?
Yeah, do like what England sounds like
Here's the horse clomps
This is like a village
Yeah
Your sconebread's ready, guv
That's good, cool
That's what it'll be like there. Travis, it's so weird that you're in England right now
I mean, not while you're recording this
But like, when you're listening to this, probably, you're in London
Oh, wait, when I'm listening to it?
Justin, I don't listen to our own
You're in England
You're in England, dude, how lucky
How are you preparing?
Okay, this is the thing about us
A lot of people, we don't talk about it enough
No, we don't talk about Bruno
It's like Bruno
We don't talk about it enough
We all work out of our houses
Our houses are not acclimated to, like, outside play
Outside our house
Or the sun
So we have to have extremely specific nigh on hermetic conditions
Correct
That just sort of follow us around
If we are to perform in the way to which people have become accustomed
Travis, you are like, you're leaving the bubble in such a major way right now
I've done a couple things
You know how you're compensating
I've done a couple things to prepare
You can't, you're
Travis
I don't want to get too worked up about this, but you're going into a situation
Where if you were
In discomfort or inconvenience
President Joseph
Gordon Biden himself
Could not intercede
On your behalf
Well, I have diplomatic immunity
You're risking major political repercussions
I moved to DC
So I could be closer
To the support of daddy
I mean, Joseph Gordon-Biden
By the president
So that if I get hurt or uncomfortable
Daddy would be
I mean, Joseph Gordon-Biden would be right there for me
Yeah, no, J.G. Biden gave me diplomatic immunity when I get over there
So that's going to help a lot
That's going to help a lot
Also, I learned
I don't know if you guys know this
Every McDonald's in the U.K. operates as an American embassy
So if I go there
That's good
So the two things that I've done to prepare
Is one, I got those
Those shoes
That are like rubberized
And they're like toe socks, but they're like rubberized shoes
And that's going to help me walk on the cobblestones
Well
Did you really get the sock shoes?
Well, I got it adjusted for the cobblestones
For the cobblestones
It helps with the grip
Did you see Free Solo?
So fucking funny
I really expanded the canon a lot
Now, the second thing I've done
Did you ever read that children's book
Where the man sells hats by stacking all the hats on top of his head?
Yes
I think it's called Come Get These Hats
I've done that, but with masks
So what I'm going to do is
I've got a stack of masks
About ten masks deep
That I wear on my face
Each one more powerful than the next
And did you say Sticky Ricky hat stack shoes?
Is the name of that book?
Yeah
Then the monkeys come and Sticky Ricky is like
You took my hat stack, I don't want it to do now
To God that I had just said Sticky Ricky hat stack
Into oblivion
My track could be lowered at that point
So I was no longer on it
We're going to have Rachel raise it up and lower it
By the way, Tricky Ricky hat stack
Oh, Sticky Ricky hat stack
Is the sequel
That makes a lot more sense
That's the vivid entertainment version of it
It sucks that me and Justin are just stuck here in stupid old America
That's okay, you can hold it down
We've been here for so long
And haven't gotten a break like you're about to get
Hey, I also just days ago
Just two days ago
Remembered that I needed to dig out my power adapter for the plugs
Can we get this shit together? It's 2022
Can we figure this out guys? It's metal and electricity
I'm not saying it has to all be the shape of America's plug
I'm saying how can we not as a planet universally decide on a plug shape
Let's talk about it
Let's get into this
Countries get electricity at different times
There's a chart I'm sure
At night you don't need it
Can none of them
Are they so horny for electricity
That they can't wait to ask the next country
How did you guys do this?
What was your plan?
You meant they get it at different times throughout history
Not that everybody takes turns using electricity throughout the day
There is someone who did it first and then there's someone who did it second
And the person who did it second looked at the country that did it first
And was like, fuck that
We can do a better plug
But that's not how science works
That's not how tech works
Where you do one thing and then you rock with it
Although that is how we've done plugs
I think it sucks
Every place has their own plugs
And sometimes it's easy to get them twisted up
Because there's different shapes of prongs
I want just one big prong
One big prong
One big hole
Not, I guess, big enough for a kid finger
But like
You're going to the promised land because the UK just made a rule
Every plug's got to be USB-C
No more lightning over there
They don't got lightning in England
Bring plugs
They threw away all the lightning cords
You have to
That's the weird thing
King Charles did it
And then the only thing
Then he abdicated and handed it to William
That one thing was bugging me a lot
What people don't realize is that
Queen Elizabeth
Made a law that it all had to be
Micro-USB
And actually it was
Initially mini-USB
It was mini-USB, the really chunky boy
And Charles would sit behind her like
Mom, please
Mom, this sucks
I can't charge my Nintendo DS
Mom
Please make it so that it's here
The first thing he did when he's king, he's like, what's up?
Give me all your lightning plugs
They're going on a bonfire
And what is your second proclamation?
I didn't think beyond this
I didn't have a lot of time to think about it
Just like the last 70 years
But I've decided
I'm done now
William, take it home
The crown owns all the USB-C cords
So
Those are all owned by the king
By the TV show The Crown
Okay, bye
The king
Now owns all the swans
In England, right? You know this thing
That owns all the swans
Now the king owns all the swans
What?
The queen
The monarchy of England
The queen of England
She owned all the swans
They legally belong to her
Correct
If you fuck with any swan in England
The queen could come to you and be like
That's my swan
That sucks
As long as we're on this note
As long as someone whose job is like
I take care of the ravens
And that's his deal
That's fine
That's one bird keeper is fine
Did the swans sign off on this?
She also owns all the whales
People don't talk about that as much
It doesn't come up as often
She owns all the whales
It's rare, Justin, that you're driving too fast
Down the motorway and hit a whale
She's not as worried about those
Well, she's not as worried about anything anymore
Do you think
She's dead, Griffin
It's time that you accept it and move on
Do you think when King Charles got the crown
He found some swans that he had had particularly bad interactions with
And was like
What's up now?
Now who owns you?
Justin, I actually think what happened is he got the crown and he went to sleep
Heavy head, by the way, let's establish
And then he was awoken in the middle of the night
That was a bit of a fall
But this crown is quite heavy
And he was woken by a tick on his nose
And there was just like a crowd of swans around
And we're like, all right
Now that she's gone, we've got some demands
We want to make sure that you're looking out
For our whole deal
If you could bring back long necks as a beautiful thing
I think that that is gone
There's a narrative that is spreading
That you're not supposed to give bread to birds
And we hate that
We don't like that
So if you could bring
Bread and also
Peanut butter M&Ms in there
We love peanut butter M&Ms
And we never get to eat those
And we've wanted to declare war on geese for a while
And if you could like back us up on that
If we could form some kind of alliance
Of Britain and swans
V. geese
That would be really huge
They all have a straight face for a long time
And they all bust up like, ah, just kidding
Geese and swan are the same birds
One of us is pretty and one of us is ugly
But that's just like humans, right?
Some of you are prettier than others, right?
Anyway, where's mom?
What? What happened?
Anyway
That was, I think, actually the most
Moving part of her state funeral
Is when all the swans
In England showed up to pay their respects
It was really beautiful
But Travis, you're in
England. I hope you're having a good time
I hope you're enjoying yourself. I hope I am too, Justin
It's the future me
Do you think you'll come back with an accent?
I actually think I'll come back with
Less of an accent than I have now
Oh, okay. And what's that
Going to sound like, Travis?
Hello, I am Travis
This is Travis and I am doggy
Yeah, that's less
British. Is this more pleasant for you,
Griffin?
Kinda, actually
When Travis leaves the country
Griffin and I become functionally unemployed
This is true
And such, we have had to record
A lot of content in the past week
True
And I, honestly, I'm feeling
Sometimes that goes one way
Where it's like, I have nothing, I've never been funny
Reddit's right
And then
Reddit's right about everything
Sometimes it goes the other way where I just start feeling
Loose. I feel like this is my default state
The juice is loose, for sure
The juice is loose on this one
It's an advice show
We're gonna read advice
We're gonna do more than two questions this week
Let's go. We only did one last week
Only did one last week
That's a huge, that's a
I mean, 100%, can't be 100%
Well,
I believe the conversion rate, Justin, is one
American question to 1.2
British questions. I've been
Setting up for a little bit
By the way, though, I will say
Exchange rate, you're going at a real
Real choice, baby
I don't acknowledge the
Importance of money, so I guess
That just doesn't matter to me. One currency
One prong. One prong
For all. Uniting us
Thank you. Earth dollars
Earth prongs. That's what I've always said
Bit prong. Bit prong
There's one prong for the
Blockchain. Okay
Um, I work the
Graveyard shift at the chain grocery store
Typically my job is to put things on shelves
And make said things on shelves look nice
Use a planet gram
Do some merchandising. Oh yeah, planet
Gram. Just love that. Oh god, what I wouldn't
Do for a nice planet gram right now. However
I also
Find myself bringing
Damaged goods to the damaged goods pile
Choice, so another guy
Can scan it and the store can get that
Money back. Most of the
Time, these are things like
Dented or leaking cans, crunched up boxes
And exploded jello cups. However, sometimes
I will find an open box
Of granola bars in the back of the shelf with a few
Missing. Probably because someone decided
Just stealing one or two would be easier
Than stealing the whole box. My question is
Would it be morally okay for me
To also take a granola bar
From that box. Yes, get the fucking granola
It's not like they can go back on the shelf and the scanning guy
Just needs to do the box itself, but also
Like, it is stealing. That's from
Conflicted in Colorado. Okay, okay
Okay, Griffin is right. Here's the thing
What you are asking is the wrong
Question, question asker. Is it
Morally okay? Yes, absolutely
Might you get in trouble if you get caught?
Yes. That is because
Business practices
Rarely line up with morality
Listen
They expect you
They almost want you to steal the granola bars
And I'm not even going to say the word
Verb steal anymore. It's
Your labor
Has value
And you understand that, and your employer
Understands that, and I can almost guarantee
That you are not being
You are not receiving fair compensation
For that. But they can't tell you
Like, you're
Going to be paid $11.50
An hour, which is like
Not enough money for anything
And also
If you want to swipe
If you want to take
Also we offer vacation
We offer vacation time to the
Nature valley
Quink, quink, quink, quink
And where you'll have a
Crunchy time
They can't
Say that. You need to take the granola bars
You need to compensate
Yourself with everything that you possibly can
Okay
Food dates, expiration dates
They're made up. So we waste lots of
Food that way. In Montana
In Montana, they made a rule
To protect the dairy industry there
That you have to throw milk
Out 12 days after pasteurization
Which is a massive
Incredible waste. That's ridiculous
You can't even turn the stuff into cheese
Anymore, because the processing plants
Those that moved out of Montana, it's such a
Ginormous waste. And the people
Who, they were talking to a grocer
On plant money, who's in the system
And it's illegal for him to donate the milk to homeless
Shelters. Illegal!
For him to donate the milk
But he
You know what he does? He doesn't
Donates the milk, because it's the right
Thing to do. And the right thing
For you to do, is to not let these
Bars end up in a landfill
Unless that landfill is called
Reggie's tummy
And your name is Reggie, and your body's a landfill
Reggie! And then just like, take all
Of them, eat one of them, hand out
The rest to people you see who need some
Who need a granola bar. And can I tell
You something? That's
Pretty much anyone could eat
A granola bar at any time. That's why
If it exists, no one's ever like
I'm starving, I can't wait to get
Home and eat a granola bar
You have the granola bar with you, because that's
Your moment to be like, I'm not hungry, but maybe
I could be hungry in the future
That is the tagline of granola bars
Absolutely, it's like
You don't want to eat this, but if you don't
Eat something, you're gonna throw up
So reach for Nature Valley
Nature Valley, it's literally
Better than nothing
Um, hey
Do you all want to go
On over to
Visit my friend
And yours, the wizard? I feel like
We were just there. Okay
Well, we were just there, we do this every week
Summer sent this in, thank you
It's just like I see
The wizard more than I see our dad
And I don't know how I feel about that
I feel, I mean our dad doesn't have
Magic wisdom
Not magic wisdom, but I mean
He's seen a lot of shit
He went through World War II, I think
Yeah, he definitely did one of them, right?
Our dad did at least one war
He was in one of them, did he do
Wait, hold on
Is our dad a draft dodger?
No, dad's not a draft dodger
He would
He was extremely close to being
Drafted, and then
The war ended, so he didn't
Get it
Drafted. How convenient
As a result of this
Specific one only thing
Dad used to extol the virtues
Of Richard Nixon as a president
Because whatever actions
He did take
Didn't prevent dad from going to Vietnam
Whatever else
Richard Nixon did the shit thing right
One of our worst presidents
Save for our daddy
Okay
As a beneficiary
There's a very good chance the three of us
Either wouldn't have been here or might have
Been raised by a very different man
A different Clint McElroy
Oh god
You okay? You hit your elbow?
No, I'm having
The idea of our dad on a battlefield
Is giving your son
His bud rimshot voice
As he's getting shot at
Stop, stop
Oh man, in at least one of the
Planes, Clint McElroy has probably been
Anyway, our dad's not
A good soldier, this is
SummerSent this in, it's WikiHow
How to take care of a
Monster High doll
If you have a Monster High doll
But you don't know how to take care of it, this article can help
Do you all have any of these in your house?
Yes, I have Monster High dolls
No, I don't allow representations of
Demonic figures into my home
Okay
We just watched the Monster High movie
There's this thing now with Kids Entertainment
Where they turn cartoons
Into real people
Like, The Really Loud House
You know that
Uncanny Valley real people
As the cartoon characters, Loud House Christmas
That's a series now
Why do we need to bring cartoons to life with real people?
It's very upsetting to me
See, I thought you meant like, where they were like
You know how you love My Little Pony Friendship is Magic?
Let's make them into more people
Now they're called Equestria Girls
And it's like, we're just gonna ignore the fact
That they were once horses
And are now people, it's normal, it's fine
Don't worry about it
I saw one of Hey Arnold, but it was
It's the equivalent of looking at Deviant Art
And like, taking one strap off the shoulder
Like, is this what you want?
Okay, well
We'll make it more human-like, I guess
Anyway, I was gonna make a great
Hey Arnold joke, but that time has passed
Now we're gonna learn how to take care of a Monster High doll
Tending to your doll, comfort the doll
Make sure she's not shy or afraid
Close your eyes when something scary is happening
And read about her online to make sure she is comfortable
With any activity you might do with her
Wait, wait
That last bit? Yeah
Whoa, that
Hey, start to finish
Sometimes there's a rollercoaster of emotions in a thing
This was like a rollercoaster of like, questionable
Except it just kept going down
Further and further
If there's necessary
Care steps
To the toy I've purchased
At Target for $15
I expect that documentation to be provided
Alongside the toy
It's not like in
Fucking gremlins, they're like, look at this little
Cutie pie, real cute
You gotta take good care of him
Get online, call the helpline, check the forums
You'll get there
Not that it would've fucking mattered
Yeah, that kid
He had three fucking rules, dude
Three rules, not hard
Hey, you know what? I own a dog
Way more rules about keeping that damn thing alive
It's like a billion rules
Don't give it grapes, you know what I haven't done yet?
Giving my dog grapes
Yeah, you're crushing him
You couldn't keep track of the fucking time
To not feed them after goddamn midnight
You loser
I know, I know
Change the doll's clothes
Here's the thing that I don't like
Griffin, I want to acknowledge something in that
Go ahead
Make sure your doll isn't scared of things
But also cover their eyes when something scary happens
And that just seems to me like
I'm teaching the doll to be afraid
And also, aren't they monsters?
Yeah, they're Frankensteins and Dracula's and mummies
Why, they're not scared?
Yeah, famously
Frankenstein's famously not afraid of
Anything
Except fire
And a little girl one time
And water and a
Shadow and a bug
Is a werewolf afraid of the moon?
Or silver bullets or
Does a werewolf acknowledge that those things are scary?
It's afraid of how much it loves the moon
It's like, oh, there's that thing again, I need it
I need it
Change the doll's clothes
You don't want to be in the same outfit for two days and neither does she
That's two assumptions you've just made there that are both
Equally incorrect
Buy her new clothes at a toy store or other shops
You could also use other doll clothes that fit
You can even try to make your own
Also have a container or such to keep her clothes in
You don't want to lose them
As a parent
That last bit is actually clutch
They should listen to that, get a container, folks
Get a container and make sure you keep all the clothes
In the container
Somehow my children have like
Sort of shorts
Dead drops all around the house
So that if they
If things go wrong
And we need to bug
Out
They have options
Shorts?
Shorts with in-reach
I will say that
One of the things that I was not expecting as a parent
Is how many
Different spaces you need throughout your home
For Barbie shoes
Every room
It's like a fire extinguisher
Except for Barbie feet
Which is like, well yeah
In case there ends up being a Barbie within six inches
Of any place, make sure that there's at least
One pair of shoes in there
At least according to my children, that's the deal
For some reason chapstick has to be fucking everywhere
Kids love this shit
You guys heard about this?
Kids love chapstick and acorns
I mean what if, you know
If we can make acorn flavored chapstick or chapstick shaped like acorns
Richmond
Cause what if Skipper drops a glass
And it shatters
And now all of a sudden Barbie don't want to get cuts on her feet
And you need shoes everywhere
Take her outside, they need fresh air like we do
They don't
If you bring Draculaura outside, make sure she has a toy umbrella
Or sunscreen
So she doesn't burn
If you bring Laguna, make her weight in water
Make sure you always keep an eye on your doll
As not not lose it during your excursions
That's true because if you're not careful
Hawks who's down picks it right up
Hawks who's down will eat Draculaura whole
I don't
It's fucked up that in the same paragraph
Is like, they need to go outside
But Draculaura will die outside
It's a high risk game for Draculaura
She needs it, but she will die if you do it wrong
She'll burst into flames
And that'll be on you
The wet one must stay wet
It's a spooky season, right?
I feel that more and more these days
Vampire lore is getting pretty loose
With the ability to go outside
If I could take an umbrella out
It's not that restrictive as a vampire
If that's covering it
Then it's just like, oh, I guess I'm fine now
I can wear a big hat and some
I believe the word was sunscreen
Never once in Vampirina
Do we ever see her feast on human flesh
And I know that seems like a big jump
But it's something I've been thinking about a lot lately
And now my only six-year-old daughter
Started to question like, she's a vampire, right?
So she drinks blood
And I don't know how to answer that
But on the other side
Dracula won't get her
Like, that's why we love summertime
Treat the doll like a child
You are her mom
So you need to take care of her
Give her food, baths, and basically follow these instructions
To make sure she is a happy doll
Keep the doll safe
She might get broken if you don't
Or worse, what's worse?
Dead
Yeah, Lotso Love Bear
You might throw her into a big fiery pit
With all of your childhood toys
Down a grate
Where you can see her
But you can't get to her
Oh, that would be the worst
Oh, that's bad
Yeah, feed her to a Pennywise
Pennywise eats your doll right up
Another kid takes her
From your hand to the playground
Because the kid's bigger and stronger than you are
But they don't know
To go to wiki how to find out
That Draculaura is alive
So that's a fake
Then you don't keep her grades up
Undress the doll in a private place
Like a bathroom or closet
Or she might get upset that other Monster High dolls saw her naked
Thank you
That's based on decency
You actually should not be there either
You should leave the doll on the floor
And then leave the room
You need to use tools
That mechanics use to get into your car
When you lock your keys in the car
And you close from under the crack of the door
Now I think though
There should be a step above that
Where she's like, ask your Monster High doll
Does she want the other Monster High dolls to see her naked
Because maybe she's just like
I love this
I'm proud of everything that Monster God gave me
Thank you, Monster God
For my rockin' bod
That's what I say every day when I wake up
I step out of the shower and I loudly announce
Thank you, Monster God, for my rockin' bod
And then I lotion up
This is me talking, by the way
Not a Monster High doll
That would be weird
No, this is important, that's Travis saying
How he does his moisturization
Create a humbly and proudly
And devoutly
And resoundingly
It's kind of like the opening scene
Praise Monster God for my rockin' bod
And then I flagellate myself in private
Then I apply the lotion
It's basically like the opening to American Psycho
Except there's like a swamp blob outside
Like, yes, my child
Yes, my child
Good, good, good
Anything else? Pancakes?
Create a home
Where is home for your doll?
In your drawers? Under your bed?
Well, imagine this
A nice house for your doll to sleep in at night
A place to have parties with friends
Or just eat pizza
I'm not gonna
This is such a big part
This paragraph is way too big for me to read
And have it be funny
But basically, if it's a water doll
Make it look like water
If it's a wolf, do woman
Oh, in the home? In the home, yeah
And then make sure the doll likes her home
Fill it with furniture and make sure there's a bathroom
You may also choose to give it a theme
If you had Draculaura
You can make the walls black slash pink
And make sure she doesn't have any windows
Design the house depending on what the doll is like
I'm worried about
What you're doing to the resale value
What you're doing to your equity
In the home
If you remove the windows
So that your vampire doll
Doesn't die
You're assuring at that point
The house will only be sold to other Draculauras
Which is, you're really limiting yourself
It's a much limited market
Are they talking about like
In your actual home?
No, there's a guy like a shoe box
They got like a shoe box
And they've taped up
Some pictures of scary stuff inside the box
Which is basically
Oh yeah, they love that
But not too scary
Give your Draculaura
Gallons of blood
Pour it right over her
She'll love it
I'm gonna shoot through this next section real fast
Brush the doll's hair, style it
Matches her outfits, give the doll a bath
Remove grime
With nail varnish slash polish remover
And get some q-tips, do be careful with that
Because you might also remove
Eye and
Mouth and face
Parts of it
Change the clothes, we already did that, thank you
Clean the doll's
Clothes routinely and clean the doll's hair
Just one more time, gonna get in there and make sure that
That hair is very very clean
Um
This is a baby
This is a
Baby
Oh, what you're doing is taking care of a baby, is that what you're saying?
Yes
This is a baby
And maybe there's something to that
Because that's part of the simulation
And that's what's cool, but also the baby
Can turn into
Some sort of
Lich or something
Also, I just want to say
We're all three parents
If one of the girls in Monster High could turn into a lich
What would her name be?
Um
Yeah, this is a good one
I don't know
The naming conventions of Monster High
Lichina?
Sounds great
Well, I'll come back to it
The author of this WikiHow article, we're all three kids
We're all three parents at this point, we got kids
And the author
Of this WikiHow article is assuming that
What children love most about toys
Is the amount of restriction and responsibility
That come with them
I don't think that's the case
My daughters both like having dolls
And baby dolls, and then they mostly spend a lot
Of time swinging those around
And dropping them off stuff
And just really kind of fucking them up
In a way that I don't think they're like
Better be careful of the sun
Oh, gotta make sure I bathe these things
So much as they're like, look at this slide
And then drop them from like four feet off the ground
This article
Is so much longer, the next segment
Is all about individual tips for each
Monster High doll, so maybe
We'll just like
Shoot through, if you're playing with Rochelle Goyle
Make sure you give her a good
Pet
I assume that means
Like a familiar or a creature
And not to like
Pet the doll hard or something
Like that
With Frankie Stein
This is an important one, and don't get these
Switched up, if you play with Frankie Stein
You can give her a boyfriend
If you want
But if you're playing with
Abby Bominable
If you're playing with Abby Bominable
Don't make Abby flirt with
Any boys she says is not
Honorable, that's
Abby Bominable
Says is not honorable?
Or don't make her flirt with any
Boys that she says is not honorable
Like that boy's not honorable
Like this boy
This trash bag
This trash bag over here
Leave that one for Frankie Stein
Who will eat up the trash, cause she will date
Whatever
If you're gonna give Frankie Stein a boyfriend
You should make it out of spare parts of other
Kins or something, right?
I think she'd really appreciate that
That feels like a thing Frankie Stein would be into
Make me a boyfriend
This is a huge one, if you are playing with Claudine Wolf
Make sure that when you turn off
The light, Claudine goes crazy
And you may be wondering
How do I do
How would I go about accomplishing that?
And the answer is
I guess you tape her to a Roomba
A light sensitive
Roomba?
And then you shout the command word
That makes the Roomba go just like fucking
Ballistic
Just absolutely ape shit
I mean if you're playing with Claudine
Justin, speaking of Roombas
I just watched Hocus Pocus 2
You did not tell me what a significant plot
Importance
Roombas have in that movie
Yeah, Roombas are a huge part of the plot
If you are playing
If I told you
That
In Hocus Pocus
At one point, Kathy the Jimmy
Can't find a broom
So she duct tapes two
Magical Roombas to her feet
Like a hoverboard
Did you think that I was making that up as a joke
For our show or that I'm saying
Apart from the movie Hocus Pocus 2
That's good and a good joke
And I bet you, can I say something?
I bet you Kathy fucking
Sold it. I bet you she made you bust up with that
Oh, she's having the time of her life
Yeah, and so are you
There is one prolonged shot
In the movie as the
Characters on screen are very minimal
In the foreground and mostly the focus of the shot
Is just a glowing Walgreens
And it is a Walgreens
And it lingers on it for
What feels like 30 solid seconds
And then Walgreens is
Referenced, there are multiple
Scenes in a Walgreens
Walgreens once again plays a
Pivotal role in Hocus Pocus 2
And every shot is framed as like
Kathy the Jimmy, Bette Midler
And a huge red W in between them
Always separated and framed
By Walgreens logo. They replaced Sarah
Jessica Parker with the Walgreens logo?
Yeah
Hey guys, if you're playing with Cleo Denial
Feed her grapes and
It may seem like she can't
But if you push the
Grapes into the
Into her face hard enough
You can make pretend
Anything. They will go away. They will go away
Eventually
Um, if you're playing
With Toralei sometimes she might scratch the furniture
That's it. Like you know that that's what
You're gonna go with. If you're playing with
Ghoulia Yelps, this one's
This one's great cause if you are playing with Ghoulia Yelps this will be
My last tip for this
Halloween segment. You gotta feed her
Brains and fast food
Kill
Living things
That have a brain
In it to give to your
Doll and or
Hit up Barbies
If
Arby's sold brain
If Arby's sold brain meat, which
Their motto would make you
Think that they do. They got the meat
Yeah, you'd think
You should be able to go into Arby's
And be like, for me, I would like
A big Cheddar Boy
A number 16 Cheddar
Boy combo meal
And for this one, Ghoulia Yelps
And you put her up on the counter and you say, you know what to do
With her. You take her back
To the back where you keep the
The bad meats
The meats that you maybe don't want people
To know that you do have on offer
And you make sure she is sated
Yeah. Thank you
Of course. Thank you. She'll die without it
And she's my best friend
What about Cauliflower?
The doll Cauliflower
The brains? Fuck off
Oh, I thought you were saying there's a Monster High doll called
Cauliflower. That's awesome
All the other dolls are like
It could be Griffin, it would be Carla Flower
Thank you very much
But what would that be referencing, Charles?
What great monster is that?
That's fun if there was one of them that was just like
Vegetables. Yeah
It could be anything just
It could be Swamp Thing. It could be Man Thing
It could be Audrey 2 from Little Swamp of course
It could be, there are man eating plants
All over the fucking place. Read a book
Charlie got these toys for her
For her birthday
Riley got Charlie
This stuffed
Guinea Pig in a cage
And the thing about it is that
It's pregnant
With other smaller
Baby Guinea Pigs. Oh, cool. Great
But the birthing happens
Automatically
Huh? So
On a certain timer
You turn it on and eventually
The first baby
Well, what it does is it pops out of the top
And just kind of lands on the mom
Guinea Pig and rolls off and then she had a baby
And the mom eats it. Yeah, normal
No, mom does, you know, you open that and it's like a surprise
Toy, right? You see what kind of Guinea Pig
Just like real life
And it's set to do this over a 24
Hour period
Where periodically, over this 24 hours
This thing will just give
Birth. Does it at least make a noise?
Can you set it in the corner and tell
You hear it go like
And then you know like, oh honey
Yeah, there's noises. Not again!
There's 100% birthing noises, 100%
But if you bought this gift
For somebody who does not have that
Kind of attention span, like say
A child
There is a switch on it
That's basically like
Turbo mode
It's like it gets
Here we go
You like
Flip this switch to make this
Guinea Pig just go into like
Turbo child birthing
And it's probably the
Wildest option that
I have seen on a toy is like, let's just kick
This birth cycle into overdrive
And crank it up
Let's go to Money Zone. I think it's Money Zone time
Yeah, let's go to Money Zone
It's better with you
You know guys, with my international travel
I have been studying up a lot
Using Babbel and I
Have been studying
English. So I now say
Yeah, I've learned how to say like bangers
And lift and
I say like biscuits and flat
How did you pull this off
I know that you don't really apply yourself
To stuff. Well, I already said Justin
I used Babbel
I guess I was going to
Drill down on like maybe what even
Is that at all? Oh, okay
Well, it's like an app
It's a language learning app
That sold like more than 10 million
Subscriptions and it's not just English I should point out
You can also do like Spanish or German or Italian
Or French or Portuguese or Swedish or Turkish or
Dutch, Polish, Indonesian
Norwegian, Danish
Russian, and yes, English
We need to get the Animaniacs at this point
There's too many. They gotta come up with like a fucking
I mean I just said, okay, with Babbel
You only need 10 minutes to complete one of their
Bite-sized lessons so that
You can start having real life conversations
In a new language in as little as 3 weeks
Now this is a problem because I did just start
Learning English
Two days ago
Right. So, but by the time
I get back, now other
Language apps use AI
The movie for their
Lesson plans, but Babbel lessons
Were created by over 150 language
Experts. Those are human beings
Not some phony-blowny computer
Brains. Yeah
Fucking Jude Law over here
Just like repeat after Jude
Law. Yeah
You know how Jude Law went around
Telling lonely ladies about language
And stuff? Yeah, man
And it's voiced by real native speakers
Not computers. Who needs them?
With Babbel you can choose from 14
Different languages that I've already listed
Right now, get up to
55% off your
Subscription when you go to
babbel.com slash my brother
That's B-A-B-B-E-L
Dot com slash my brother for up to
55%, that's a lot of
Percent off your subscription
Babbel language for life
Her Majesty
Served Great Britain
And the Commonwealth
Loyally for over
70 years
And while, of course, we feel
A profound sadness
We must remember
She lived a long life
And died in such a way that I think
Many of us would want for ourselves
She was at home
Surrounded by her
Family
And, of course, she was listening
To the Beef and Dairy Network
Podcast
The Beef and Dairy Network Podcast
Is a multi-award winning comedy podcast
And you can find it at maximumfun.org
Or wherever you get your podcasts
You're in a theatre, the lights go down
You're about to get swept up by
The characters and all their little details
And interpersonal dramas
You look at them and think, that person is so obviously
In love with their best friend
Wait, am I in love with my best friend?
That character's mom is so overbearing
Why doesn't she just stand up to her? Oh God, do I need
To stand up to my own mother?
If you've ever recognized yourself in a movie, then join me
Jordan Cruciola for the podcast
Feeling Seen
We've talked to author Susan Orlean on realizing
Her own marriage was falling apart after watching
Adaptation, an adaptation of
Her own work, and comedian
Hari Kondabolu on why Harold and Kumar
Was a depressingly important movie
For Southeast Asians
So join me every Thursday for the Feeling
Seen podcast here on Maximum
Fun
Dun dun dun dun
I really thought we were going to do a second question
That's okay, we'll get there maybe one day
No, I'm doing
The second question now
Oh, that's how it is?
Just a little flourish for it? Nope
Now we're doing the second question
Maybe I'll change my mind
Now I have to think about it
My six year old son recently discovered Pokemon
Hell he is
And is obsessed
My husband and I know nothing about the cards, the game
Or the universe
The headspace, the experience
The lifestyle
The agenda
If I may be so bold
Recently my son got a
Mewtwo
Griffin
V-star
Rainbow
In a pack
Oh, fuck
Oh, man
Our Googling says it's a pretty valuable card
Yeah, that's putting it lightly
It's
Powered chart, sir
The thing is, he's six and he's mostly
Into the game for the trades
If we let him keep this card, he will trade it
For Lord knows what
What's the protocol here? Let him make his deals
Protect him from older
Kids taking advantage
Sell the card now and buy him a bunch of other packs
Of cards with the proceeds
That's from Pok Perplexed in Pittsburgh
You've come to the right place
Indeed
The economy
Is fueled
By
Suckers
And it's that there's a circle of life
Around this whole thing
You are correct
In that if you do not intervene
One day, your son's gonna leave
The house with a Mewtwo
V-star Rainbow worth
Now Hawkeye's gonna swoop down, take it
Put it in its nest
According to the
I mean, the recent
Sort of like
Pokemon trades that I've
Been reading, it values that one
At about $5500
If he leaves the house with it
He's gonna come back with a fucking scratched up
Moldy ass Dewgong
With a fucking bent ass
Corners and people have written
Like custom attacks with marker
On it, like one water
Energy, 150 damage
And this always hits, like
Fucking like
Your nev- your dumbass
Friend's nephew Kyle
Is just gonna like walk away
Whistling $5500 richer
I congratulate you
On having the clarity of mind
As a parent to look at your 6 year old
Child and say like, hey this kid's
A rube, I mean look at this kid
He's 100%, he's got mark written
All over him, I did my best
But I raised an absolute maroon
This guy's absolute
And listen, I love that he's so wide eyed
And open to the world, but this kid's gonna get
Taken to the fucking cleaners
And Kyle's gonna
Have a little
Little nice day for himself, you know what I mean?
Like it's a service that your
Son is providing to Kyle
I was the
I both gave away
Some real beauties
And also benefited
From some real
Some real dummies, and that's
But that's the way of things, isn't it?
Griff's been the Kyle, and he's been
Your child. I've been the Kyle, I've been
Your child, I've been all over this
Great world of ours. But he's never been
To me. That's the
I've never been, I've never visited
It, Justin. Even once.
No, Griffin, he's never been
To Maine.
You've never been to Maine.
I have never been to Maine. No, we
Went to Maine, didn't we? Doesn't it feel like
We should've gone to Maine by now? Foxwood, is it Foxwood?
No, Foxwood's not Maine. Foxwood's somewhere else.
No, no, no, it's Massachusetts, I think.
So...
The answer's simple, you let him make the trade
To shitty Kyle, and then
You bump into Kyle as he walks away
And he's like, ha, another great deal
Just to check his pockets. What? The card's gone.
That's right. You got it.
Because you've been taking pickpocket classes at the Y.
Yeah, and child
Child pockets are the toughest ones
To pick. So little. So tiny.
So little. So you did have to, you had to study for a couple
Years to get good at it. Luckily
You saw this coming a mile away because of
Your son's
Easygoing demeanor. And you looked
At him when he was three, and you were like, someday
This kid's gonna get taken to the cleaners, so I better start
Pickpocketing now? Long con.
I think. Oh, wow.
Hold on, wait, let's hear Justin out.
No, I just meant, it's the long grif.
Like, you've been planning for a long time
To rob this kid. Yeah.
Whenever Kyle, whoever Kyle ended up being
Yeah. The deck was stacked against you
From the beginning. Yeah.
Kyle thought he was in charge? No, no, no.
No, no, no. You're the director of this little play.
Now, I was... Kyle is
Really your puppet. Yes.
And this is all to teach
You are just so,
So naive son of last night.
I think, you know,
My kid's almost six, and if I said
If you give me this, I can
Then turn it into a lot more
Of the things you like.
That feels like a slam dunk explanation.
Okay. Right? That if I say
This one card,
I could use this to buy you many, many
Packs of cards.
Wow. Right? Like, that feels like something that kid
Would be way into. Right?
Yeah, you can also just take a picture
Of the card, and let him carry the picture around.
There you go.
Cut it out.
You can have a bunch of those, you know what I mean?
You can just trade those to Kyle.
Sell the card, buy a laminator,
Print it out, make a new card.
You know, there's nothing illegal about making
Your own fake Pokemon cards and selling them.
Yeah. It's not illegal.
There's no one, it's not legal fucking Tinder.
It's not money, yeah.
What are they gonna get you on?
Counterfeiting? Come on.
Take their granola bars,
Sell the fake cards.
This is America, baby.
Cause that's good, cause sometimes you have an idea
Like, what if there was an even smaller Pikachu
Named Squeakachoo, and then you can
Make him. You can make him
Be real with a printer
And a laminator.
And he's got
An attack that costs no energy.
It does 300 damage.
And ruin someone's credit score.
And if it's a
A card game, then it's not fan fiction.
It's a mod.
There you go. Oh, this is DLC.
This isn't Velma and Shaggy
Kissing. This is an expansion
On the
Velma and Shaggy universe.
A modification. An upgrade.
If you will.
Also, I gave Shaggy
Big pecs. Cause I love that.
I like his shaggy pecs.
Could we do a
Shirt. Do you think we could sell a shirt
With a strong Shaggy on it?
It's like, strong Shaggy?
No, cause it's like
I think it's a meme. I think actually
Strong Shaggy is a meme.
Like, for whatever reason
Kids like
Shaggy if he was really strong.
I don't know why, but this guy keeps
Popping up in my YouTube videos. And every time
I see him being very strong and
Beating up Huggy Wuggy or any of the other
Sort of fucking video game
Degenerates.
And the kids go crazy. And it's like
That dude is high
On drugs. He is
Casey Kasem. He has no friends.
He eats dog food. Steals people's
Sandwiches. Steals people's sandwiches. Please
Do not aspire to be this man.
He has wasted his potential.
What if we made a t-shirt that was just
A series of pictures of like
Shaggy on a sofa. Shaggy on a
Counter. Shaggy in the
Shower. Shaggy being caught on
Camera. What do you think?
In the shower? Yeah.
But we saw him in the
Shower. It wasn't me.
Oh, okay.
Because he's Shaggy, right? But he's on the sofa.
No, I get the joke now.
I guess in my mind when I heard
You say let's do a t-shirt
With a nude cartoon
Character license. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I should note this isn't like a joke. This is a separate
Business I want to start where we are selling these
Like a hot topic or something. I think that these
Would actually do really well in that market.
Not as like a McElroy Brothers joke
Thing, but to like branch out into
Actual like more like memetic
T-shirts. You couldn't sell it at
A hot topic. You could sell it at
A kiosk outside
Of the hot topic because as far as I can
Tell from mall kiosks
Anything fucking goes.
Anything goes. You can have Shaggy's
Dong fully on display in the shower.
You fully, fully can.
It's like international waters if you're in the
Mall hallways. Yeah, we've got
Shaggy nude on t-shirts
And Pelotons. Come on in.
This just says Pelican-ton.
Yeah, it's my version of it
Where you're riding the bike and there's a
Video behind you of a Pelican
Chasing you. It's an
Expansion to the Peloton.
It's not a rip-off. It's an expansion.
I trademarked it myself. I wrote
The idea on a piece of paper and I mailed it to myself
And I haven't opened it. So see you in court.
This is legally binding.
My neighbor recently removed the hedge on their side of the fence
Between our properties. This fence
Is around two feet from my house and it's not very
Tall. This means that the neighbors now have
An unobstructed view through my window into
My bed. Even though I keep the blinds
Low, I still prefer to keep a fan in the window.
Which requires them to be
Open far enough that I'm certain my neighbors
Will have a line of sight from their windows straight to my
Junk. Am I
Still good to sleep in the nude?
Should I let their
Decisions to remove the privacy hedge decide
How I dress at night? Or do I give
This provenly nosy
Neighbor an eyeful in hopes she
Plants a new privacy bush?
That's from bedtime
Bush in Bremerton.
You
Chose to use the word bush.
You chose it. You chose
It. You could have said something else.
But you didn't.
This feels tricky
To me. Oh, it does?
Feels fraught. Travis,
Don't just- Travis, tell me what they should
Do and don't just say, plant another
Taller bush next to their bush.
No, it just- it strikes me as like
Um, I
If you are not bothered
By it, right? If you're not like,
Oh no, what do I do now? If it's
Just like, well, you made some decisions
And this is where your choices
Have brought you, I will
Continue on my momentum
Like, unless
Acted upon by an outside force.
You know what I mean?
There are two different kinds of naked.
You don't have clothes on
And you're worried there's
Any chance on
Earth someone might see you.
Or, there's the
Times when you're naked and you're just like
You. That's who you are.
You're in your body.
You're feeling you're sexy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And you're saying
Thank you, monster god, for my rock and bod.
And, this
Person is never going to be able
To get into that second head
Space. Right. Because
There's always the possibility
That you could be being perused.
It's not about the neighbor, it's about
You. You need to be able to be
Not just nude, but indescribably
Perfectly nude.
Deeply. A nude soul
As well, if you will. Yes.
Emotionally nude.
Okay.
So what do you do then, Justin?
You plan a second taller
Book. Okay, now hold on. I was explicitly told
I just didn't want you
To take mine. Oh, okay.
I didn't
Know we could do that. We've been doing this show for over
A decade. I know. I didn't know we could say like
And I called dibs on this answer.
I just came up with it. I was like, I don't
Want to interrupt him. I'll just put a bookmark
In so he doesn't take mine.
So good, dude.
If I was going to invent that rule
I wish I had done it for
I was about to say better joke, but like odd joke.
You know what I mean?
The idea you get.
Are any of us truly nude in the dark?
Huh.
If you're in the dark, in the darkness, and no one can
See your privacy
Are you
Even nude?
Huh.
Do you think when the darkness
Is in the green room, anyone ever leaned
In and just like shut off the lights
Real quick and slammed the door and the
Band's like, oh, here we go again.
Yeah, sure.
So there's always a joker. Is it there?
Yeah, for sure.
Thank you so much for listening to our program.
I'm sorry
That my brothers denied you that
Wonderful Munch
Squad. I was definitely really, really
Going to do. Save it.
Do two next time.
But, you know, I hope you had fun regardless.
That's all we, that's all we ever
Hope for you. Enjoy yourself.
Is that all?
Wait, is that all we ever hope for?
That's all we ever hope for.
Oh, man. Okay. I'm learning so much on this episode.
Maybe would it kill you to buy a shirt from time to time.
You know what I mean?
There we go. There it is.
Maybe a deluxe blanket.
Speaking of that, Justin, it's so funny you should make that.
What?
We have a Garrow blanket on sale in the merch store
For the very, very esque
Garrow blanket over at MacroMerch.com
We've also got our Candle Nights wrapping paper back
Designed by Justin Gray
And 10% of all merch proceeds this month
Go to Fair Elections Center
And listen, it's not just that. It's all the other merch there.
And it's time to start thinking about that
Holiday season.
It's creeping in. I feel it.
I feel that creep.
My children have now each gotten a Garrow.
The Garrow stuffy. Same.
They are really enjoying talking
To each other
And then constantly forgetting
That he's a Binocorn, which is fun.
They keep calling him a Rhinocorn
Which I enjoy immensely.
Let's explore that.
I mean, a Rhino is already kind of a Rhinocorn.
Exactly.
But imagine if you said, this is a unicorn
Except it looks like a Rhino.
Yeah, sure.
This is going to be a thanks from Montaigne.
Thanks, Montaigne, for the use of our theme song
My life is better with you.
It makes you stronger to cure it.
That's true.
And if you have fear
Any fear, any weakness
The song makes it go away.
Oh.
Yeah, in the scariest times
The song makes you strong enough to face it.
Wow. That's cool.
How do they do that?
Is it like a binaural?
Or like a subconscious thing?
Yes, both of them.
That's amazing.
On the tour front
The shows in San Jose and Denver
That were postponed
Have been rescheduled.
April 27th, San Jose, California
Adventure Zone
That's still with Abria
Which is very exciting. It's going to be super great.
April 28th, San Jose, My Brother, My Brother and Me
And April 29th, Denver
My Brother, My Brother and Me
All existing tickets will be honored for the new dates
If you can't attend the rescheduled dates
Keep an eye out for an email from your venue
Or AXS
And you will have 30 days for when you get that email
To request a refund
And if you don't have tickets but want to go
We will be selling those tickets
You can get those on sale now
Travis promises that he won't get COVID this time.
Promise.
Cross my lungs.
November shows in Washington DC
With Brendan Lee Mulligan
DMing Badlands 2
We got the shows in Detroit and Cincinnati
And Mask
And proof of full vaccination or negative COVID test
Within 72 hours of event start is required
And don't forget to pre-order
Taz 11th hour now
Go to theadventurezonecomic.com
To pre-order and those are coming out
February 21st. Faster than you think.
Yep. That's it.
Everybody stick to your guns.
I'll do it. I feel like I didn't contribute much this week.
Stick to your guns.
No, that's not what we went with. We had something different.
What was our new thing?
I think it was whoever didn't contribute the most tested.
We just rolled that out fairly wisely.
Then we had a new thing.
I don't know.
I don't know but it's also from a future episode for the Halloween special.
I don't think people have heard yet.
Okay, well then I'll just say that
Let me do it anyway.
Okay.
Because I have to go in 30 seconds.
Don't ever compromise.
For any reason.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
Thank you for watching.
Maximum fun dot org. Comedy and culture.
Artist-owned. Audience-supported.