The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
It's a new craze, and good girls do you wanna just say hey I wanna, just say hey I wanna.
Hello everybody, welcome to my brother my brother me an advice show for the moon
my name is justin i'm sorry i didn't know what we were doing here i thought we were just doing
our scales i thought we were just moaning my name is justin mcElroy i'm the oldest brother and i'm the
my name is impossible to put anything spooky into i am like a twitter handle i've tried oh
dustin tried dustin keep go on go on this little journey dustin no let me do it dustin diamond
the scariest cast member diamond dallas page oh my god bryce dallas howard i'm i'm travesty
mcElroy does that work is that something like travesty yeah i don't think that's a halloween
no like travesty i don't think it's especially halloween i'm uh i'm travis how about ghoul
rat you're just doing a rebus i think ghoul rat fin fins are fins are kind of scary right like
it could be a shark fin mummy roi justin i mean mummy roi would work for any of us wouldn't it
yeah uh what's your name little one it's i think it's ghoul rat fin mummy rat there's a second
rat that's his witness protection identity mr mummy rat uh here's your milk thanks come inside
quick that's not a witness protection work now you have to live here too i can't you know too much
you're not like in hiding mummy rat well that's kind of a weird name god damn it you found me out
not again i wish this was a better disguise i gotta stop witnessing murders around halloween
they have fun there at the police department movie would be about a dracula that witnessed
a murder on halloween and then they put him in witness protection he had to try to blend in
in like a new neighborhood where they couldn't know that he was dracula now here's my question
justin is the fact that he is a dracula completely coincidental or is it connected
to the murder in some way like did he see a wolf man get killed no that's racist travis
that you think you hear dracula and you think oh they probably did a murder no no no i'm not
saying the dracula did the killing i'm saying that he just witnessed another spooky character
like he maybe saw boo berry get killed no no no that this is the best part it was a gangland mob
slaying so now the mob is after dracula and then at the end of the movie he's like well i try to
blend in and play by the rules he's got a cop partner i tried to blend in and play by the rules
but it looks like i'm gonna have to play by the one sorry sorry play by the ghouls yeah i'm gonna
have to play i try to play by the ghouls but now i'm gonna do this one and he puts on uh a big pair
of sunglasses like track style and then the last 15 minutes is dracula murdering um uh an army of
mobsters and holy shit trademark trademark trademark tmtm no it doesn't work like that
print out this podcast print it out all of the transcript and then mail it to you and i also
justin um if i may uh leapfrog and add on here i've been trying to uh kick start restart the uh
the movement of novelty halloween songs let me throw out dragon black right and that's that's the
big like epic number that plays yes and so like you know they used to be like surf rock but now
what if like all halloween novelty songs were like really like hardcore rap and like really
like hard rock and how about this can bounce this off you bitch better have my mummy nice
nice nice griffin is that a griffin original it's nothing it's nothing it's not a thing it's like a
cloud maybe like please hammer don't haunt him is that like hardcore that works too that's about
as hardcore as it gets justin you're begging for someone's life don't spook me another good one
another really really hardcore quit haunting you really earning that explicit tag on itunes
you can't spook this okay so now you're just adding spook into yeah but like uh the first
one wasn't an mc hammer song so i had to like do it again okay how about this they call them second
chance bits yeah this is welcome to second chance bits listen this this one about don't spook me
he's got a deadline for tomorrow can we get a foster in here to take these bits are looking for
there forever home can you nurse this bit back to health it needs daily medicine for its for its
stomach problems oh man it's shedding internally can you nurse this bit back to health it's gonna
ruin your carpet let's do our spooky uh spooky spooky halloween episode by which i mean we did
not think to ask for halloween questions unpreparedness is haunting i have an idea
yeah this is a i'm serious about this no why don't we listen why don't we ask for halloween questions
on twitter right this second save these questions for next week ask for halloween questions on
twitter right this second answer them as they come in rapid fire style i mean everybody's gonna be
like what should my costume be i guess that'll be a fine bit like we can talk about what the
hot shit is for this year and put the tweet out real quick you guys retweet it i was working on
my podcast late late one night okay i have tweeted i have tweeted that we need these questions i'm
going to answer the first one that comes in and just go ham on it i okay i want to say this i
tweeted we need questions hey jenny hey jenny first person respond i literally said we need
halloween questions for an mbnbm we were recording right now and you tweeted wear a shirt that says
life and hand out lemons jenny no i don't know it's a halloween costume idea yeah like that's
not not even a question jenny oh it's barely a thought and then jenny immediately said wait you
weren't asking for costume ideas okay jenny no oh yeah open up the flow baby here they come
turn the handle here they come oh yeah baby any second now here we go timothy johns asked my
birthday is on halloween so could you wish me a happy birthday not a i guess technically
i like that do we do we have the physical capability to do that yes next question
next question could we do that this one comes in from october name change what's the least sexy
sexy blank costume somebody could wear like sexy pirate super sexy no joke christian
messaged me 37 seconds ago what's the worst sexy costume possible it's a hot topic this is a hot
button issue can i hit you guys can i hit you guys with this first of all 420 finally got one
second of all what about just sexy dick and you're just a big dick because it's like
it's gonna be second you're a big dick in like lingerie no no well yeah maybe that is how you
get the idea across although you'd look just silly wouldn't you a little bit not like how
do you sex up a dick like it's already the sexiest you give it a really like like ripped abs
this is a dick with really defined pecs that's not where those go though your your dick don't
have those i'm just talking about a dope hog and how do you like maybe a sash that says world
sexiest dick that's good that's a great costume on the nose but don't put your sexy dick on
anybody's nose how can you be sexy star wars and this one's gonna be also pretty conceptual
because you're not talking about a star specific character but rather i'm not talking about slave
leia i'm not talking about crotchless han i'm talking about sexy star wars they don't talk
about that when he came out of the when he came out of the uh crowd carbonite yeah the carbonite
that they'd frozen his crotch off his dick was well no his crotch was there but the crotch of
his pant was gone and it was just let's just say i shot first during that scene if you know what i
mean do you think that there will be a lot of sexy bernie sanders out there this year you know there's
gonna be a million sexy bernie sanders's i heard that sexy pizza rat costume is already on sale
oh it just sold out no and it's gone and it's stopped being funny damn just missed it should
you eat all the good candy first or save the best for last that comes in from carissa carissa
is this a good idea i don't know we can at least milk it for a little bit i feel like we had very
very different um candy storage ideas yeah like what what was our concept there travis what was
your sort of plan mine was very much um i would hide it away until a mouse found it and then throw
it all away yeah definitely a mouse based economy yeah that was kind of the built-in
expiration date of whether a corner of the bag was gone or not yeah i ended up with a lot of like
uh like the sprees where there's like three in a package you know what i'm talking about
like a little paper package with three sprees and it's almost like what am i gonna do with
like is this even three sprees yeah opening the thing i would end up with like a pillowcase full
of those and just like you can't throw it away because it's it's candy and you're a little kid
you can't just like get candy whenever you want to but also at the same time like oh we're going
anywhere inside me for sure can i read this one because it made me laugh when i read it's from
buick said something like that they said which cursed me with revolting rhythms what does that
mean and how is it cured uh just take some zinc that usually knocks them yeah usually knocks them
right out it will take usually like two or days two or three days for it to be fully flushed out
so sorry you gotta pass a lot james asked this i i will be gone halloween night but i still
want to leave out candy how can i ensure that nobody just steals the whole bowl not how any
of this works if i see a bowl with candy sitting on a stranger's doorstep i'm gonna do one of two
things not touch it because it could be a it could be a an improvised explosive device and i don't
fuck with that and the other thing it could be is that i could i will take all of it now that i'm
an adult looking back at like trigger treating and all the fears where people were like they
might put drugs in the candy now i'm an adult and i realize like who's this person who just has all
these extra drugs lying around that they're gonna waste on kids right it was just like oh yeah i
spent hundreds of thousands of dollars on drugs and i'm giving them away and that was hot that
shit was hilarious let's do some heroin to celebrate oh no what what poor forethought on my
part we put our good heroin to those apples that we gave kids damn it well i'm gonna go shave oh
damn it i can't do that either ironically as we learned from super sized me the this whole
time the candy was the poison super sized weed i got a question from brendan i don't get off work
till after 11 on halloween is that officially too late to engage in spookery uh they have a
name for that brendan and it is vandals like you're a hooligan at that point they have another name
for that it is november well no as long as you do something spooky before 11 59 and 59 seconds
but if you're good but then it's basically we're talking about a spooky purge yeah all my favorite
romantic comedies revolve around like a guy just trying to find a girl that he can spook before
midnight just gotta find somebody really sneak up behind him and give him a good scare well he was
cursed and he was told if he didn't spook by midnight spook true love true spook he would die
it's true it is true that did happen that's not a movie that's real it was called true spook that
event in real life well again it wasn't a movie it was a real event that we all refer to as true
spook you remember i read about it on snopes how do i make this is from dr g how do i make glasses
work with my costume i don't have contacts you gotta play through the pain baby i know this
feels i know how this works because i i have a beard and as a bearded man you either have the
option to like choose a costume that is spectacled or you are you know wolverine but with glasses
you know what i mean you're you're dumbledore but with oh you're nerdy wolverine yeah oh i'm
just travis i'm a wolverine thing but like everybody's got these things like unless you're
like a super like hot guy or girl you are probably like every halloween costume i think of like am
i gonna go as wolverine no i'm gonna go as husky wolverine like where i want to go is like uh
frankenfurter from rocky horror picture show no i'm gonna go as husky frankenfurter like it you
gotta people have to know that it's just it's just for laughs you know in the end in the end
it's not though it's serious it's serious i met um i met a couple of my neighbors last night and
they invited um a few of us to their halloween party and like last night was the first time i
met them and this will be the second time i see them and they i imagine they're gonna go hard i
don't know how hard they're gonna be and it's it's very stressful this idea of costume like
competition the original plan is we're going to drive in and we're gonna go see hocus pocus
driving you don't need a costume at the drive-in but now unless you want to cosplay as one of the
sisters hocus or yeah i mean check check my mean the sanderson sisters check sorry my nijimi out
check my nijimi out i said hey everybody come coming around check my nijimi out you know i
didn't think i'd get a lot of use for this full body nijimi costume but it is really paid off
i used it for that bank robbery and then i haven't touched it since she was so nice when she did the
full nude cast for me so patient it took me two or three tries she's a wonderful actress she
she genuinely is a wonderful actress and she can stand very still for long periods of time
which is very important she can play a witch she is transformative yeah the weird thing about it is
that after she lost some weight um she was nice enough to come back and uh oh she's done several
several casts for me yes am i nice enough to come back and take another cast i mean she was kind of
insistent yeah yeah like she didn't want me to run around without hey griffin this is she said
peek nijimi yo g this is your girl nijimster and i just want to let you know i dropped a few lbs
and i'm gonna swing by tomorrow around three i hope that works get the get the plaster ready um
and i'm all shaved all ready to go and uh let's uh let's get this party started nijimi out after
the holidays like after the christmas and she put it back on like five or six pounds she wanted to
do it again at five pounds right a five pound differential she's like let's get this bad boy
going heat up the clay heat up the clay i have so many like just it just looks like i've skinned
several different jimmy's like it like nijimi comes to my house maybe it's like especially warm
and that's where she's decided to do her annual molting it's it's a real horror show
what halloween costumes did you have high hopes for that turned out terrible that's from jake
oh i don't have these i uh well last year rachel and i did bob and lynda belcher uh and so did
travis and teresa and so did our friend bradberry and liz and uh i don't know how it worked for you
guys but nobody recognized us outside of a single uh trio of friends we ran into at a bar who dressed
up like bob and lynda and there was jean there dressed up as bee squash that shit was dope but
otherwise nobody like i i i was on a bad streak there of putting a lot of effort in costumes and
getting absolutely no recognition which is why we do it i showed up one year to a party and
did some bar hopping as a contestant from legends of the hidden temple and i like bought a blue
barracuda shirt and i had like the gold helmet and the knee pads and everything fucking nobody
nobody zero buddies i i couldn't i most of mine really work um i i'm pretty good at this whole
halloween costume but you can be good at putting together a costume and still not have anybody know
who the fuck you are and best costumes that have ever like succeeded with people going oh my god
i get dexter like in the height of the tv show yeah yeah yeah that that went before it got shitty
and it cost like zero money and then i did done you just you just murdered some people yeah and
i did quail man and it only took me ruining a green sweater i uh when in my mid teens i saw
the indie film six strings samurai but a guy who looked like buddy holly uh traveling around a
wasteland with a sword and a guitar on his back and i thought man that is a cool movie so for
halloween that year i dressed as uh well husky six string samurai and uh just ended up being
i didn't have a guitar at the time so i just a guy in a black suit with a sword on his back
and then you're just samurai buddy holly not that anybody would have gotten it like the other way
oh i know that one kind of art house i'm into it indie smash uh yeah costumes are a real nightmare
i have no idea what i'm gonna be this year one year my best one was i went online and i bought
a plumb bob that lit up like from the sims and just put that on my head i'm a sim fuck you
i i don't i actually think this may be the first year that i don't do anything like i don't have
any halloween plans right now i don't have anything on the books uh i i may this may be adult first
like just a handout candy and do nothing let me look around my office right now i'm gonna start
listing off things this will be fun i'm gonna start listing off shit i have in my office
and you can tell me what i can do with it okay okay i've got some foam baffling here okay um
phone man i got a fake potted uh plant looks like i've got a a green chalice that dad got me for my
birthday uh has kind of a fantasy theme i've got a dj hero uh turntable um got um guys dj phone
plant cup man that didn't work nope no that wasn't a good you know what the worst part about that was
it was both a bad costume and a bad bit i would have been happy if either one had panned out
i would have been thrilled i'm looking at some tweets right now about being gauzy is there
something there uh here we go it's ben gauzy and i just cover myself with gauze yeah name tag that
says ben yeah that's pretty good uh i got a question from i'm just picking one at random here
you know there's a lot of questions about candy corn a lot of people are really down on candy corn
i just guess i guess i just need to touch in with you guys about candy corn uh what's your what are
your feelings on me personally i don't think it's as bad as everybody makes it out to be you know
sometimes it's kind of it's got a satisfying chew and it's got a waxy quality that i i kind of like
i kind of feel like i'm punishing myself when i eat it and i guess i really like it i think it's a
real chore do you think what do you think is a chore about it travis what's like biting off the
little segments and see if they're different flavors they don't have i did justin and then
i became a man and put away such childish things now i only eat food for sustenance to live to live
and it's candy corn is like eating sugary candles and i don't have time for that shit i eat i eat my
soylent and then i'm back out there working for money none of this is true right i'm just i'm out
there grinding every day so that one day i can retire and pass it on to my kids i don't have time
to eat sugary candles yeah but i i do actually enjoy candy yeah i think they are right i like
the pumpkin and chocolate variants i would like to make my own elton brown taught me how to and
i've just never done it seems like something you don't need to know i mean it's never gonna
come up in a job interview if that's what you mean wait you waste your time which mbmb am classic
goop would make the best costume and that's from the davin porter finally something i care about
classic bits i feel like this is dying out a little bit i feel like maybe we need to pivot
back to our regular it's too late now griffin we're too deep in it i can't even see i can't
see the beginning we just gotta work towards the other end if a trick or treat or ask for
gluten-free and or peanut free can i slam the door on them that's from zach yeah yeah yeah peanut
allergies those aren't a thing hilarious what well they're still little they'll bounce back
from they just have to eat through it and come out the other end okay now wait a minute but okay
but but you don't get you don't get to order like you're not placing an order for halloween candy
i'll have the uh asparagus and uh salmon that sounds great thank you i'll wait here i'll wait
here go prepare it uh and could i get a uh glass hold the ice of still water thank you still water
please not sperm excellent uh this is from john what's the protocol on touching trick or treaters
as part of my not slash gimmick whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa this is the most this
is the most important advice we're gonna give don't do this thing don't do any of this thing
can we okay no no this is this is the question what costume could this person possibly be wearing
or touching a trick or treater is like you just won't get what the costume is unless they are
touching a trick or treater what's the character from babes in toyland they're like catchy's kids
in a giant night kid getter cake getter what about child spider and it's a spider for children
oh you're a spider no no no watch no look you get it now oh you're a child spider some sort
of child spider i'm guessing yeah you got it maybe you got bozo the clown and you have to
keep redirecting the idiot kids towards the buckets in the grand prize game like no dip
shit it's over there you were so far off i hate you do people still do that where like you have
to like go through the grand prize game on bozo's super sunday show they do not no i mean like a
spooky haunted porch thing to get to that can't like walk through these plastic bags and then you
can have this the candy and it's like man listen this is a simple one in one out transaction i say
trick or treat you hand me the candy i say thank you i leave the porch i leave the porch jonathan's
monster tweeted what's the worst halloween costume related goof slash disaster you've
had oh had i thought i said heard because if it was heard i was gonna say that last question
uh there's a question here from arrogant wanderer who says my friends are celebrating halloween as
couples they're all in relationships and want me to go should i i'm single the answer is absolutely
yes well wait hold on what do you mean they're celebrating as cut like they're just going to
get together in a circle as couples and be like nice like are they going to a party are they going
to a scary movie so what do you mean they're they're probably just going together like to
trick or treat together as couples because you get twice the candy as adult couples holding bags
we're adult couples so we could carry all the candy we're hollow tonight high five we don't
even have to go back and switch out bags or nothing i love being married and i love having
a significant other in my life the only thing that is made harder is the costume
yeah thing because it's like there's a lot of things that i come up with are like oh that would
be a killer costume for me because it has to be the right fit you know this has to be something
you can you can live with but it a lot of times it's like really dynamic guy and then so what
i'll just be in a dress or something you know what i mean like or or or the reverse right like
if she dresses as buffy and i'm gonna dress as like what zander i'm gonna wear a hawaiian shirt
like that's i don't i don't have that problem because teresa has been dorothy from the wizard
of oz since she was like six for every halloween that's easy god i wish i had she has a costume
in storage halloween comes it's dorothy time and she puts it away for next year god i wish i
thought to do that yeah fuck i wish i thought because of this one it's just established like
it's not weird right it's just the thing that she does if i try to do that in a couple like i'm an
oddball but if i've been doing it for years it's like my thing yeah oh god that's it's genius um
i want to talk about the question that we addressed for a moment john jonathan's monster
about the worst halloween costume related goof slash disaster you pack because i don't know if
i ever talked about this on the show but the year i lived in chicago me and my roommates like went
around the town we went to a couple parties uh and did it up chicago style baby deep dish
only i put off getting a halloween costume until the day of and so i went to the halloween supply
store next to the trader joe's uh in roscoe village and i rolled up there and it was pretty barren and
the only thing i could find that i enjoyed was the costume from kickass the hit movie kickass
and comic book kickass so i bought it but they didn't have my size they only had a size smaller
than i wore i was like oh that's probably okay that costume is spandex and it was basically
it was basically what it was
so kind of like turned my whole body into like some sort of dick museum
like i was so proud lights highlighting it the glass and like a little placard like donated by
griffin and it basically was just like hey guys how's it going nice to meet you i'm real uncomfortable
and i'm very cold and yeah thanks for asking that is my dick so um i went to a party uh the first
party we went to and i checked out the situation and i never checked out your situation yeah it
was a bad situation so fortunately i reached into the backpack that i had the foresight to bring in
case that i did not feel confident enough to pull this bold look off and i went in their bathroom
and i put jeans on underneath the costume and then i just looked like a weirdly dumpy legged kickass
it was bad bad beat griff it was a bad beat it was a bad beat and a bad year and the costume cost me
like 60 dollars last year teresa and i worked uh in a haunted house that uh was in a very rich
family's garage there's this company that like basically comes in and they throw big halloween
parties and they build like really um let's say uh you know thrown together how uh haunted houses
in people's garages and uh teresa and i were scaring in it and uh an eight-year-old ballerina
came out walked out to me i jumped out oh she looked at me looked at me and reached up and
smacked me real hard in the face fuck yeah and then i had to like go up to my boss and complain
about the eight-year-old ballerina that hit me in the face and how i didn't want to do it anymore
is it because you didn't scare her good enough no well it was like her eighth time through i
think you know she'd seen it she'd been she'd been around she knows how where the scares are
ah i love that punk shit that's dope i mean don't hit obviously that's like that's rule number one
for me just like in life guys if you listen seriously don't hit but that shit rules well
it's already demoralizing enough to be the person scaring in a haunted house because it's just like
you you like have it's not i don't know what type of person does it and feels rewarded though i
imagine there are those people but i do it and i'm just like ugh i know like best case scenario i
just scared the shit out of someone worst case scenario i jumped out and went and they just
looked at me and walked past like there's not a good feeling that can occur unless you scare
someone and they go oh thank you thank you for that i feel alive for the first time wonderful
spooking that was real top-notch spooking only now do i appreciate the things in life that have
been empty to me before now thank you you've made me realize how precious this thing we call life is
i can now love great i can love for the first time i must go talk to my ex-wife sydney won't
let me put up any spooky decorations like anything that looks really scary like i found a hand that
i wanted that had a sign in its hand that's like here's your sign it says bill ingvall zombie zombie
bill ingvall kill ingvall it was called and uh oh god you've just triggered me you've said my
you've said my code phrase i must go wait no i must go there's no leaving i'm putting i'm putting
the rifle together as we speak goodbye wait wait wait wait wait this is important what is it that
in the context of this that you are going to go do that you have to go do and he just he just hung
up i think he's gone it's too late now it would be very unfortunate if the trigger phrase for him to
go kill bill ingvall was kill ingvall that's a little on the nose little on the little bit on
the nose actually good man sherry and candidate two is not very good no no the code word was like
you just had to work assassinate the president into a sentence and then if they heard it watch
out buddy because then they were going to do that he's still off for yeah i think he's probably
still going and doing his thing justin yeah are you going to are you gonna uh take charlie trick
or treating this year you know i've actually been thinking about that scraps because i don't know
uh i last year we sat on the porch and handed out candy that was fun but i don't know if it's
like i don't want to be the people that the the the people with houses are thinking
are just trying to run a scam for free candy like we don't know where to buy candy at
yeah i mean i don't want to be that guy i feel like she's she's she's like oh how to go
i don't i can't what are you talking about we're talking right now about taking baby charlie uh
trick or treating yeah whether or not i can take charlie trick like i think it'd be fun to just go
i don't have one of those unicef boxes so maybe i could tell people i'm collecting for unicef
and just have like a bucket or like a grocery a kroger bag i don't think she's gonna get a lot out
of it no really i was gonna say she seemed she's like pretty on the ball for like what one one in
three months like griffin if you could tell me what she would get a lot out of so i could leave my
fucking house and not feel guilty about it yeah just like a fantastic do you want a list of like
10 things i can hook you up like a raffi concert i got i got what baby's craze
doing a lot of margaret research let me tell you about some shit hit me all right a big old shiny
balloon nice that's one that's one and you can't you were you thought i couldn't even produce one
huh what a surprise that must be she likes beards nope now that's too hard to get your hands on a
real good one a bowl of fake beards a bowl of fake beards this batch is a choking hazard you
gotta think about non-choking hazards let me hit you with this goldfish crackers uh hey uh this has
been our halloween super special uh we're gonna cut it off here thanks for all the questions
it's time to go to the money bin that's weird i like this is this episode reminds me of those
boxes and nerds used to get that had two flavors in them mm-hmm yeah this is what if we did that
we spent a lot of time doing like my brother my brother me and the adventure zone well if we just
did one episode and we called it the adventure brothers well that's too close to the other thing
and that shit me undies is your place for getting things on you underneath the things that people
see that underpants so comfortable it's spooky it's terrifying you like literally you will you
will be scared to underpants death it feels like i'm wearing some sort of ghostly shroud it feels
like a mummy gently cupping my testicles all right they make them well there's underwear
did you guys get lounge pants or is it just me and sid no stop bragging about your fucking lounge
pants yeah they're great uh hotchi mochi they maybe if everybody tweeted at me undies and said
we love your product we buy a lot of it if you'll send travis and griffin some lounge pants hold on
lounge pants hostage yeah emotional hostage um just when you wear the lounge pants what kind of
classic universal monster does it feel like it's cupping your pants it's like a
classic universal monster does it feel like it's cupping your genitals and or but it
it feels like they all decided to put aside their differences
one thing for once to do something together like they always sit out of here creature from the
black lagoon i want dry testicles uh they are right now they're 20 off your first order when
you go to me undies dot com slash my brother and if you don't love them your first pair is free
thanks for asking what halloween monster it feels like it's cupping my testicles both of you griffin
you don't have the lounge pants well i have regular underwear when you wear your me on these
men's briefs what does it feel like it's cupping your testicles and or buttocks it feels like the
classic halloween monster death man you guys know about death man right tell me about death man he's
very oh my god he's scary imagine if you will the green skin of a frankenstein uh-huh sharp
teeth of a wolf banana but two of the sharp teeth are longer like a dracula okay and then he does
have some bandages but those are just covering wounds they're not like his clothes he has other
regular clothes on and if you see him it's too late once you see him you've initiated the bond
is he sexy he can be depends on what you're into huh i can't tell i can't and also it depends on
like what he's wearing and like how he's done his hair and if he's like been taking care of himself
you can't discount confidence that's so right right now i'm wearing like a shitty polo right
now and some old jeans because i need to do laundry as soon as we're done like i i'm a little
greasy because my fans turned off in the room like i'm not sexy right now can i get sexy sure
and the same as you know you're right i didn't mean to pass it like pass it as just a blanket
statement does he have the capacity to appear sexy yeah of course feels like everyone everyone
does everyone does you know that's such a good point griffin yeah what does he do to uh teens
if he kept well i told i told you well you you see him he forms the bond once the bond is formed
it's unbroken until one of the two of you dies or until thursday rolls around on thursday it resets
thursday next or like because like it is like the coming thursday or it's it's the shitty thing
right trav if you get bonded on thursday you've got to wait until the next thursday oh that's
that's weak that's the worst but if it's like wednesday night like if it's wednesday and you
get and there's this uh death man like knock on the door um which is just like a regular knock
but there's a lot of whaling then go you can open it because like you do only have like a few hours
so you're gonna have to deal with this fucking guy but do it before it turns midnight or like it's a
whole thing but watch out if he touches you don't let him touch don't let him what happens if he
touches you oh boy you are in for it like what what happens don't leave me a suspense well you're
gonna start getting thinner oh no wait like like an unsettlingly thinner like the movie thinner
no not that fast but you are going to lose a little bit of weight but then after but then
like so far after the cycle you're gonna regain that weight you're gonna be back to the normal
weight that you were so frustrating it's really very very frustrating because you just went out
and bought those new pants for yourself that you liked so much guess what you got to return those
and while you're on your way back to the gap to return those pants you get hit by a truck and die
oh no no what a twist that's how that's how death man gets you one of the interesting things about
death man is that i thought when you said his name uh which i recall correctly is death man
yeah he would like like his touch would like kill you like it would kill you to touch him it does
it was but like very indirect it's very like final destination stuff it is if if the final
destination of every death in the movie was like guys we gotta stop returning these pants
just to eat the loss okay no i hey mom i thought you said we were heading home oh yeah i just
remember we had to return the jeans at the gap no they don't even give you cash to give you
store credit yeah that's as good as cash idiot um anyway uh that was a good bit and the next
middle see if we can get something good out of this i want to tell you guys about oh shit i've
been waiting to talk about blue apron blue apron is this meal delivery service for less than ten
dollars a meal blue apron sends you fresh ingredients perfectly proportioned making cooking
healthy meals really easy and fun each balanced meal is 500 to 700 calories per serving uh you can
get stuff like spicy korean chicken wings brie and pear grilled cheese sandwiches catfish piccata
and fresh fettuccine it's amazing and i have to say i am a uh a blue apron subscriber i don't
remember if i was last time we advertised with them and it has no fucking kidding guys it has
changed the game right it has changed changes the game right i like i love cooking but i'm not the
kind of person that goes out and buys like ingredients to cook specific meals i just buy
like the same shit every time i go to the grocery store and they they like they've changed the game
like i've cooked stuff that i didn't even know existed i've cooked like like weird grains that
i don't even know the name of now but like are delicious and i cooked them there's uh uh the
spiced pork chops oh yeah hell yeah we got those spice pork chops that was the best yeah that's
law with hops in them oh yeah there's like an october fest like meal that it's it's really
amazing it's changed the chicken the chicken yeah this tar spiced chicken is really good uh
there was like a some sort of like uh um shrimp like uh low boil thing that i did this week like
it's it's it's really really good food it's really healthy and i'm cooking more than i've ever cooked
in my life and i'm like getting better at cooking and like it is all around like the best thing i
have done and not only that but this is a new thing that i noticed uh just from being a customer
that they've started to offer more and more like child's friendly options not that anything they
had before i thought was like a child would hate this but you know maybe you got a little bit more
of a picky eater you want something they have that now yeah like they're doing it they're covering it
they're doing it all i could go on and on and on and on um and we will and we will here we go
one time i made ramen it was it was crazy the lobster roll yeah and okay we gotta stop uh you
can check out this week's menu and you can get your first two meals free if you go to blue apron
dot com slash my brother seriously let's change the game it's real good stuff uh you will not
regret it this next message is for future jazz and the message is from past jazz so it didn't ship
did it we both knew that was a possibility you did everything in your power to make it happen
cheer up just remember it's on them so rock out and remember the only thing you can control is
if your job is done on time what do you think this is uh probably organ transplant stuff oh
my god high stakes yeah listen i don't jazz don't play i thought maybe it was jace like short for
jason well maybe that's that's because you don't know jazz right i think maybe jace it's not it's
jazz short for jasmine okay maybe jazz is like a game developer and like their game didn't ship
on time that would be a hell of a thing what if it's oh what if it's about taxes
and what does that mean like she like she didn't send just didn't send like the taxes in on time
and now the government is hunting jazz across this great land of ours and the irony is is that as
jazz uses like our highway system and goes to the national parks to hide like jazz is using all of
the things that jazz's taxes aren't paying for as it's on you how ironic um here's another message
it's for swamp master sebastian uh and it's from turbo lady holy shit this is great so far turbo
turbo lady says to swamp master sebastian happy birthday boo i think it's happy birthday boo
happy birthday boo i'm a ghost since i couldn't find you a real life telekinetic salamander with
a disembodied voice of jeff bridges um were both of them on peyote when this message was written
or just us or just us am i on peyote right now and are we recording uh oh my god this isn't a
mic it's a snake i've been talking to a conch shell this whole time oh my god uh because i
couldn't find you a real life telekinetic salamander with the disembodied voice of jeff bridges i got
you something just as spectacular a birthday message from the brothers i hope your 39th year
is even better than the last 38 here's to a lifetime of adventures disasters and my bim bam
fueled road trips love your lady and also love your lady yeah yeah it's important when you're
when you're when you're just like neck deep in a peyote fever dream um and you're just like
following the spirit veins of the world back to the center of it all it's real important
that you have a good lover when you're in the sweat lodge might as well sweat lodge for two
you know what i mean don't just build that sweat lodge for one no make it big when you're in the
black lodge and you're uh audrey looking for agent cooper yeah find him when you're staying
at great wolf lodge and you're in the water park get passes for two you know what i mean like maybe
it's just cheaper if you just get passes for one and you're doing magic quests and stuff but like
why not get two wands and then you and your lady can both do magic quest that's a great it's a
great as opposed to just making your weight in the car that's really fucked up and maybe the first
time because you want to scout it out yourself before like you do because what if it's not fun
and you want to know what all the good spells are yeah but i mean don't like no more than a
half hour tops like then then go get her and be like it's safe come on in it's safe there's no
there's no mummies or death men death man's not here now so you're safe i took care of him
he did touch me we have to keep these pants man doesn't here's here's one thing death man doesn't
have any money how's he even gonna get into great wolf lodge well you can just walk in
you're safe there you're safe at other places you're safe movie theaters in the theater he's
not gonna go in there he doesn't have any money not since the divorce not since the divorce it
was really really hard on death man he's had a tough time you know who he was married to who
dracula whoa whoa really yeah and so i think that there's maybe like a little bit of chip
on his shoulder because everybody knows dracula i'm biz and i'm teresa and we host one bad mother
a comedy podcast about parenting we say all the horrible things about having kids so you don't
have to and you can come across as the magical vessel pinterest perfect parent society wants
you to be one bad mother because this is hard and nobody gives a check us out on itunes and
maximum fun.org i want to make a point okay we said we're gonna split this right now there would
be absolutely nothing crazier than an episode of this program if it's 50 minutes of halloween content
and 10 minutes of non-halloween content for i guess for non-observers to try to make it like a
pan religious thing oh don't worry we have a non-halloween option that's just it's weird
it's weird way to the back can i change a yahoo to be halloween themed oh this okay this one's
about fear perfect how about this this one was sent in by zoe kinsky thank you zoe climbing
that ladder it's by yahoo answers user anonymous they ask um charm jarmel charm moosh charm moosh
asks silly irrational fears and how to overcome them i can't remember when i first found out about
this fear but it feels like i've been suffering from it for years it was rational it would be
okay but it's far from rational uh basically i'm absolutely terrified such disturbed repulsed by the
extinct shark called megalodon nope not great whites or any living shark just a long dead fish
it wasn't a huge problem as i could avoid seeing hearing anything about the creature pretty easily
that is until i went to south carolina and there was a skeleton recast there and that was enough
to get me to weeping my friends even after explaining it to them found this hilarious and
have since been sending me funny megalodon pictures anyway they can despite it frightening the hell
out of me uh they say it's a stupid fear and i need grow up and i know they are right but that
doesn't stop the hysterics the panic the tears the nightmares how can i overcome this i feel like the
more exposure i get to the extinct animal the more hypersensitive i become i okay i the the fact
that you encountered a megalodon uh-huh even though you know you have a paralyzing fear of
megalodons is insane do you know how easy it is to avoid megalodon related content just check on
yelp and look where it says megalodon statue yes or no yes or no and then if it says yes just don't
go there and also can i say real gold star friends when they see you weeping at the site and they're
like let's send her some photos looks like you found a glowing weak point it's this giant old
ass fish wow guys if i saw somebody weeping at the skeleton of a megalodon i would laugh
like a misinformed racist man at the don rickles show like i i the only way you can turn that is
like somebody comes up to you are you crying you go yeah i'm just sad they're all gone such a sad
story beautiful beautiful great monstrous beautiful creatures this beautiful beautiful
lovecraftian hell monster oh if only i just wonder what it would have been like if i could have met
him while they were alive can i can i devil's advocate here real quick i fucking get it imagine
being a caveman person or something you're swimming in the ocean having a beach party
you see one of those things as soon as you see one of those things it's you're done their mouths
are their mouths are so big i just want to jump in and say that caveman beach party usa is already
copyrighted by my copyright and mailed it to myself death man cave caveman beach party and
the other thing that we said we're going to copyright dracula cop all definitely definitely
copy written biteless protection program that's probably what oh nice that was under the cover of
night what did you hear when i said bite let's protect no no i'm giving you a tackling that's
the tagline okay undercover of night is the tagline well you guys did the title and tagline
so i guess i'll just do the whole script the tagline is he's wearing a cape behind the drapes
biteless protection program colon colon undercover of night he's like peeking through
the drapes oh and his partner's name is night with a k this is a good movie can we get can
we get a plot line in there about how he's recently divorced from death man yes we can
griffin crossover hit of the summer and also and also deadpool is there yeah is megalodon
they were just king shit of fuck mountain huh like i'm trying to imagine that way he's gonna
step to him like we're at the top of the food chain right but a shark will still eat our ass
because if we get careless for like a second well if we do if we do anything seal like right um
um nothing can eat a megalodon except a bigger megalodon okay but still a megalodon um super
megalodon were they just on top of shit were they just sort of rule how did how did they go extinct
that's the ultimate carelessness they they just became whales well i don't think that's just sort
of scientifically sound i think the more logical thing is that they they thought it was so sweet
when they ate stuff that because it was that they ate too much stuff oh we're stuff to eat
you know what i mean they created so did yeah well i got that they got they got the megalobetes
hi i'm killford brimley
fuck it oh wait what about krillford brimley let me try again hi i'm krillford brimley
oh fuck that's good it's real um can i do another yahoo since i didn't get to do any
the whole show as long as it's like spooky yeah this one's spooky uh bats are pretty spooky right
yeah sure yeah yeah that's good okay this one was sent in by uh game recognized game rachel
spurling thank you rachel it's by yahoo answers user mother green who asks
what would batman think of marijuana would he look down on people who use it
this is like a random question that popped in my head also i'm bull boo word nice um good
like what would he think of people with anxiety using it or any other medical condition
adds a really interesting twist there because at first you hear the question you're like
i don't know if he likes to party or not this is a tough question but then he adds another layer
of what if you needed it what if it was medical herb riddle me this batman what do you think of
that dank herb but for medical use i think it all depends on what else you're doing like that's a
good answer man marijuana seems like a low-hanging fruit but if the penguin's like i wear this this
monocle for my glaucoma like and he also smokes pot i think he's going to go with that i don't
also smoke spot i think he's going to try to bust oh i thought he will probably add it to the list
of charges oh i see i see what you're saying if he runs into the penguin he's smoking that big fat
old kush rod um and he slaps it he's like what the fuck we're in portland it's totally cool he's
like no it's for the the robberies oh okay good point i did do those do you want to do like chill
for a while before we go though i don't think i can handle prison right now i kind of melted
back into the riddler there a little bit there a little bit touch which batman villain would you
okay listen listen listen uh-huh for once which batman villain would you most want to get high with
poison ivy nice oh my god travis got it in one the kush that she grew would be super
fun running a little low on that sweet air but allow me grow powers i don't know what she
did we do all batman villains have the same voice in our universe listen it's me harvey dent
i'm that black mask fellow what's his name i'm clay face did you hear the news let's
let's get sticky it's me mr freeze i've gone from mr freeze to mr chill
oh i bet he could hot box in that helmet well bane's got it just flowing he's just got like an
extract bones just got a bonus bones just got that shit that thc juice hey hey guys guys what
if he was called man bat you know it'd be the worst fucking mad hatter can you chill you know
be even worse scarecrow did you guys hear any cops fuck off scarecrow that's not freaking me out
hate you scarecrow calendar man's just like hey guys guess what day it is are you about to say
april 20th yeah how did you guess yeah how did you guess i was gonna say april 20th we're dodging the
question would batman be down with it and the problem is is you give it to catwoman she just
bats it around you know what i mean she goes crazy okay would batman be into it or not
uh you know what he studied i bet i bet he's down i bet he's down
okay but he's gonna have to give me something more than that i'm just saying that like he
studied with razz al ghul right right so i know that fool likes a party that's what i'm saying
you're telling me that when he was hanging out like in a tibetan monastery thing that he wasn't
also like and now we must enter a meditative state plus pass you know what i mean like
like i'm just saying that i think batman's down but what happens in most most monasteries yeah
trap that's how they do it but i bet that he uh would get really mad if he caught robin doing
it like oh yeah like a really you know kind of uh hypocritical kind of thing uh alfred quick i
need uh gps coordinates on uh funkel and factories okay hold on hold up yep where is my iphone
can you slow down and spell that for me my dude hey hey siri where's the franklin factory let me
find that for you bong master 5000 oh uh hold up i i did that as a joke oh fucking steve jobs right
okay he's played a good prank on me alfred i'm dead oh not again oh damn so this has been my
brother my brother and me it's an advice show for the modern era fuck this episode was scary yeah
very scary very creepy episode of our show uh hey let's keep this uh fun this holiday spirit going
huh yeah uh you want to tell the people a good news good news let me pour you all a glass of
good news hold on a glass of good news did you see that did you see the person who made uh uh
somebody made ginger beer and they were looking for a name for their brand of ginger beer and
they called it good news nice tight yeah cindre it looks like this gentleman's name is but uh
my anglo-saxon tongue probably stumbled butchered that yeah uh tell me good news good news is
candlelight 2015 it is happening tell them when and where december 21st that's a monday that's a
monday at the big sandy superstore arena uh monday monday we sold out the arena already
sorry we did not sell it out i should point out there have been all the tickets are still available
still available this good news is we're doing it on a monday so like everything in heinz will be
open on like our last time when everything was closed so everything will be open it's december
21st 8 p.m uh we are gonna the plan is right now to put tickets on sale on friday but you
could check out um uh our twitter account or which is mbnb am or uh facebook whatever i do
not as soon as we have details we'll get you a link and everything i do not anticipate that it
will sell out as quickly as our like new york show sold out and like some of our pacific northwest
shows sold out so um i guess you have a little time it won't require there's no telling sometimes
yeah i don't know i don't know um but it's gonna be real fun it's gonna be a holiday treat it's at
a different venue from last year so like i know so you'll be able to hear our human voices yeah
you'll be able to talk uh saw bones will be doing a show there um maybe some other special guests
hard to say uh i feel like you should tell them what the other special guest is gonna be i feel
like you should throw your fucking hat over the fence well i haven't checked yet i'm not sure i
haven't checked with the special guests yet okay see if they can do it get that hat ready to throw
it yeah i will um so that's gonna be we don't take details yet like i said but they'll be on twitter
and facebook and stuff plan is loosely this friday to go on sale um but if you're if you know you're
gonna be traveling through the area or you want to come it's fun it's in our hometown we uh we can
tell you some cool places to go uh we had a blast last year it was like one of the dumbest nights
my entire life it was great really really stupid uh and it's gonna pop off again this year it's
gonna be bigger and better than ever candlelight candlelight check it out it's a pan-religious
pansexual personal pan holiday for you the people and we want you to come celebrate with us we love
you uh thanks to john roderick in the long winters who used for a theme song it's a departure off the
album putting the days to bed it's gonna make a great halloween gift put it on at your halloween
parties there's probably some spooky undertones there maybe i don't know uh and also go listen
to the other maximum fun shows we got other shows we do like the adventure zone uh we got uh saw
bones and justin does with uh his wife sydney who's a doctor uh it's a very funny very informative
very wonderful show we got bunker buddies travis does with his buddy andy travis kind of produces
kind of guests on can't pet your dog um and then there's other shows that we don't do did i forget
we have so many fucking irons in the fire did i forget i mean i objects on them i also produce
baby geniuses and they just had their 100th episode with kristen schall it's really really
good highly recommended it's a great starting place uh there's like a best of and everything
mixed into it that i edited and did a really great job with um good job travis there's other
shows though like jordan jesse go there's uh stop podcasting yourself throwing shade uh there's pop
rocket there's one bad mother there's lady the lady uh lots of really really great shows you can
find them all at maximum fun.org uh we also we haven't mentioned in a while but if you get a
second if you could go on like itunes and like rate review and subscribe it only takes a second
and it bumps us on up them charts yeah gotta get up those charts oh my god oh also if you get a
second could you go check out trends like these the uh show i do with my friend brent where we
talk about the stories that are trending on the internet and help you make sense of really weird
stuff um justin has a show he does with his buddy dwight called things i bought at sheets it's a
food review quiz show you can find it on youtube it's on youtube just search for it go check it
out sheets show is that right she's sheets with the z show.com great um show.com and one last
plug justin and i probably have a new episode of monster factory out today nice video we do a polygon
where we make ugly characters in games this time just a solid if you like those as much as some
people seem to please tweet about it and tell your friends to do the same uh so we can justify
spending way too much time on them oh god so much time uh that's it um thank you all very very very
much um we love you anything i'm forgetting you have to read the last question oh yeah this last
question was sent in by level 9000 yadru druid drew davenport um thank you druids by yadru answers
user another anonymous person charmas asks nice coffee it's become the man soul's fuel
my name's justin mcroy i'm travis mcroy i'm griffin mcroy this has been my brother my
brother may kiss your dad square on the lips
maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported
we're dave and graham and we host stop podcasting yourself we started this podcast back in 2008
before podcasts had to have any kind of concept so we don't really know how to describe it it's
kind of like going to the barber shop if your barber knew all about the first season of the
show elf it's like a 90 minute massage where the masseuse is two people talking to each other with
a third person it's like the monsters of metal tour only quieter no music and just talking
it's like a makeout session but without the lips touching they just talk a lot
download stop podcasting yourself from itunes or maximum fun.org