The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello, everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother and Me, the advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
Oh no, I'm Griffin McElroy. Travis, what's the matter, partner?
What's wrong? I didn't get the call, you know? Today, when we're recording this,
it's the first official game of the NFL 2020 season.
Oh no. Once again, I didn't make the cut.
Oh no. You've been practicing so hard.
Yeah, but I don't get to feel up the pigskin.
You can't fondle the pig, and you got the tire in the backyard that you throw the football through.
I flip the tire, and then I throw the football through it.
And then you just stomp through it. Most of your practice is tire-based.
I remember when me and Justin and you were playing out in the field,
and you found that tire, and you picked it up, and you said, now I can play football.
Well, it was a magical tire, or else what was it doing in that field? You know what I mean?
Like, there wasn't a car for miles.
We were confused when you said, this tire is the key to football.
But then we watched you practice with it. You worked so hard. Your body looks so crazy.
And I didn't get the call. I didn't get the call.
And so another season. And I thought this year, you know,
is like COVID-19's out there, and so maybe they'll need more people.
Yeah, maybe it'll be like that situation where that one bartender from Philadelphia,
and they were like, hey, you come play for us. But nobody called me.
That movie's wild. Because it's like,
if this fucking dude could play football, why not Travis with his magic tire?
Right. I didn't get the call. I waited. I waited by the phone.
Every day, I even drafted myself to my ding-dang fantasy football league,
and now I look like a total tit.
Yeah, you're probably not going to get many points off your own sweaty, your brow.
Trav, I'm sorry.
They won't let me write in my points.
Say like, well, today I played touch football, and I scored three touchdowns.
So that's 21 points.
This should have been your year, though.
It should have been.
If not this year, you know?
No one's even going to be watching, you know what I mean?
Because like, they can't go to the stadium.
No.
Right? And so you would think that they would be like,
let's try some weird stuff this year.
This would be the year for like a donkey that kicks field goals, right?
If they're ever going to do it.
Yeah.
Or Tony Danza, the incredible field goal kicking garbage man.
What is that?
I think you nailed that.
I think that's what you're talking about.
I mean, baseball is having fun with that.
I don't know if you guys have been keeping track.
I'm not one to follow the sports news, but I did see a story today
that the Atlanta Braves won a game yesterday with a big 29 runs.
So it feels kind of like they were just like,
guys, let's just have fucking fun.
This doesn't count.
None of this counts.
Let's just have fun with it.
Why don't you throw a few slow boys down the plate?
Let me get a few grand salamis and next game I'll let you do it
because none of this fucking counts or matters.
It has just occurred to me that there was never an equivalent
of like rookie of the year, but for like the NFL,
where it's like, hey, that nine year old threw that football pretty good.
Get him in here with all these like 400 pound men.
Or I mean, in the NFL version of rookie of the year, he would be huge.
Like, and that would be his thing is that he would be like a linebacker
and he would be the Hulk.
He would be-
But he's like 10.
But he's 10 years.
He's a 400 pound, 10 year old, just monster, absolute unit of a lad.
The garbage picking, field goal kicking, Philadelphia phenomenon
is the full name of the film starring Tony Danza
as a garbage man that is good at football.
And that's gotta have great SEO.
You know what I mean?
So easy to remember, clear to search for.
Was the story of that movie,
can you believe this professional sanitation worker can also be an athlete?
They give an average guy a shot at the NFL.
Why?
And they make him the kick.
Well, cause he's the kicker, so who cares?
No, but I mean, even then, was it just like, hey, that guy,
let's see if he can do it or was there a contest?
I have like vaguest fucking fragment of a memory
of him kicking like water bottles really far.
And they're like, yes, this translates.
Yes, you are the guy.
Half of the players in the real life NFL
is because somebody saw them like throwing fish at the fish market
or like tackling a bear.
And they say, yeah, that guy's very good at tackling.
Scouts will sometimes just go to the tire store
and watch how people shelf tires and move tires around.
And they're like, that's football, baby.
The end of that film,
I pulled up the Wikipedia page to get the right name.
At the end of that film,
the holder of the football fumbles the snap
and Tony Danza grabs it and scores the game winning touchdown.
So even the creators of the garbage picking field goal kicking
Philadelphia phenomena agree that a kick is too boring of a way to end.
It's just not interesting enough.
It has to be a touchdown.
You can't just make it a good kick.
That's nothing.
I mean, I would, I disagree
because I would watch a game that's just kicks.
That's just kicking back and just field goal after just a shootout.
Soccer.
Oh, fuck.
Wait, what now?
But the ball would be super silly.
Like they wouldn't, that's what I love about the American.
Put a little water in it.
The European football is like spherical
in a way that is sort of like geometrically pleasing to some.
But I love the way that when American football hit the ground,
it's like, good luck fuckers.
I want more weird balls in sport and by which I'm,
but when I say that, I don't really want it that bad.
I really feel like in order for sport to move me these days,
you need to score 29 big, big runs in a single game.
Cause that, fuck yeah.
Now we're playing some like broken, you know, MLB 2K on the dreamcast.
It's transformed into Blaseball.
If I may, here's what I think would really,
if I might fix football in 2020 to get more people watching.
Cosmic football.
A lot more like, you know, after hours bowling alley
where everything's like, you know, black light and like neon.
And like, maybe you play some like, especially funky music,
PG-13 music, if you will, Cupid Shuffle,
where you're not sure where the sexual part is,
but it sounds pretty good.
It sounds good.
And that's great, Trav.
Say, is part of your plan also maybe make the field a little bit shorter?
Maybe get rid of some of the penalties
and then maybe have a sort of strict opinion
about political demonstrations on the field there, Vince McMahon, or?
Wait, in XFL, is there like the ball is black light?
Yeah, yeah, it is.
Aw, no.
Well, it's so you can make sure everybody did wash their hands.
For safety.
It's for safety.
Oh, but you like, all the uniforms are black, right?
But, but you put some like neon reflective tape on
to make them look like stick men running around?
Oh, or skeletons.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah, for the Halloween season.
You can dress up.
You can do your own costume.
That's cool.
That would be like when we played mascot football.
When I was, I played mascot football
at a River City Locomotives indoor arena football game,
and I was cowabunga, the cow for WTCR,
and I went out there on that beautiful field,
and it was my crowning achievement
because I did run in a beautiful touchdown,
but I only accomplished it
because Louie the lightning bug
sacked the fucking shit out of Shoney Bear
and sent her forehead flying 10 yards down the field.
It was-
I've been in that cow costume.
Visibility is low.
It is limited.
It was an incredible catch.
It was, it'll be the end of my movie.
Nothing I've done after that is gonna be better,
but it's also going to be the start
of Louie the lightning bug's movie
because he really made Shoney Bear eat fucking mud.
There's a scout who's like,
give me that lightning bug.
He tackles good,
but then he can only tackle in the lightning bug costume.
You gotta play it safe around me.
Is Louie the lightning bug a universal reference
or a local reference?
We'll find out, won't we?
Should we do a question?
I'd love that.
Thank you so much.
Sorry, I'm really excited about all the good Munch Squad
I have this episode.
I feel like I've been seeing a lot of Munch Squad
in the ether.
I feel like people are getting-
They've all just been saved up in the pipe.
There's been a big clog.
It's so, I almost don't wanna,
oh wait, oh wait.
No, no, you can't do that.
Yeah, you can't Munch Squad for some reason.
Just rip it, baby.
Give me question number two.
I'll do a couple throughout the show.
Can we do that?
Can we just do a couple throughout the show?
Okay, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Munch.
Okay, Munch Squad.
It's podcast within podcast.
Profiling the latest and greatest of brand eating.
There's just so much going on that I need to talk about.
You guys hear about the Candyman?
What?
Don't say it again.
Candyman is David Klein.
He is the creator of the Jelly Belly.
Okay.
Oh, I heard about this.
So he, not Jelly Belly's themselves,
but the creator of the Jelly Belly
who kind of struck out on his own
after I assume selling the brand
for a lot of money.
The Candyman is doing-
Ah, you said it three times.
Okay, I knew you were just,
I wanted to get it out of the way.
So I beat you to it.
So he is doing a Willy Wonka style
Jelly Belly, a Willy Wonka style treasure hunt
where he is going to give away a candy factory
if you find the golden tickets that he has hidden around.
Okay.
He couldn't even like take it and turn it and twist it.
He just said like,
like he watches like Willy Wonka with his kids
and said, ah, fuck it.
And he's just gonna like copy and paste
Willy Wonka's whole deal?
No, no, Travis, he's not.
He's gonna mix it up quite a bit.
There is a gold ticket hidden in one in each state
as I understand it.
Yeah.
I will now tell you the particulars of this contest.
And this is, I'm reading directly from thegoldticket.com.
How to play.
Each treasure hunt game will have a game location
and a start date and cost $49.98 to play.
And then it says, this is the cost for the riddle.
This is the cost for the riddle?
This is the, it says in parentheticals,
this is the cost for the riddle.
The registered person who purchased the game
will be signed up in a private forum.
You must have a Facebook account.
The day and time your treasure hunt starts,
you will receive the riddle in your group.
You will be looking for a gold ticket
in the form of a necklace with a tag
that includes a code you need to verify your find.
Winners will receive $5,000.
Gold ticket codes must be submitted to,
this is the email address.
All treasure hunt players will be eligible
to join in on the ultimate treasure hunt
where I give away one of my candy factories.
Okay, but, okay, in real life though,
getting that candy factory means
now you have employees to worry about
and like payroll taxes and like fucking workman's comp
and OSHA and shit.
It's not like, yes, let's fold this river of chocolates.
Oh, yes, I have that, everything's eatable.
I think OSHA gives a little bit of just a,
it gives a bit of clearance to candy factories.
If Willy Wonka's film is to be believed.
I think OSHA is like,
they're doing something wonderful and whimsical over there.
Let's just let them do what they need to do
to make these jelly beans.
Yeah, I mean, assuming, sorry,
I got a little bit distracted
because I was absolutely paying the $50
I need to get in on this incredible treasure hunt.
West Virginia, you could-
Guys, don't get it twisted.
$50 is the cost for the riddle, okay?
So I'm pretty excited.
You could take this for West Virginia.
That's what I feel like.
I feel like I've got a pretty good shot here.
What's stopping you from paying the $50,
getting the riddle,
and then just blasting that out
to our millions and millions and millions of listeners?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Cause I paid the cost for the riddle.
Right, that's not the, no prize to enter
or like, you know what I mean?
Like anyone can enter,
but if you want the riddle, you pay $49.
I'm assuming that you have to pay the $49.98
to get the riddle,
but I'm not going to give the riddle away for free.
I wouldn't do the Candyman like that.
He and I are going to be working in very close concert
when I start doing the candy factory
the way I want to do it.
If you know what I mean?
What kind of big changes do you got planned, Justin,
for the Jelly Belly brand?
It's okay.
I can't stress this enough.
This is in no way connected to the Jelly Belly brand.
Candyman is a different guy.
He sold Jelly Belly.
Jelly Belly has no, there's going to be people
walking up to a factory like,
I'll take this one.
No, we're not doing, that's not the thing.
So what does he produce in his mini factories?
Do you want me to list the products of CandymanKitchens.com?
There's crime scene candy and blood and cloth.
Ew, God.
That's one, that's one that you can get.
You know what, just leave it there, J-Man,
because now I want to win so I can shut it down.
Shut it all down.
Make this stuff ethically, do it different.
I believe in farm to table blood clot candy.
Here's a quote.
The world needs this right now.
We have received thousands of comments from people who say
this has come at such a perfect time.
We've received thousands of comments of like,
please give me candy factory, I need this.
I was just thinking about how if somebody did a Willy Wonka,
it would really start fixing shit.
Yeah, that would fix it all.
So I'm so excited about that.
I will keep you guys abreast of my progress.
Okay.
This will be the greatest Riddle Me Piss of our generation.
And maybe the last one so that the stakes are very high.
Yeah.
If I win, you can't do Riddle Me Piss anymore.
And if you win, I assume you're retiring
from My Brother, My Brother and Me.
Oh, the show's done.
The show's done.
Oh, the show's over, yeah.
I have a candy factory.
It'll be Justin's candy factory,
but I'm assuming you will let us sort of,
you know, join the board at least and we can sort of-
Oh yeah, yeah, you'll be on the board for sure.
I need to get my wisdom teeth out soon
and I'm looking to sell them to an artist.
I'm really tight on money right now.
And as an artist, I love supporting other artists.
The issue is I don't know how to find
any artists looking for teeth.
I looked everywhere and no one is buying.
How much should I sell them for?
How can I sell my teeth so I can eat
through a straw for a while?
That's from Strap for Cash in St. Paul, Minnesota.
Or Minneapolis, Minnesota.
Minneapolis is a city in the-
There's so much going on in this question.
I don't get out of the house anymore.
I've been to this place and it's but a faint memory.
There's so much going on.
My favorite thing about this question,
what makes me love this question
is that you question asker were like,
and so I'm gonna sell them to an artist.
Don't get it twisted.
No artists are buying them.
So this is a wholly created scenario.
I'm gonna search Craigslist for teeth.
Okay.
There's 287 results for teeth.
I'm gonna check eBay for human teeth.
Yeah, I should have-
I don't wanna just make something up.
I should have been more specific.
Well, here's-
I got a lot of-
Okay, okay.
All right.
Let's all explain sort of what we found.
Okay, have you found prices?
Travis, you're not looking at prices, right?
No, I'm not.
Okay, let's say 20 teeth.
Okay.
What would you-
What do you think the going set is on that?
20 teeth?
Are these adult teeth or baby teeth?
These are a lot.
I'm looking at the very first result.
How many-
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
It does specify pre-owned.
Oh, okay.
Good.
Okay, okay.
Glad that mystery's cleared up.
Lot of human teeth.
The very first result.
This is the new Haunted Town Watch.
I'm just gonna talk about-
Okay, lot of human teeth, 20 teeth.
What are you gonna pay for these teeth?
What do you think the-
I'm gonna say 200.
200 for the lot.
Current bid is $50.
Okay.
Now, that's not a buy it now.
There is a buy it now.
I have eight fucking grotesque teeth that I'm looking at
that you could buy for 35 bucks.
They are vulgar and they make me want to throw up.
Now, there's a really-
This says nice set of human teeth for crafts.
Hand selected 27 count.
Intact crowns with some signs of minor decay
and incomplete root formation to perfect.
Perfect teeth.
And now this is 27 perfect teeth.
What are you gonna give me?
For 27 perfect?
Perfect teeth.
There's a buy it now.
Uh, I'm gonna say, okay, I was way off last time.
I'm gonna say $100.
Wow, $125.
So that's where we're at price-wise.
So let me just run the-
Also, backdoor, welcome to my new pitch for a spinoff
of Antiques Roadshow.
I brought in my teeth.
Oh, these are excellent.
These are, this is colonial style.
I love this.
If we're doing four wisdom teeth,
then at most, if we're using this,
you're gonna be able to sell them for 18 and a half bucks,
which ain't nothing, but it's also, I don't know,
not a lot to pay rent or whatever.
You gotta look at the market, right?
Cause you gotta think,
baby teeth are probably way down there, right?
A lot of baby teeth floating around.
Everybody's got them.
You know, like you had them at some point,
you lost them at some point.
It is guaranteed that there will always be
more and more baby teeth on the market.
Then right after that has to be wisdom teeth, right?
Like wisdom teeth is a thing that comes in
and almost everybody gets their removed.
You gotta think, top dollar is going for front adult teeth.
Grown folks teeth, yeah.
Yeah, like those front four.
This reframes the popular holiday song,
All I Want for Christmas is my two front teeth.
And it's like, don't be so fucking,
like I want a Nintendo 64 for Christmas.
Like we don't always get the things that we want.
That would be like $500 for two front,
the best teeth are your two front teeth.
Maybe incisors, I might give you incisors
because incisors, you only got four of them.
And they do a lot of the ripping and tearing work, right?
Molars, that's all grinding, right?
A lot of those that are in the back,
you don't even see them as much.
Incisors though, I feel like maybe those are the money teeth.
It's hard to say.
I've decided, I've just made a decision.
I'm gonna set up, okay, yes, this will be good.
I'm gonna set up a program.
Oh boy.
I, Justin McElroy, will buy the teeth for $100.
Question asker, please give me your Venmo information.
I will Venmo you the teeth for $100.
This is an enormous breach of-
$100.
Power dynamics.
I feel like-
No, listen.
Yeah, there's a condition coming, hold on.
There's a part two, okay?
If you are an artist, please email us
with the subject line, I will use the teeth,
and then tell us in as much detail as possible
your plans for the teeth.
Oh boy.
We will then read some of these on the program
and choose the best use of the teeth
that we will then legally own and arrange shipping
from the tooth holder to the artist.
Now, I want to stress something.
Me and Travis have nothing to do with this.
Yes, one, legally Griffin and I are not a part of this.
Two, anyone listening to this who's like,
I'd sell my teeth, this is a one-time thing.
It's a one-time deal.
We're not going to set this show up
as a black market tooth exchange.
Just this one time, and if, listen,
if you are not A, a legitimate artist,
who B, does not have a legitimate use for these,
because you know we're going to fight,
we'll be all over you for pictures,
descriptions by the moment, use of the teeth.
I'm going to need all the details,
so do not try to wade into this
like you're just going to pick up teeth craft.
I need a real artist who has a real great idea.
Hey, are we sure that this is entirely legal?
It doesn't feel so much legal to me.
Because we're paying a human being for part of their body
and then we're giving, yeah, no, correct.
I'm sending $100 to a friend
who will then be so inspired by my generosity
that they're going to mail their teeth to a stranger.
That's all that's happening here.
Okay, so at no point are you going to touch these teeth?
I can't stress this enough.
I at no point want to see or possess these teeth.
Until they are art.
The deal is off.
Until they're art.
And then I double don't want them.
Yeah, then you need to donate that shit to a museum.
Then it belongs to a museum.
So I don't want the teeth.
I don't want to see the teeth until the art is.
And then I still don't want them.
Not in person, for sure.
No, but this is a tooth patronage.
Please follow up.
Just reply to your first email with your payment information.
I will buy the teeth on consignment.
No, you will send them a gift of $100.
I will send them a gift with the understanding
that you will then send the teeth to a deserving artist
who would just love those chompy little crows.
And I swear to God, if somebody's like,
I'm going to glue them to Mona Lisa.
That's fucking funny.
That would look funny.
Stop it.
Don't waste our time.
You're keeping real artists who really need real teeth,
real bad, from our awareness.
So please don't do that.
Here's, can I?
Get that email address, by the way, it's mbnbam.maximumfun.org.
And just make sure the subject line is,
I will use the teeth in all casts.
And hey, let's not make it weird, okay, everybody?
Let's keep it pretty chill.
Let's keep it cool and nice.
Nothing weird with these teeth.
What if it turns out there's a huge tooth demand, though?
Oh, I thought you were going to say a huge tooth.
You get the teeth in and it's like,
whoa, what the fuck?
This was a deep root.
Can I do a Yahoo that was sent in by Yohannes?
Yes.
Okay, thank you, Yohannes.
It's from an anonymous Yahoo answers user.
I'm going to call Dr. Teeth, who asks,
this question's so powerful.
Which actors would have played Frasier
if Frasier could regenerate like the Doctor on Doctor Who?
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes. Dr. Frasier is at an opera,
chandelier, snap, falls from the ceiling, smashes him.
Smashes him dead.
The only way to kill Frasier.
The only way that Frasier can be killed.
And then everybody's like, oh no, Frasier, he's dead.
But then he starts to glow.
Kelsey Grammer turns into-
John Lithgow.
I was also thinking John Lithgow!
Boom!
Amazing, amazing.
John Lithgow, a second chandelier, whoop, snap, right on Johnny boy.
He starts to fucking glow again.
This time he turns into Justin.
He turns into Justin.
No, it doesn't turn.
I have to name an actor now.
Yeah, you weren't already thinking of one?
Come on, play the fucking game.
Get your head in the game, boy.
This is a game, boy.
Daniel Radcliffe?
No.
No, Travis, you can't.
No, we only yes on this show.
Okay, I missed the question.
I mean, you guys sound insane to me right now.
Wait, you missed the question?
You guys sound so wild.
I just missed the question.
Okay, Travis, don't tell him the question.
Justin, I want more answers to the question.
Okay.
Daniel Radcliffe is crushed by-
What have you heard so far, Justin?
I heard John Lithgow and something about a chandelier.
Okay, perfect.
Do you know everything you need to know?
Daniel Radcliffe is tragically smushed
by a third, even bigger chandelier.
His body starts to glow and he transforms into-
Larry Bird?
Oh.
An interesting choice that I don't hate.
Now that might seem like a stunt choice.
But Larry Bird, I will say this,
probably knows a lot about wine.
I don't hate it, Juice.
Wait, how does wine figure in-
How does wine figure in-
You're never gonna believe this.
Now, who would you-
The first chandelier-
Who would you partner with Larry Bird?
No, because there's not two doctors on Doctor Who.
No, but the doctor gets new companions.
Okay, wait, so there's Doctor Who,
there's wine is involved, okay.
Okay, the first chandelier-
Doctor Who gets new companions, though.
That's true.
The first chandelier-
It's gotta be Jordan, by the way.
I'd love to see the two of you.
Oh, I could hang with that.
The first chandelier zips back up to the ceiling
and then falls on Larry Bird, tragically killing him,
but his body starts to glow
and then he transforms into Who next, Justin?
Well, can I give you another point of data, Justin?
What I was gonna say,
maybe see if this will-
Give me a hint, yeah.
Richard Dreyfuss was what I was gonna say next.
Richard Dreyfuss is a very,
I will say this, Travis, a very dry choice.
And I'm gonna squish him basically immediately.
Okay, that's fair.
Richard Dreyfuss transforms into Who next, Justin?
In this classic role that is not Doctor Who.
Aaliyah Shawkat.
Huh.
Holy shit.
I'd watch the fuck out of that.
Yeah, I mean, I've watched the fuck out of that.
Would, okay, let me see if I can phrase this
in a question that won't give it entirely away,
is that would there be any dramatic changes
to the personality of this classic character
as played by Aaliyah Shawkat?
Or are we just going straight down the middle?
Shorter?
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Urbane, probably more urbane.
More urbane.
Not possible.
Okay, erudite?
More erudite.
Holy shit.
Wow, fucking-
Wait, let me make sure that word means-
It's gonna be off the charts.
Oh man, I was trying to Google the definition for erudite
and I Google the definition for erudite,
which is so embarrassing on like three different levels
at the same time.
Erudite.
So, I mean, Justin, I'm gonna go ahead and tell you,
we are talking about Frasier,
and I think Aaliyah Shawkat as Frasier
is one of the boldest sort of choices you've-
Frasier!
I put it right up there with Larry Bird though,
who I think right there, Larry Bird was announced
and I think a big part of the audience was like,
no thank you, stunt casting.
But it wasn't stunt casting, he auditioned.
He said, don't give it to me just on my name,
give it to me based on merit.
He auditioned, nailed it.
Even Kelsey Grammer was like,
that's more, he's more Frasier than-
He's Frasiest.
And so they gave it to Larry Bird
and Larry Bird did great.
He ran for nine seasons.
I think that most television sitcom producers are cowards.
Yeah.
Because, let me hit you with this.
Season three finale of Fresh Prince of Bel-Air,
they fucking, Aunt Viv is like walking down the stairs
and then like trips and goes over and falls horribly
and is just dunsies.
And Fresh Prince is like, oh no!
But then she transforms into a different actress
and that's the way that they fucking write that out.
That's how they write that off.
You don't just do a switch, fucking Two and a Half Men.
Well, I guess they did do a sort of in-fiction thing
for Two and a Half Men, but-
But not to say he didn't just regenerate
into a different character.
That's fair.
Because here's the thing, Doctor Who,
that was bullshit they made up to recast the part, right?
Yeah.
It's not like, well, it's just true about Time Lords.
No, they fucking made that up.
Anyone could make that up.
Anyone can do it.
You guys wanna hear the fucking best,
I actually have the best casting for Frasier and Nott.
Okay.
This is what would happen if it was getting rebooted today.
I'm gonna get Johnny Galecki and Jim Parsons
as Frasier and Nott.
I love it.
They're back.
They're back together again.
Okay.
The Big Bangs are banging once more.
And get Kaylee for Daphne.
Now, Justin, it just kind of feels like what you're doing
is you're both rebooting Frasier,
but also Big Bang Theory.
This is sort of your back door.
Mayim Bialik is Ross.
Easy.
Okay, you're just kind of slamming Big Bang Theory
and Frasier together and seeing what noise it makes.
I'm just hearing the wet slap of Frasier and Big Bang Theory
just kind of running into each other in your large head.
Who plays Martin, Justin?
Wil Wheaton.
Okay.
And who plays the dog?
John Ross Bowie.
John Ross Bowie is back with Christine.
Christine Baranski was on Big Bang Theory.
Okay.
Perfect.
You guys know a lot about this.
I think she was probably also on Frasier.
You guys know a lot about Big Bang Theory.
Thank you, girl.
Yeah, you know, you hope somebody's gonna notice.
Let's take a quick break.
Oh, wait, hold on, Justin.
Parsons, Galecki.
Which one's which?
Which one's Frasier?
Which one's Niles?
True West.
True West, baby.
It's True Westing it.
True Westing it, baby.
Every episode's a True West.
And so they swap episode to episode,
not halfway through each episode?
Interesting.
No, every commercial break, that's the best option.
There's very distinct glasses.
That's great.
Maybe they have hats that they always wear.
Let's take a quick break
and then we'll be right back with more great content.
Holy shit.
Smooth.
Do you guys remember when Kelsey Grammer fell off that stage?
Oh, yeah, baby.
I think about it every day.
Every single day.
Hey, Griffin.
Yeah.
Bring me some food.
Nope, you're too far away from me.
No, I'll tell you what food I want.
Okay.
And I'll give you money for it.
Right.
But you have to bring it to me.
No, you're several thousand miles away.
That sucks.
What am I supposed to do?
Starve.
Damn it.
Or use DoorDash.
You can do DoorDash.
Oh.
Yeah, that's the other option.
What is this DoorDash you mentioned?
Oh, it's the app that brings food
that you're craving right now to your door.
It's weird that you're asking me all this
because it is in the copy points.
And so I think like if this is a-
Oh, wait, you're reading from something?
If this is like a need that you need filled,
there's literal text information in front of you.
It's really easy to use it.
You just open the DoorDash app
and you choose what you want to eat
and then your food will be left safely outside your door
with the new contactless delivery drop-off setting.
And then they have all your favorite local restaurants
that are open for delivery.
And you just pick them-
I haven't gotten any new food into my house
since March of 2020.
Oh, no, that's not good.
Well, you should be getting more food,
but also DoorDash is a really great way to do it.
And right now our listeners can get $5 off
their first order of $15 or more
and zero delivery fees for their first month
when you download the DoorDash app
and enter the code BROTHER.
That's $5 off your first order
and zero delivery fees for a month
when you download the DoorDash app
in the app store and enter code BROTHER.
Don't forget one last time,
that's BROTHER for $5 off your first order with DoorDash.
Hey Justin.
What's up?
I want you to make me a website.
I don't know how to make a website.
Well, I'll tell you how to make it.
And then if anything breaks on it,
you'll be there to help me fix it 24-7.
How's that sound?
That's a huge amount of pressure, Travis.
I don't think I can.
Well, I need you to use some beautiful templates
and I need help showcasing my work
and selling products and services of all kinds.
And I assume you offer analytics
that help me grow in real time?
I can barely do the website.
What fucking good are you then?
I'm just gonna use Squarespace.
You can get, hey,
you can both get out of here.
From now on, I got two brothers, DoorDash and Squarespace.
That's it.
Those are the only brothers I answer to
and I look forward to spending Christmas with them.
Wow, this is so combative.
Hey Squarespace, I love you.
We're blood now.
Thank you for helping me promote my physical online business.
Thank you for having everything optimized for mobile
right out of the box.
Thank you for free and secure hosting
and nothing to patch or upgrade ever.
You've always been there for me
unlike my two lazy brothers
who will neither bring me food nor build me a website.
So everyone else leave your friends and family behind
and join the family Squarespace with open arms.
Go to squarespace.com slash my brother for a free trial.
When you're ready to launch,
use the offer code my brother to save 10%
off your first purchase of a website or domain.
Squarespace, all the family you'll ever need.
It says that.
It says only us, no one else or else we'll know
and it's over.
It says turn over all your physical belongings
to Squarespace.
We're all the family you'll ever need.
Wild that it says that.
It does.
I don't think that's good.
I mean, listen, from my experience so far,
it's all the family I need.
Okay.
Hi, my name is Graham Clark
and I'm one half of the podcast stop podcasting yourself,
a show that we've recorded for many, many years.
And at the moment, instead of being in person,
we're recording remotely and you wouldn't even notice.
You don't even notice the lag.
That's right, Graham.
And the great thing about this, go ahead.
No, you go ahead.
Okay.
Okay, go ahead.
And you can listen to us every week on MaximumFun.org.
Or wherever you get your podcasts.
Your podcasts.
Can I do another Yahoo that was sent in by a lot of people?
Give me that big, dirty, stinky Yahoo.
Jesus.
This one was sent in by several people.
Like I said, it's an anonymous Yahoo Answers user
who I'm going to call Tammy.
Tammy asks, is it impolite not to open the window
when a crow who used to be my friend knocks on it?
Wait, I used to be friends with a crow in my street.
He comes to my window for snacks
and has sometimes brought me cool rocks.
But last week he saw me walk my dog and hacked at him.
My dog was so scared.
I'm extremely mad at the crow now and can't even look at him.
He doesn't get snacks anymore.
But now he started to knock on my window.
I feel so impolite not opening, but I am still angry.
Should I maybe wait until he is sorry
or apologizes in some way?
Well, neither of those are going to happen.
Yeah, I will tell you, Griffin, for a second there,
I thought what the question asker meant was,
this is my friend.
He died and is now a crow.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah, and he keeps knocking on my window.
Let me tell you this, Tammy.
Your mistake here was you forgot that at the end of the day,
no matter how many shiny stones or snacks
you exchange with this crow, it's still a crow.
And crows is going to hack at dogs, right?
This is kind of like the frog and the scorpion
where the scorpion's like, hey, give me a ride.
And the frog's like, no way, dude, you're a scorpion.
And he's like, nah, it's cool.
If I kill you, I'll die too.
And then he does kill him and he dies too.
And he's like, you forgot I was a scorpion.
Wow.
Except this is like the Tammy and the crow
where Tammy was like, hey, be my buddy.
And the crow's like, you absolutely got it.
Also, I'm going to peck your fingers.
And you're like, oh, a crow?
It's like, yeah, I'm a fucking crow, dude.
I don't know what to tell you.
Here's a shiny pebble or whatever the fuck.
Did you read, there's an internet story,
one of those like, nature is beautiful.
Where it was like this crow
that like befriended a family or something.
And then one day the family like,
dropped their camera lens cap off of like, a thing.
And they're like, oh no.
And then like, the next day,
the crow had brought it back to them.
And that's fucking great, man.
That's beautiful.
Tell me another one, Pawpaw.
That crow was really there for them.
Hey, Pawpaw, will you tell me one about the war?
Well, one time I was down at Foxhole,
really missing my sweetie.
And when I woke up the next morning,
a crow had flown my girlfriend over to Germany.
Same crow?
Yeah, and we made love while the crow watched.
That was the deal.
That was kind of the one stipulation.
So it's like, War Crow, the 2011 movie.
Did you guys ever see War Crow?
And my girlfriend got pregnant
and we named the baby the crow.
Did you guys ever see War Crow by Steven Spielberg?
The movie where that wartime couple
made love in front of a crow?
It had an extended 49-minute long
Foxhole-based sex scene,
while it was actually a grackle that they cast.
A stunt grackle.
Just watched the whole thing
and is, I guess, inspired a generation?
Yep.
I have seen some crows around my place lately.
I was driving home a couple weeks ago
and there was like 20 crows lined on the road
blocking my return to my home.
You know what that means?
That was extreme.
Do you?
Yeah.
Gonna be a long, cold summer.
Long, cold summer.
But the thing I want to say about crows
is when you see a crow in real life,
it doesn't look like they should be that big.
They're extremely big.
And when you see a crow, it's kind of like,
whoa, are you sure?
Yeah, the first time I saw a crow was in War Crow
and I wasn't expecting them to have four legs
and big, meaty haunches and a very long head.
Is War Crow especially big
or is it just he's got a lot of heart?
He's got a lot of heart.
Well, it's both.
It's both.
He's very large and he cares a great deal.
And well, no, his physical heart is far too big
and that's why he dies in the movie.
But then they make an apartment out of his heart
like at the end of James and the Giant Peach.
I haven't seen War Horse.
And what's this?
That's a sequel.
Oh, okay.
Sequel.
I haven't seen War Horse,
but I assume from the title,
it means it's the first and only horse used in war.
And that must have been very disconcerting
for everybody on the battlefield
the first time that a horse entered.
Get that thing the fuck out of here.
Wait, what do we do with this?
Can we throw it?
What are you supposed to do with that?
I'm afraid I'm trying to shoot humans.
I'm gonna hit a beautiful horse.
To be fair, I was on the other side.
If I was on the other side, right?
If I was the enemy and suddenly I just saw
a horse walking towards me,
I would lower my gun and be like,
hey now, what's up?
But then that horse pulls out a gun,
shoots the man.
Dang it.
I'm like, oh shit.
I feel like using a War Horse
is an abuse of the beautiful relationship
between a human and a horse.
Sure.
They trust you implicitly.
Your souls are intertwined.
You shouldn't be leading them in battle
against other humans because they will,
but they're gonna be up that night like,
what's going on?
Unless.
It's reciprocated.
If there's a war between horses,
the horse gets to bring us.
The sequel to War Horse is Horse War.
Yes, Horse War is the sequel.
And the horse is like,
I will take you to kill these men,
but you must promise me that when my people go to war,
you will be there.
I will be riding your back at that time.
I will ride you into battle, Jeff.
This is my steed, Jeff.
Whatever you say, Butter Maiden.
You got it.
All right.
Jeff, it's the Butter Maiden.
The time has come.
What?
Really?
Holy shit.
Yeah, dude.
The fracture between the Calgrani
and the Bilatush has gone too far.
There will be no peace.
You, Jeff.
Saddle up, Jeff.
Do you have the long stick of Far Death?
My gun?
Yeah, we still-
Yes.
Yeah, I still have that.
Bring it.
I've seen what it does.
I bet it will be effective on horse flesh.
Now put on the saddle, Jeff.
Enlist your foals.
No, not on me.
Do your foals.
No.
We've covered that Butter Maiden will be riding Jeff.
Obviously.
That's established canon at this point.
Don't make horses go to war.
I love you.
Welcome to Munch Squad's podcast,
the podcast profiling the latest and greatest brand eating.
We have already talked about the Jelly Belly treasure hunt
that has nothing to do with Jelly Belly.
And now it's time for a celebrate good times.
Come on.
Sorry, a what?
It's a celebration.
Okay, wait, can I guess?
He just chose Crab Shack?
No, sir.
Planners unveils a collaboration to celebrate baby nuts.
That's what they went with, baby nut?
Yeah, bud.
So Mr. Peanut didn't die as he was supposed to,
but at the same time, Mr. Peanut apparently has had a child
this whole time named Baby Nut,
but Baby Nut turned 21 and is now Peanut Jr.
Wait, are you with me so far?
Absolutely not.
Okay.
Is this like one of those timelines things
where like one comic book series is about Wolverine,
but one is about like Logan before he became a Wolverine
and one is about like Weapon X or these all happening?
It's all happening at the same time.
Mr. Peanut had a son.
The son was named Baby Nut.
The son turned 21 and became Peanut Jr.
He's got Jack disease.
No, he's 21 years old.
So wait, Mr. Peanut had this son 21 years ago
and this is just the first time we're hearing about him?
Was he born out?
Have you been paying that close of attention to Mr. Peanut?
Like in every ad if he's like,
and also I have a son anyway, eat peanuts.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
I will say that this actually makes sense.
That one time I was watching it was like,
we got all kinds of nuts and it makes sense.
And then he opens the letter and he reads it
and he kind of crumbles it up and he's like,
I'm not ready to accept this responsibility.
And now I understand what that was in reference to.
If this Munch Squad were a loading screen,
it would be at 3% progress.
I must move on.
Mr. Peanut has a son.
His name was Baby Nut.
He turned 21 and became Peanut Junior.
Okay, yeah.
To celebrate this,
planners today unveiled a limited edition run
of beer flavored peanuts co-branded with Natural Light
as part of a marketing stunt
surrounding the rapidly aging spokes nut.
Planners and Natural Light beer flavored peanuts.
Oh, hey, press release.
You can't just throw in a term like rapidly aging
and not make me think of like a Star Trek episode
or a Doctor Who episode.
Like, listen, he'll be dead within the week.
Let him have this.
So the Natural, I don't want to be classist,
but Natural Light isn't the best tasting liquid.
But there's other liquids that I think are superior in taste.
In fact, other liquids in the beer family.
In fact, other liquids in the cost-effective,
low-cost beer family that tastes maybe even
just a little bit better than old Natty Light.
So strange bedfellows.
Perhaps a Miller High Life.
It is the Champagne of beers.
I would take that.
Or perhaps a PBR, well-known hipster brand.
Yeah.
Justin, what else?
I'm trying to piece this all together,
but planners, so Baby Nut.
Baby Nut.
So, okay.
All right.
I'm trying to piece this together.
Justin, you've got a lot of string tied up on this board here
with a lot of pictures going between it.
Please explain.
Right.
Okay.
So remember when Mr. Peanut died?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Worst day of my fucking life.
So at that time, Baby Nut is what?
More from the corpse of Mr. Peanut?
As I understand it?
Yeah, yeah.
Totally.
I didn't want to correct you.
Death of Superman, then there was Superboy,
and the Last Crooked Don, and then I believe Steel
was in there as well, and yeah, of course.
So he was Baby Nut is what formed from the husk of Mr. Peanut.
Sorry?
Like a phoenix.
Okay, sure.
That's fine.
But he formed from the husk of Mr. Peanut,
and then he is transmogrifying now into Peanut Jr.
Does that make sense?
Huh.
You can keep saying it.
This is, I think, about the fifth time
that you've tried to walk us through the timeline of Baby Nut.
So here's the ad.
Give me 20 seconds.
Just listen to this.
Don't say anything.
I.D.?
Yes, sir.
Wait, so you're telling me you fell off a cliff,
came back to life as a baby, and now you're 21?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's been a weird year.
So Mr. Peanut Jr., he's now 21, and because of that,
they're making beer nuts that are flavored like the,
you understand?
Yes.
Yeah, but if I-
And it's to celebrate people who miss their birthdays due to COVID.
That's what this says here.
That's super, read the exact quote.
That sounds super nice.
This comes after Baby Nut, who was introduced in February
during Planner's controversial Super Bowl ad,
morphed into Peanut Jr. earlier this month
as a way to connect with consumers whose birthdays have gone by
with little to no fanfare due to COVID-19 quarantine measures.
That's so sweet.
That's really nice of them.
Can I also just pull back your curtain there a little bit?
Because what they're basically saying is like,
we committed to this like Baby Peanut bit
and weren't going anywhere with it.
So as soon as we saw the slimmest off ramp, we took it.
Right, we took it.
Now it's Peanut Jr.
And can I also say just after that ad you played it,
it does kind of sound like Peanut Jr. is using a fake ID.
It's very suspicious, yeah.
The read on it is definitely like,
huh, yeah, it's been a weird year.
Can I have my beer now, please, sir?
Please.
At the time when he morphed, the quote was this,
Peanut Jr. still has a lot to learn,
like what his favorite go-to drink is,
as he continues to grow up to become a peanut of the people.
Jesus.
And apparently, that was the quote given at that point, right?
But now we know what his favorite drink is,
and it's apparently Natty Light.
Yeah.
Which actually tracks.
I mean, it tracks, except for the fact
that he probably inherited the peanut planter's fortune.
Yeah.
And does not need to drink Natty Light.
Oh, it's ironic.
Maybe that's what's happening.
Okay, I would have gone with a Bud Light Lime-A-Rita,
but that would just be my guess for what baby junior Mr. Peanut is into.
So now we're going to go a little bit deeper.
See, Natural Light is an economy beer brand
owned by Anheuser-Busch InBev,
which, like planter's owner Kraft Heinz,
has ties to Brazilian investment firm 3G Capital.
Wait a minute.
This goes all the way to the top.
It goes all the way to the top, baby.
5G isn't causing COVID,
but 3G is causing Natural Light flavored plant's peanuts.
It goes all the way to the top, and you can buy these nuts.
It just says here, I tried to click the link,
it just says you can buy these nuts if you're a dirt bag, it says.
So I guess if you're a dirt bag, you should be able to find them.
As is so often the case with MunchSquad,
now I want to try it.
I didn't before.
Nothing goes together.
This is from Mike,
executive creative director at Fainter Media,
which has engineered a lot of evil in the past few years.
Nothing goes together like beer and nuts.
We were thrilled to work with Natural Light
to make the union official with beer flavored peanuts.
Okay, but it's not like when Cheez-It and House Wine partnered,
they didn't make wine flavored Cheez-Its.
That would be actually very good.
Pretty cool.
I think I would actually really like that.
I have had a peanut butter stout before.
I have had what I would call nut flavored beer.
Okay, do you like it?
I am not at all interested.
It's a weird flex, but okay.
I'm just saying I'm not at all.
If someone said,
do you want me to soak these peanuts in beer before you eat them?
That's probably not.
I would say that sounds disgusting.
I'd assume the nuts are not soggy and wet, Travis.
And I'd hope not, but what do you picture?
It's got beer dust on it?
Just like a dusting of beer flavor.
Like a flavor of beer.
You know how flavoring works.
Probably made with beaver anus.
Why did you say that?
Why would you say that?
Oh, they use beaver like anus like juices
in a lot of fake flavorings.
That's so gross, Travis, why do you do that?
I don't do it.
You don't do it.
That is a real thing.
Now everyone listen to the sound of,
this is for your ASMR triggers,
the sound of my brother googling beaver anus.
I'm doing it quietly on my phone, thank you very much.
Oh, huh.
Hey, cool.
Yeah, I guess so.
So I guess anything that you eat that has flavor in it,
you're doing a little, you're just eating ass.
You thought I was lying, didn't you?
You thought I was wrong.
I don't know what I thought.
All right.
Wow, yeah, look at that.
Why?
Why, is it good?
Who discovered this?
That's what I need to know.
Who's like, that's actually, I wanted to eat,
I said I would eat the entire beaver on a dare,
but I'm enjoying the ass more than I thought I would.
I just happened to have on my desk
that I've been snacking on a little bit,
some jelly beans.
Those are going right in the fucking garbage can.
Is beaver anus in jelly bellies?
It's in Haribo.
I think I'm okay.
Okay.
Oh, jelly beans have a shellac on them
that is made from the secretions of a bug.
Okay.
A bee, a beeswax?
No.
If you see an ingredient titled confectioner's glaze,
see if that's on your jelly beans.
It's in there, yeah, they do.
I mean, I'd rather eat bugs than eat out a beaver's butt.
I don't know them.
You know what I mean?
How come it's just beavers?
How come God gave the beaver the most flavorful butt glands?
I don't know.
Here we are.
Well, in this truth all together.
This is the worst episode that we've put out so far.
Just because of the truths contained within?
I mean, I think all around,
I don't think there's anything redemptive
about what happened before this.
Like everything we said in the episode
doesn't balance out the whole beaver butt thing.
No, God no, Christ no.
No, I mean, we would have to give out
the winning lotto ticket numbers or something.
Okay, this is the thing.
There's a food dye in Nerds
that's made from crushed and boiled beetles.
Yeah.
Sure.
All right.
So we're all fucking nasty, nasty Timon and Pumbaa.
Let's end it, the show and episode.
Now to be fair, Griffin, you have numerous times said
that Timon and Pumbaa made you want to eat those beetles.
You want to eat those bugs.
Yeah, well, now you've got the opportunity, thanks to Nerds.
But I want to be able to give consent to Timon and Pumbaa
before I eat the bugs.
I don't want them tricking me.
Yeah, not like, yeah.
You gotta watch this, too.
Try this, Simba.
It's beaver ass.
It's the one thing we love out here on the savanna.
Beaver ass.
Hakuna my ass.
Delicious.
Uh, I think I'm going to go back and deal with Scar.
No, he won't have you anymore.
You've been sullied.
You better eat this.
He'll know you ate the ass.
He'll know.
If you go back, we're going to tell everybody
you ate the ass and loved it.
Beaver ass pancakes.
Beaver ass tortillas.
Beaver ass tacos.
We got everything.
Something smells like vanilla ice cream,
which almost universally contains beaver ass.
It's me, Scar.
I ate the beaver ass.
Mufasa's like, don't eat the beaver ass.
I thought I told you.
What, ghost dad?
I've missed you so much.
You come back to talk to me.
I told you to never eat beaver ass.
I reject you.
I can no longer recognize you as my heir.
Just want back to say I'm disappointed.
Anyway, bye.
Hi, it's me, the beaver.
I'm up here with your dad,
and I can't believe you ate my ass.
I'm dead and you ate my ass.
The king.
You're no king.
That's what Rafiki is wiping on him, by the way,
just in case anyone was wondering.
It's a mixture of beetles and beaver ass.
You're nasty.
Go out into the world.
This is Scar's entire plan,
is to trick Simba into eating beaver ass
and then tell everybody,
well, it looks like you've beaten me,
but before I surrender,
just one more thing.
Just one more thing.
Yes, I told all the giraffes
that you ate beaver ass and also geese.
They know now,
and the beavers were not thrilled.
Let me tell you.
Well, some of them were,
but you don't know how they are.
Some of them are extremely flexible
on a moral spectrum.
Thank you for listening
to what is presumably not been canceled, a podcast by us,
the McElroy brothers called My Brother, My Brother, Me.
We hope you have enjoyed your time with us
as we continue to soldier on
through this absolutely bizarre period in our planet.
We wrote a book about how to podcast.
It is like a guide that will actually
walk you through step by step,
but we wrote it, so it's also kind of funny.
I think you'll like reading it.
Hey, I'll say it.
You will like reading it.
You can pre-order it at McElroyPodcastBook.com.
What are you waiting for?
Go do that.
Let's see, what else?
Thank you to John Roderick in the Long Winters
for the use of our theme song
as a departure off the album,
Putting the Days to Bed.
You can find that on the internet
and a bunch of different places, I bet.
And thanks to Maximum Fun for having us on the network.
Go to MaximumFun.org,
check out all the great shows there,
shows like Stop Podcasting Yourself.
And Heat Rocks, and a whole bunch more.
All at MaximumFun.org.
Also, we got some good new merch up
there at the McElroyMerch.com store,
including some bee pins that represent the three of us
and our dad as a horrible bee monster.
So make sure you check that out.
Don't forget to get registered to vote
and vote early.
And make sure you do some research on local elections
because it starts local, then moves up the chain.
Plus there's a lot of Senate seats up for grabs
and then vote for Joe Biden.
Thank you for being here.
We hope you're hanging in there doing okay.
Don't forget artists.
I will use the teeth.
Teeth owner, get at us.
This final Yahoo.
We're not narcs, this isn't a sting.
No, it would be a very weird roundabout sting if it was.
This one was sent in by the wizard Emma Cant.
Thank you Emma, it's Yahoo Answers user.
Another anonymous one,
stop being so fucking scared and do and stand up for yourself
for once.
Billup asks,
does anyone really believe it's a coincidence
that the two surviving beetles are the circumcised one?
I could not have for money told you where that was going.
My name is Justin.
Hi Travis, I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been My Brother, My Brother,
may kiss your dad's square in the lips.
Hey girls, do you wanna just say that I wanna?