The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello, everybody, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother, Me, and the Advice Show from the
Modern Era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I'm your middlest brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother and 30 under 30 media luminary, Griffin McElroy.
Oh, I'm sorry. I can't, I can't contain myself anymore hearing that amazing annunciation and
that diction. It's because, you know, you got the lips. There's no tip of the tongue.
There's no Cheetos residue in there blocking the sound waves.
The teeth. It's pick watch 2019. Had the water pick for a little over two weeks or so
sitting in the Amazon box and I looked at it every day and said, not yet, not yet, not yet.
But I had about 10 minutes to kill just before recording and I got in there and I just super
soaked the heck out of it. I had a lot of trepidation the first time I used my water
pick. I was fairly sure that there was, there's definitely a pressure at which you know you're
gonna rip it up in there and you're just sticking this tube in your mouth and going for it.
Yeah, I'm just worried that if I ever used one I would accidentally set it to sand blaster.
Yeah.
And it would just tear both the enamel and then everything underneath the enamel,
just straight out of my mouth.
But I gotta say refreshing other than the horrible pain of pressure washing my inside skin.
Uh-huh.
I gotta say the results, folks, I saw a little bit of tastation come out of there.
Yeah, and those haven't even been around since like 1999.
Do you think if we mentioned tastation's enough,
eventually the company will just give us the IP?
I don't think it exists. Wait, who owned it? Is that Nestle?
That's Hershey's if memory serves.
Hershey's.
Yes. But anyway, I used the water pick today and my congressional medal of honor has yet
to appear and I'm confused about that.
That's strange.
Or at least a big boy sticker.
Griffin, I do need to know when you said the pain in your mouth,
the blasting your inside skin.
Blasting it.
Can you compare that? I've never used a water pick.
Could you compare that level of pain to something for me?
Have you ever used one of those massage chairs at the airport
that have like the balls in it that go in?
Imagine just putting your teeth right into one of those somehow,
like sort of sitting on it teeth first
and just sort of get over the hygiene issues associated with that.
But, you know, physically that's sort of the feel that we're talking about.
I don't care for that.
And then the water, there's a sort of, you know, manners issue
of what you do with the water as it's being blasted in.
You don't want anybody to see the unsightly side of you,
you know, getting on in there and just dribbling water out of your mouth
like some sort of sea monster.
So do you swallow it all?
The answer is yes and it's bad.
Now, I just assumed that as you did it,
you would kind of keep your mouth open
and it would just be like pouring from you
like a character in a sci-fi show that was drowning on dry land.
Sure, like a human water feature situation.
Yeah.
Yeah, but folks-
You close your mouth tight around it, it'll blast out your nose
and then it'll do a number on the sizes.
But I have so much air moving between my-
The gaps between my teeth are so big
and I'd never appreciated it.
The space between.
Yeah, there's a little-
The gap between.
Let him keep going.
I want to.
That's all the words I know.
That's all the words he knows
because it's the only words in the song.
I used my water pick today.
Let's not lose the point of this.
We can make jokes, but I used my water pick today.
Where is that?
We need a combo t-shirt,
I used my water pick today and hey, I might go eat some charcuterie later.
What's up?
Just a two.
And then once the charcuterie is trapped in my teeth,
I'll use the water pick again in a never ending cycle until one day I die.
My favorite part is that the sort of relationship I've built
and how it's evolved with my dentist,
who at my first cleaning was like,
oh my God, because it had been a while since my last confession.
And then every sort of six months or so, he would be like,
wow, you really need to floss.
And he'd be like, you should really be flossing
or at the very least go get a water pick.
And then like on my last appointment, he was like,
I know you're not going to floss.
I give up, go buy a water pick.
And then I used it two weeks later.
Are you sort of hesitant to use the teeth again?
You kind of hate to because it's like...
I'll be honest, yeah, a little bit.
And I'm trying, yeah.
So I'm trying to figure out if there's other holes I can get the food in.
If there's other sort of stuff I can do.
Yes, and other places to put the food.
There's gotta be other places I can get the food in.
And I know the first thing you're gonna laugh and joke about
for this scuzzy podcast is my ass.
I would never.
I was going to say you could freeze dry it,
crush it up, snort it right up your nose.
That's now we're going somewhere with that.
Yeah, I'm trying to think outside the bun, Griffin.
I'm not just gonna say ass.
Oh, you can put it up your, oh, put the food over your ass.
Just eat like a pickle up your butt.
I would never say that.
But if you wanted to nose-boof some frozen shark udder-y,
then I don't think there's a law against that.
I have an exciting new feature for the podcast
that I'd like to pivot seamlessly into.
Before, because Griffin mentioned Taste Stations.
Half an hour ago.
My mind has been on Taste Stations.
And this feature, I think I'm gonna call it Where Is It Now?
And this is a feature where people on the internet
talk about a thing that they miss very dearly
and we can all share in that with them
and be there and bond with them.
And this is a thread from the Straight Dope.
Are you guys down with this? Are you feeling this right now?
Are you asking us or is this part of the comment?
Yes, I'm asking you.
Okay, yes, let's go.
Are we good? Yes.
Travis, verbal confirmation.
This is from the Straight Dope.
Wolfmeister.
February 27th.
Holy fucking shit.
Today, the day we're recording this,
exactly the day 15 years ago.
2004.
Granted, this is not the most pressing matter of the day,
but I'm sure it's important to some people.
I visited the Hershey's website in 2004,
and they don't even list it as one of their products.
On message boards, it is rumored to have been discontinued.
Of course, the only message board that matters
is the Straight Dope message board.
So, are Hershey's Taste Stations discontinued?
I find it hard to believe these things are popular.
IMHO, these are far better than Werther's,
which are incredibly overrated.
Get them fucked up.
If Taste Stations have been discontinued,
is there anything similar out there?
Werther's.
And you know what I think of Werther's.
They say it right here, you know what I think of Werther's.
And then, a day later, they say,
well, there's no responses, okay?
A day later, well, I see my posting has gone from
relative obscurity to total oblivion.
Some of the dopers here must have a sweet tooth?
Isn't anyone else a fan of these candies?
Free Range Maniac follows up,
I'm sure I've seen them up here.
I work in a large chain drugstore,
so I'll have a look and see if I'm right.
Maybe they just discontinued them in the States?
I know you have candy and chocolate
we never see in Canada.
Paul in Qatar says, what were they?
Wolfmeister, the original Paul,
Taste Stations are, perhaps were,
a great tasting hard candy,
sold in bags of about one pound.
They came in a lot of flavors,
butterscotch, caramel, and so on.
No, stop, that was it.
There's butterscotch, chocolate, and caramel.
So, there's not a so on, there's three total.
To me, and a lot of other people,
they were the greatest tasting candy ever made.
Wait, they weren't, I'm sorry,
there wasn't like a strawberry and cream one?
What am I thinking of?
There was like a hard candy that was like a swirl.
Ooh, yeah, I know what you're talking about,
but I don't know.
Free Range Maniac says, yeah, I checked today,
they're being discontinued.
Maybe they're more popular in Canada?
That was February 28th, 2004.
October 24th, 2012.
Anno Domini, 2012.
Chuckles14901 is coughing.
The dust, what's this old post?
Look, I could just make it out.
Some of the inscriptions here.
It's about taste stations.
I gotta get my two cents on these.
Hold on a second.
Tap, tap, tap.
There are few candies as delicious as the taste stations.
The mint was smooth and refreshing.
The caramel is tasty.
But there's only one candy that ever made chocolate.
Taste stations.
Wow.
No one has made such a delicious candy as the chocolate,
which tastes like dark chocolate or fudge.
It is wondrous.
My heart is breaking.
I would love it if I could find a place that still sells them
for shipment to the States.
I would pay $10 a bag of mint and chocolate taste stations
shipping and handling not included.
Wow.
So you can reach through time and find taste stations.
This can will pay you $10 for a bag,
just not going to cover the shipping and handling.
Justin, this is see a need, fill a need kind of deal.
I'm saying maybe the next McRoy endeavor isn't a podcast,
isn't a TV show, isn't a graphic novel.
Bootleg taste stations.
It's bootleg taste stations.
If we're making 10 bucks a pound on these things,
now this is breaking bad too.
We got that crunchy brown.
We get some people to build some compartments
into their fenders on their old jalopies,
have them drive them down.
Maybe we make them up in Canada
and then they drive them down to the States.
We sell them there and then we fly the money down to,
I don't know, Cuba maybe, and we buy more ingredients there
and the cycle continues.
Taste stations money, baby.
That was a lot of taste stations talk.
Bring it back.
But I think in the meantime, we should do a question.
I love that, Griffin.
You read my mind basically.
I was on a three hour drive this morning when I got hungry.
I spotted a sign on the highway for a hotel chain
that I knew had free breakfast.
I like whatever you're doing here, Justin.
This is a very like noir kind of reading you're doing.
I was on a three hour drive.
I think it's appropriate.
I didn't know that going in, but I feel good about it.
It really works.
Wanting to save a few dollars, I stopped at the hotel
and walked into the lobby pretending I was a guest.
I went straight to the breakfast bar
and helped myself to biscuits.
Oh my God.
And gravy.
I don't know if it was paranoia or if it was legitimate,
but as I was eating, I got the feeling the hotel staff knew
I wasn't supposed to be there.
Unlikely.
I was the only person in the breakfast area.
After seeing three of the hotel staff talk quietly
to each other and look my way,
I gulped down what was left of my orange juice
and made a run for it.
I went out the hotel side of the door
as to avoid walking by the lobby,
and thus the staff turns out the side door
led directly to the outdoor pool.
Keep reading.
There is a fence surrounding the pool
that is too high to jump.
And because I'm not a guest at the hotel,
I don't have a key to get back in
and look for another exit.
I'm stuck. Help.
What do I do?
That's from being caught stealing in Baton Rouge
and you deserve whatever you have received here.
I've got a great suggestion.
Go to jail.
Go to jail for the crime you did.
Go to... You fucked up this whole thing!
You couldn't at least go to the bathroom for like an hour
and then walk in from the bathroom and go eat.
The reason they know that you're there,
that you're not a guest at the hotel,
is because you walked in from out...
They saw you park your car, come into the hotel,
and eat their pancakes,
and then drink your juice really fast
as you looked around at them nervously
and then sprinted out the side door
to just go take a fever dip.
You fucked up every step of this heist
and you need to go to jail for it
and while you're there you can reflect
on how to do better heists.
You know where they got a lot of free breakfast?
Jail. Jail at it.
All the free meals.
One time when mom and dad were visiting Norman, Oklahoma
where I went to college, Boomer Center,
they were like,
yeah, you and your friends come over.
I think Brent went with me and they said,
and we'll get breakfast.
We went back to the hotel to meet them.
They just took us over to the continental breakfast
there at the hotel.
I'm pretty sure that isn't how it worked.
I did eat it. I was very hungry.
I was in college.
I still feel tricked by dad
and by extension mom
saying, we'll get you breakfast.
By which I mean, Best Western will get you breakfast.
Eat up.
They got it to you. You had it.
That's like saying, hey, do you want to go get lunch?
Cool. Let's break into my neighbor's house
and I'll see if they have any sandwiches.
Not at all like that.
That one's breaking and entering.
The other one is a bending, though not a breaking of policy.
It's a bending and entering.
If you were going to kick in the doors of this hotel,
if you were going to plant a C4 charge
in the front door of this hotel
and smash and grab some pancakes,
I'm not against.
You know me.
If you're trying to save a buck with a little harmless steal,
I'm all for it. I love it.
But you would have been better served
planting a demolition charge in the front door of the hotel,
throwing in a smoke grenade,
running in, grabbing four muffins
and running out.
You did a bad, bad, bad job.
Especially once you introduced that the food you ate
was biscuits and gravy.
If you grabbed an individual container
of Lucky Charms or you grabbed
a frozen Danish
that had been thawed out, that's fine.
Someone made those biscuits and gravy.
Absolutely.
You know what's wild about it, Travis?
Thank you.
There's something about it that's been bothering me,
and it's only now occurred to me.
The fact that you sat down...
You motherfucker!
You didn't just want to steal.
You wanted to sit there and fucking relish it.
I've never been to a continental breakfast
where you could not have swooped
a banana, some yogurt,
a Danish,
some, I don't know,
even a mouthful of bacon.
I mean, whatever.
Whatever it is, you could have been
in and out before they even registered
your presence.
But no, you wanted to sit down and really enjoy
the ambiance
of the Holiday Inn Express.
And as long as we're just doubling down
on being angry at you,
our listener, the last sentence here
about, it turns out the side door...
I'm assuming is now a skeleton
in the backyard of the Holiday Inn.
The side door leads to the outdoor pool.
There's a fence too high to jump,
and I do not have the key to look for another exit.
I feel like I'm playing fucking Zork.
I don't know what else is there.
I can't send in my answer by mail.
Do you have a holocaust cloak?
Do you have a wheelbarrow?
Or a deck chair?
Something that could build an escape plan here.
Let's do a yahoo.
I'm so mad.
I'm not done.
We don't often ask for follow-ups,
but I would like a follow-up,
where we're told beat by beat
how the conversation of you offering to reimburse them
for the biscuits and gravy went.
Like, excuse me, what are you doing out here?
Uh, yes.
I stole your breakfast.
Okay, cool.
You're gonna have to rent a room now
to justify eating our breakfast.
How about I...
Okay, let's play a game.
I don't want...
Let's send jokes out of the room.
This is a skill testing puzzle for you.
You are gonna steal the breakfast.
You're not a guest at the hotel,
but you have to talk to the staff first
before you can steal breakfast.
What is the lie you're gonna make up?
You can't say you're a guest there.
Are you ready? This is what I would do.
I'm going to be checking in later,
but I know that check-in isn't until three o'clock.
Would it be all right if I went ahead
and grabbed something from the breakfast board?
If I smash and grabbed something...
I didn't mean to say smash and grab.
Can I break and enter into your breakfast place
and have the food?
I promise I will get you back later at three
when I definitely stay here.
Here's my ID.
This is a Pokemon card.
Rubble rubble!
My pockets are full of yogurt.
You missed it.
My dad was robbing you fucking blind
of Danish while you were talking to me.
All this trick in the book.
Yeah, it's rough.
How about that Yahoo now?
Yeah, I guess.
Here's one that was sent in by Emma Kant.
Thank you, Emma.
It's Yahoo Answers user Round Square who asks...
Okay, come on.
How do I make other dogs respect my dog?
My dog lacks confidence
and is clearly not an alpha male.
He acts submissive towards other dogs
and tired of defending him all the time.
How do I teach him to defend himself
so he won't be bullied anymore?
Oh, okay.
The question I'm asking probably means
physically defending him,
not like when your dog walks away saying,
hey guys, he's doing his best.
Hey, can we all just be cool with Ralph?
How do I make other dogs respect my dog
who I have to defend with my human abilities?
The obvious answer is
you're gonna dress up like a dog
and then when your dog comes around,
you're all scared of that dog
and be like, oh, I wouldn't mess with that dog.
Like, you guys see this guy over here?
Oh, he's rough.
And then the other dogs will be like,
are you the actual Scooby-Doo?
And you're like, um, yes.
And then you let your dog kick your own ass.
He's my cousin.
Scooby-Doo's my cousin
and I got a dad that works at Nintendo.
That dog just beat up Scooby-Doo's cousin
and Jim Tendo's son.
This new dog is cool as hell, guys.
His cousin is Scooby-Doo
and his dad works at Nintendo?
Why is that other dog picking on him?
Hey, jerk, leave Scooby-Doo's cousin alone.
Back off of our new best friend,
Scooby-Doo's cousin. We respect him.
Oh, I was just about to show you guys
my four skateboards,
but it looks like I can get my ass kicked
by this big cool dog.
So that's backfired.
Oh, my plan.
Oh, that's the one.
No, that's working as intended
because the cool dog is your dog.
How did you guys lose the plot that fast?
No, but I'm just saying everybody loves Scooby-Doo's cousin.
They don't want to see him beat up.
That is the fiction that develops
and everybody likes the new giant dog,
the new man-sized dog so much.
Well, then you show up the next day
and you're horribly injured
and cool dog, your dog,
has taken care of you
and is nursing you back to health.
You know what? I like that cool dog.
He brings Scooby-Doo's Nintendo cousin around.
We hunked out our differences.
Yeah, we figured it out together.
Maybe we go the other way then
and opposite of my plan
and you dress your dog up like a human
and then teach him to walk on two legs
and then you bring him around.
All dogs, I think, instantly have
some form of respect for a human.
I think that's a good part.
And then you get him a fake ID
that's old enough to buy beer
and then the other dogs are going to be so fucking stoked.
Yeah.
I don't know of a dog old enough to buy beer.
I don't think there's ever been a 21-year-old dog.
That's the dog dream.
Every dog is like,
if one of us can just make it to 21,
we're going to fucking party.
I told you to quit smoking, Jerry.
No, I mean, for a dog, that is three.
So a three-year-old dog can stumble
into a super America and say,
let me get that high life, please.
Yeah, I mean,
you got to get your dog jacked.
You got to get your dog fucking diesel.
Yolked huge.
And I don't know how you do that.
I don't know how you do that.
I don't know if there's dog gyms.
I know you can take them somewhere
to train them for Westminster and all that.
But I don't know how you get them.
There's no Ninja Warrior gyms for dogs, I don't think.
Can dogs build muscle?
I was a dog trainer for a while
and I don't know the answer to this question.
Can dogs develop new muscle?
And I'm terrified of this.
I mean, if you crank them full of pure whey
and get them, you know,
pulling tires, doing some CrossFit,
five, you know,
seven hours, five days a week,
then they'll die.
So don't do that.
But there's got to be another way.
Oh, I know.
I freaking got it.
Oh.
You put the mask on them.
From the mask.
Okay, capital T, capital M, the mask.
Or the son of mask,
when the dog gets it on and gets really, really big.
I think the dog gets on both of them, Gervin.
So either one, you are correct.
Somebody stop him.
Somebody stop him, indeed.
He's peeing all over everyone.
And his pee is so hard, it's like a fire hose.
It's so powerful, it has killed Jamie Kennedy.
We are down one lead actor.
Please, somebody save Jamie Kennedy
from that dog.
Did that dog just piss so hard
that Jamie Kennedy died?
That's a cool dog.
Not another Kennedy.
That there is an elf.
Did you know that Jamie Kennedy is Robert Kennedy
and John F. Kennedy's little brother?
Did you know that?
I did not know that, Travis.
He's the last one.
I started a new job about five months ago,
and one of my coworkers and I started bonding
over mediocre romance novels.
I haven't read any since middle school
because they're so heteronormative.
Not hot.
But I remember a lot about them
because my mom still loves to read them all.
My coworker is in her 60s,
and she's just happy to have something to talk about,
so I didn't mention this.
Two months ago, she recommended this series
of 20-ish books that she has all of
and offered to lend me the first one.
I accepted with no intention of reading it
and returned it after a week saying it was really good.
Oh, no! God damn it!
This is before you fuck up!
This is the breaking into the hotel breakfast
of human social interchanges.
This is rough.
She came in the next day with the next three books.
Now I'm on book eight.
I have not read any of them.
How do I make her stop?
Oh, my God.
And that's from, oh, God, there's actually 26 books.
Folks, you have to tell us the names of these franchises.
Yeah.
And you have to reach out to us
before you fuck up.
But I will say at this point,
it seems like you've already got
a fine trajectory going.
You've made it through eight.
You've got 18 more to go.
If you could just keep up this, like,
take it away for a week, bring it back,
like, yeah, super hot.
I loved all the caressing.
And then, like, maybe you can make it through all 26
and come out the other side.
Half a year gone, yes,
but you're free now.
Free from this genie's cave.
Sorry, guys, I gotta go sign for a package.
Yep.
Oh, gotta sign for a package.
Nice.
This is how all great
romance novels start, right?
Yeah.
Somebody shows up at your door with probably
alcohol if you have to sign for it
and be over 21.
Griffin took out
the stylus and whipped
his stylus around,
signing on the tiny
electronic pad.
The letter spilled out of his
hand.
Like so much black jizz
first a G.
Black ink jizz.
Ink jizz first a G
and an R
and then an I and an F.
Could you spell your last name for me,
said the delivery person.
I'm about to climb it.
I'm totally gonna finish.
Although I am gonna deliver
an orgasm to you.
I'm delivering a plentiful
orgasm.
Did you need another orgasm? I could be back
tomorrow with another delivery.
Or go back and add your middle
name and I'll climax again.
Yeah.
What did I come back to?
What did you come back to indeed, Griffin?
Yeah.
How was the delivery?
I was signing for a package. Did you guys
already come up with like funny fake names
for the thing? Cause I usually do those.
But if you already did them, I don't want to double up.
Wait, sign for what? Sign for a package?
Wait, what?
We were making it like you were in a romance novel
where you were being romanced by the delivery person.
Oh, and I was gonna make love to the mail carrier.
Yeah, you said you had to sign for a package.
Okay, so yeah, I can tell you
what happened down there if you want.
Yeah, make it saucy.
His name was
Garbanzo.
Yeah, the sexiest name.
He was eight feet
long.
Whoa!
He handed me my
package. I said,
this looks like the
special shoes I ordered
for the boat. And then he said,
yes, yes it is.
You ordered
special orthopedic boat shoes?
I ordered boat shoes,
but not boat shoes,
but shoes for a boat. Do you know what I'm saying?
Anyway, Garbanzo.
Go into
extreme detail. I'm done with
pornography. Go into extreme detail about your boat shoes.
Are they shaped like boats?
Boat shoes. They breathe really well.
Anyway, Garbanzo said,
have fun on the boat. This is just chapter one.
You don't bork in chapter one.
Of course. I wish that they
would. Just get that out of the way. Chapter one of the
romance novel is where all
the sex happens. And then the next 27
chapters is just like a character doing
their taxes. Yeah, but the problem
is Garbanzo turned into
a swarm of bats. He flew away.
Classic. Sexy.
Yeah, now how can I resist?
The bats?
Yeah, let me get it
in that cloud of bats. Nothing
makes me heartier than Garbanzo.
The cloud swarm of bats.
That's
my favorite Night Vale character.
In case anybody's been
asking, my favorite Night Vale character is
Garbanzo, the swarm of bats.
It's also my favorite Magic Tavern
character. It's a
crossover
event. And
Gryphon has sex with him.
Not yet.
Magic Tavern already does
have a living swarm of bats
as a character. That's such a better
show than ours. Should we go to the
money zone at least? Yeah, they don't have
a money zone.
Go ahead and start.
I gotta feed the cats.
They're scratching at my door. Ooh.
Gotta feed the cats. Uh oh.
I wasn't here for the last time you did this,
but are we gonna be like,
does that make you horny, baby?
No, Gryphon.
Here's one about Casper.
Casper makes mattresses
and when you get on
them and you fall asleep,
then it's the best.
The best dreams.
You definitely get the best dreams.
Your bones
feel better and
get longer while you sleep
on them because of how it sort of
cradles your natural geometry.
Creates an environment
that is really, really
compatible with bone
elongation.
There is one thing. It's while you're
asleep, you're actually absorbed
within the mattress. Yes.
As soon as you wake up, you're popped right back on top.
So you're absolutely fine. You'll never know it.
You won't know it unless
the Goblin King comes up.
Yes. Now you've got an
issue, but Casper guarantees
90.9.9999
99% chance
the Goblin King will not attack.
No way. So
we have not done any of the things that they
want us to say yet. So here's a lot of that.
They got free shipping and returns
to the US and Canada.
It's no hassle if you're not satisfied.
You get to try it for 100 nights and then
if you don't like it, you just send it right back
and you banish the Goblin King right back to
once he came.
I think we all have Caspers at this
point. You've heard us talk about how comfortable they are,
but I'll say it again. It's pretty freaking
comfortable. You can get $50 towards
select mattresses by visiting
casper.com slash brother and using the promo code
brother at checkout, that's casper.com slash
brother and promo code
brother for $50 towards select mattresses.
Terms and conditions apply.
I'm starting to think that these businesses
listen to our show because they've stopped including
the phrase enter my brother in here.
Yes. They've wised up.
I would like to tell you about
MeUndies. Now we've
talked about MeUndies before. I could tell you
about their underpants
and shirts, which are like three times
softer than cotton.
They're different prints.
You can get like solid colors, adventurous prints,
you can match with your partner, whatever.
I want to talk about the sleep pants,
which is I think
maybe the greatest invention ever given
to humankind. Real good.
They are the comfiest things
I've ever worn, ever.
And I would like to be buried
in them. And you can get
your 15% off your
first pair of MeUndies free shipping
and 100% satisfaction guarantee
if you go to MeUndies.com
slash my brother, that's MeUndies.com
slash my brother.
Do you have teeth?
Yes.
But if he wants the space between
clean, he's got that covered,
but what about the nasty fronts and backs?
Well, that is the
purview of Quip.
The backs and fronts are
awes. They're awes. Back away,
what a pig. Oh, they're affordable
teeth. Sorry.
Are you doing
something else right now while
talking about this? No, I just
sat back down. I'm trying to get my fucking bearings.
Quip was designed to make brushing
your teeth more simple, affordable, and
even, dare we say it,
enjoyable. They've got
sensitive sonic vibrations
and a built-in two-minute
timer that pulses
every 30 seconds to remind you to switch sides.
Brush heads are automatically
delivered on a dentist-recommended
schedule every three months for just $5.
You know, it's always exciting to get a
package, and sometimes it's toothbrush
heads. Quip is
backed by over 20,000 dental
professionals. Quip starts at just
$25, and if you
go to getquip
.com
slash my brother right
now, you get your first refill
pack for free with a Quip electric toothbrush.
That's a refill pack
for free at
getquip
.com slash
my brother.
Wow, that jingle
was free, so they didn't even
have to pay for that extra.
Unlike Griffin Space Jam,
which I had to pay $500,000.
I'm so rich. Have you
ever watched a movie so bad you
just needed to talk to somebody about it?
Well, here at the Flophouse, we watch a bad
movie and then talk about it. Yeah,
you don't have to do anything. We'll watch it and
we'll talk it. We do the hard work.
Featuring the beautiful vocal talents of
Dan McCoy, Stuart
Wellington, and me, America's
rascal, Elliot Kalin. New episodes
every other Saturday at MaximumFun.org
or wherever you get your podcast, dude.
Bye-bye.
I have a Yahoo here that was sent in by Level 9000,
Drew Drew, Drew Davenport. Thank you, Drew.
It's from an anonymous
Yahoo Answers user, who I'm gonna call
Baby Boy Asks.
Alright.
Jim Carrey tribute party?
Smiley face emoticon?
His best movies he's
made. Top 6?
Things I should decorate with. Food.
Activities. Contest.
Music. Ect.
Which I believe is supposed to
mean, etc.
Anything to make this party off
the roof.
Ultimate.
The thought, again. Anything to
make this party off the roof. Ultimate.
Ha ha. Smiley face emoticon.
Please.
And thanks. I would say
just off the top of my head, if you
want to make it
like, a real
ultimate Jim Carrey tribute party,
you're going to need to reference
Copper Mountain.
The film he did in 1983
that was a made-for-TV movie, co-starring
Alan Thicke.
That was basically
an hour-long
commercial for a
Club Med location.
That sounds great.
Listen, a great film.
You could also maybe do
All in Good Taste.
We know, we know. Hey, did you guys know
that Travis knows a lot of Jim Carrey stuff?
Yeah, we get it.
Let's talk about snacks.
Number one, he's Eggman in the new Sonic movie.
So I would say eggs.
And that one's taken care of.
That one's taken care of.
Maybe just pieces of rubber.
In that TV show he's on,
I think he's got a puppet or
something named Mr. Pickles.
So, pickles.
How about some incredible Burt Wonder toast?
That's good.
It would be Burt toast.
It would be another one of those things.
Oh, like Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Guacamole.
That's very good. Earth girls are cheesy.
That's good. What's that one?
Earth girls are easy.
Yeah, I know, but like...
Oh, it's just cheese, but you get cookie cutters
and it's like, you know,
shaped like a woman.
There's also the Cable Pie.
That's pretty good.
You're gonna take all those spare
HDMI cables or those red, white,
and yellow cables that we don't use anymore
and you're gonna put those in a short crust.
Mm-hmm. Plum and plumber.
Oh, delicious.
It's a bunch of plums and you put
a picture of Christopher Plummer on them.
We're gonna start off the evening
with some aperitifs.
We got a sampling of different
beers to enjoy. It's called the
All Flighty, then.
That's pretty good.
It's a good place to start. The Man on the Moon pie.
That's snacks. We got snacks
that we fucking nailed down six years ago.
Friar Friar.
Things I should decorate with.
I think a big sign over the front door
of the party that says, do go in there
is a good start.
Yeah, it's good.
End of that one, though.
Decorations are harder than snacks.
You blew right past snacks.
I didn't blow right past snacks.
We spent a long time in snacks,
but we have lots of things to figure out.
I agree myself on pie-reen.
It's just like your pie.
I can't believe this dude's
playing fucking Dr. Robotnik.
I need to take a minute
away from the bit and just close my eyes
and visualize that good
wrench heat he's gonna bring to this
honored role of Dr.
Ivo Robotnik.
Don't forget the series of
unfortunate events heat too, Griffin.
He's been so great in character roles
in the last five to ten years.
God, I can't wait.
Hey, I've got an idea
for the party.
Why don't you have
Ed Harris show up
and just every once in a while
peek at people from behind
a corner or something like that
with his camera.
Wait, so is Ed Harris a decoration in your mind?
Yeah, he's decoration.
Ed Harris is sort of a performance.
I do like that.
Let's move from closet to closet
and whisper like, zoom in.
Zoom in.
Darryl's double dipping.
He's double dipping
in the guacamole.
Zoom in on Darryl's
gross dip.
So,
I think activities.
Mr. Popper's penguins. That one speaks for itself.
Mm-hmm.
Every time a new guest comes in,
you say, I love you, Philip Morris.
I say, yes, ma'am.
That's a good sort of call and response.
Also, you could all just have free cigarettes out.
That could also be the smoking movie.
That's good.
Also, you could confront some of your friends
who have been lying to you for a while.
Like, if you know
you have an untrustworthy friend,
there's going to be a chance to be like, liar, liar,
and then see who's lying.
Or you could make it a fun party game,
but I like mine better where it's like
the culmination of maybe some
deep-seated distrust.
If we wanted to do a contest,
we could just do
Jim Carrey impressions.
Well,
the problem is everyone's super good at them.
So, it just ends up being a tie.
Like, Justin, do yours.
Okay.
Um, hello?
Hey, I'm Latke.
Okay.
That's my impression of Jim
doing an impression of Andy
doing an impression of Latke from Taxi.
Here, can I do one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Looks like they got murdered with a knife made out of their own bones.
And that's from Dark Crimes,
his 2016 movie he did.
Ah, cool, cool, cool.
Yeah, this is sort of a darker...
Here, can I try again?
Disgusting number keeps showing up.
I love this character.
I remember this film.
Just finish the impression.
Disgusting number keeps showing up
all over the dang place.
Did you figure it out yet?
Farts.
And that's, I believe...
Oh no, Griffin broke himself.
It's just nice to laugh.
It really is.
Did we do all of them? What didn't we do?
Oh, music.
Just play that fucking Cuban Pete from The Mask.
Until everyone leaves.
I think I could make it through three.
It depends on how good the spotless mind guacamole is.
Because that might get me to stay for a couple more.
Yeah, I think that's it.
Oh, with the Etcetera.
I think Etcetera is just
invite Jim Carrey to be there.
He would have a great time.
He's the only guest.
He's the only guest. This party's almost certainly going to go off the roof.
Someday...
You guys promised me someday
we can record a commentary track
for Ace Ventura or Pet Detective Jr.
I think about...
Do you guys have things that you think about a lot?
That you haven't seen?
Yeah, my wife and kids.
Theoretically.
But you can't really bring yourself to actually ingest.
Oh, so it would be a coming in fresh commentary track.
Yeah, it would be like a first time watch.
Because Ace Ventura or Pet Detective Jr. is like that for me.
Came out in fucking 2009.
Never seen it.
I watched the trailer for it probably 500 times.
And I've never watched the movie.
Because I know it wouldn't be pleasurable.
But I am like obsessed with the idea that it exists.
I guess is the best way of putting it.
Do you guys have stuff like that?
I still have not seen...
Oh, what's the fucking Johnny Depp?
Mordecai. I still have not seen...
I've seen a lot of Mordecai.
But I couldn't finish it.
I watched I think the first 25 minutes of it.
Yeah, I was about to say Mordecai didn't age well.
But Mordecai didn't birth well.
Yeah.
This is shame.
How about another question?
Yeah, I love that.
Farm wisdom.
Don't make a blunder down under farm wisdom.
That's not farm wisdom.
This is a farm wisdom.
That's right.
We're going to farm wisdom Australia in addition.
From Ben Hetherington.
No, wrong.
No way was that right.
Ben Hetherington.
Yes, you fully skipped it.
We fully did.
I was coming in hot.
There's a lot of letters all jumbled together.
I was just trying to churn through.
Ben Hetherington missed farm wisdom.
And rather than
complain like some people do when they miss
bits, Ben made it happen.
Bringing us some
Australian farm
wisdom.
If you have farm wisdom, submit.
Please do.
This is one of my favorite segments to do.
It's just hard to find the exact right flavor.
But I think Ben has done an admirable job
here. Kangaroos
and emus
cannot walk backwards.
The structure of a kangaroo's pelvis and tail
won't allow it. However,
nobody knows why emus
can't.
It might just be won't.
But that's why they're both featured on the
Australian government's coat of arms
and out
in the 50 cent coin.
They're supposed to signify
that our country is always moving forward.
I would maybe hazard
that there are other reasons kangaroos
are on the Australian currency.
But I do like Ben's
suggestion here.
Yeah, ad astra and all that.
Hmm. Ben?
You got these things
running around on a farm, bud? Maybe an emu?
I'll give you that because they have the big eggs.
But I've never had
kanga milk, I don't think.
People eat kanga meat.
I mean kangaroo meat is
pretty popular.
There's commercial kangaroo farming.
There's a commercial kangaroo industry.
Yeah, so read a book, Griffin.
Yeah, read a book.
I would like to pause it, Ben, and I don't want to put you on blast,
but I say this only because it's exactly what I would do.
Is it possible that
some people might know why
emus don't work backward and you don't?
Nobody knows.
Okay.
I bet somebody knows.
Apparently, according to the
Wikipedia article called
kangaroo meat, that my day has taken
a strange, twisty turn.
I didn't expect to be here when I woke up.
There's a thing called kangatarianism.
And that's where you
only kangaroo
meat. You're so wild
for it. And it's apparently
based on environmental and ethical grounds.
Unsurprising.
Goats smell really bad. Surprising.
It's a common occurrence
here to catch wild goats,
and the best way to do so
is to track them by smell.
Wild goats
are common in areas in northern
New South Wales and southern
Queensland and Australia, and can fetch
a tiny profit when sold to a goat farm.
Even with our especially blunt
sense of smell, a person can tell
the size and distance of a goat herd
at distances of up
to a mile.
Yeah, I mean, goats don't smell
very good.
Damn, that was funny!
I'm just on the Wikipedia
page called kangaroo industry, and I'm
trying to turn my fucking ignorance
ship right around. You can't get me
I'm reading about the kangaroo
meat industry, and you come at me and you're like
goats don't smell good. There's
two pieces of information presented to me. I'm
going to go with the savouriest nug.
Dingo's eating lamb
has been a big problem for stock farmers in Australia,
and the easiest solution is to buy
alpacas. Alpacas hate
the living shit out of dogs.
Wild or domestic, it will
often bomb a sheep and act as their guardians.
Alpacas can deliver a devastating
kick.
And a devastating insult.
Yeah, they're so mean. They're insult
comedies beyond reproach.
Alpacas can deliver a kick
as their hooves will grow in
displayed claws if not trimmed,
and can hit anything within two
yards in any direction.
The lamb birth rate can be
significantly improved by
having alpacas in the herd
because they make sheep feel safe, and the
reduced stress allows the ewes
to carry a lamb to term.
This is fucking
soup to nuts
bananas. What this
has said is
like, let's just
take it one thing at a time.
Okay, the dingos eat lambs.
Yes, that all tracks for me.
Alpacas hate dogs.
Okay, I will have to take
your word for it on that. Alpacas
can deliver a devastating
kick as their hooves will
grow in displayed claws if not
trimmed. So you basically have to choose
an alpaca that you are making
bad already. You are
letting grow into a battling alpaca.
And can
hit anything within two
yards.
That's six feet. What?
What are these
alpacas fucking doing?
Yeah, they look. In what sense
Ben? They look so goofy, but
they're actually the predator.
Apparently.
They can kick up to six feet.
Am I understanding that correctly?
If I'm understanding it correctly, up to six feet.
I don't see how it's possible.
I think two feet of that's just
claws.
I also, I think my
favorite part of this though, is like a
sheep looks around, sees what
he has to assume is a giant version
of itself and says, that
makes me feel comfortable fucking.
That's chill as hell. I'm gonna
totally carry this baby to term now. Look at that
giant ass sheep here.
If I looked over and there was like a twelve foot
Travis. His legs
were guns.
I feel comfortable now.
I'm horny as hell.
Let's go. How about a question
or is there more farm wisdom?
That's all the farm wisdom I have. I like that.
I mean I ask for more as if I need more.
I am sated. That's good. That's good stuff.
Thank you Ben. Folks, keep that farm wisdom
coming in. Would love to
have a little bit more of it. How about another
question here. Every so often
some coworkers and I will go out for a night of
KOK. We all have fun,
but I'm easily the worst singer.
Kinda screechy. God I love that fucking
awareness. Inspirational.
I'm the worst singer in the group and
this draws a lot of teasing from the whole office floor.
I have a good sense of humor
and I'm happy that everyone can laugh at my
mangled 80's hits. But I thought
taking an actual singing lesson would help me get
out of the comically bad range. To my surprise
a number of my coworkers were very against
the idea of lessons. Saying that I was
taking it too seriously and being a
killjoy. Should I continue
with the lessons or is it wrong for me
to deprive everyone of my unique
voice? And that's from Music Al
in Mobile, Alabama. I'm gonna go
super Saiyan over here.
I've never been confronted
by our questions
as much as I have been this one episode.
Yeah. Because hey
hey, hey
why did you tell your coworkers about the
singing lessons?
Why did you tell your coworkers about the singing
lessons? You didn't wanna have
that she's all that
moment where you get up there and you're like oh yeah
you made fun of me in high school when
I had this job in saying weird. Well
look at me now.
I am like a bird.
And you sound that good.
Like that.
Like an angel. Like I just sounded.
Cause I took singing lessons. I didn't tell anybody
about it. I hate to
bring it to you but I'm afraid
period.
But I'm also afraid that your
coworkers like
that you're not good at karaoke cause
it makes them feel better at it.
And they're gonna say like oh you're taking it too
seriously. But they're afraid that you're
gonna become a dominant karaoke-er.
And that they
cause here's the thing. If you
stop being the bad one, someone
else is gonna become the bad one.
And they're all afraid it's them.
Too true.
You need another reason
to be getting good at singing.
I think maybe you're trying to get up on
the voice. I think you're trying to meet Gwen.
I think you're trying to meet Gwen and Fam.
Can I
proffer this?
Stop going to karaoke.
Keep taking singing lessons.
Six months from now,
the friends are all at karaoke.
And then a new singer
enters. They're wearing a
tiger mask and a tiger costume.
They're an amazing
singer.
No one can guess why this tiger has entered
the karaoke room
they have rented. They're scared for their lives.
Hours pass.
Is it a believable tiger costume?
It's a
very colorful
and powerful.
And hours pass. Your friends drink
with the tiger. They bond with the tiger.
They learn the tiger's likes
and dislikes.
The end of the night comes.
You exchange numbers
with a guy that
you met there. You go home.
You lie down. You realize that you forgot
to dramatically reveal that you had been
the tiger all along.
You remind yourself the next time
for sure, when you show up
at karaoke, you will definitely
definitely definitely pull off
your mask dramatically to reveal that you were
in fact the tiger all along.
And that beautiful voice was attached to
the former
not so great singer.
Time goes by. You realize it's been
three years. You married that guy.
You're still the tiger.
You look back. You wonder
what have I become? And the answer is you've become the
tiger. You're more comfortable now as the tiger
than you've ever been before.
And then one day he pulls off your mask
and your head falls off.
You go back to karaoke.
They don't remember the tiger.
So we're basically starting from scratch
again.
You can just be a great singer. You don't have to be a great
singer to excel at karaoke.
There are two songs.
Our former boss,
Christopher Grant, sings
does karaoke with a passion and
a gusto that I find profoundly moving
and the gusto and passion are on
point and I'm going to stop there. But
Chris has also through his karaoke
artistry introduced me
to Hames the Wire
and Telephone Line by
Yellow
that I had never heard either of those songs before.
Two songs that I adore brought to me
by the artistry of one Christopher
Grant and his karaoke
skills. It doesn't matter how talented
you are. Now let me say this though.
Don't do cake. You're going to be
tempted to do cake. But then
one minute into cake you're going to realize
it's pretty fucking boring.
People liked cake when it was cake
but they don't like me faux
caking out here because it's just mostly
talking about cars. I'm basically talking
about driving fast.
I don't think
that this is a great
karaoke. You don't have to sing good to do karaoke. You do
have to love the song you're doing.
I've seen so many people make the mistake of doing like
I'm going to do a funny song
and then they most likely
don't know the song well enough to do
it. But two, halfway through
everyone's like okay I get it and now we
have another like five minutes of meatloaf
left. Yeah practice your
songs at home folks because you never know.
It's so important to be
great at karaoke. It's the most important thing.
That is going to do it for us
on My Brother My Brother Me this week.
Thank you so much for indulging
us and letting us
just jab your ear off here.
We barely let you get a word in
edgewise. But we
very much do appreciate it. Hey can I
real quick before I forget like I forgot
last week. We're going to be on the going
on the JoCo Cruise soon.
Which is very exciting. But out there
on that there open ocean we won't have much
internet. So if you're going to be on the cruise
and you have a question that you
would like us to like answer please
send it in now and include
like JoCo Cruise in the
subject line so we can go ahead and put together a question
list for our live shows on
the boat. Speaking of
next week's episode on March
11th is going to be our live show from New Orleans.
I just edited it and
dang that was a fun one.
And then the week after that we're going to kick off the
Max Fun Drive. So
we will we'll have more on the Max
Fun Drive. If you're a new listener
of my bim bam we're part of maximum
fun which is a
pledge supported network and you
can help us out and all the other shows that
you like and get some cool
get some cool stuff in exchange. So
that'll kick off the week of March
18th and
we'll tell you more about it then.
Also when you're listening to this it'll
be March 1st which means that
there will have been new. It will not
it will not be March 1st. It will be
March 4th which means that there will have been
new McElroy merch on
the up for sale for
three days. And there's
some really cool new stuff and we're going
to try to keep putting more and more new stuff
up there all the time.
So if you want to check it out go to McElroy.family
and click on Merch or you
can go to McElroyMerch.com and
while you're at McElroy.family go
ahead and click on tours there
and get your tickets to see
the Adventure Zone in San Jose
my brother my brother and me in
San Jose and my brother
my brother and me in Salt Lake City. That's April
2nd 3rd and 4th. Get those
tickets McElroy.family
click on tours.
Is that it? Thanks to John Roderick and
The Long Winters for these for our theme song It's a Departure off the
album Putting the Days to Bed.
Go listen to Dr. Game Show on Maximumfun.org
we just picked them up decided about that one
and y'all want that final.
Yes. Yes. This final
Yahoo was sent in by Level 9000
YadruDru at Drew Davenport. Thank you Drew.
It's YadruAnswers user Jurek
who asks
Ants with wings
Who are they?
My name is Justin
I'm Travis McElroy. I'm Griffin McElroy
He's been my brother my brother and me
Kiss your dad's brown lips
Maximumfun.org
Comedy and culture
Artist owned. Listener supported
Welcome back
and thank you Dan for that scathing
report. As you know Maximumfun
Drive is coming up March 18th to March
29th which has some folks
pretty excited but as families around
the world get ready to celebrate this season
of giving community and quality
podcasts some are
wondering if it's just too much.
Are they though? They are.
Some people are all for comedy
and culture but with 45 shows
offering hundreds of hours of bonus
content plus all the Maximumfun meetups
taking place around the world some
people think it's too much
while other people think it
sounds totally awesome. I took my
granddaughter to the mall to get her picture
taken and the mall pod fairy was
short and I you know I'm just gonna say it
I'm sorry but everyone knows
the pod fairy is tall.
Well I think we should just leave it there.
Until next
time here's the news you need to know
Maximumfun Drive runs from
March 18th through 29th. Be
sure to listen to all of your favorite podcasts.
I know I will.