The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody, and welcome to my brother, my brother,
mean advice show for the modern era. I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
Oh, there's a turkey in the studio.
Oh man, not again, oh not again.
Could one of our producers come in here and get it?
Yeah, if you could get the turkey.
Any one of you?
Someone come get the turkey, the turkey has now soiled my coffee.
Dillip, could you come get it, or Susman?
Don't touch it like that.
Susman, show Dillip how to touch it right.
Oh God, Susman, no.
Boy, I wish we hadn't pardoned, boy howdy,
I wish we hadn't pardoned this turkey for all its crimes.
To be fair, most of its crimes were white collar,
and it has used its skills to help solve other crimes.
As everyone knows, we may need a little bit of setup here
if you don't follow the news.
And perhaps, and I'll say it, it's most ill-advised policy.
This administration has decided that all pardoned turkeys
must live with us, or any other podcaster.
Our name got pulled out of the hat.
Of course, everybody knows about Stinky Fred,
the turkey that lives at the Joe Rogan Show.
And I'm just hoping, what podcaster do you guys hope
gets a turkey next year?
I kinda would like to see Mark Maron interview a turkey.
He already did, if you ask me, Gallagher.
Guys, that's one real turkey.
Is there a Maron episode with Gallagher?
Oh, there's a famous Gallagher Maron episode, Travis.
Get with the fucking net, dude.
I am up to here in turkey shit,
and ready for the holiday to be over.
For those of you who can't see,
Griffin just pointed to the bottom of his shoe.
It's not really that dramatic.
Nah, I'm swimming in it.
In the fiction that we've crafted,
whose house is the turkey at?
I think that in this world, in the fiction we've created,
we were all in the same studio living together.
In like a full house kind of scenario.
As so many television producers who we have floated the idea
of making a My Brother, My Brother, Me television show
have suggested, we all live together in one swinging pad.
One of us is married.
One of us is in a long-term relationship.
One of us is a swinging single.
Also, there's like four dozen fucking turkeys in here.
Yeah, and here's the twist that makes this really special
and why I think this is coming this fall to NBC
is that one of us is a coyote.
And that makes things so funny and a little bit sexy
with all of the fucking turkeys.
And all the turkeys are like paying tenants, right?
So like, we can't eat them, right?
But we want to.
And also, thank you Justin for not giving away
because one of us is a turkey,
but you don't find out which one until like season three.
Yeah.
Well, that's interesting
because Justin actually said one of us is a coyote,
but the idea that one of us is a turkey
is also very powerful, Travis.
And I'm going to bring this up to Ryan,
who's the showrunner on this one.
Oh, we got Ryan.
Ryan Reynolds.
We got Ryan.
No, it's just Ryan.
Oh.
Yeah, he's the exotic Norwegian television showrunner.
He made fucking cheers.
But anyway, this is Turkey House coming this.
And this has been the pilot to Turkey House.
Turkey House, one coyote.
This is Turkey House.
And I hope you guys liked it.
And this was the intro for this funny episode
of my brother, my brother and me.
It was a funny introduction.
Turkey House, colon, one coyote is the second season.
We're doing it like Terrace House.
Yes.
With like, you know, boy, ex-girl in the city.
That kind of deal is one coyote.
And then season three is Turkey House, colon, too many eggs.
Yep.
Next one is Turkey House boys versus girls in the city.
This one, we're drawing a line down the middle of the house
and we're putting some fucking catapults in there.
So this is an advice show.
Catapult, more like birdapult.
That's one of the jokes that happens.
That's one of the many jokes that we have
in season four of Turkey House.
That was supposed to be saved for the trailer for season five.
I'm sorry, everyone forget, forget I said it.
Wow, Travis.
Wow.
We've got nothing.
So I'm going to go back to the joke board for season five
and I'm erasing that one.
And now it's blank.
Yeah, there's no more jokes on the board.
A bird in my hand, more like a hundred birds in my hand.
If it makes you feel any better, Justin,
the joke board for this episode of my brother,
my brother and me, as far as I can tell,
was Griffin makes a turkey noise
and then we just kind of, everything else
was just that one little twisted brand of magic that we-
Griffin, you were making that turkey noise?
You kidding me?
I thought you had a turkey with you.
What a betrayal.
Okay, okay, okay.
I was making it with my throat
because I am the one who was-
You're the turkey.
Please, God, we got to start doing the podcast.
This is it, Griffin, this is the podcast.
Betrayal, we're in it.
This one's getting a little long in the gobbler.
So if we could just swing right on one-
That is how we finish season five,
the final season of Turkey House.
This one's getting long in the gobbler.
So that's the last line of dialogue.
Class dismissed, and then we flip off the light.
Class dismissed, I love, I do love class dismissed.
Every show should, at the end, every show,
the last episode of Law & Order should be like,
one of the cops is like,
anyway, criminals, we caught all of you.
We got all of you.
Class dismissed, turn off the lights.
Yeah, shit.
I have a rare condition called laughter-induced syncope,
which is a fancy way of saying,
I faint when I laugh too hard.
All the studies I've read say
the best way to treat situational fainting
is to stop doing the thing that causes it.
I'm not gonna stop laughing, so my question is this,
how do I tell my new friends they don't have to worry
when I suddenly lose consciousness during a fit of laughter?
That's from fainting goat girl.
Sunglasses, big, loose suit,
weakened at Bernie's, is this anything?
Huh, huh.
Is this any, I'm partying with my new friend,
they start cracking up so hard that they faint,
but they're wearing a big sort of Blues Brothers suit,
and they're wearing sunglasses.
I look at them, and I think, hell yeah,
that must be a cool thing that people are doing now,
is just sort of a surprise siesta situation.
And maybe have a friend with you who, when you do this,
say, they're processing it, right?
And it makes it seem like, wow, not only do they enjoy my joke,
they're really taking it in.
They're really appreciating my contribution
to the conversation.
Hey, what was up with what just happened to you?
Oh man, your joke was so fucking dope
that I had to dream about it right now.
Sometimes I hear jokes that are so funny and so cool,
I think, I'd like to play with that in the dream space.
And so I go immediately to sleep right there,
and right then and there.
Here's, I've never, I don't think I've ever done this
on a show before, but I am going to offer my services here
to the question asker.
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'll travel around with you,
and when someone makes a really funny joke,
and you feel yourself starting to laugh too hard,
I'll then make a joke of my own making
to level you out back down to the middle.
Travis is the comedy chill out tent, essentially.
I'll make a joke that you go, I mean, conceptually,
that's funny.
Yeah, it's kind of a thinker, huh?
I guess that's, yeah, that's funny in a way,
it has the structure of a joke.
If Justin and I are bringing the acid,
Travis swings back in with the base,
just to keep your pH as close to zero as possible.
Yes, and I'm willing to do that for you,
I guess for the rest of your life.
I guess that's what I'm offering here.
Let me tell you something about friends.
Okay, oh, everybody, wait, hold on, give me a second,
let me get in place.
I'm ready to laugh about Ross and Chandler, please go.
Joss, Roey,
Pandler, Chibi.
Those are my new set of friends.
No, let me tell you something about friends.
A true friend will still worry about you
even if they know why you fainted.
Yes.
I still think there should be concern,
I think concern is fair.
You were standing over a big pile of broken dishes,
you know, when you were laughing so hard.
When you were laughing so hard.
Other unsafe things,
come on, play with me in this space.
Yes.
You know, unsafe stuff.
Yeah, the bus saw factory.
Yeah.
Bus, thank you, bus saw factory.
You were working on a girder, building a tall tower.
Yeah, and it was lunch break,
you were having a big 1920s sandwich.
Oh yeah, and a big old thermos of coffee
with your sandwich, I guess.
Having a big stogie, looking out at the 1920s
New York City skyline.
One of your friends tells an off-color joke,
it's the 1920s, so probably about,
I don't know, Eisenhower.
Woo, off you go, I'm concerned.
Your real friends are always gonna worry about you
when you faint, and that's fine, that's healthy.
I think that's normal.
Has this never happened to you guys?
Laughing so hard that you fainted?
Yeah.
No.
No, I don't think so.
Okay, this has happened to me.
Well, but Justin, you have a tendency
to get a fit of the giggles, in a way that
Griffin and I don't really.
I titter like a polite little mouse,
but Justin, you rip and roar like a big,
I don't know, like a monster truck.
Yeah, you start going, and I've seen the tears
flow from your eyes, the color rise to your face,
I've seen you near death from enjoying
a joke I have made so much.
I would love a super cut of all the times
that we've gotten noises out of you on this show
that are more like, bleh!
Like, do you, like, let's like,
Trav, hey Trav, do a laugh for me, like one of us.
Okay, and when I do it, I'm like.
But sometimes, Justin, when you do it,
you're like, bleh!
Is that what it's like?
Yeah, wow. Sometimes that.
And it doesn't start like that, but you get there,
and that's probably, so if I guess.
You know how Dennis Nedry sounds
when he gets hit in the face with the spittle?
Oh, this is a good, yeah, please, go on.
It's like you were laughing at that noise that he made.
Justin, don't take this as us slamming you,
or dunking you, or burning you, or razzing you,
or zapping you, or anything like that.
I'm saying you would pass out less
if you opened the glottis a little bit.
Or if you just didn't enjoy things anymore.
That, no, stop it.
I want Justin to have a joy-filled life.
I'm just saying, when you have a laugh in there,
don't squish it down and give it a, bleh!
Open the glottis, and just, ah, and let it out.
Yeah.
Speaking of.
Oh, let's hear you try it.
Pry open that glottis, and let them.
Do something fucking funny.
Farts.
Here's what, now, let me see if this makes me,
I came up with a joke.
Okay. So, let me say it,
and see if I laugh hard enough.
Okay. To where, okay.
Bernie Man?
It's like Bernie Man, but with Bernie Sanders.
Is that anything?
Bleh! Oh, God.
Shit, actually, I kind of get it now, Juice.
That feels good as hell.
It's like I'm a laugh crockpot.
It's like I'm a giggle pressure cooker,
and I keep it down there, and I feel it more.
I feel the happiness more.
I'm glad I could help.
Do you guys want to, how about a Yahoo?
Yes, please. Yeah.
Tessa sent this in.
It's from Yahoo Answers user, Colin, who asks.
Hey, thanks, Tessa.
I'm thankful for you.
Can a principal have a paper that says
list of student I don't like?
Oh, definitely.
Yeah, for sure.
I was supposed to interview the principal at my school,
and I walked into her office before she did,
and I saw a paper that said that,
and it had a list of freshmen, sophomores,
juniors, and seniors.
Right as she walked in, she hurried up and took the list,
and hid it in her desk.
I'm surprised this teacher needs a list,
because my list of people I don't like
is kind of always at the forefront of my brain,
just sort of cooking there.
I'm shocked that this person is having
such trouble keeping track.
If I may, perhaps they misread this,
the question asker misread the situation,
and that was the weekly list turned in by each teacher
to the principal, so they could keep a catalog
of just the worst little shits in the school.
It's like, hey, we're all gonna get together,
in the teacher's lounge, and compare notes
about what students we don't like,
who we're gonna give detention to or fail,
just cause the ones who, I don't know,
maybe we'll hide something in their desk,
and then yell at them for it.
You know how teachers are.
Like chattering teeth.
Yeah.
These freaking millennials that show up
with their chattering teeth,
causing a ruckus in my classroom.
Yeah, you get it, with their joy buzzers,
and I don't know, their sticky hands
that they use to whip across the room
to collect things from one another.
Oh, I hate those.
Their wax lips.
Yes.
Oh.
You know what I don't like?
What, Travis?
I don't like their troll dolls,
with their tall hair.
Okay, thank you.
And their little weird belly buttons.
Oh.
They stick it in Jeff's nose,
and then he gets into a sneezing fit,
and I'm trying to talk about algebra.
They won't stop tickling Jeff's nose with the troll dolls.
Yes.
I'm going to confiscate every one of them
and burn them in a big pile.
Another big problem is that millennial baby names
are pretty wild now,
and so maybe it's tough to member those.
Yeah, like Diplo.
Diplo is a big popular one.
Skrillex.
Jandice is a huge one now.
Suisman.
Nedry.
John Jirndi is huge.
Travis.
If you guys were teachers,
what subject would you teach?
This is a fun question.
Drama.
Driver's Ed.
Which means also coaching.
Oh, yeah.
I would be Driver's Ed.
I would go at it backwards,
how most of the time they let the coach do Driver's Ed.
They would bring me in for Driver's Ed,
because of how good I was,
but then I would have to do coaching.
What would you coach?
You know.
I don't.
Skateboarding.
Nice.
Uh-huh, a skateboarding coach.
I'd probably coach e-sports.
They say those who can't do teach,
so that would be actually a really good gig for you,
Griffin, with a skateboarding coach.
Yeah, it's easy.
Get up there.
Jump.
No, not like that.
I'll push you.
Let me push you.
Now make the board go up with you when you jump.
No, not like that.
Not, I would show you, but that's too easy.
You need to find, everybody's got their own style.
You fell over again?
Don't do that.
I'm gonna pull out this row of bleachers.
Just make the thing go up with you
and you grind all the way down it.
No, not like that.
Oh my God.
Now do a Chrysler 360.
Why are you having so much, F, F.
F's across the board.
All right, Justin, what would you teach?
How am I?
Okay.
If I don't have any more, just like cooking.
You know what they need in school?
Just like basic life skills.
Sure.
I would get, you know what my class would be
called the real shit.
Yeah.
What it'd be is called the real shit
and I would tell your students how it really is.
I would teach, this is a class that I wish
they had been taught to me when I was in.
Pirating media.
Yeah, that would be another one.
That's a good one.
In high school, I wish that, this is a class
I would teach of the importance of opening mail.
Cause you know, sometimes you get the mail
and you're like, I'll open this later.
And then you open it like three weeks later
and you're like, oh, that was an important letter.
I'm gonna get yelled at, right?
And you think as an adult,
you would just open the mail when it comes.
But I feel like somebody didn't teach me that.
And maybe I could go back and teach them
the importance of opening mail in a timely fashion.
That would be a short class.
You think that, but do it, just as in big letters.
Juice, I think you'd be a good cooking teacher
for cooking class.
However, the worst school fight I ever saw in my life
was in my high school cooking class.
You're kidding.
It was a, it was like a five person, like co-ed,
just real hullabaloo, a real hooskow.
So like, what do you do?
You're teaching about how to make, you know,
taco salad or whatever.
Yeah, definitely.
What happens when that, when the hooskow breaks out?
Here, Griffin and I worked it out.
Okay, okay.
Okay, you ready?
Yeah.
Hey, those are my tomatoes.
Those are actually my tomatoes.
I mean, let's hit each other a lot.
With tomatoes?
Okay.
I'm already hitting you.
I hit you in the face and in the neck.
I'm hitting you back,
but I'm hitting you the best and hardest.
Justin, imagine I hit him in the neck and in the torso.
I hit him in the gonads.
He hit me in the gonads and I fell down over,
right in my, right in my orbs.
Oh God, he's hitting me in both butt cheeks,
like bongos.
Punching both butt cheeks, I have one, two fists.
I'm just pounding them, pounding, pounding, pounding.
It's okay to squeeze one.
Oh no, one of my butt cheeks popped.
I popped one of his fake cheeks.
Oh no, it was actually real.
I don't know how this has happened.
Oh God.
Teacher, teacher, I made the butt cheeks come out.
Oh, it's right down to the bone.
Teacher, teacher, I see his bones.
Oh no.
Oh, my butt is sliding down my leg.
Oh God, it's in my knee.
Hey, do you guys want to see some new Fortnite dances
I've been coming up with?
He's dancing on my broken butt.
Have you stopped the fight to unite the class?
Is this a different student?
Yeah.
Who's trying to unite the class?
Hey, hey, hey.
And they're disliked of him.
Guys, guys, cut it out.
This one's called the silly tornado.
Oh, now you're punching my butt.
I guess you didn't like it.
No more butts punched.
I would just do, I mean,
I have a pretty good teaching style.
Because it seems like you just ignored it
to talk about blueberries.
No, I just let you fight it out.
See, if I catch you fighting in class,
I'm gonna make you fight a whole pack of them.
So you love fighting.
It's the cigarette thing, but more.
So if you like fighting one person so much,
I'm gonna make you fight a whole pack of students.
Cool.
Okay?
So you'll fight a big, big group the next time.
Okay, wait, can I try this now?
I want to see what my teaching style is
and you two fight and I'll see if I can break it up.
Hey, Grimbo, I really hate your guts.
Oh yeah, kiss my nunchucks.
Hey, you two.
What's this really about?
I'm proud of you and I support you.
Okay, let's team up.
Let's team up on this nerd teacher.
I'm gonna kick his nunchucks.
Oh, they're punching me in the butt.
Oh no, my butt.
Now Griffin and I are the teachers.
Okay.
And Travis, you fight yourself.
So don't listen to what this guy says.
He always lies.
I'm the real history teacher, not him.
I'm punching myself in the butt so hard.
He just came in here.
I know he looks exactly like me
because he copied my skin and my face.
Copied my skin and my face.
I'm the real history teacher.
Which one do I fight?
Well, say something true about history, real teacher.
Real teacher.
Go ahead, I'm waiting.
World War I was a hologram.
Okay.
It's my first time doing a secret Santa exchange
and I got someone who I've only met once.
The only thing I know about this person
is that they're into feet more than the average person.
Waka waka.
Wait, hold on.
Read the rest of the sentence, though.
Their job specializes in feet.
Okay.
And they don't seem like the type
to use standard presents, such as candles.
Well, should I, no one uses the candles.
That's not the point.
Should I embrace the feet thing and get a goof?
Or is there a special secret Santa ultimate present
I can get them to impress?
That's from Man I'm Not Sure in Melbourne.
Okay, just real quick.
I'm going to speak, is it podiatrists?
Who are the feet doctors?
Podiatrists.
Their job specializing in feet,
they probably don't like it if you describe it
as like they're into feet more than the average person.
Probably don't love that.
Yeah.
My oh me, I'm a proctologist.
Let me open up this package from my friend I've met once.
Well, that's a asshole.
Interesting.
I've never bought a candle for somebody for a secret Santa
because they seem like someone
who's just going to use the hell out of that candle.
You do it because it's like in a fancy jar
or like it's holiday themed.
You can always go with like, I don't know,
like a Jimmy Dean sausage specialty platter or whatever.
Yes, there's a spectrum of acceptable
sort of person agnostic gifts
that you can get someone for the holidays.
And the most base of these are, you know,
the Target gift card or whatever the hell.
Something that you're going to,
this is something that you can have and you can use,
but you do not need
because I don't know you enough to know your needs.
Yes.
This is, I have done a lot of like white elephant,
Santa, you know, secret Santa things.
And let me tell you, here's the hierarchy,
the spectrum of gifts.
At the top is the like, I know you so well
and I absolutely nailed this gift that you weren't expecting.
A novelty shirt referencing an inside joke off Redbubble
or some shit like that.
Right, that's the best.
That's easily the best.
Then the next step is totally generic, but usable, right?
Big tin of popcorn, candle, a gift card, right?
And then at the bottom is I sort of knew you
and took a stab in the dark.
That's where you get a thing where
not only can I not use this,
I now also don't like it.
So like, cool, I don't know what to do with this.
I know you like dogs.
Here is a picture of some dogs framed in a nice frame.
That's nothing, this is nothing you've given me.
You've handed me air, essentially.
I was gonna search for candle that smells like feet.
And as I began to Google it, there was an auto-complete.
So quick auto-complete challenge.
What are the top five things that people search for
completing candle that smells like?
I'm gonna say fart.
No, no, incorrect.
I'm going to say, and this may be cheating
because I saw it on like my Facebook feed,
like rainy cement, like wet cement, rain.
No.
Shit.
Petrichorus is what you're looking for.
Books.
Uh-huh.
Is weed.
Yeah. Okay.
Matches.
I like that.
I love the smell when I light it,
but then that just goes away.
How could I keep that going?
That must be the one that just like haunts
candle inventors of like, just can't get there.
Then there's candle that smells like rain.
And then the last one is candle that smells like gasoline.
Whoa.
That's a wild, that's a wild ambiance.
That might, maybe that's not somebody looking to buy that.
They bought one and it smells like that
and they're terrified.
Or possibly that Jeff Gordon searched that 50,000 times.
Yeah.
So much so that it shows up now as a frequently searched.
What if you just put out like a new,
like Yankee candle that just was labeled like,
smells like candle.
That would really like boggle the noodle.
Oh Travis, that's so fucking wild.
How does that brain work?
Here comes, here comes a Justin laugh.
If this doesn't get it, then what will?
It smells like candle.
Oh, yeah, dang.
No, it wasn't bad.
I mean, it wasn't bad.
We need to invent, and this could be fairly lucrative.
We've done this before at the magic acorn,
but that was, I think we can all agree that was rude,
cop out, not practical gift at all.
We need something else in the popcorn bucket sort of milieu.
Like a neutral gift that's just like as good as a gift card.
Something like, you know, fucking paper towels.
God, I'm always running out of these things,
but still more of a gift than that.
That, oh yeah, but that's not it, right?
Because that doesn't imply,
I want something that both implies
I didn't know about you,
but I thought about the human experience, right?
Ooh, that's a good point, Trav.
To quote the home wrecker in Love Actually,
I don't want something I need.
I want something I want.
And in that one, she's talking about her boss's sex,
even though he's married.
What about a scarf?
Again, in Love Actually, she gets him a scarf,
and it's quite a, that one's thorny,
because of Love Actually.
That one's a little bit thornier,
because she gets him a scarf.
What about a laundry hamper?
Not expensive, but something everyone uses,
but I would never think to buy at the store.
Maybe you get a laundry basket,
like a really nice one with nice handles,
and then you go into their house early,
and you break theirs.
Uh-huh. Cool.
And make sure- I guess that could
really work with anything, huh?
That particular strap.
Break it right in front of the front door,
so they see it.
Like, as they're leaving the house that day,
like, ah, dang, wait, what's that?
I got a new one, a secret Santa.
What fortuitous circumstances.
Put the shards of their shattered laundry hamper
inside of the new laundry hamper
when you give it to them.
That'll really flip their fucking bean, dude.
What about, oh, here's a good universal gift.
Oh, he's got one.
Yeah, get a big bow, and put it on their car
outside in the parking lot, right?
And then you pull back, and say, I got you that.
This is for hunters, I'm assuming?
What?
This is for hunters, mainly, I'm assuming?
A big bow, no, excuse me, like a ribbon bow.
Got it, okay.
And they're gonna look out the window and see it,
and they're gonna laugh, right?
Because that's funny that you did that.
And that's all you're really going for, right,
in this bleak existence, is one bright moment of laughter
shared with a new friend.
Because you were the funny friend
who put a giant bow on a car they already owned.
Oceans eight on blue ray.
Thank you.
Finally, one of us says it.
It's a great flick, not enough people saw it.
Sandy's bringing all of her heat.
If it had been the first one in the series,
y'all would've loved it, right?
I would've loved it because we would've had two more.
Oceans nine and 10.
We still need those, by the way.
If you, please, I'm begging you, please, Hollywood,
make nine and 10, or else I'm gonna do a movie marathon,
I'm gonna have to sit in silence for four hours
before I can start 11.
Please don't do that to me.
Out of respect, out of respect for these fallen films.
I'm gonna have to hire local actors to act out
what I think would've happened in Oceans nine and 10.
And while that is good for the gig economy,
it's not good for my pocketbook.
Okay, how about you put a SD card,
and you wrap that up, and you give it to them,
and they say, what's that?
And you just say, Bitcoin.
Huh, but it's not?
It's not Bitcoin?
I mean, it's not on there.
That's not how Bitcoin works.
And then you can just start explaining how Bitcoin works
until they've left the room.
The room?
How about a guest role in Oceans nine?
Huh, now I feel like that only works.
This only works if you're Sandra Bullock, by the way,
or someone with equivalent juice.
If Sandra Bullock got me in The Secret Santa
and got me a candle, I mean, I feel pretty good
because I got a candle from Sandra Bullock,
but I'd also be like, ugh, Sandra Bullock,
you don't know me better than this by now?
Now, hold on just a fucking second,
because I'm pretty sure old Sandy B has access to smells
that you could not even fucking imagine, Travis.
That's true, she can get me the match-scented candle.
That's, you're thinking too small.
Like, you don't know what you don't know
about Hollywood smells.
We haven't reached that echelon yet.
Maybe when we walk that Trolls red carpet,
we'll be taken into the sentitorium
and granted access to the forbidden smells.
But, I mean, I would love one of Sandy B's secret candles.
Yeah, like, here's a candle that smells
like winning an Oscar.
Yeah.
Hey, this question, a lot of questions we do
don't have villains other than just life and how it is.
This one does have a villain.
It is not even Thanksgiving yet.
Why is this office busybody looping people
into Secret Santa?
My brain isn't even there yet,
and we're already having to fight about Secret Santas.
You could have gotten to know this person much better.
You had time.
Oh, shit, you have time now.
Well, that's a good point, Trav, I guess, yeah.
Yeah, right?
I guess that's true.
Maybe this is why the office busybody,
or perhaps just friend group busybody,
has done this now, like, hey, you have six weeks
to learn about this person,
and maybe the best present you'll give them is friendship.
This is what Tuesdays with Maury is about, I bet.
We gotta stop saying that every episode.
I know, but I'm just so fascinated by it,
but I'm afraid to read it,
because I think I'll be disappointed
if it doesn't live up to all the predictions
I've made about it over the past, you know, 500 episodes.
Maybe they have put in the legwork
to get to know this person,
and they really are just all about that foot life.
Oh.
Do you know what I mean?
Their house is a foot locker.
Maybe we were wrong at the beginning,
when we were like, it's probably not a bit.
Maybe they did put in the effort,
and they're like, oh, how's it going, Dr. Stanson?
Exquisite toes.
Like, that's like the heat that they bring.
And I'm not saying people who are into feet
are all about that, but I'm saying
this particular podiatrist is into it that deep.
And also, to be fair, I think we maybe jumped to podiatrist,
but all this is they're just specialized in feet.
They might work at a foot locker.
Possible, possible.
If you are a podiatrist, and the question asker says
they specialize in feet, that seems like
a weirdly general way of putting it, right?
It seems like they could have given us a bit more than that.
That would have given some color, I think,
that would have helped.
Maybe, maybe, it's hard to say.
The holidays are tough for everyone, man.
It's so true.
Is it possible to find, is there like a candle sommelier
that you could talk to and say,
give me the candle that's the exact opposite of feet
so that they can burn it in their office
to create a neutral experience?
I'd be here.
Are you talking about fucking smell canceling technology,
Travis, because if so, yes.
Opposite candles that create
the exact opposite smell waves from feet.
Huff the unfoot.
The unfoot.
That's powerful, Trav.
I think, can you get a patent for bullshit
that doesn't exist but should and might?
As long as that's possible.
I think that's specifically what patents are for.
Yes.
This is mine.
No, no, I, no, patents are for,
I figured out a way to do things.
I'm saying a patent for like,
if someone ever does this, I got this,
because like I thought about, oh,
that it needed to happen.
So we can tell a fib to Uncle Government
that we invented the unsmell.
Yeah, what are they gonna do, send someone over to check?
Yeah, what are they gonna do?
Come in and be like, oh, this doesn't pass the smell test.
Mm-hmm.
See, it feels good to let them out, doesn't it?
It does feel good.
Just rip them, baby.
Hey, if I'm gonna buy some secret Santa presents,
I need to go to the money zone.
Oh, well, let's go then.
Get on my back.
Wee.
Griffin, get on Travis's back.
No.
All right, then follow behind, like a sad song.
Oh, yeah.
You know what I wish I could have for Christmas just once?
A good night's sleep.
But I've been sleeping on this pile of hay and rocks,
and I just don't know what to do.
Not just like the baby Jesus.
Just like the baby Jesus.
Except all year round, and not just at Christmas.
What do I do, fellas?
Oh, jeez, Travis.
Well, boy, you gotta go to Casper.
Yeah.
You gotta also tell us if you're gonna set us up like that,
because I thought that you were driving this car,
and then I looked outside,
and you were like a half mile behind us,
and Justin and I were in the backseat trading Pokemon.
I thought Travis was driving,
and Griffin and I decided to look at some of the local flora
and fauna while he drove us to our destination.
No, I was driving.
I just needed you all to check the map
to see where I was going.
Okay.
Oh, bud.
Yeah, listen.
That's a full-time gig.
I can't be occupied with that.
Casper's great.
I'm trying to do my Sudokus back here.
Casper makes the mattresses.
They're so nice.
We all got them.
Got the in-laws in town right now.
They're about to crash on our Casper.
So psyched, so jealous, actually, of them.
And there's products, guys.
These products are cleverly designed to mimic human curves,
providing supportive comfort for all kinds of bodies.
And yeah, the original Casper,
it combines multiple supportive memory foams
for a quality sleep surface.
And it's got sync, it's got bounce
in just the correct sort of ratio that you want.
And also, they got that 100-night risk-free sleep
on it trial that it's gonna do you just right.
Justin, take it over.
So here's what you're gonna do.
You don't wanna take our word for it.
You wanna find out for yourself.
We are untrustworthy.
We are shady.
Proven.
Go to casper.com slash brother
and use the code brother at checkout,
and you're going to get $100 towards select mattresses
by visiting casper.com slash brother
and using the code brother at checkout,
terms and conditions apply.
There's a 100-night risk-free sleep on it trial.
Just give it a whirl, casper.com slash my brother,
and then use the code brother at checkout to save 100 bucks.
I wanna tell you about my new service that I've invented,
and it's called Blayubrin.
And basically, what I do with this service
is I send you already made meals,
and then you're gonna take those meals
and break them back down to their individual components.
Like a puzzle.
Yes, exactly like a puzzle,
except it's like if you bought a puzzle
and it was already done in the box,
and then you had to take it apart.
Fuck, that sounds good.
I would love to smash big puzzles for a living.
And here's the-
It's the best part of puzzles.
The best part about Blayubrin
is that when you are done,
you're gonna ship that on to somebody else,
and then they're gonna take
those individualized ingredients,
they're gonna make a meal out of it.
Right.
Are they gonna eat it, you're asking?
No, that would be disgusting at this point,
because it's easily like two or three weeks old.
They're gonna ship it on to the next person
who's gonna break it back down to the end,
and so on, and so on, and so on.
And if that's fascinating, Travis,
but I'm gonna give you a counter proposal.
How about this?
How about instead of that, whatever that was,
it wasn't comedy, but whatever that was, Travis,
how about instead of that,
they head on over to Blue April
and get ingredients delivered to them,
and they can make something
worth celebrating this holiday season.
So they make the meal and send it,
they send the meal to someone?
No.
No, you actually consume it on site
in front of God and everybody.
There is a wide array of Blue Apron recipes.
They can kinda customize it to different diets.
I've been going a little healthier lately.
Last night, Sid made lettuce wraps
with some beef and farro in it.
It's delicious, it's delicious.
They have wonderful meals that you can make at home.
They're fun to make, and I'll say,
even more fun to eat.
Whoa.
Maybe this season, give yourself the gift
of learning how to be one of the great chefs,
and I don't mean competent in the kitchen.
That's what Blue Apron wants me to say.
What I'm gonna say is begin your journey
towards becoming the next Ratatouille chef guy.
Remi, thank you.
Start now.
Bring the magic of the kitchen back and enjoy a home.
Bring the magic back, bring back the magic of your kitchen.
Hey, bring that back.
Bring Magic Mike back to your kitchen
and have him cook you a home-cooked meal.
Check out this week's menu and get $60 off
when you visit blueapron.com slash my brother.
That's blueapron.com slash my brother.
Blue Apron, cook more.
We interrupt the podcast you're listening to
to tell you about another podcast.
That's right, we got this with Mark and Hal.
That's correct, Mark.
This is Hal.
We do the hard work for you,
settling all of the meaningless arguments
you have with your friends.
So tune in every week on the Maximum Fun Network
for We Got This with Mark and Hal,
and all your questions will be asked and answered.
You're welcome.
All right, that's enough of that.
We got this.
Can I Yahoo?
Please do. Please do.
This one was sent in by Ethan.
Thanks, Ethan.
It's a Yahoo Answers user, oh geez, I Am Male, who asks,
before Tarzan learned about humans,
why is he the only one who's wearing a cloth
while the rest of his gorilla families are naked?
Okay.
Well, I assume it's because gorillas
have a natural protection for their bits,
what with fur and hair and stuff,
and just the way that they walk.
Where humans, because we stand upright,
would have that genitalia exposed and dangerous.
Plus, it would really hurt when you're swinging on vines.
Counter.
Okay.
You don't know that Tarzan doesn't have
a patch of fur down there to protect his stuff.
Well, I mean, I assume he has some fur, you know what I mean?
His monster bush, Trav.
Yeah.
Because he lives in the jungle
where they don't have electric razors and shit,
so he's probably got mad fur down there.
But he probably uses a humorous animal tool,
like on the Flintstones, where we would have,
I don't know, I almost said a beaver,
but that's a little too on the nose, huh?
They have, and I'm thinking about this now,
in Flintstones, he had some sort of weird
prehistoric squirrel guy, right,
who chewed off his beer when he shaved in the morning.
Do you use this?
Ew, wait a minute, is that real?
But Travis is speaking gospel,
like they had animals that occupied.
Like his teeth would go like brrrr.
That's not, but it says,
he's eating Fred Flintstone's beer tray.
He doesn't, I don't think he eats that,
I think it falls harmlessly to the floor.
But Justin, you're.
He's getting, okay, stop.
No, you haven't even let Griffin
get to the heart of the question.
You're in year 2019, I'm in year 3120,
let me get to my shit.
I'm not saying that he is eating some beard,
that's what I'm saying.
Yeah, but let Griffin finish,
because I can see where Griffin's going.
Come with me down the road, the rest of the highway,
because you're 100,000 miles behind me.
He trims the beard, you know he's doing bushwork as well.
Unless they have a separate, nastier, prehistoric squirrel
that gets in there for the edge work.
It's not possible.
It's not efficient, it's not cost efficient,
it's wasteful.
Hey, Fred, can we talk?
It's me, your shaving squirrel.
This is no longer a living.
I've been talking with.
What are you talking about?
It's a symbiotic relationship.
It's not though, because I don't eat the pubes,
I don't need the pubes to live.
I've been talking with.
I need your face hair to live.
Yes, I've been talking with the mammoth
that you use to wash your dishes,
and I've been talking with the pterodactyl
you use to play your records.
And we've decided to unionize, Fred,
and basically the one point, the one point
we all agree on is none of us wanna eat your pubes.
Can you imagine the squirrels all sitting around
and one squirrel's like,
I think you know the worst part about people?
It's when they make you eat their bush.
And then all the other squirrels just fall completely silent.
Jeremy, what did you just say?
Yeah, you know, when they make you eat their bush.
Shut up.
That doesn't happen.
No, that's nothing.
It's nothing, okay.
We agree that's nothing, but can we also agree
it's pretty whack that Tarzan reached a certain age
and his gorilla family is like,
you gotta cover that thing up, son.
That's weird.
What is going on there?
Cover that shit up, dude.
I can see your whole penis, dude, cover it.
Look at Grog's, right, now look at yours.
Now look at yours, it's different, isn't it?
Cover yours up, Tarzan.
It's so different, I can see your whole boobus.
That would be a completely different Tarzan experience
if like Jane and like the whole party was there
and Tarzan just walked in sans loincloth
and everyone's just like, oh God.
And they're just like looking at the sky
as he's like, aye, Tarzan.
They're like, yes, yes we are aware.
Your whole business is just there, Tarzan.
Tarzan's business?
And then you have to explain, I don't know, modesty?
He like steals a top hat from the wealthy benefactor
of this expedition and puts it on his head
and he does a little dance with the Rosie O'Donnell gorilla.
But the whole time the mini driver character's like,
dude, dude, bud, it's out your thing, please.
How often do you think animals in nature
are out like running around or whatever
and just thinking like,
man, I wish we could cover this stuff up?
I would love to have pants right now, it's cool.
And I'll tell you why,
it's because I just ran over some reeds
and I got nipped a few times by him
and I wish I had some sort of shell or protection
like the turtle has.
It's also like cold, man, I wish I had clothes on.
Oh boy.
All right.
I could have done another 15 minutes
on animals in Australia.
Yeah, sure.
I want to munch.
Squad.
I've been hearing from a lot of my Canadian friends
about Christmas pizza.
Now Christmas pizza is a product of Boston pizza,
which is owned of course by Dragons Den,
stalwart Jim TreLiving, used to be a mountain.
That always sounds like you're saying Jim for a living.
Go on.
Nope, it's Jim TreLiving.
Yeah, he owns Mr. Lube, owns Boston Pizza, huge success.
And Boston pizza is going hard this year.
They are going hard because it is the holiday season
and they are bringing you a caroling pizza box.
Huh.
Now this isn't gonna seem that wild, but we'll get to it.
So the pizza box, when you open it,
it will play the song Carol of the Bells.
How, oh, how?
So you open it and I'm assuming they're,
you know, we perfected this technology with greeting cards.
You just open it and then it'll play
Carol of the Bells, right?
Boston Pizza's Niels Van Ooyen, a senior marketing manager,
says that many of its pizza recipes
are unexpected and creative,
so it wanted creative assets to match.
He says that a caroling box is a continuing expression
of the brand's unique point of view.
Oh, that's a long sentence that means nothing.
Here's our point of view.
What if the box sank?
Now, boys, why are they making a caroling pizza box?
You might ask.
Well, for one, they're seeing takeout and delivery
become increasingly irrelevant.
Boston Pizza's classically sort of a sit down chain
where you can enjoy a nice poutine pizza with your family,
but right now, they're providing something very special
and it's the Christmas pizza.
Huh.
Imagine a pizza that you love, okay?
Imagine it with all your favorite toppings.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Okay, now get a rake and scrape all of those off, okay?
So the good toppings are off, right?
Yeah.
So now we're gonna scoop on
their seasoned rotisserie turkey.
Okay.
A house-made stuffing.
Rosemary sage cream sauce.
Oh, okay.
And Italian cheeses.
Okay.
And then we're gonna ladle on some warm turkey gravy.
Oh, boy.
Some warm turkey gravy.
And right in the middle, a huge dollop of cranberry sauce.
Oh, boy.
Oh, and when you buy it, you get a free Toblerone with it.
Okay, okay.
That's not on it.
The whole time, I was like, this sounds dope as hell,
waiting for the goof to kick in.
It's receiving a free Toblerone at the end
that really takes it over the top for me for some reason.
You get a free Toblerone.
I would.
With this delicious pizza.
Here's what I would be afraid of.
Now, we are, of course, forewarned,
but if I was somebody who just ordered a pizza
from them and it came and I opened the box,
and upon opening, the box began making
any kind of noise at all whatsoever,
I would drop it on the ground.
Like, I would throw it across the room,
assuming, I don't know, there's a swarm of bees
or something inside.
Is there bees inside?
Sorry, I'm reading down here a little bit.
There are bees inside.
Just to let you know how wild this place gets,
they also have cranberry barbecue ribs.
I don't understand this restaurant at all.
Well, we ordered a shitload of cranberries.
We just got them.
We gotta put them on everything.
The box sings to you and it's got Thanksgiving inside it.
Yeah.
This is one of the best things you've ever brought,
I would say, Justin.
Hey, if you guys can be quiet for 30 seconds,
I wanna play you an ad for it.
That's right.
Munch Squad AV, here we go.
Christmas pizza, Boston pizza,
this is an ad for a pizza.
Cranberry sauce, gravy on toast,
turkey as well, and also cheese.
Why is there cheese?
Cause we love cheese.
Turkey and cheese, four kinds of cheese.
Come try our Christmas pizza,
this commercial's for Boston pizza.
It's a turkey dinner on a pizza,
pizza underneath the turkey dinner.
Christmas pizza, free topper room,
with a pizza, get it today.
Boston pizza, the gather round.
Free topper room.
That's what they're.
Free topper room in the pizza,
but not on the pizza, don't get it twisted.
It will certainly melt in the delivery process, guaranteed.
I really appreciate that you did that, Justin,
because it did answer my one qualm
with this incredible Thanksgiving pizza,
which is that they still went ahead
and put some fucking cheese on it.
It's not-
They did put cheese on it.
The rest of it, whatever,
cranberry stuffing, mama's broccoli salad,
whatever, go nuts on it,
and it's Thanksgiving on some crust.
I'm into that.
But then they actually also melted some cheese all over it,
and that commercial kindly explains,
well, we like cheese.
Yeah.
Okay, Boston pizza.
Hey, because we had cheese,
and so they should have said-
Hey, gym for a living.
We have it with a bucket load.
Gym for a living, could you step in to R&D real quick?
So, wait, hold on, let me do my fucking gym for a living.
Yeah?
Well, we did what you asked,
and we put a whole fucking Thanksgiving dinner
on a Christmas pizza for some reason.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, that is great.
The problem is-
I love the sound of this pizza.
Well, there's nothing to hold it off.
It's just a bunch of wet, goopy ingredients
kind of piled onto a flat surface.
It's just going everywhere.
So-
Well, let me think about my assets.
I got Mr. The Lube, does that help?
No, I would say that just,
that would make it more goopy, I would argue.
Okay, I also own Boston Pizza,
the restaurant that we're standing in right now.
And you know what we got at Boston Pizza?
Pizza?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll let you get there,
because that's going to be real satisfying.
Singing boxes, I don't know, Jim.
You had us working on that too.
Can't we just make regular pizza with like-
Cheese!
It's just that I didn't get my chocolate and pizza.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
God damn it.
These rocket boots were supposed to kick off
whenever I said cheese,
and I was going to blast out the ceiling.
God damn it.
All right, hold on one second.
Fuck.
Let me try again, hold on.
Cheese!
Oh God, he exploded.
Am I still here?
No, you're on fire.
Oh damn it, hold on, let me get this out.
He's melting the cheese on the pizza.
It's perfect.
It was all part of my plan.
Anyway, I'm glad I could help.
Cheese!
Okay, now it's working.
God damn it.
Now it worked that time.
Ah, shit.
Hey, how about another question?
Yeah, do you have a question about what just happened?
I don't have any questions for all I just have,
it makes perfect sense to me.
It all tracked to me.
I'm going to need to travel for work this week.
And I said I was thinking of driving myself.
While my co-worker's thinking of flying
or taking the train.
Man, it's a boring start.
Let's hang in there though.
Together so far, it's pretty boring.
I don't see what's boring, the rest of the question is,
and if we leave at the same time
and I'm going 60 miles an hour.
Right, yeah, all right.
Sorry, let me find my place here.
A co-worker who I absolutely can't stand
said it would be cost effective if I took someone with me.
Pointing to himself.
Yeah, we got it.
I think I responded kind of non-committally.
How the fuck do I shut this down
so I don't have an aneurysm during a three hour drive
with this completely inseparable person?
This is tough because it is more cost efficient.
Yeah, it is.
That's true, it's much more cost efficient.
You could tell them your car's cursed
and anytime you drive with someone, they die.
Okay, but that's gonna be tough to believe, I worry.
Yeah, but I would also argue
if this inseparable person isn't also completely dense,
they're gonna read between the lines
and get that you don't wanna ride with them.
Do you think that?
Because I find that people,
one of the things that they lack,
people who are tough to kind of hang out with a lot,
one of the things that they tend to lack
is sort of basic, you know?
Yeah.
Kind of like getting it.
The stuff that we all kind of agree to without saying it.
Right, yeah, just sort of like the stuff
where like we all get it.
Like the type of person
who would invite themselves along
on a three plus hour road trip
with someone who they don't really get along with.
Well, they don't know, see, okay, Jarv, here's the thing.
They don't know they don't get along with you.
This is what I'm saying.
They don't have the stuff.
They don't have what it takes.
Okay, I'm changing my mind on this.
You need to go on this road trip.
It's the holiday season,
and if holiday planes, trains, automobiles, I love it.
What's the one with the dude from Married with Children
where he goes to pick up his, I guess, new son,
like stepson or something?
You remember that one.
It's not called, no.
Sorry?
Yes, with Tim Allen, Timothy Allen?
No.
Right, JTT?
No, there's that one.
JTT's in it. I'll be home for Christmas.
No, on that one he goes home by himself.
Yeah, that's not what I'm talking about though.
I'm talking about the one with Ed O'Neil.
Good flick though, good flick.
Where he goes to pick up the kid
and has to like drive him back to his family.
You know the one.
Duff.
Yes, thank you.
Ed O'Neil's only been in one movie.
If you had just said the words Ed O'Neil,
there's a chance. I said Ed O'Neil at least twice.
Duff.
Dutch. Good flick.
It was Dutch, damn it.
Dutch, Griffin, it was Dutch.
Did Justin play it?
It wasn't Duff.
It was Dutch.
Damn it.
Duff's my porn parody.
Huh, that's a weird one.
That's a weird conversion there, Justin.
Okay.
So anyway, do a Planes, Trains, and Automobiles with him.
It was Dutch.
I gotta stop doing this podcast with the two of you.
The cover of the movie has him carrying the child in a bag.
Wow, that is grim.
Yeah.
The T in Dutch in the title is just him shrugging,
which says a lot about the movie to me.
Ethan Embry is in it.
Ethan Embry is not in my porn parody.
I do not know where you heard that.
I could never afford Ethan Embry.
No, he's in Dutch.
He plays Doyle.
The two main characters in this movie
are Dutch Dooley and Doyle Standish.
That's rough.
I say go on the road trip, I think.
To get to know his girlfriend's son,
a working class good guy,
volunteers to pick him up from a prep school.
I'm gonna play Pokemon.
Only to learn that her son isn't the nicest kid.
Written by John Hughes.
What else about Dutch trash?
JoBeth Williams is in it.
Oh, huge.
I'm gonna look at the trivia.
Right now, I feel like how 80% of our audience feels
when we discuss Frasier.
I finally get it, everybody.
Can we talk about Frasier real quick?
Oh my God.
In a meta sense,
not one that requires knowledge of Frasier.
People who listen to our show
talk a lot about how our Frasier jokes go over their head
because they never watched Frasier.
I want to be kind of clear about something.
We didn't watch Frasier either.
We don't know.
We osmose some Frasier.
There's Frasier particulate in the air that we inhaled.
I have watched, I would say 45 minutes of Frasier
non-consecutively.
Yeah, hey guys, don't sweat it.
Nobody watched Frasier.
We all just agreed.
We all allowed it to be on,
but nobody actually watched Frasier.
There's not some context you're missing here.
It's Kelsey Grammer.
He is-
Fancy boys.
A fancy boys, but the dad's isn't.
And he has a dog and a stinky chair.
That's it.
End of synopsis.
Should I do another question?
Because I almost certainly cut about 90%
of that hot Dutch material and threw it right in the-
Oh, that should be the porn version.
Hot Dutch.
Hot Dutch material.
Now, wait a minute.
Travis has just opened up a cool idea,
which is just like, if you want to make a pornography jaws,
you would just do hot jaws.
Hot jaws.
Mel Gibson turned down the role of Dutch.
Are you fucking-
You can't pivot back around-
Nothing is Dutch.
Dutch is nothing.
If our audience doesn't get fucking Frasier,
they're not going to get Dutch, okay?
None of us on this call saw Dutch.
Is that agreed?
Wait, hold on.
Guys, this is a tasty one.
This is a tasty.
Six of 15 people found this interesting.
Hold on, hold on, Travis.
I gotta fucking, cause you said it.
I had to sing the tasty Dutch trivia jingle
or people will go wild.
It's Dutch.
Don't worry too much.
Cause it's time for Dutch.
Hot Dutch trivia.
Now, there's a piece of trivia.
Six of 15 found this interesting.
Dutch, parentheses, Ed O'Neil.
Wait, hold on.
That's a bad hit rate.
I see nine out of 15 people that cared enough
to go look at the trivia for Dutch.
You had to rate it very good.
Looked at it and said,
this actually isn't very interesting.
I'm sorry that I wasted so much time
looking at the trivia for Dutch.
And you said, hold on, I gotta put this on a podcast.
Dutch, parentheses, Ed O'Neil, and parentheses,
says that at one point in his life,
he drove a concrete truck, period.
He and Doyle later hitch a ride on a truck
that carries concrete pipes.
End of trivia.
Why are we talking about this fucking movie so much?
There's some trivia too, but it's mostly spoilers.
Sometimes I don't know how to stop it, Griff.
That's what worries, that's what I get worried, honestly.
I've tried a few times, Justin.
I'm gonna have to say, you're a little bit complicit.
You did write a whole song for Travis's-
It's a jingle.
Okay.
If you're not gonna do them, I got to.
I got another Yahoo here.
And we'll do it real fast.
We gotta end on not Dutch.
I'm looking through the cast list down-
Graham Robux- I'm just trying to see
if there's any hidden gems.
Graham Robux, from Yahoo Answers user la-la-la-la,
who asks, when you catch a Frisbee, what are your options?
Huh.
When you catch a Frisbee, what are your options?
Like, keep it?
Catch it with both hands, or one hand is cool.
You can do the one where you jump in the air
and you catch it under your leg,
like you're a neat youth pastor.
Behind the back. I would say the best option
is to always act like it's the first time
you've ever successfully caught a Frisbee.
And make it a real celebration.
You know what I mean?
Cause catching it's not assumed, right?
There's no guarantee in this world
that you're going to catch that Frisbee.
So let's treat every time like it's your first.
Yep.
You could also catch it and take a big bite out of it.
Yeah, catch it in your mouth like a doggie
and take a big bite out of it,
but then nobody can throw the Frisbee.
So that's actually not,
I'm gonna say that's actually not one of your options.
I mean, it is an option.
I would say probably the biggest crack up you could do
would be to catch it
and then immediately spin around 180 degrees
and chuck it as hard as you can
at a person that is not there.
That would be a real crack up.
Yeah, and you can shout like, catch dad.
And then you throw it to nobody as far as you can.
And then you can look kind of sad
and no one's gonna ask you to clarify what just happened.
I guarantee it.
You know, the director of Dutch,
it was his last movie he directed.
You could throw it up in the air
and then have it coming right back down to you
and then say like, it's just me from now on.
You guys can go home
and you keep throwing it up to yourself.
You could catch it and be like, oh nice, Dutch on DVD.
But this only works with the Frisbee is Dutch on DVD.
Correct.
You could have another Frisbee
that you throw at the other Frisbee in midair
to knock it out.
And when you do that, you yell, Beyblade, rip it up!
This has been our show, my brother and me.
Catch her to throw.
Do a back flip in midair.
If you are in Canada
and you get one of these Christmas pizzas,
please tweet us a picture.
Make it clap right on that Frisbee disc.
What it looks like.
Cause I bet it does not look as tantalizing
as these images make it appear.
I feel like that could break bad really easily.
And if you are listening to this
and Dutch is your favorite movie,
please let me know.
I'm gonna hang up on the Skype call.
You guys finish it.
Please let me know if Dutch is your favorite movie.
Oh, Griffin did leave.
So anyway, this has been my brother, my brother, me.
We hope you enjoyed it.
We hope you're gonna download Dutch today.
And oh, Griff's back.
Thank goodness.
I wanna thank John Roderick and the Long Winters.
I'm just gonna barrel on through.
Cause I-
I won't reference the D movie again.
I can do a noise cancellation.
The D movie is the, of course, the third sequel
to the B movie.
Okay.
All right.
Now we're back in safe territory.
Make a judgment on B movie.
We got it all out of our system.
Okay.
Go ahead, Travis.
The latest episode of Paul Blart Moncop
Till Death Do Us Blart is out now
where we watch Paul Blart Moncop 2 every Thanksgiving.
The three of us and Guy Montgomery and Tim Batt
from Worst Idea of All Time.
Episode five is up now if you haven't listened to it yet.
Also, because it is a new month,
there's lots of new merch to check out
over at McElroyMerch.com.
We're excited to see you all at Candle Nights
here in a couple of weeks.
If you're gonna be at the show,
make sure you send in questions,
make sure you write that they are, you know,
for the Candle Nights show in the subject line
that goes for Yahoo's as well.
What else, fellas?
Oh, if you can't come to Candle Nights,
you can still be a Candle Nights star.
Every year, Riley Smurl and the other two Smurls,
all the whole Smurl family,
of Still Buffering fame raise money.
This year, it's going to contact
a Huntington-based organization.
This is a 24-hour rape crisis center.
And it's a fun organization.
And for just $5, you can get a Candle Nights star
that we will display during the show.
So I think that's pretty cool.
Absolutely. Honestly.
I think you should go do that right now.
I want to thank John Roderick and the Long Winters
for the use of our theme song.
It's a departure off the album,
Putting the Days to Bed.
Great tune, great track.
One of the best, it's Rolling Stone's best song.
They said. They said it.
Rolling Stone said best song.
And thanks to Maximum Fun for having us on the network.
Go check out that hot new website, MaximumFun.org.
Go look at all the shows on it.
Oh, you know what's a great gift?
You know what's a great gift to get someone?
If you say Dutch on DVD, I swear to God.
The knowledge that in just a couple months,
they are going to receive a copy
of the Adventure Zone Graphic Novel Book 3.
Oh, right.
You can pre-order that now, maybe include like a letter
about it in an envelope that says,
hey, in July, this book's all yours.
It's based on the Pedals to the Metal arc
and it is so good, y'all.
Super good.
It's so good.
You're gonna like it.
I got a final Yahoo here.
This one was sent in by Jeanette.
Thanks, Jeanette.
It's from an anonymous Yahoo Answers user
who I'm gonna call Dumpy asks,
what was the best decade of the 1990s?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
My name is Justin McElroy.
Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
It's been my brother, my brother.
May kiss your dad's square on the lips.
I hate the girls, do you want to say, and I want to.
Maximumfun.org.
Comedy and culture.
Artist owned.
Audience supported.
One, two, one, two, three, four.
Hi, everybody.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Sydney McElroy.
We're both doctors and
Nope, just me.
Okay, well Sydney's a doctor
and I'm a medical enthusiast
and we create Sawbones,
a marital tour of misguided medicine.
Every week I dig through the annals of medical history
to bring you the wildest, grossest,
sometimes dumbest tales of ways
we've tried to treat people throughout history.
And lately we do a lot of modern fake medicine
because everything's a disaster,
but it's slightly less of a disaster every Friday
right here on Maximumfun.org
as we bring you Sawbones,
a marital tour of misguided medicine.
And remember, don't drill a hole in your head.