The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello, and welcome to My Brother, My Brother and Me, and it's an advice show for the Modron era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy. I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother and 30 under 30 media luminary, Griffin McElroy.
Justin, for a second, it kind of sounded like you were starting with like a Yakov Smyrnov thing
there. Hello, hello America. Is that still, is that still topical? Yakov Smyrnov, is that?
My name is Chester Bengleton. I come from other country.
Okay, I guess follow-up question, is it also now deeply problematic,
and maybe has it always been? Hugely, hugely, wildly.
Defo.
Oh, good.
Have you? I mean, but his show is like so wildly patriotic in its best length.
And so incredibly xenophobic.
It's weirdly very xenophobic. It's like he got in and he was like,
that is it, everybody. Nobody else different. I'm the last one. Everybody else figure out.
Yakov Smyrnov looks at Borat and he's like, that's too far.
You've gone too far.
Wait to ruin it for the rest of us.
Becoming Dracula a little bit.
So sorry that we missed the day of days. We try to come out with an episode on every 420.
And honestly, y'all, we just couldn't get it done.
I tried to do April 20th episode, but then I got high.
So, and that's when we could have done.
That's when we could have done, but we did.
Do y'all remember that song is all about responsibilities this person had,
but they didn't end up doing them.
It's a cautionary tale.
It's a cautionary tale. And it's really a powerful anti-drug message.
If you think about it. Yeah.
Cause it's like I was supposed to pay my rent and then I got high
and then I got evicted from my apartment and lost my job.
And I was supposed to read at the library to kids, but then I got high.
Yeah. I was supposed to take my heart medicine, but then I got high and I died teens.
And now I'm a ghost warning you from beyond the grave. I know the cush is fun.
But then I got high.
A lot of people are excited for the episode we got coming up here in about 17 episodes
because it will be the 420th episode.
And I don't know how to start laying the groundwork to not disappoint those people
because of how, just how profoundly detached we are.
I feel like to make a weird pop culture pull,
it kind of feels like in Buffy the Vampire Slayer
when the demons like don't celebrate Halloween because it's so cliche.
I feel like for our 420th episode,
we should just make it devoid of any jokes about dank nugs and blunts.
Alternative idea.
And I had this last night and I was thinking about it.
We, instead of putting up a proper episode,
just take all the audio out of an episode of Family Guy and put that up instead.
Is that now?
Justin, you know some things about entertainment law.
Yes.
If I put up just 23 tight minutes of Stewie and Brian,
just thinking about these two clowns makes me start rolling,
even when I'm not on the cush.
It's a great question, Griffin.
You can do that.
The one issue you do need to be careful of
is you gotta make sure you have the audio from the commercials in there as well
because that's the only way it counts for them towards that money.
And that's Seth's money, guys.
Hey guys, I'm not here to take Seth's money.
That's his money.
So you gotta leave the commercials in it on that one.
Let me ask you a question.
What if, instead of just straight taking all the audio from one episode,
we did a super cut of an hour of all of the uh and er sounds
from a bunch of episodes of Family Guy?
Oh, a Family Guy.
I kind of thought you were going to say our podcast
because there's a lot of source material.
No, no, no.
All Family Guy, and you just hear all the different voices,
most of them Seth, and you just hear all the uh, er, uh, ah, uh, eh.
What if we did just one episode of my Bim Bam
where each of us brought an episode of Family Guy
and just tried to recap it as much as we could?
Like a book report?
Yeah, a book report, and we could talk about all the great cutaway jokes,
and we could talk about the baby trying to kill the mom.
Do you think America would listen to a podcast called
that Great Family Guy Humor?
This is us recapping individual select episodes.
Oh, we call it Extended Family Guy.
That's good.
Nuclear Family Guy.
We'll keep workshopping it.
I'm just so sorry we missed.
I didn't do really any good weed humor.
I tweeted one thing at like 4.05 on 4.20 thinking like,
okay, and then in 15 minutes a punchline,
and then I didn't. I didn't.
I forgot. Then I got high.
I was gonna tweet something so funny, but then I got high.
Snoop on the evening of 4.19 tweeted,
don't forget to leave milk and cookies out for me tonight.
That's pretty good.
It was, I had a very good chortle.
We leave it to the professionals,
the professionals who know where weed even comes from.
Thank you.
The ground from Gaia.
It comes from Gaia.
I keep telling everybody it's natural.
Even John Boehner now is on the crazy wave.
Does he party?
Yeah, now he's in the industry.
He's in the biz now.
I'm so worried that someday when she is much,
much older and understands language,
that BB is gonna write a tell all book
that reveals my horrible secret
that I don't know where to get weed from.
And most of these jokes are based on nothing.
Yeah.
I'm just so afraid that everyone's gonna find out
my nasty truth that I didn't do as much drugs as I said I did.
And I don't know where it came from, this idea,
or why every time anyone sees the number 420 in the wild,
or on the same topic, the number 69 in the wild,
and they make sure to snap a pic and send it to me.
Because both those numbers are not numbers
that reflect the core of my being.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
That's the thing is the McElroy brothers,
we don't celebrate a lot of artifice.
And like the only artifice and irony we have
is that we are cool.
It's that we think that we are edgy in any sort of way.
Any sense.
Like I'm almost to the point where I could get it
for my glaucoma.
Like that's about where I'm at on the scale.
So let's help some people.
Oh, by the way, Texas, if you came out last weekend,
is that, was it last weekend?
Yeah.
Yes, last weekend.
Thank you.
That was very fun.
You were all good eggs.
And thank you to everybody who came to the Moon Tower Show,
the Schmaner's Moon Tower Show.
Oh, that was good.
Oh, it was so good.
Good.
It was amazing.
Do you think maybe we could,
do you think maybe we could open with a Yahoo?
Cause I got four Yahoo's this week that are all club bangers.
I'm very excited about.
This one was sent in by Adrian Cowles,
who is so deep in the game right now,
just like crushing it, crushing it, crushing it.
Thank you so much, Adrian.
Well, on their way to earning a nickname perhaps,
or a tagline.
Getting there.
It's by Yahoo Answers user NickA07, who asks,
how do I be brave on the Twilight Zone Tower of Terror?
Well, good news.
It's not that anymore.
Now it's the Guardians of the Galaxy prism break extreme.
Not in Florida, baby.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It's still a big drop, right?
It's still a big scary drop.
And I don't think.
Yeah, but now there's a raccoon sitting next to you,
holding your hand.
Okay, well that might help.
But let's imagine that wasn't true.
This will be my first time going on a drop tower ride,
especially at Walt Disney World's Hollywood Studios.
Is that what it's called?
I felt like I don't want to go on it because I'm scared.
And I am tired of being scared.
But my mom's said she's going on it,
but her back hurts.
I'm worried something could happen to her
if I don't go on with her.
IDK, what to do when the time comes?
What should I do?
Should I go on with her or not?
How do I be brave for this ride?
How do I feel safe?
I am just afraid what it will feel like
when I float off my seat in the air when dropping.
I do worry too much, lol.
Seriously, I need help.
Okay, wait.
We'll get to that in a second.
What does this person think that they are going to do
to help their mother's back while they're there?
Just hold the spine.
Hold the spine upright while the drop is happening
and try to cushion the tailbone when the ground hits.
I think it's wild that this is a ride
where you plummet 10 stories
and then come to an immediate zero miles an hour stop.
Yeah, by hitting the ground.
By hitting the ground, it's extremely dangerous.
And I guess, hey, you know what?
I just figured out where they get all the fucking ghosts from.
And it's the former writers of the ride.
So it's cool that Disney World has two exits,
really, if you think about it.
The main one in front of Mickey's castle.
And then the Tower of Terror,
which is sort of a more permanent exit.
I'll tell you what not to do.
If you're asking me about Tower of Terror etiquette,
I can- Not etiquette.
Fear.
But I'm gonna tell you what not to do.
I went on the Tower of Terror, Teresa and I went,
and it kind of hovers at the top for a second
before plummeting to your death.
Hovers at the top.
And just before it dropped,
somebody let out a blood-curdling scream,
before it dropped.
And everybody's emotional ride was ruined by that.
Because everybody just turned around and went,
and then it dropped.
I thought you were gonna say
they let out a blood-curdling toot.
Which might be nice, actually,
because somebody toots and you're like,
oh, who did,
whoa, at least I'm falling out of the fart cloud.
Yeah.
So that could be something
you could be grateful for the drop,
because it's like,
oh, Mickey, get me out of this fart cloud.
It is Mickey, right, who does it,
pulls the drop lever?
Yeah.
He appears out of nowhere and is like,
I'm here.
Goodbye.
You're fucked.
Peace out.
Hold on to your mom's back.
Don't forget to hold your mom's back.
Tootles, bring me the hemorrhoid donut.
Tootles, bring her mom's back.
I got this one wrong.
This is how I get my kicks.
Be careful.
My mom's spine telescoped on this one.
Now, which one was that?
Who was that, Griffin?
That was Donald.
Now, here's how Donald went.
Oh, please give me Donald.
That would be actually much scarier.
Oh my god, drop it, drop it, drop it.
I can't.
Kill me, kill me.
Escape Donald, the ride.
Is it possible to...
Do you know what would make
Twilight Zone Tower of Terror
a hundred thousand times scarier?
What?
If one out of every 20 rides,
or maybe it's 50-50,
it just operates like a normal functioning elevator.
Ah, that would be good.
It takes you up to the top,
and then it's like, here we go.
And then it slowly lowers you back down to the ground.
And you get a little speech about expectations
and disappointment.
But then, you don't know which one you're gonna get, right?
I just made it scarier, they're not less scary,
which is what this person asked for.
Griffin, how about this, right?
50-50, one time it operates like a normal elevator,
which is it starts to drop,
but then it opens on like every other floor,
and someone goes, oh, you know what,
I'll get the next one.
And like, so it's just kind of like,
oh, we did, oh, oh.
And you keep thinking the drop is coming,
and just like Skrillex,
you gotta wait for that drop,
and it never comes.
Oh, I mean, I can't stop thinking of ways
to make it scarier,
but I'm thinking about my own
sort of real life elevator fears.
And obviously getting stuck is bad.
That's one way to make it scarier,
is if it also sometimes just like stopped.
But what if the doors open on one floor,
and there was a big family,
all with a bunch of suitcases,
and you knew they were gonna try
to all squeeze on the elevator.
Oh, no.
Hey, listen to this one.
Listen to this joke I got.
All right.
What if on one floor it opened up,
and there was a guy, and he was in a suit,
and his suit just had a bunch of summer squashes on it,
and his name was Reginald Q. Summer Squash,
Summer Squash, and he kind of did his thing.
Now, what's his thing, Justin?
What's his thing, Juice?
Can you describe the...
Exactly.
Oh, okay.
He's his own thing.
I'm really glad you said that, Justin,
because I was gonna make a goof
about like you're on the elevator,
and you know you have to get somewhere important,
but a whole bunch of like people
that just got out of the pool,
and are still like dripping wet get on,
and you're trying.
But your thing about someone in a...
Let me get this again.
Summer Squash suit.
Was that it?
Now, is he by himself?
No, there are two sort of spooky entities with him
to be decided later.
I gotta say, this does remind me of Saturday Night Live bit.
Haven't seen it.
Yeah, well, it was very similar.
Go to bed early on Saturdays.
Typically got a newborn, so...
The bit was called Gilly.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, that was back before I had kids.
Gilly.
You unloved child.
I'll scoop up Gilly.
If no one else here will love the Gilly sketch,
I will take care of Gilly.
Please climb into my satchel, Gilly.
I'll carry you through the wasteland.
I'm here for you, the sketch, Gilly.
My favorite on Saturday Night Live
is when someone's doing an impression of somebody,
and that person actually shows up,
and it's so embarrassing.
How could you do this?
How did you not know that Hillary Clinton was right there?
You didn't know.
I'm right behind you.
Catherine McKinnon was doing an impression of her,
but then the actual Hillary showed up.
How awkward.
Catherine McKinnon, is she your third grade teacher?
Are you on that formal of a basis for this, McKinnon?
You think I'm just gonna be all chummy and be like,
yo, Kate, what's up, buddy?
Special K.
How about a question?
I recently made some new acquaintances
who live just a few blocks away from me.
My friend and I were recently at their place
working on a project,
and we commented on their beautiful enclosed porch,
to which they replied,
oh yeah, you're free to use it anytime,
even if we're not at home.
I was shocked by this offer,
but laughed it off as if they're just joking.
However, my friend said she planned to drop by
and knit on their porch later this week
when they are at work.
Am I right in not hanging out in the home of someone
I don't know very well when they are not there,
or am I missing out?
That's from porch squatter in Portland.
This is unacceptable.
It's clearly unacceptable
because we could get into a debate
about where does house start?
For me, I feel uncomfortable walking in front
of people's houses on the sidewalk sometimes
because if their kids go out there
and do chalk drawings on it,
that's house, baby.
I sometimes feel weird driving by a house
and looking at it too long.
Mm, yeah.
And then your little gold tooth shines and sparkles
because you're planning to steal all their treasures.
Oh, the idea of someone,
I just feel 24 seven,
someone assumes I'm casing the joint.
Yeah, for sure.
So I think we could get into a debate
about if porch is house,
except for the fact that it is an enclosed porch.
When you put walls around it,
hey gang, when you put walls around it,
that's a house, baby.
This is true.
Think about the difference
between garage and driveway, right?
That is basically driveway outside,
garage inside.
That's a house.
And now that's a house.
If I took my kitchen and did sort of a open concept,
that's not what the term traditionally means,
but I knocked down all the walls in the kitchen
and put up screens instead
so that everybody could smell all the great pies
and cookies I'm always making,
then that's still house.
Do you know what I mean?
You can't just go in someone's house
when they're not there.
End of discussion, it feels like, right?
Is there a discussion to be had?
You do have the direct,
the person did directly say,
feel free to use my porch whenever.
I did do this in college though.
I would go to Jason Eldridge's house
and we would all sit on his porch and use his grill.
Even if he wasn't at home, and he was always at home,
so this is theoretical,
but if he wasn't at home,
if he was at Arby's or Office Depot or something,
then we would just sit on his porch.
But I was younger then.
It was a different time.
I think there's an exception to be carved out
for weed and EverQuest dens,
which is kind of what Jason's house was,
I feel like, for you guys.
At that point, it's more of a community space.
It's more of like a neighbor.
It's like 18 to 24,
what we would traditionally think out of as a hangout.
Yeah, it's your peach pit.
Rather than like somebody's family home.
Yes, it's a non-starter.
Let me hit you with this,
how do you guarantee that they're not home?
Because you gotta be sure.
I'm talking about you,
you need to break and enter first just to make sure nobody's home,
and then lock the doors up as you're leaving,
and then you can hang out on the porch,
because can you imagine hanging out on the porch,
and then somebody walks outside like,
what the fuck are you doing?
I'd rather have that than for me to be sitting on the porch
and somebody comes home from work
and they've had like a terrible day at work,
or like their boss yelled at them,
and they didn't get their shit done,
and it's just like,
hey buddy, just me reading on your porch, drinking some lemonade.
You sure do look rough.
And it's just like, get the fuck out of here.
This is my fucking castle.
Eventually, you're right, Travis,
if you do this every day,
eventually there will come a day
when they're like, get off my porch.
I need this porch today.
This is important right now.
Did you schedule this?
I hung up a thing and it says mine on every day.
Get out.
That's the reason I get it.
Every day, get out, the reason I couldn't do this
is because it's not in my house.
I'm like a toddler with the number of accessories
that I require.
What if I got there and I realized that my Pepsi Max,
because it was in a useless 20 ounce plastic bottle,
got warm because all plastic bottles do instantly
the second you take them out of refrigeration.
It got warm and now I have a warm drink.
What do I do now?
Well, I guess I drive home.
I guess now I have to get in my car
and drive back to my house.
Also, the problem is that they invited you to use the porch.
So if you don't use the porch, it's gonna be rude.
You gotta do something pretty heinous on that porch
to get that invite revoked.
Do you know what I mean?
And then you won't have this problem anymore.
So I don't know what that looks like.
I don't know if that means leaving a bunch of ham slices
all over.
I don't know if it means leaving a bunch of roast beef slices
I don't know if it means hiding pepperonis.
Unless.
Unless you start making improvements to the porch
because Justin's made me think like maybe you set up
like a mini fridge out there, right?
You make enough improvements until now it's fair use
and it's your porch.
It's our porch.
I've remixed it fair use.
It's a fair use porch.
Yeah.
That could be good.
What if you buy me a mini fridge I hate
and then I can't just,
I was gonna get a mini fridge next week.
Now you've bought me one I hate and I can't justify it.
I'm stuck with this one.
It's got room for half a Coke.
The other half sticks out the top of it.
It only cools the bottom half of the can of Coke.
Why did you get this terrible fridge?
It was on sale.
There's three baby teeth in it.
Like what?
Does this use?
Was this someone who was storing baby teeth in?
It only cools half a Coke?
Maytag has a new fridge
and they put the baby teeth right in there
because it's supposedly soaked up the stink really good.
I don't know if you ever smelled the baby tooth before
but good God.
Yeah, it's rough.
This Yahoo was sent in by Graham Roebuck.
Thank you, Graham.
It's Yahoo Answers user question mark who asks,
how do you, let me read a voice.
How do you eat a hot dog in a fancy way?
And then there's a picture of a hot dog.
Just for reference?
Yeah, it's a big Frank, big thick Frank.
Big Francis.
With a line of mustard on it.
How do you, excuse me.
I'm going to the marina later
and some of my fellow business,
I don't even know what like fancy people sound like.
Maybe it's like Downton Abbey,
but an episode where they all crush some dogs.
You know what I mean?
So like Matthew comes in, he's like,
Uncle, look what I've discovered from the Americas.
They're like our sausages,
but they don't taste like any sort of discernible thing.
They call them wieners.
They call them wieners like a dick, uncle.
So I've invited the Duchess over for dogs
and I'm trying to figure out how not to get mustard
on my fancy boy gloves.
And I tried biting into one of them
and it expressed a juice
that managed to get all over my frock.
And so uncle, uncle, help me eat the hot dog in a fancy way.
There's no scene in Downton Abbey
that would not be improved by one or more of the characters
enjoying a hot dog as it continued.
What if just once there was a really dramatic thing,
you've lost it all, how could,
and as it panned across there's just a servant
sitting in a chair and he's eating a hot dog
just as it like just kind of goes past in a tracking shot.
And you're just like, wait, hold on.
Is that the under butler just eating a hot dog?
I think that guy's eating a hot,
is Lady Crawley eating, oh my God, it's a hot dog.
She's got like five of them on a paper plate.
That's the episode.
She's an American.
And so she can eat the dogs and bring them all in
and she'll be like, oh, you guys are gonna love this.
I don't know, it looks like one of our sausages,
but it stinks a lot.
She's got like a paper plate of hot dogs
and like a two liter of like store brand root beer.
And like that's it.
That's it.
And then maybe the servants are all eating it
and all the rich people are like,
I would never eat the hot dog.
A hot dog, how could you?
You've heated the dog, it stinks so bad.
Why do I wanna eat it and watch baseball?
And then they all do.
And then they're like, you know what, pores?
Maybe we have more in common than I initially thought.
Now hand me a, do we drink the hot dog water?
What do we do with the water left over from the hot dogs?
Bring me more tubular meat.
Give me a split bun and some tubular meat.
And then they decide that only they can have hot dogs
and they don't let the servants have them anymore
because now they're-
You can have this lobster and filet mignon.
Give me another one of those round boys.
And then there's an episode
because Lord Grantham is only eating hot dogs
and it's been three weeks.
He just loves them so much
but it's the only thing he'll put into his body
so that he's become wracked with illness.
And then World War II happens.
And then there's no more hot dogs.
They gotta send all their hot dogs to hands.
To the war effort.
The Titanic sank.
There were 20 tons of hot dogs on the Titanic.
No.
Did someone think of the hot dogs?
All of those round boys at the bottom of the ocean
getting eaten by those fish.
How much better would Titanic have been
if at the end an old woman threw a hot dog into the ocean
and you watched it for 40 minutes
as it disintegrated in the water
and then it sunk and it landed on the jewel of the ocean,
the heart of the ocean.
How do you eat a hot dog in a fancy way?
If I ever saw somebody with a knife and fork
I would call the police.
So that's out.
I think you dip it in water to help you eat it faster.
That's what Kobayashi-
I'm sorry.
You've watched Joey Chestnut do his work
and then you thought,
wow, what a fancy fucking gentleman.
What a fancy bully.
You've thought that.
That's the thing.
Think this way Griffin, right?
Have you ever been impressed by someone eating hot dogs
outside of a hot dog eating competition?
No, but I've never watched a hot dog eating competition
and thought anybody there was fancy in any way.
Well, it depends on how you define fancy, doesn't it?
Because yeah, if you're talking fucking Downton Abbey, no.
But if you're talking like skateboard trick fancy?
If there's no fancy way to eat a hot dog,
then the best you can do is get it over with
quickly so you have more time for like cotillion classes
or what the fuck ever fancy people did.
I see.
So if you blaze through the dogs,
then it's like you have plenty of time to go like,
you know, polish your shoes or-
Yes.
If you pair the hot dog eating with a fancy thing.
Why?
If you, oh.
Hot dog, why?
Why?
Okay, so-
The meat might not be fancy, but boy, this-
Name a wine, name a wine, name any wine.
The Chardonnay that we-
You pair it with Chardonnay.
You would not, oh, hot dog with Chardonnay, Justin.
I just wanted to say, I Googled hot dog wine
and the top result is the Marshall Hall of Fame Cafe
in Huntington, Virginia.
I don't know if they have a dish.
Don't boil it in water.
Boil it in wine.
Boil those wieners in wine.
Make them wine-ers.
Oh, these Franks will get you fucked, dog.
Oh my God.
These are Griffin McElroy's 100% alcoholic hot dogs.
You're going to love these.
I bet the Dave Matthews Band wine pairs really nicely
with a hot dog.
If you're going to Frank down,
I think maybe have some of the Dave Matthews Band wine.
That would be so good.
Or maybe some of Sting's wine.
Yeah.
Wait, can we go back to the Dave Matthews Band wine?
Cause I just got there and it's,
it'll drink you under the table and dreaming.
Thank you.
There it is.
Yeah, it took me a second, but I wanted to circle back.
Okay, good job.
Those are many fancy ways of being a hot dog.
And now I would welcome you all right this way.
Through the adjoining chamber into here, the money zone.
For cigars and brandy and hot dogs.
I want to tell you about Casper.
Then do it, coward.
Casper, one, supports my brother, my brother and me,
but also supports you while you sleep.
I have a Casper mattress.
I have a Casper mattress, I sleep on it.
When I, this is very good.
Yeah, listen, this is not a joke.
When we tour, I love getting out there,
seeing the fans, doing our goofs, hitting the road.
But you know what I don't love?
Being away from my Casper mattress.
Now here's the thing you're thinking.
Oh, this sounds too good to be true.
It must be super expensive.
No, no, no.
They offer affordable prices because Casper cuts out
the middleman and sells directly to the consumer.
It's a great deal and a great mattress.
They combine multiple supportive memory phones
for a quality sleep service with the right amount.
And you're thinking, oh, what?
Right amount of sink or bounce?
No, no, no, both sink and bounce.
And you can be sure of your purchase
because Casper is 100 night risk-free sleep audit trial.
Right now you can get $50 towards select mattresses
by visiting Casper.com slash my brother
and using the coupon code mybrother, all one word,
at checkout.
Terms and conditions apply.
Casper.com slash mybrother, promo code mybrother,
all one word.
Can I tell you about Audible?
Do you use Audible as much as I do?
Because I use it.
I use it more.
I probably use it most.
How much do you use it?
Go ahead, Justin.
I love Audible.
They have lots of books that you can listen to
and it's much better than podcasts
because at the end of listening to a podcast,
you're like, uh, fine.
At the end of listening to a book,
you're like, I'm better.
I've grown.
I'm a better person now.
Audible has an unmatched selection of audiobook
and spoken word audio products.
Audible is the internet's leading provider
of spoken word entertainment.
They're great for helping you be a better you
whether you wanna feel healthier,
get motivated or learn something new.
Our listeners might enjoy,
what am I listening to right now?
I don't know.
You just set up that reading books makes you better
and so good luck.
Can you find one?
Well, I just wanted to pick one to highlight.
I know, but it's gotta be a book
that when you read it, it makes you better.
You know what's so good that I just finished actually?
Jake Gyllenhaal reads The Great Gatsby.
So good.
He does an amazing reading of it.
I read it.
Did I read it just so I could listen
to the book club episode of A Flow for the Magic Tower?
No, yes.
But Jake Gyllenhaal does a magnificent job with that.
Can I recommend one?
Yeah.
I really liked Vincent D'Onofrio reads Guy Fieri Family Food
125 Real Deal Recipes Kitchen Tested Home Approved.
Man, Griffin, I gotta go get a fucking towel
to clean my computer, you dick.
You got him.
Let me recommend a whole bunch.
I recommend Stiff, The Curious Lives of Human Cadavers
by Mary Roach.
It's very educational.
Allison Rosen just put out a book
that's about tropical attire encouraged
and other phrases that scare me.
It's very good.
I just accidentally played it.
And you can find basically, I think,
all of the Poirot novels or the Agatha Christie's Poirot novels
read by Hugh Frazier, who was in the Poirot Masterpiece Theater series.
It's really good.
Highly recommend.
I actually have another.
I have a real one.
Hey, literally, time out.
Stop the show, because I have to stop this recording
so I can clean my computer.
Oh, God, Justin.
Because it's fucking covered in coffee.
Because you're dumb ass dumb garbage.
I actually, I have a real recommendation
if I can do it real quick, because my other one was a joke.
But I think the audible would appreciate it more
if I gave a real recommendation.
Now, we just stopped for five minutes
so I could clean my stuff.
No, this one's not a joke.
This one's not a joke.
So it's not going to make you laugh so hard
you spill your coffee.
So it's OK for me to go ahead and get some coffee.
Yeah, get a big sip.
I'm just getting some coffee here.
Yeah, a big sip and hold it in your hands.
So what I want to recommend is actually,
so Maggie Smith from Downton Abbey,
it's funny we were just talking about it,
did a reading of Guy Fieri Family Food,
125 Real Deal Recipes Kitchen Test at Home Proved.
That was really good.
And she reads it.
The trash can nachos will move you to tears and diarrhea.
OK, let's end on a real one,
because I was really excited when I found this.
The Series of Unfortunate Events series.
Read by Guy Fieri.
It's really good.
As read by Tim Curry.
Oh, that's even better.
Yeah, is that real?
Yeah, it rules.
Anyway, Audible's offering our listeners
a free 30-day trial membership.
Get a free audiobook with a 30-day trial today by signing up.
Go to audible.com slash my brother
or text my brother to 500-500 to get started.
And I read that last bit,
so I think Travis should read the first Jumbotron here.
OK, this is for Joe, and it's from Candace.
Hi, boobles.
Yeah, that's right.
I said boobles.
I'm sending my message of love
and caring out on the airways for the cutest babe ever.
Love, your sweet, sweet girlfriend, Candace.
Um.
Deal with it.
Handle it.
Why did I take such an aggressive tone?
I don't know.
Boobles read with that, and now I've said it.
But read with that sort of that fury, that passion.
It was really something to behold.
I think maybe it's a that's right,
because it kind of reads as if someone just said,
what did you say?
And I was like, yeah, that's right.
I heard you reading that, Travis.
I thought, this is the episode that's gonna get us the webby.
Here's a Yahoo.
Nope.
Here's a Jumbotron.
Yeah.
Here's a Jumbotron for Zach, and it's from Fred the Human,
Kaz, Elden Toss Cobble, Donara, Nethgoria, RIP,
and Morniel, who say, this is the unskippable cut scene
where you get a Jumbotron,
so don't jump in a portable hole
and fly away on a spectral horse.
What's this?
What are they talking about?
It's so fanciful.
A portable hole?
It's magic and fanciful.
I feel like I'm in a real Harry Potter book.
Thanks for putting up with us
and for introducing most of us to D&D and Taz.
Happy whatever holiday is closest
to when the McElroys read this.
So Earth Day.
Welcome to Earth.
Day.
What if he had said that?
Because it was Earth Day when it happened.
Welcome to Earth Day.
Or what if he had punched me and said,
like, welcome to Good Burger.
Home of the Good Burger.
What if you kissed him instead?
I have something I'd like you two to read.
It's called What If You Kissed Him Instead.
Let me do this one.
This is for Ryan W. and Josie G. from Alphazor.
Josie, you almost crashed a car
because the tower was too dang tall
and then you used Shelby's towel.
I hope no student of yours, yo, teaches you
and I'm lucky to be your friend.
Happy B-day.
Ryan, happy B-day
and thanks for being such a great brother.
I'm really proud of you
and I love you a lot.
I just wish you listened to my bim bam
so you could hear it.
Just shouting into the void.
Just screaming at the night sky.
Brother!
I communicate to you through podcasts.
You don't listen to.
Welcome everyone to the live wrestling
spectacular in Los Angeles.
So far the world's most boring wrestling
podcast has been destroying the competition.
Isn't there anyone who can save us
from this travesty?
Wait, could it be?
It's tights and fights.
The perfect wrestling podcast.
Tights and fights is here to save us
from the monotony of boring wrestling podcasts
with hilarious conversations.
Woke trips through the history of wrestling.
And joke about the finer points
of people wearing spandex.
What a match!
And the tights and fights podcast
will be back every week.
Thursdays on Maximumfun.org
or wherever you get podcasts.
Please, these hosts have families.
Tights and fights.
Podcast.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
I have a game.
A very fun game.
Is it a new bit?
It's a new bit.
It's a new game.
I think we can only play it once.
I don't know if it's going to be recurring.
It might, you know what?
We could probably play it more than once.
I am going to give you-
Do you think Ellen said the same thing?
Like, I've got-
I'm gonna dance.
I've got this, I'm gonna dance once.
We'll see.
You think Jimmy Fallon was like,
I'm gonna do a game with you,
Dwayne, the Rock Johnson,
but this is the only one.
So don't ask me to do any more games.
No, this is a game that I'm going to play with you.
I'm going to play with you.
This is called Celebrity Wine, Why Not?
Okay.
That's the name of the game is Celebrity Wine, Why Not?
And you can spell it however you think is like funniest.
I'm not a big pun guy,
but I'm going to name some celebrity wines
and their score from Wine Enthusiast.
Their rating from Wine Enthusiast.
What's that scale go up to, 100?
It is a scale of 100 and like straight.
I'm just going to be straight with you.
There is no wine on this that rates below 82 points.
Oh, okay.
So it's like 82 to 100.
How bad do you think your wine would have to be
to get like a one?
Would it just be like water and like dirty water?
I think Coke Zero gets a one, not wine.
To give you some sense of what we're talking about,
how limited the scale is here,
we're actually talking about 82 to 95 is the scale.
If it's 82, it fucking sucks.
Like we can all agree they're on the video game review scale.
If it's an 82, it's fucking garbage.
So I'm going to have you, here's the game.
I'm going to give you a,
I have a list of celebrities
that I'm going to share with you boys right now.
And you are going to be able to pull from this list.
We're not going to share this with the audience
so they can get,
it'll be a little bit more out of left field for them.
I think.
So I'm sharing this list with you
and these are all the celebrities
that are in my list here.
So I am going to tell you the name of the wine.
You're going to tell me the celebrity
and then you're going to guess the score.
The score.
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Are you ready?
Some of these will be easier than others.
The name of this wine is 2007 Discovery Series Chardonnay.
That's Mike Ditkas.
It's not Mike Ditkas wine.
My Ditkas football touchdown juice.
I'm going to say Drew Barrymore.
It does.
You're both incorrect.
It's Dan Aykroyd.
Damn.
Dan Aykroyd made the 2007 Discovery Series Chardonnay
from Sonoma County.
Wine Enthusiast gave it a,
I'm going to say,
I'm going to say 83.
Not good.
87.
Holy shit.
Griffin McElroy, 83 points.
It's one step above toilet wine.
It is.
83 exactly.
Booyah.
You got the exact right thing.
So guessed it.
So where'd he go wrong?
What'd he do bad to get there?
It's tart and jammy with acidic one-dimensional flavors
of pineapples, vanillas, and butterscotch.
Now I will say this.
I don't think if you're,
I don't want to call Wine Enthusiast on their bullshit,
but you can't say it's got one-dimensional flavors
of pineapples, vanilla, and butterscotch
because it sounds like Dan has summed it up
at least three discrete flavors there.
But they don't have distance, Justin.
It's like two different pineapples.
Like, fuck you guys.
Seriously.
With the 83 though,
it sounds like my boy Dan took some pineapples
and like vanilla pudding and butterscotch,
blended it all up in a food processor,
and then dumped that into some three buck chuck.
83, are you fucking kidding me?
And 83 betwixt these lips?
No way.
No, no way.
We have standards.
Okay, this, I want to do an easier one.
Number 99 Icewine Cabernet Franc.
Number 99 Icewine, you say?
Oh, this is Mr. Jeffrey Gordon.
I would also say Jeffrey Gordon.
No, it's Wayne Gretzky.
Oh, is that his number?
Icewine.
Yeah.
Yeah, didn't see that name on the list.
Yeah, now name me the score that Wayne got for his wine he did.
I'm going to say 99.
Oh, that's perfect.
I'm actually going to say 89.
Wayne got 92 points from one and two.
This is very good ice wine.
Holy shit.
Wayne, you shouldn't have.
A medium cherry in color with notes of raspberry jam.
Wet stone.
Tastes like a wet rock.
I love it.
93 points.
Hey, Wayne, your wine tastes like wet rocks and ba-da-ba-ba-ba.
I'm loving it.
Thank you, Wayne.
2014 Casa de Metz.
Thompson Grenache from Santa Barbara County.
If it's Santa Barbara, I do think this one's Drew Barrymore.
I think it's Drew Barrymore.
It's Emilio Estevez's Casa de Metz 2014 Thompson Grenache from Santa Barbara County.
Wine Enthusiast gives it a...
94.
86.
92 points for Emilio.
The bottling shows very fresh cherry juice and dried roses,
as well as inviting splashes of Dr. Pepper cola nut.
Hold on.
Hi, I'm a professional wine critic, and this tastes like Dr. Pepper.
Who the doctor is in this bottle?
Let's do one more.
Let's do the highest.
No, I don't want to give that away.
Here's one.
2014.
One more?
One more again?
And what's the city of origin?
I'm going to tell you...
Oh, it's Pinot Noir.
Vin de France.
French.
Chateau de Thigne 2014.
And the name of the person is actually in this wine,
so I can't read the whole name of the wine because that would be cheating.
Okay, so...
One more time.
Mike Dicke.
The name of it?
Chateau de Thigne.
It's Drew Bledsoe's Chateau de Thigne.
I'm going to say...
Wait, can I change wine?
I'm going to say Grard Depardieu.
I'm going to guess Bas Skagg.
It is Chateau de Thigne 2014, Grard Depardieu, Pinot Noir, Vin de France.
Wine Enthusiast gives it a...
87.
82.
Holy shit, Travis McElroy.
87 points with its attractive red fruit flavors.
This is a light perfumed wine.
Travis just got the name of Grard Depardieu's wine as well as the exact score.
I don't know if we'll bring this back.
What's Bas Skagg's fucking wine called?
I need to know.
No, I need to know the band Trane's wine.
Bas Skagg's...
Skagg's Vineyard.
It sounds like a fucking, like...
Like a zone in a post-apocalyptic game.
2008 Montage GSM, so it's a blend.
Uh, I bet that means...
I don't actually know.
Bas Skagg's Leftovers.
I didn't finish these bottles, so I put them all in one.
You see a bottle on the shelf.
It says Skagg's Vineyard.
You open it up.
And it's 2008.
You taste it.
What kind of score are you going to give it?
I know it's not on the scale, but 74.
Travis?
93.
Well, boys, it is a 95.
The highest rated wine we have.
The greatest celebrity wine is from Bas Skagg's.
It's a rave for wine enthusiasts.
That's extraordinarily decadent.
Monteverde, Ganache, and Syrah blend.
So it is a blend.
Good for me.
Currently among the best in California from Bas Skagg's.
Wow.
The best at wine, the best at playing Lido shuffle.
Bas Skagg's.
Wow.
Okay, give me the band Trane's wine, Justin.
I would, Travis.
But I care about you too much to give you the band Trane's wine.
Because it is, let's see.
Can I guess?
It's going to be so much better.
Is it drops of juniper?
No, it's Save Me San Francisco is the wine from the band Trane.
That, of course, is named after a song that they did.
And it's actually an album.
So they did the album and a song.
And is it an 82, Justin?
And I guess it's a wine as well.
It's 86 points.
The San Francisco-based Roots Rockers have a whole line of wines based on their songs.
There's also a petite Syrah called drops of Jupiter.
Okay, that's fine.
The wine is dry with a hint of oaky vanilla and buttered toast.
So that's the band Trane's wine.
It's very good.
I don't think I'd ever want to drink wine and be like, mm, toast.
Yum, it's just like toast.
Yeah, I don't want to drink wine that came out of the brain of Trane.
The Trane brain.
Can I read this Yahoo?
I know it's time for a question, but the Yahoos are so good.
Yeah, please.
This one's sent in by Steven Titus.
It's Yahoo Answers user, sorry, something's gone wrong.
Call them.
Hmm, Boz asks, how do you describe taking out five blades out of your chest in a book?
Like one of my main characters in the book has got stabbed with five blades in his chest
at the same time.
How do I describe in detail of him taking out of the five blades and what he feels as
he takes them out?
Help, please.
Update.
BTW, he's not human.
May I go?
As if I'm reading, here's what I want to hear, Travis.
I want to hear as if I'm reading the audio book.
As if I'm listening to it on audible.com.
Okay.
Zebular turned to face his attackers.
What, you think this can stop me?
He said through his tentacled mouth.
He began removing the blades.
Schlorp came the first one.
Schlorp came the second.
Schlorp, that was the third one.
Schlorp, that was the fourth.
Schlorp, the fifth one came out.
Clang, he threw them all on the ground.
Clang, clang, clang.
Clang went the second one.
Clang went the third.
Clang went the fourth.
Schlorp went the fifth as he threw it into his attacker's chest, killing him instantly.
Take that, attacker, said Zebular or whatever his name was.
Zebular, that was very good, Travis.
Let me try.
Okay.
Zebular reached up and grabbed the knife handle of one of the five knives that was in him.
And he pulled it out a little bit.
Ah, fuck.
He pulled it out another half inch.
Fuck me, seriously.
He pulled it out another quarter inch.
God damn it.
Only three more inches to go, he thought to himself.
And then he blacked out from pain.
And then he woke back up.
Okay, I've got to get back to work.
Chapter two.
Another quarter inch came out of the knife.
And he's like, it's worse doing it slowly.
God damn it.
And so he pulled it out another inch and a half, he thought to himself.
Fuck.
Okay, well, only one more inch and a half to go.
And then he puked.
And he's like, okay, I've got to stop.
I've got to stop kidding around.
It's time to get serious.
It's time to get real.
And then he said this out loud.
And then in an instant, he yanked it out and then he finished.
And then he did that with the other ones at the end.
Can I do it?
Yeah.
Hercules Jr stood up from the ground and stopped being dead and smirked.
Looks like you brought five knives to a god fight.
He took the first blade by a handle and the second blade.
And it had two at the same time, as if to show off how mighty he is.
And then the third one came out pretty quick.
And the fourth one got a little rib.
And so that one was tricky.
And then he accidentally put the third one back in.
I don't know.
What a twist.
Uh oh, he said, I'm just going to leave those there.
It hurt a great deal, even for Hercules Jr, who can't be hurt.
So it didn't hurt it.
I'm sorry.
My backspace key fell off.
And so whatever I write, it's got to stay in her.
I mean, here.
I mean, here, I couldn't even fix that.
Anyway, then he fell in love.
Does the Yahoo community have any good ways of describing that?
I mean, Javec says there's a very good chance he wouldn't be feeling anything anymore.
Even if somehow someone survived five stab wounds to the chest,
I don't think they're going to last long if they yank the blades out
and let themselves bleed to death.
They're not human.
So he saw that and he was like, all right, I got to edit this question.
No, it's an edit, Travis.
He saw the first response like, ah, fuck, I should have clarified.
Gretchen Wiener says, ouch.
For normal people, they would have died.
So the person writing this book is like, ah, fuck, maybe it shouldn't be five blades stabbed.
Shoot.
Four?
Maybe four?
I think I could do four.
It depends on where.
That's it.
OK, listen, question writer, is this like four stab wounds to the chest
or is like one of them stabbed my toe?
Oh, here's what it is.
Update, Gretchen Wiener says, OK, then I got a great idea.
How about, no, you don't.
What about a lot of blood pouring out, but the blood that poured out went back in
and then his wound recovered?
So here's what it would be.
Hercules Jr. smirked and pulled all the five blades out with his five mighty arms
and threw them down to the ground.
But evil Hercules knew the job was done.
Look at all your blood, he says.
It's on the ground where the dirt lives.
Hercules Jr. smiles.
We'll see about that.
All five of his wounds open back up real wide and start making a sucking noise
and the blood slurp and the blood lifts up off the ground
and the five mouths on his body drinks it up
and all the blood goes back in him.
Now I'm ready to fight again.
I hate you, evil Hercules.
Glad I got my blood back.
Now I'm strong for fighting.
Look at how high I can jump.
The end.
You gotta know when to end your book.
Yep, end on a high note.
That's what I always say.
Thank you, yes.
I say you gotta start in the middle of the action
and you gotta end in the middle of the action.
Evil Hercules sighed.
Well, I'm out of knives.
Those are all my knives.
I thought I would only need one, but I brought five.
That was the set I got at Ikea and it only came with the five knives.
How about another question?
Yeah, we've only done one.
Hmm, yeah, that seems like not enough.
We should probably do more of those.
My wife and I recently moved into our first house.
We keep to ourselves, but try to be friendly with the neighbors.
Yesterday, one of our neighbor's kids came to our door
and asked if he could vacuum our home.
A bit confused, but trying to be a good neighbor,
we said he could vacuum downstairs.
Like a good neighbor vacuum my house.
It took about 10 minutes and we gave him five dollars.
What?
As he left, he gave us a handmade business card that said,
It said, I will vacuum your house for $20.
Now we're living with the shame of underpaying a 12-year-old
for a service we didn't want or ask for.
Do we owe this kid $15?
If so, how do we give him the money?
Hell, spotless in Seattle.
This kid.
I will vacuum your house for $20.
This kid had, let's just confront this,
a pocket full of business cards that said,
I will vacuum your house for $4
and then $15 more for however much money you gave him.
If you gave him $50, he would say,
for $65, I will vacuum your whole house.
And it's a good racket.
It's a good racket to get into.
Good scam.
Because that's the thing.
It has to be like an Artful Dodger,
like kind of, you know, the young gang of vacuuming scam artists.
Because what kid just like rolls,
it's one thing for like, I'll mow your lawn or whatever,
but like, I'll vacuum your house?
That kid probably also stole some of your jewelry.
Put the vacuum into the jewelry box,
sucked all the treasures up.
I've never thought about this before,
but if you let a kid mow your lawn and vacuum your house,
when does this start to like broach
into like child labor issues?
Immediately, instantly.
Already.
The moment you pay them a service for hard work.
So you think this is a sting?
Like this kid, if you have him back,
he's definitely wearing a wire.
So I appreciate the entrepreneurial ship of this child, right?
Because I used to mow Tommy Redd's dad's lawn
for money that I could spend on Hero Clicks,
but I used a manual push mower that didn't accomplish anything.
It just kind of, just kind of-
Mushed, just mushed the grass down.
It mushed the grass down.
And so one time I went to do it and he said,
last time, did you actually do it?
And I said, yeah, I just use a push mower
and so it didn't work very well.
And he said, I'm not going to employ you anymore.
And I said, totally got it.
$20, please.
I'll vacuum your house for $20.
I will vacuum your house for $20.
With this push mower.
I would sell, I will vacuum your house for $20 t-shirt
at our merch store.
I'm fairly sure you could not walk half a block wearing that shirt.
You would just instantly like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, come on in.
Come on in, please.
Please, this isn't your house
and we're not anywhere near your house.
I know, but I really need this service.
This is a great service.
I think you might be in the clear
because the terms were not agreed upon before, right?
This is not how business cards work.
It's not, it's a business card, not an invoice.
You need to be ready for the fact that this kid
is going to come back
and he's going to offer you the service again
and you are going to need to think of a reason
why you said yes the first time
but now it's a no from now on.
It's much cleaner than I used to be.
We found another child who does it for $15.
So sorry, Jeremy.
You got undercut, Jeremy.
Hit the bricks.
This is business.
Mark Cuban came by with his $15 house vacuuming service.
It's a robot, you see.
So I'm sorry to say that automation
is taking your job, Jeremy.
I love $20.
Don't get me wrong.
It's a good number.
It's a good number and if you're a kid,
it's basically $100.
That is the thing.
A $20 bill when you're a kid
is like blank check.
$20?
Oh my gosh.
Well, with inflation,
they'd still be jazzed about $20.
They'd still be psyched out of their fucking minds.
Probably not a good vacuuming job, huh?
Why didn't you ask how much it costs?
Why did you let this kid in your house
with no terms discussed?
If you don't ask the kid how much it costs upfront,
you are opening yourself up to a reality
in which you're like, well, what do I owe you?
And the kid's like,
oh, nothing.
I just wanted to look at all your things
and touch them.
Yeah.
Because I'm dirty and I'm nasty.
Or you're like, what do I owe you?
And the kid's like $150.
Yeah, that's all bad.
There's no good outcome here.
Or the kid comes in to vacuum your house
and he's still vacuuming your house
three hours later.
And you're like, okay, go.
That's a 10 minutes.
I'm not sure he was doing a very good job.
That's, I think we can all agree on that.
It's not a good vacuum job this child did.
So it may have been a $5 vacuum job.
If you want your house vacuumed, call me.
I'll do it for $19.
$25, but it'll be cleaned by a man.
And I will show you how a man cleans a house.
A child's not gonna do it.
I'll show you how a man does it.
Oh, Justin, that vacuum cleaner's pretty big.
Are you sure you can?
Whoa.
Yeah, it's no problem.
I'll throw it on my back like a Ghostbuster.
And you can get, like, business card says like,
I'll suck this shit out of your house carpet.
Our mom used to put, do other people do this?
Our mom used to put this weird, smelly dust.
Carpet Fresh?
Carpet Fresh.
Do people still do Carpet Fresh?
Cause I feel like I've never seen anybody else do it.
I know it used to be a thing where it's like,
I'm about to vacuum anyway.
Let me throw a bunch of dust on the ground.
I guarantee Carpet Fresh is now like asbestos and lead paint.
For sure.
Like nobody uses it.
Are you kidding me?
You're gonna use Carpet Fresh?
Oh, your feet are gonna melt off by the time you're 40.
That is gonna do it for us for this week, folks.
Thank you so much for, I was gonna say enjoying,
but that seems-
Indulging?
Indulging yourself in this pot.
Indulging us.
Yeah, that's what I was gonna say.
Thank you for indulging us for this hour.
We hope you have enjoyed yourself.
We are, okay, so we have a few things to talk about.
We're gonna try to blow through them as quick as possible.
St. Louis and Detroit.
Columbus, we're also coming to you in May,
but you have come out in a big way
and you bought up all the ding-dang tickets.
If you're in St. Louis or Detroit though,
and you have some free time on Thursday, May 3rd,
or Friday, May 4th,
we're gonna be at the Peabody Opera House in St. Louis
and the Masonic Temple Theater in Detroit
doing our podcast, My Brother, My Brother, Me,
live on stage.
And it's going to be very fun,
and we would love it if you would come out and see us.
Those shows are very close,
and there's lots of good seats available,
so please come buy them.
There's not, like, infinity tickets.
There's, like, a fixed amount in the world.
It might sell out before the time we do the show,
so hop on it right now.
Don't wait.
Go get great tickets, because you deserve it.
And if you go to mcroyshows.com slash tours,
you can get those right now.
So please come see us again, May 3rd, May 4th,
St. Louis, Detroit.
Let's do it.
And send in your questions,
and make sure to put in the subject line,
like, Detroit Show or Columbus Show
or St. Louis Show or whatever.
Also, I want to say, just announced,
we are going to be on this year's JoCo Cruise,
JoCo Cruise 2019.
We are super excited about it,
and we hope you are super excited about it too.
Well, speak for yourself.
I can't stop thinking about the Kraken.
You're worried about the Kraken?
The Kraken, Leviathan, Poseidon.
Yeah, I understand.
Well, don't worry.
We start every-
They start every JoCo Cruise
with a sacrifice to the sea.
Okay.
So that we don't have to worry about it.
Listen, there's not many cabins available,
but we're going to be on there
with They Might Be Giants and our whole family.
So like, come on this fucking cruise already.
What are you talking about?
JoCoCruise.com.
It's one of the most fun things
I've ever done in my life going on last year,
so I'm super looking forward to this one.
JoCoCruise.com.
Also want to say,
I started a secret society here in Cincinnati
called the Cincinnati Underground Society,
and we are doing a monthly show
called the Cincinnati Underground Society Show,
or CUS, and-
Nice.
Tickets for our April show are on sale now.
They are very close to selling out.
We're at about 75% sold at this point.
The show comes up Saturday, April 28th.
I've got five out of town guests coming in
and one local, and they're pretty great.
It's going to be a really great show.
We had a lot of fun doing the March show.
I'm not going to tell you who the guests are,
but trust me, it's a really good lineup.
So if you want to come out to that,
go to bit.ly slash C-U-S-S-K-E-Y 2018.
CUS key 2018.
Come to Travis's show, and also buy my book.
Justin and Sydney are doing a book,
and that's so exciting.
They just announced it.
They've been working really hard on it.
Yep.
Sydney's sister, my sister-in-law Taylor,
who's extremely talented, is doing illustrations,
and it is a book based on our podcast, Sawbones.
And you can get it at bit.ly forward slash Sawbones book.
And it's a pre-order.
It's not coming out till October,
but please pre-order this book.
I worked so hard on it.
It's so hard to write a book.
Bit.ly forward slash Sawbones book.
Please buy a bunch of copies of it.
Thank you.
Also, we got a merch store with some cool new stuff on it,
and you can find it all on-
New Munch Squad pin.
Yeah, it's really cool at mackereloymerch.com.
All right.
That's actually only for April.
So if you want a Munch Squad pin, go get it right now.
So you won't get it.
Thanks to Maximum Fun for having us on the network,
and thank you to everybody who supported us in the Max Fun Drive.
Go to maximumfun.org.
Check out all the great shows there.
If you want to see more stuff we do, go to mackereloyshows.com.
And thanks to John Roderick and the Long Winters
for the use of our theme song
and to departure off the album, Putting the Days to Bed.
Dude, you want that final, Yahoo?
Yes.
It's from Yahoo.
Sent in by Adrian Cowles.
Thank you, Adrian.
It's Yahoo Answers user spandy?
Question mark?
Who asks?
Now, back to sandals and non-white socks.
Who thought that up?
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
And it's been my brother, my brother, and me.
Kiss your dads.
Square on the lips.
Maximumfun.org.
Comedy and culture.
Artist owned.
Do you love books?
Want to get more out of all that reading you do?
I'm Bria Grant.
And I'm Mallory O'Mara.
Join us every Thursday on Reading Glasses,
where we help you read better.
Reading Glasses is a show about book culture,
teaching you how to enhance your literary life
and solve your bookish problems, like...
How do you get out of a reading slump?
What's the best book light to use in bed
while your partner's trying to sleep?
Where do you hide the bodies of the people
who talk while you're trying to read?
In the basement of my apartment building.
Ooh, that's a good place.
Let Bria and I improve your reading life
every Thursday on Reading Glasses,
Maximum Fun's new culture podcast.
Learn how to read better.