The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Welcome, my brother, my brother, and me, an advice show for the modern era.
On this week's episode, we have a gigantic palette, but there's only one hue that is represented.
And that's right, it's 50 Shades of Grey. Watch, 2015.
Step into my office, said the spider to the guy.
We gotta be. Let me check your references.
At least like you've got a lot of experience. What would you say to 50,000 a year?
50,000 Shades of Grey is more gray than your human mind and your human eyeball cones can possibly even conceive.
Curious about our health benefits?
Here's one benefit, that boner.
Here, let me describe to you one 50,000th of these shades. I'm gonna punch your butt.
Don't punch it, it's so good.
It's a book so nasty that people in the black section of Sherwin-Williams get looks like, oh, you nasty.
Oh, you nasty motherfuckers.
I'm just looking at all the different shades of gray.
This used to be a nice Christian community, Sherwin-Williams.
And you made that one dirty section.
Made a dirty, dirty color.
It's enough to make you turn to your wife and say, let's just go with mauve.
If it sounds like my recordings coming to you exclusively in the right channel of your headphones,
it's because I'm favoring that butt cheek because my other one's so tender and sore from punching.
Mr. Gray, remember last night when you punched my butt?
Yeah, I'm suing you for sexual harassment.
No, you can't check the contract, section B for butts.
That's how I keep it categorized, B section, all butt stuff, including indices J through K, punching.
My inner casual Friday.
My inner goddess awoke to punch his butt, and then he was punching my butt, and then we punched each other's butts back and forth.
You done butt punched the cum right out me.
Sorry, Debra.
Debra, I laughed.
Let me try that take again.
You done butt punched the cum right out me.
We ADR'd in all of Christian Gray's lines, so the real guy doesn't do anything.
It's just the three of us taking turns.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
How many times in the novel does he or she give the other one purple nurples?
How purple are their nurples?
I am the oldest master of your sexual destiny, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est HR representative, Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy, the emperor of piss.
Oh, man, I don't know a goddamn thing about this film or book.
I think we are nailing it.
I think we're doing pretty good.
A lot of people described it, they said it was just like pornography.
I don't think those people have seen pornography.
Do they have wet butts?
Because if not, then it's not like the pornography I've seen.
As my wife pointed out, it's probably just a bunch of butts, right?
Butts for days.
Butts on butts on butts.
I made this point to my wife, Rachel.
I feel like when I say the words I'm about to say to you, the audience,
she maybe loves me a little bit less.
I shave a little bit off of the reservoir there.
But that movie can't show penetration.
It just can't show penetration.
It cannot show penetration.
This is the nastiest book ever,
but the movie can't even show a penetration scene.
Any object in any orifice.
At best, it's a softcore, late night, HBO, Cinemax kind of movie.
At worst.
Even that can show the bottom of a ball as it penetrates, possibly.
But just a ball, left or right.
And only the bottom quarter of it.
And I'm saying we're not even going to get that.
So it's a God's damn point.
Just read a book.
Well, don't read that book.
Use your imagination.
Read any other book, honestly.
Watch the pornography of your mind.
I think there's ropes and chains, right?
Slinging hands.
Who's your daddy? Yes, I am.
And a gross misrepresentation of the whole BDSM lifestyle.
But other than that,
one minor thing upon which the entire book is built.
It's a fine read. A breezy read.
Do you think that the BDSM community
reads Fifty Shades of Grey in anger
the way the Wiccan community reads Harry Potter?
Um, yeah.
There's no butt-punching in BDSM.
What are you even saying, Fifty Shades of Grey?
What?
Now all the first-timers are going to come in
and just start punching butts day one.
That's a professional move.
Let's see here.
Hey, Mistress Jasmine,
could you step into my office for a minute?
We've had a lot of complaints.
We're going to have to let you go from the BDSM club.
Yeah.
Why? I punched one butt?
Yeah, but we have a zero-butt-punch strike policy.
I walked into the fuck prison
and just shouted whale on my pee-pee.
That's not allowed?
Okay.
No, that was okay.
I don't think that was the problem.
I can't help myself. I see those cheeks.
They look like little speed bags.
I'm training for the fight.
I got a fight coming up.
Uh, Mike's son is about to lose his first tooth.
Oh, on this show, it's like questions and stuff.
My son is about to lose his first tooth.
His best friend received $100 goddamn dollars
from the tooth fairy,
and my son seems to think that amount is normal.
How do I manage his expectations
without losing the magic?
And that's from Dentally Injured
in Delaware.
Here's the point I'll make,
and I know I'm coming at this from an adult
who is, at best, tooth fairy agnostic.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not tooth fairy theistic.
I think the truth is out there somewhere.
But I'm just not willing to commit
one way or the other.
If I had to choose
between losing a tooth
or paying $100,
I would pay $100 every time.
It's not even a question.
Each of my teeth,
I have currently in my head,
let me do some quick math,
probably $3,000 worth of teeth
going for me.
This seems about right.
I got about 30 teeth up in there.
That sounds right.
Let me count them real quick.
That would be real good radio.
I have about $3,000 worth of beautiful enamel
in my mouth,
and I'm not willing to trade any of that for $100.
Now, I'm doing fairly well for myself these days.
If I was in Hot Dog's era,
I would have gone to the tooth bank
and just started swapping those bad boys out.
Griffin, you know that the deal with the tooth fairy
isn't that you're buying the teeth from the child, right?
You're not saying,
hey, Tim, pull it out.
No, I'm just saying if we're looking for a way
to establish value, all right.
Losing your teeth is the worst.
It's the nightmare I have most commonly
is the tooth losing nightmare.
I think a lot of people can relate to that.
How much money would you spend
on leaving your mouth?
Yeah, that's a toughie, right?
I don't know what that figure,
I don't know what that's worth.
It's definitely more than $1,500
to replace a tooth in my mouth.
Yeah, now we're talking,
if we're going into the medical community,
each tooth could arguably be worth
anywhere between $800 to $20,000.
I feel like we're ignoring
something about this question,
and that is that
kids
lie all the time constantly.
They're never not lying.
They're 100% lying forever.
No question.
Call this kid's family.
Guarantee they didn't even know he lost a tooth.
Let me pitch this scenario
to you though, Justin.
Hey, Debra,
you grabbed that tooth from under Timmy's pillow,
and you put a dollar.
Yeah, I just grabbed a dollar out of your wallet,
but I didn't have any dollars in my wallet.
I just hit the bank.
Oh, shit.
Actually, I just saw one,
and I was like, let's just go with it.
I just grabbed a bill,
because who keeps $100 bills in their wallet, Steve?
This is why we have money troubles.
Justin, this is something that you're going to run into
eventually with your spawn,
your brood.
I think $1 for a tooth,
even a child's tiny,
insignificant, bullshit tooth
that can't do much chewing of anything in any way,
I think $1 is garbage.
First of all,
inflation, crazy.
Inflation would be crazy right now, you guys.
$1 isn't going to buy you anything.
It's not even going to buy you an issue of Us Weekly.
I think you're making a fair point.
I don't really see that it's up to me,
but I think it's a fine point you're making.
I'm just saying,
at the very least, $5,
and then at least the child...
But how would I weigh into that decision?
How would I weigh into that decision at all?
The tooth fairy comes to you and says,
what denomination of currency?
Where are you at economically?
They want to make sure
they just keep it within...
They don't want to make the kid richer than me
at that particular moment.
Yeah, because then they become the parent.
That's the law!
Why do you think that Britney Spears' parents
just fucking robbed her blind?
Justin Bieber just got robbed blind?
It's because none of these parents
want to be the children.
Right, and that's what happens.
That's what that Head Start thing you hear so much about?
That's what it is.
It's a parental swap-a-rooney.
It's a freaky Friday,
but it's been codified into a business.
I have a suggestion for the question asker.
Go.
Instead of money,
swap it for some kind of good,
like maybe a new Xbox game
that costs less than $100.
That's awesome.
But in a child's mind...
It might as well cost $10,000.
Yeah, like, oh, I got something.
That's way better.
That's a really good idea.
$60 for a new AAA video game
is still a crazy amount of money to spend.
But I'm saying you could pick up
a certified pre-owned game.
Oh, great.
Thanks, Madden 96
for the original PlayStation.
Oh, this is great.
I love how it has eight different stickers on it.
Thanks, GameStop.
You're a really good company.
Oh, and it smells like weed, and that's fun.
Madden 96, who was even playing football back there?
Is that Deon Sanders on the cover?
Is that Deon?
Okay, I mean, I guess I wasn't alive
when Deon Sanders existed,
but that's totally...
Why does it say on the back
Bow Nose Tackling Fidelity?
I don't understand.
How old would you say is the average kid
who's losing teeth and swapping them with the tooth fairy?
Like seven?
I should learn this.
Is that like seven?
I feel like five to ten is really the sweet spot
where all the goddamn teeth fall out of your head.
Childhood is the worst.
Because I feel like
maybe he's going to lose sight of the fact
that his friend got 100 bucks
by the time he gets like a 20.
Yeah, or he'll lose sight of it
when the parents of the $100 child
go completely broke.
They could go completely bankrupt.
Because they're going to spend $30,000.
Well, $3,600 if they keep it up.
I would like to suggest
that if you are leaving $100,
there is no amount of like being rich
where you would think that is a good idea.
I would like to suggest
that if you are leaving $100
under a child's pillow
for a tooth,
there is only one logical reason
that you are leaving $100
and that is only one logical reason
that would be happening
and that is money laundering.
You are trying to launder a large sum of money
through your child's mouth
so the federales can't get their grow units on it.
It's also,
I would pitch another scenario
that this kid's parents
forgot to swap the tooth
like the last three times.
Oh, I see.
We got to do something big for this one
or he's going to stop believing.
Well,
I'm glad we could talk about that
instead of my thing.
I was saying that they are equally likely.
I thought they were honestly,
I mean, if I was running
a chuckle school, I would say
the concept of
forgetful parents versus money laundering.
Money laundering.
Maybe more comedy.
Oh, you want to interrupt to get that?
Yeah, cool. Like what do you got now?
What do you got now, Keratop?
I got your chocolate and my peanut butter.
I got my peanut butter and your chocolate.
They're forgetful money laundering parents.
Did we launder that money?
Ah, we're in jail. Fuck.
We were supposed to launder $10 each time.
We'll just do $100. No one will notice.
Surely he won't tell the kids at school.
Where do we put the books we've been keeping
for the mob? I don't even know.
Fuck.
Which mob are we in?
I'm so shitty at this.
Are we in your mob?
Sorry, sorry. I know this is awkward.
Are we in the Scarface mob
or the Japanese mob?
Are we Yakuza?
Honey, are we Yakuza?
Are we supposed to be putting Yakuza money
in Dylan's mouth?
Is this ornate dragon on my back
a gang thing?
I just love dragons.
Is there a rumble tonight or is that tomorrow?
Did we miss it?
Honey, I just broke a pool cue
over my knee and God help me
if I could remember what I was going to do with it.
That was our last good pool cue.
The other ones are all warped and bent.
If only we hadn't spent all that money
laundering it for our child
and the two fairies.
Honey, you put the actual money in the laundry.
No.
This is bad.
Now this is like the Amelia Bedelia school
of mafioso life.
You're such a scatterbrained mafioso.
You're supposed to put dates in the pudding
so you cut up a calendar.
You're Amelia Bedelia.
Amelia Bedelia Corleone.
You don't know nothing about money laundering.
You dummy.
Y'all want a yahoo?
Let's just take a quick moment
and take our game and recognize
the game of Rachel Sperling.
Thank you Rachel Sperling.
Rachel Sperling who was at the
San Francisco live show.
It was basically a celebrity.
We got a bunch of emails and tweets
from Rachel Sperling.
And Davenport was there.
My boy D. Big D.
They fought.
The ground shook.
And San Francisco's not there anymore.
Just because there was a flurry of blows
exchanged between them.
Thank you Rachel Sperling.
It's by yahoo answers user Jacob who asks
how can you dominate
each zodiac sign?
What is every zodiac's weakness?
I just want to know
how can you dominate very zodiac sign
in a friendship type of way?
How do you become dominant in a relationship
with any zodiac, especially
Geminis? I would also
like to know what every zodiac sign's
weakness is emotionally and
mentally.
Here's some Fifty Shades shit
isn't it? Okay so
wait hold on. Is this dude looking
for something that's like oh if you make eye
contact with a Scorpio they're yours forever.
And that's right Travis. If you make
eye contact with a Scorpio usually it's hard
to do because Scorpios are trained to just
sort of look into the
middle distance.
They will look intently
at a chin or nose but never in the eyes.
But if you can trick one of them into doing it
their soul is
legally your property.
So that's what Scorpios are all about. That was very
astute Travis and I didn't know that you were
a student of the stars.
I only know one other one.
What's that? It's Aquarius.
If you squeeze their right pinky finger
short squeeze, short squeeze, long
squeeze, short squeeze, short squeeze,
short squeeze. Just bang out the Konami
code on their digits
and then what does that do?
That means
that they owe you five dollars every day
for the rest of their lives. And you do that
to enough Aquarii.
You got a little cottage industry.
Yeah you're set. You're good to go.
Cancers they actually
have a glowing weak point on their belly.
That one's easy.
If you punch that then they void their
bowels.
And you've got that on them.
You punch that it flips them over.
They kind of lie there on their back like
and then you want to use a
Deku nut. If you use the Deku
nut it stuns them.
Right.
Taurus.
I mean just stop
giving it gas I guess.
Low MPG.
It should put a stop to it.
Uh huh.
Also if you just sort of take grab their
horns then you can just like fucking
flip them right over. They can't do anything.
It's like grabbing a cat by the scruff
of its neck. And then there's
the monkey. No.
They're weak against fire.
No. No. No.
Bulbasaur
is weak against fire and
bird types.
So.
God you're being
such a. You're acting like a real Bulbasaur
right now.
I know you're a Taurus but um
I'm in Aries and
as far as I know I don't really have any
weaknesses.
If that's your weakness you're hubris.
Yeah I guess that's true. If there's a movie with a robot in it
and something bad happens to the robot
I'll cry for three and a half
weeks. That's a big issue.
That's a big one for me. Hey Griffin
are you going to go see Big Hero 6? I don't think I will.
Thank you because I have plans next
Friday.
I don't want to still be crying. I don't want to still be crying
about Big Hero 6.
Pisces. Their weak point
is the heart. You gotta stab them in it.
Oh God.
Okay well I think that would work for most of them.
Not so much an emotional mental weakness.
I'm pretty sure everyone's weak in their heart.
No but Pisces
are especially weak.
Like here on your sexual contract you've written
down don't stab my heart.
And I have to be honest I wasn't planning on
doing that but I guess it's good to have a balance.
But now super curious.
I just want to say that I love the
context of this question more than anything.
I love it.
I love that there's a guy sitting there going like
I just want to be friends with everyone.
So how can I dominate them?
Well you can't. You know what demands
you can't be friends with somebody
until they're just fucking
terrified of you.
It's called the Biff School
of making friends.
You really have to terrorize them
into being your buddy.
Justin you have just broken my heart in twain.
This idea
that the plot of
Back to the Future is really about
lonely lonely Biff.
McFly!
McFly what are you a cancer?
Come here. I'm gonna punch your tummy.
You find that
weak point. What if in the
moment when George McFly stood up to Biff
Biff was just heartbroken like
but I thought we were friends.
This is just us right?
I give you a hard time
and you're kind of a dork but like
Geminis of course their only weak point is being covered
in manure. It's the only way to kill
one. It
nullifies their regenerative
process.
Cause there's two of them.
And also if you kill
one with manure it ripples back
through their bloodline and kills
all of the past versions of them with
manure as well.
If you wanted to do it scientifically
you could kill the past one and it would ripple forward.
That's a much easier chronic.
Makes a lot more sense.
Man.
Just now thinking about that.
If Marty McFly had just sort of
murdered
what's his face? Mad Bill Hickok.
What was it? Mad Dog Tannen.
Mad Dog Tannen shot him
right in the dome.
Or covered him in
manure and then shot him.
Or else there's no fucking.
Well it's the only way.
It's the only way to ensure that the job gets done.
Covered him in manure and shoot him.
And then that pretty much takes care of
well just about everything huh?
That wraps
up the series I guess.
Do you guys want to do?
Should we do Future 4? I don't think we can.
Because there is no
friction there. We murdered
all BIFs. Past, Present and Future.
The BIFpocalypse.
What if the fourth one is
they realized they needed at least one BIF
to like save the world.
And you have to go dig
back. Dig BIF out of
the poop before it gets shot.
If it gets shot it's fine. Don't worry about it.
No you have to go shoot yourself
before you shoot BIF.
You are the gunman on the grassy
noble. You are the third
man. You are the one
who has to bring yourself down before you shoot.
Back into the future.
Solid.
Thank you. Thank you. Delicious.
Next question.
Let's see. We got one here.
I'm going with my wife
and a part of her family on a rather expensive
trip to Ful which has been
planned. Florida.
Florida.
Which has been planned for several months.
We are now very close to the trip
and a 50 something year old sister
who originally declined invite is
interested. However she doesn't want to pay
and wants to sleep on a cot with her boyfriend
in our beach front homes and closed
patio.
How should we handle this? That's from Jim City
Slacker. Oh it's easy. Tell him
to fuck off. What are you even talking
about? We don't
want to pay so you're not going to get any money
out of us and we're also going to make you feel super bad
by sleeping on the ground.
Is that okay? Is that an equitable
solution? We don't want to pay and we
want to have sex on your patio. We're not
only going to not contribute we're going to
make you feel shitty the whole time you're there. Is that
okay? Does that sound like do I am I a
good vacay buddy? So like
if you want to if you if you want to
take them and have them not pay
because times are tight but they
want to like hang out with you that's fine. Do
that. But don't like
this. I fucking
hate that. I'm not going to pay so
I'll just like live in poverty while you guys
do it up sleep in your
like you know thousand thread count
sheets while I huddle
up on the floor underneath some
Us Weeklys. If you have any
bread crusts or any
rinds. Are you guys going
out to a nice dinner again? Well
don't forget the doggy bags I guess.
Right that sucks. And then feed us like dogs.
Just leave
leave your leftovers in a
pile on the floor
outside the mud room and we'll
me and Dan will just get to them. Don't
forget to slop your in-laws.
Go ahead and put in a garbage bag if you
want. We'll just tear open the garbage bag and
then sleep in it later. We'll use it as a
blanket. We'll use it like
a little food womb.
Just sleep
in your trash.
Now that sucks. Don't put any
chicken bones in there though. You know how we
get. Dan choked on the last one.
He's dead now. I crawled inside
him for warmth. You thought
he smelled bad on the outside.
Well we haven't bathed in three
weeks. We don't have a
fancy shower like you people.
No I think that Griffin is
right and if it's like a matter of like they always
wanted to go but like they couldn't
afford it and now it's like hey would it be cool
if we went like that's
different than like hey sure
fuck it we'll go with you. I'm not gonna
pay because you already paid for everything right.
So like there's nothing to pay for. That's
shitty. Yeah that sucks.
I mean I'm not even saying that.
I'm saying if they want to go and not pay and you're fine
with it because you want to spend time with them and they
don't have the money right now and you
feel bad for excluding them and then your family and you
want to chill cool then have them along.
But the I mean
this is more advice for them than it is for you
I guess but just this act of like
we don't have money
so we're gonna
live like poppers
while you guys do up the high life like
that sucks. Can you imagine
being the
boyfriend and asking off
for work like
hey I'm gonna need this week
in July off
I am going to
stay with my girlfriend's
family on the patio
for free
for a week. I don't know why you would be
so specific with your time off
request. I think I'll eat a sandwich
on Thursday and maybe
see a movie on Friday.
I just think this is the ultimate expression
of beach life. I'm pretty sure
this is how Jimmy Buffett was born.
Like he realized he couldn't come back.
He was conceived on a patio. He was like
well once you stay for free
in somebody's enclosed patio
of your girlfriend's family
you really don't get to come back from that level
of chill. You can't
rebuild a normal life with your societal
bounds. Right.
What is this tie? It's a noose is what it is.
Cause I once had the ultimate freedom
of sleeping in a
cot in an enclosed patio
with my girlfriend's family. I made love on a cat.
What?
On a cot on a patio.
I know freedom.
You said I made love on a cat on a
patio. Well that was my favorite
Jimmy Buffett song. Stay.
And my favorite scene from Garfield's
Two Kitties.
Stay put Fluffy. Dad's almost
done.
Do you think that's what cheeseburger in paradise
that song is about? Is that
Jimmy Buffett was starving to death on a family
vacation he didn't pay for and then a miracle
burger just appeared on his naked chest.
Just floating. Floating
in the air. He had to chase it down the beach.
It's not your time James.
Cheeseburger to paradise.
Cheeseburger I found in the trash
with my in-laws. Leftovers
half of a burger.
Some old french fries and half
of a cake. It's just a cheeseburger
I found in the trash.
Cheeseburger or else
I'll die.
I like mine before the maggots get
to it. Next to the ketchup
but not the cheeseburger.
Next to the ketchup but not
next to tampons.
None of that is in the garbage.
Cheese tampon in paradise.
Can't be too picky when you're close to
the edge.
Jimmy I don't think we can
release this song.
Use your imagination to just
get it down.
Hey Jimmy could you come to my
office real quick? I want to talk to you about your latest
single. Yeah it's just sandwiches
there. They're probably not
going to be good. Yeah it turns out it's the most popular
song ever.
We can't have it on the shelves.
It's uniting the world like
mild stallions.
He had to travel 800
years to the future to pin cheese
tampons in paradise.
How about a money
zone? Yeah.
We've talked about this before and we'll say it again
90 percent that's the amount
of time that you are in underpants.
Not sure.
Get old fast.
No listen I don't want to like cause a stink with
the bullet points that Meandis has provided us but I
would say that number is much much much much
much much higher for me.
When was the last time you weren't wearing underwear Griffin?
I mean there's a
like an eight second period. No not even
that I would say about I would say there's about
a four second period there when I switch between
pairs of Meandis and
that's about all that you can get out of me
vis a vis my ding dong being exposed
to the world. Well
not everybody has those sorts
of
restrictions I think. Oh they
are not restrictive at all. They are
breathable and soft and I need them on me
at all times.
I am technically
speaking wearing Meandis right now
if you guys have to know the truth.
Wait what do you mean technically like
you're wearing one on your head?
He's turned them into he's fashioned them into a sharp
bangle. I'm legally
wearing Meandis right now.
They're contractual Meandis.
I'm wearing contractual Meandis.
We call them Meandis by the way.
At this point I just
assume that everyone's does like
made the switch but if you haven't
Meandis is a great fitting
pair of underwear that's two times softer than
cotton and that is no BS.
100% true. They are lovely.
If you go to Meandis.com
you're going to find incredible styles
and different looks for both men and women.
If you're you know it's
a little late because you've done Miss Valentine's Day
but let me just throw out matching underpants.
It's a good look. It's
Presidents Day right? Today is Presidents
Day when you're listening to this. Sure.
Yeah. God it's going to be hard because
they have to ship them and stuff.
If you can go to the the Meandis
factory and get them hot off the
tap and then just like throw those
on your tip and then you're going to have
a Presidents Day style
that your partner or
your future partner that maybe you haven't even met yet
is just going to go a ga ga for.
And the Meandis fabric
is it's awesome. It fits great. Doesn't
ride up and it literally
pulls moisture away from your skin so you're cool
all day long. You're so comfortable
wearing these goddamn underpants. They're
so lovely and they're also
environmentally friendly and they it's
it's wonderful. If you go to Meandis.com
slash my brother you're going to get 20 percent
off your first order and free shipping.
Go look. I promise you you'll see a style
you'll like and then
you'll order them and you'll say like oh
my god why have I not been girding my loins
with these like my whole life. Let me
ask you two a question.
Hit me. Let me ask you two a science question.
Okay.
You put the Meandis on
and then it draws the moisture
away from your zone.
Uh huh. That is that
was that's what we've been told by corporate overlords.
And I've been told. Like a Fremen suit.
Yeah. I've been told that yes it's a Fremen
suit. You put it on and
I've also been told this just sort of by
my zone because it knows what it likes
and it likes dryness. And
it's Bluetooth compatible. It pulls
away your gooch juice
and it pulls it all away and it keeps
it super dry and it removes the moisture.
But it doesn't get very
soggy. Is it teleporting?
Your gooch juice
away? Is it like a wizard?
Where is the juice going?
I don't know. The juice is loose.
The juice is loose but is it being fucking
procedurally atomized?
What's going on?
Is it vaping my juice?
Have you seen Willy Wonka in the Chocolate Factory?
And you know Mike TV? Yeah.
Okay. Every time you wear Meandis
someone on your television gets wet underpants.
Okay. That's cool.
That makes perfect sense. Anyway go to Meandis.com
slash my brother and try those
out. You're going to love them.
Who else we got?
Well we've got like
old school friend of the show.
Oh man. Classic. Nature
box. Classic
pals at nature box. I'm trying to think
of like how do you not already know about nature
box at this point? I just
assume that everybody at this point is wearing
Meandis and snacking on nature
box which are whole. I mean
you're going to snack right? Everybody's
going to snack. Everybody knows that. But
what nature box affords you is an opportunity
to do it in a healthy style.
Healthy. Not just healthy but like
with a rotation of like brand
new snacks every time you receive a box.
Like you're not going to. There's so many
options. So many different choices. You can choose
the same ones if you're like oh my god I
love those pistachio power clusters.
I never want to not have those. Great.
You can get those and then try like three or
four new ones that month. You know what I mean?
And you're like okay now I love this. We just
did garlic plantain chips.
Whoa that sounds good.
They're insane. They're so
good. I have to make sure I don't just
keep eating them because then
all I will taste for the next three days
is garlic. But they're so good.
And tiny bananas. That's
what a plantain is.
A plantain is like a little baby banana. It's so
cute. But yeah there's like you can also
there's stuff like dried berries and like
some dried pineapple slices that are so
good. So basically any kind of
snack that you like whether it's savory, sweet,
spicy, whatever.
Umami. You're going to find
something at Nature Box that you're like
okay yeah that sounds incredible.
And then you know you mix and match a couple
new snacks. And they have zero
artificial flavors, colors, or sweeteners.
Zero grams trans fat and
no high fructose corn syrup. So it's like
the best. And here's the best thing about
it in case you didn't already know.
You have the chance to try Nature Box for
free with a free trial box
featuring five of their most popular snacks.
It's making me angry
now that you're lying. I am not
lying Justin. I am 100% telling the truth. There's no way
any deal could be this good.
It is that good Justin. And you know why?
Because we love our listeners. Nature Box
was like I don't know about these free snacks guys. And we put our
foot down and we dominated them. We stared
them in the eye and we said give them free
snacks. And they said okay please don't punch us in the
butt again. And they said but
you have to go to their house and hand deliver it and then
mouth feed it to them like a baby bird.
And I said that's fine. And that's
the only, listen, it's not ideal.
You're gonna wish
that you were eating these delicious
sriracha roasted cashews
without us having to chew them up and spit them
in your mouth like a baby bird. Well an adult bird.
But that's just
the way the cookie crumbles. But it won't
cost you anything. And we're very
discreet. We come in an unmarked brown
box.
Please don't cover the breath holes.
So go to naturebox.com
slash my brother and get a free trial box
now. Where'd all my plantains
go? We eat them in here because we
had a very long journey in the postal service
system. I have
a call to action for you listeners
and that is to pick up Robocopter
Ski Patrol at Amazon today
and make your life and the lives of your loved ones
demonstrably better.
That word is so great isn't it?
Demonstrably.
Cause it's got demon in there.
And monster. Yeah. You can make
the lives of your loved ones full of
demon monsters. But better
what is. What the hell is this thing you're telling me
about? Tell me what it is. Robocopter
Ski Patrol. I want you to when you hear those
words Robocopter Ski Patrol
first I want you to just sort of
smile. I got my wallet out. Just like
you saying it I got my wallet out.
Think Doctor Who crossed with
Archer and a little bit of high grade alcohol
consumption. Does that sound awesome?
Then you want Robocopter
Ski Patrol. The best way to buy someone's
love especially the authors
and you know you want that.
This is a book written
by Aaron Seacross
that you can get on Amazon.
They have it on paperback or Kindle
if you like digi stuff.
And it is about a group of
quote idiots and perverts
and an international
conspiracy and there's
a great drawing on the front of the book
of the Robocopter in question
that looks like maybe I did it
when I was seven years old.
It kind of reminds me of the album art
or the cover art for Grant Andrews
Kid Cop which is
my classic book coming soon to Amazon.
It looks great. So that's on
Amazon now. Think about
it. Look inside your heart.
Just decide that you need Robocopter Ski
Patrol in your life. And then
just buy it. Don't think about it anymore.
I have a message for Kevin.
Riptide Ruiz. I think
I fucked that up. And it's from
Ginny Rampage Hernandez
and Sean Bandana Mitchell.
Ginny or sorry
Rampage and Bandana say to Riptide
The starry eyed
angler gnashes through spinal
caps left by spinal taps and constant
lashes and knickknacks fallen
around her tummy sack. Lay your
head on the supple breasts of the mayor smoking
crack. That laugh that was bathed
in ichor comes from playing
like a matador has us rolling on the floor.
Did I ever tell you your mother
is a whore? Woof.
Woofa doofa. Hoofy doofy.
Rampage Bandana you're better than that.
What happened?
What did I just read?
What was any of that?
I think you're a slam poet now.
I think I might be. Did I not slam
that hard enough? The starry eyed
angler
gnashes through
spinal caps.
Hold on. I'm going to decipher this real quick.
Oh Riptide
just graduated from college. Congratulations
Kevin. Congratulations Riptide.
We're very proud of you.
It was a hard time
getting through Spinal
Taps University.
You did a really great job. Happy
graduation.
Now you have a wide
world of opportunities just laying in front
of you. I'm Jesse Thorn. I'm
Jordan Morris. The federal government
has millions of dollars in programs
and opportunities that you need to
seize today. You're a taxpayer right?
Well then you've got it coming.
Learn the secrets you deserve to
know. Find the bowling alley
under the White House and the laser tag
arena underneath Congress.
Learn the real story behind Nicholas
Cage's dinosaur auction.
Find out why the Department of Energy
has banned shirts. Learn the
locations of America's secret
alien bases and Dan Ackroyd.
Find out where the Library of Congress
keeps its kasingles.
For all of this and more
drop us a line Jordan Jesse
Go 123
iTunes Street or wherever you download
podcasts. Take us in.
Farm
wisdom
farm wisdom. It's been a while.
Make a cake right out of hay farm
wisdom. Make a what now?
wisdom. Make cakes. I got make
a but then what? Make a cake
right out of hay farm
wisdom. I thought you said cake
rat. Have the saddest birthday
farm wisdom.
Well not if you're a cow.
If you're a cow I
go down real soon. It would be fucking dope.
Farm wisdom. It's back.
Griffin read the first one.
This one is from Hannah who says
donkeys hate canines.
To protect your sheep from coyotes
you should get a couple of donkeys.
They get lonesome if they are only
one. Ain't that the truth. Be
very careful. They will sometimes
kick and kill pet dogs.
Man.
You gotta really hate
dogs. Yeah.
You know that movie Must Love Dogs?
Don't try to set
a donkey up with Jenny Garofalo.
I don't know what I just said.
No that was
what that movie was about. Was she in it
or was that true about cats? Nope.
Oh fuck. Okay.
So now I know that. Also
about coyotes. They love to
hunt domesticated dogs.
The way they do it is to send one
coyote of the pack to play with the dog
and lure it back to the pack where they will kill
it and eat it. They don't eat
the paws though. So if you see
your dog playing with a coyote get it
away fast. What the
fuck coyotes?
They're all honeypotting
all over the place. They're setting up these
irresistible honeypot play
pin traps. This is some
fucking garbage.
I can't believe
that coyotes weren't
any better
than this. You'd think they would have a little more
respect for their superiors.
Why do
you think they consume all the
coyote but they draw the line or the
dog but they draw the line at the paws?
Because that's the part that's been on a
human floor.
It's too prim and
proper, you know what I mean?
This is fucked up. Hey, you like
to play? Hey, check out
this butt. You want to sniff it? Yeah, let's do a
butt sniff. Hey, you know where we can find a lot
of other butts? We can just sort of slam
jam on and just sort of
sniff all day until the sun comes down.
I can tell you back in my
coyote house. Come back to my coyote house. I got
about six or seven butts there and we can go sniff them
together and you'll come home with your paws intact.
I promise you're going to have a great time.
Don't mind all the paws laying around. We got piles
of paws, piles of paws. Don't worry about those.
Those are from other dogs but they're not
as special as you. I'm sure you'll pass through our coyote
gauntlet just fine. Unmarred.
Just come on through, come on through.
Butts are just a little bit further, a little bit further
and chomp.
I also want to say
Hannah, thank you so much for sending these in.
But I can honestly say even without this
little snippet of farm wisdom, if I looked
out my window and saw my dog playing
with a coyote, I wouldn't just be like
aww how cute.
That's sweet. I'll tell you what else I
wouldn't do though. Get
in the middle of that
because clearly coyotes
like to eat dogs very very much
and I don't want to
I don't want to be the one
who is saying please don't do this.
Oh you don't want to take that away from
the coyote? Well no
I don't want to take me into
the coyote. I don't want to be
eaten by a coyote.
If Justin had his
I love dogs. I love dogs.
I know where they sell them.
He loves coyotes but
the outside of them. Not the inside.
Not the inside. I don't need a better look there.
I love dogs.
I know where they sell dogs.
Yeah. Do you guys want a yahoo?
Sure, yeah.
This yahoo was sent in by
level 14,000 Yajur Shaman
Drew Davenport. Thank you Drew.
It's by Yajur Answers user
Ricardus who asks
Scientists
try to dim the sun
witches pray
so that the sun doesn't shine.
The result will be
famine. What needs to be
done about this?
Okay, so
run it back.
The question asker is
just stating the fact
that scientists
All facts here, baby.
Okay, scientists are trying to dim the sun.
Fact. Correct.
While simultaneously
on the other end of the spectrum
witches are trying to stop the sun
from shining. Oops, both
worked. Now we got famine.
Yeah.
If we need witches and scientists to agree
that just one of them is going to keep
the sun in check. Because right now
there's a little bit too much
between the science and the prayers.
Sounds getting a little too dark for my
taste, thank you.
Did the scientists go to
the witches as like
one option for
keeping the sun in check? Like listen, our science
isn't getting it. We have
one other scientific solution, witches.
Please, please, just
dim it down. Keep it down. See, I
was thinking that it was more of a circumstance
in which the two sides just forgot
to communicate with each other. Yeah, that's what I
think is happening. Oh no, it was an off week.
Science was supposed to keep the sun
not burning the planet up.
And they're like, no, because last week
wait, hold on, was it an odd numbered week?
Oh no, we scienced and magicked.
We scienced and magicked too dark.
Science had the week off.
It's so vitally important that
at least one of these two organizations is
doing something about the goddamn sun now.
Or else what's up, day after
tomorrow, solar flares,
Golden Gate Bridge, that's gone.
The sun got melted by the sun's extreme heat.
Why?
Okay. Ionosphere?
Witches did that, so you have
them to thank for the ionosphere.
No, here's the one thing I will say
to Justin's point. I love
anyone who poses a question
and then ends it, like, poses a hypothetical
and it's like, what can we do to stop it?
It's like, but you, but you,
that's like saying, like, what if demons
attacked, demons and monsters
attacked Earth? What could be done?
This is, this is, Travis, this is fucking
Debate Club 101.
If you even open up
your, uh,
if you even open up your statement
to be
possibly disproven, if you
show even a fraction of a shadow of doubt
in your own mind, then your enemy
debater is gonna come at you with a
hearty riposte, and he's gonna tear
your shit apart. This is why
just like a coyote
does with a dog.
I appreciate this question
asked here. Doesn't want to get hung up too
much on the will they, won't
they of witches and
science. Will those two kids ever get
together?
This person has left right
to, let's get, of course
it's going to happen. Let's work on
solutions together, internet.
Let's get a plan together
for when this does happen. Okay, we're gonna have
to get the daughter of the Witch King to
fall in love with the son of the lead
scientist, right? And it's like
what science and magic together
this couldn't possibly be. But then
they really hit it off, and they're like
man, love would be great if we weren't so hungry
because of this blasted famine.
Oh, solutions.
She'll fill his belly
with her magical
spawn, and when
that baby comes out of his body,
fully formed man,
he will be the
solar lord. Please tell me
Travis, there is at least one
or Griffin, please tell me there's at least
one response to this.
A question from someone saying
okay, I'm picking up what you're laying down
let me uh, fly my pen. Finally someone had the
balls to say it. Well, we're
all thinking. Uh,
well, first off, let me hit you with
Saucy's response. My fucking voice
Saucy is in the comments.
You know when he's got something to say, you can't fucking
keep Saucy down. And
Saucy said, damn some
does sound good right now.
Nice.
Whoa, Saucy,
you completely, you just intentionally
misinterpreted dim sun. And he
did it. That's classic. That's fucking classic
Saucy. And he just, oh my,
someone call an ambulance because my gut just
fucking busted. Now I'm septic.
Um,
Witness of Jesus, uh,
has a pretty level headed, um,
response that has nothing to do with the Rothschild
banking cartels. Oops, no wait.
Uh, ultimately, we need
to put climate changers in jail for
fraud and embezzlement of taxes.
We need to get rid of the United Nations
and all treaties, and we need to
put the last ten presidents in jail
for treason with the Rockefellers and the
Rothschilds for being enemies of
American citizens. Witches need to
repent, no doubt. Everything
thinks their own versions of
sin and idolatry are okay. Not so.
Everything that offends will be destroyed.
And to me, the true definition of a witch
is one who poisons.
So just like everything.
All of it.
I love a comment that
even the question asker who asked about
witches and scientists did me something like,
whoa, calm down, crazy person. Guys,
chemtrails are obviously a
direct result of President Obama
through Carter's
witch sin. What?
We need to put the last ten presidents in jail, even the
dead ones. We gotta put
them. We need to
exhume Reagan, and it's the only
way we're gonna get rid of these god damn
chemtrails.
Fuck me.
Jesus. And a witch is just
someone who poisons.
No, a witch is
not that. No, that's just unfair
because you're gonna lump a lot of just regular
poisoners in with witches.
I just want one question that is just
gonna be relaxing to answer.
I don't think that's so much to ask.
I just want one soothing
question. Yeah.
You mean it's not soothing thinking about the witch
led solar death of the universe?
Yeah. What is your opinion
on returning food if your order
is incorrect? There we go. This is nice.
And does your opinion alter
if the food is takeout rather than
dine in? Recently I ordered
a calzone from a local pizza- okay,
listen, you know what? I don't
need this whole story. They got your calzone
wrong, right?
Well, no, okay, the fuck up that they did
is, in my mind,
treasonous.
I think they should be hanged from the
neck until dead for what they did
to this man's calzone. I ordered a calzone from a local
pizzeria in which the filling I received was ham
rather than pepperoni. Hang from the neck
until dead.
Dead in the street.
This is high treason. High
calzone treason. Drag
them away. With a calzone,
you didn't know till you bit into
it. You couldn't look and say like,
oh, you had to take a bite and be like,
oh, oh.
You went from having pizza
simulcrum to this
weird chicken cordon
bleu with no chicken mess.
You've hammed me, sir. You've hammed
me.
God, I hate ham. I've been John Hammed.
Ham, you are so close to being him.
Are you suggesting that John Ham
earned his nom de plume
by going to calzone-serving
restaurants and hiding
his horrible namesake
inside of those sacred pockets of
dough? He's like Johnny Appleseed of
ham.
Oh, Christ.
Johnny Hampleseed.
I totally get it.
This is a tough, tough thing because if you're
in the building...
I'm sorry, I'm still thinking about
getting ham. I'm angry.
When I thought I was getting pepperoni. I'm sorry,
Travis. Go ahead. No, I was just going to say if you're in the
building and it's brought to your table,
it's so easy to be like, oh, I
ordered ham, but
I ordered pepperoni. Even then,
I was with my friend the other day. He ordered
some boneless chicken wings, got bone-in chicken
wings, and the look
on the face of the server when he was like,
oh, they were supposed to be boneless, and you could
clearly see this process of like, oh, I don't
know what to do with these then.
I can't unbone them.
Eventually, he was just like, no,
it's fine. Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
When I started reading this question, I was thinking
almost... I can't
imagine a scenario where I wouldn't just
grin and bear it because for me, the
social discomfort that I would be
causing myself and this person
by sending it back
would be too extreme to stomach.
But not more extreme
to stomach than fucking calzone
ham. That is, I guess,
a bridge too far for this guy.
The bigger concern for me
is not the
awkwardness of the initial exchange.
It's the, okay,
everybody who also got their
food just now, go ahead and eat,
and I'll watch you, and then later,
you'll watch me eat a pepperoni calzone
from dream of
my hamless future.
Now, I will say this.
Even if I didn't send it back,
I would still...
If I was in the restaurant,
if I was dining in, I would still say something.
Because at the very least, my meal should
be discounted because you fucking got it
wrong. But
it's so much tougher with delivery
because unless you open the
box, take a bite of the fucking
hamzone, and drive back
to the... And that is not a good look
to tell the delivery person, like, wait,
one second. Let me taste this first.
You take a bite first.
You take a bite of the king's calzone.
John Ham got me last time.
No, but, like, that idea of, like, if the drivers
are, like, your only option is, like, to drive
to the place.
Chasing him down the street.
Stop, stop! There's been a ham mistake!
Charlton!
Come back! You've stolen my dignity!
Christopher, there's been a ham,
a terrible ham mistake!
You must stop
your vehicle.
Someone summon a ambulance!
On the subject
of
getting the meal discounted
because they made a ham mistake
inside my dough,
I would not worry so much about
immediate fiducial restitution
because I would
sue that establishment for every
goddamn penny that they have.
Walk into the court with, like, a neck
brace on.
I would fucking
take Papa John.
I think that, um,
one of the things that bothers me about
getting the wrong item is when I correct
them, and then they take
the wrong item back.
Like, no, that's mine now.
You put it in
front ofwe were at that coffee shop
this weekend across
from the Hotel Kabuki. They gave me the
wrong drink, and I had to
correct them, and then they took that wrong drink
back, and it's like, hold on a second.
This is mine now. I'm gonna
decide what to do with this. You focus on
your thing. I'm gonna decide how I distribute
this. Maybe I wanna split it. I don't
know. You've created an impossible
minefield, but I do think I can eat
around the ham.
It's gonna take me a while.
I might have wanted to cut the crust off and turn it
into breadsticks. You're not the boss of me.
I've actually brought my pet
crow here for this very reason. He
digs into the calzone and
removes the ham so I can enjoy a
ham-free experience. He's my
ham man. He's my ham crow.
If you eat it, you have
just, like, entered into
the situation, the possibility of impropriety,
in that you are creating
ham calzones
with the intent of eating them,
in which case that means
you like ham. Get
outta here. You disgust me. You like secret ham.
You'll never know how much ham will be
in that bite. Enjoy. Secret dirty
free ham. You fucking
monster. You put in the, you're hungry
and you put in the one ingredient you know no one
would ever eat, and that's
ham. And it
all would've worked out if it wasn't
for the one guy who ran down the
street chasing the delivery driver
and unraveled your dastardly ham
plans, John Ham.
Do you think the first person
that fucking, the
calzone guy, everyone was like, well,
we did it. We perfected food. And
then the first person was like, I
can ruin that. Some fucking
gnarled fucking necromancer
was like, I know what to do.
You all seem to be enjoying
your precious calzones.
I think it is a good point
that I think the difference, so like, the difference
between the boneless versus bone-in wings
and this is that
that is just form version
different. This is like content
version different. Where it's like
if you ordered a steak sandwich and they
brought you a chicken sandwich, like
that's a fucking thing. Well, no, because
ham and pepperoni are still technically
cut from the same
delicious cloth. But you understand what I'm saying, this idea of like, I
asked for a specific, this is like
if you ordered buffalo wings and
they brought you teriyaki wings, like
that's a problem.
Like they just got it 100%
wrong. What if, if you got a ham
calzone, could you not just
sort of sit the ham out
and wait for it to turn into pepperoni?
Just
age it in the sun.
The, the inclusion of bones
in the wings is a, makes it a much
is a much bigger jump
I think than pepperoni to
ham. Cause the inclusion of bones in the wings is
ruining the illusion
that I have that
meat just comes from the store.
Right. And that's as much as I have to think about
it. Meat, this meat comes from the store.
See, I hate
the bones cause it slows down my consumption
process.
I gotta work around something.
Not as much as ham slows
down my calzone consumption process
which is to say absolutely.
It absolutely terminates
the process. Absolutely ham zero.
No one's seen Griffin for 40 years.
He took a bite of a ham calzone
and had to retreat into the mountains
to really think about things. He turned into
a jade statuette.
Remember when Griffin
ate that ham accidentally and turned
into a jade statuette
because he didn't want to be alive anymore?
All the best folk stories
start with Griffin eating a ham calzone.
I miss Griffin.
I miss Griffin. Not as much as
I would have liked to share his pepperoni
calzone though. Goddamn.
We were gonna split that. He jumped on that
grenade for me and he turned into a jade
statue. Well if you want to wipe the taste
of ham out of your mouth, go to naturebox.com
We want to thank again
for being a sponsor on the show and you can get something like
barbecue kettle kernels to wash that
terrible, terrible ham taste out of your mouth.
No, no ham guarantee at
naturebox.com slash my brother.
If you want to pretend that your ham is a little
person, go to meonies.com slash my brother
and buy some underwear to put on it.
You get 20% off your
first order and right now you get free shipping
for your ham underwear.
The perfect size for your ham.
Oh Christ. This ham is
really fucking dry. Yeah, I know.
I've been storing it in meonies
and it has moisture wicking properties.
I'm trying to turn it into pepperoni.
Thank you to everybody who came to our
live shows.
In San Francisco and L.A. we had
a real hoot I would say.
It was a hoot nanny if I may be so bold.
Thank you to the folks at
COBS and
the Hollywood Fairfax Cemetery.
Everybody was super, super nice
and really helped us to
get those shows off the ground for you.
And also Sketchfest people were amazing.
If you're going to go into Sketchfest,
you need to go next year because it's incredible.
We will
probably be posting the San Francisco
live show in, I don't know,
in a few weeks. We're kind of keeping it in the chamber
because Justin's about to move
and we'll probably be disconnected
from the web for a while.
We are going to publish that one,
but it may be a little while.
We got
PO Boxes. Mine's 54.
PO Box 54,
100 West Virginia 25706.
Mine is 173469
Los Angeles, California
90034.
There are still
tickets available for Chicago and Milwaukee
shows coming up.
I think it's bit.ly forward slash
mbmbam Chicago and bit.ly forward slash
mbmbam what Travis?
M-I-L.
So go there. They are very
close to
sold out.
I know that Minneapolis is
already sold out
and I'm checking the most recent count
right now. It looks like we are
89% sold out in
Milwaukee and 76%
sold out in Chicago. So
if you've been thinking about getting tickets to that,
do not sleep on that any longer.
It is time.
We've received a lot of great questions already,
but we've got an upcoming episode with Paul
Scheer as our guestpert.
If you would like him to answer one of your
requests for advice, email us
mbmbam at gmail.com
or mbmbam at maximumfun.org
and those questions
should be about Jason Statham movies,
thank you notes, or weird
collectibles. Just make sure to put guestpert
in the subject line so it's easy for me to
find and that should be
coming up soon.
Max Fun Drive is coming up. That is
the Maximum Fun Network's annual
two week long
fundraiser thing.
I don't know what to call it. But it's a lot of fun.
We have some bonus length
episodes. We have a
extra donor
only episode.
And you won't want to miss
this year's donor only episode
because it's very special.
That's all I'll say about it. But yeah, that's
coming up. What are the dates
for that? I believe it's the 6th.
It starts March 16th.
Okay, starts March 16th and goes for two
weeks. So it'll be a very special
time if you're a donor.
Thank you very much. If you
have not given to the show and you want to support
the show, it's a great time to do it. See, it's cool stuff.
If you've ever tried other shows on the
network, it's a really great time to check those out
because everyone's going to be bringing their A game shows
like Oh No, Ross and Carrie,
Lady to Lady,
The Goose Down,
Flop House, all kinds of wonderful
shows, including Saw Bones with
Justin McElroy and Sydney McElroy.
It's a marital tour of Misguided Medicine.
It's hilarious. It's Teresa's favorite show on the
network and one of the few that I am not
on. So that's cool.
Okay.
Yeah, thank you all very, very
much. And also thanks to John Roderick
and the Long Winters for the use of our theme song, Is a Departure
Off the Album, Putting the Days to Bed.
Are we done?
I think we're done. Is that it?
All right, Griffin, one more question. We're going to grow on.
Bounce This Final Yahoo Off You is sent in by
Drew Davenport. Thank you, Drew. It's by Yahoo Answers user.
They are anonymous.
Can't see their name.
No username. Okay.
It's by an anonymous Yahoo Answers user who
asks, What
is Barack Obama's username
on the PlayStation Network?
I'm Justin McElroy. I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been my brother, my brother, and me, Kiss Your Dad
on the lips.
Maximum fun dot org.
Comedy and culture. Artist owned.
Listener supported.
Hello, I'm Taco, the elephant magician.
Mural High Church here, the master
of clerical magic.
I'm Magnus Burnside, the fighter.
Did you guys like that?
Did you, the listener, like that?
You were just swept up in a world
of high fantasy and magic where anything can
happen and anything is possible.
Hi, I'm Griffin McElroy, Dungeon Master for the
Adventure Zone, a new podcast on Maximum
Fun in which magic and mystery intertwine
for a very erotically
charged role-playing experience.
You can catch it every other Thursday here on
MaximumFun.org or iTunes. It's for
Dungeons & Dragons, but with family.