The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to a very special,
very personal episode of My Brother, My Brother and Me. We have an announcement to make
uh to begin this uh episode and um gosh guys I don't really know how to well I mean we we've
consulted a lot of our family and friends and a lot of people we really respect and
I think it's time that we just you know it's 20 dirt it's time we come clean it's 20 that's so
true Travis it's 20 dirt it's time to dig it up come clean we have been doping there it is beginning
in June of 1998 basically over a decade before we would begin the show in preparation
to record this program we have been injecting bull semen into our buttocks nature's funniest animal
nature's funniest liquid uh directly into us um every day every hour for the past 15 years I am
I am fucking chock full of bull semen and like it it's I sweat the stuff and it's
right do you know how the human body is like 75% water at this point Griffin is like 72% bull
semen right um it's why I can't really run I ambulate slowly but it's because I'm very viscous
inside um and he he basically can't go to a dairy farm they will go hide he basically if he walks
runs through with hands outstretched he can impregnate 10 to 15 cows a second yeah they get
it's amazing they they will try to get on top of this and now I'm flattered now a lot of people ask
how you get into this sort of there is a an underworld I guess and I'm I'm I'm worried about
outing people but I guess well let's use let's use code names then we'll say schmorton schmorris
okay schmorton schmorris got us into it and uh he was one of the first that really turned us
onto it and dan kennison basically sam kennison but he's dead so like yeah yeah and uh what's
that other angry guy shouty kind of shouty fucking everybody likes him because he said a bunch of
raymond things on him bill you know comedy bill bill cosby yeah that's it so bill cosby
i'm so full of the pussy but that's how we started we didn't we couldn't take the injections
phil william cosby was my comedy coach in high school sure and we were trying to make state for
comedy comedy stay and he says uh you know that show the state that's what that's what it's about
he says you look he did it but in a bill cosby voice how would that sound
um you gotta get a leg up on the competition and so that's melting at the end of it that's when i
started well he was so so just jam ram jammed with cum and like um so like that's how i got
started was pressure from from coach cosby yeah uh listen guys let's put this note we will continue
to inject ourselves with bull can you guys believe that they didn't induct anybody to the comedy hall
of fame this year yeah yeah just because of all the jizzing we've been you got to retire from
comedy for five years and i can't think of anybody well and the problem is is like even after that
when you break comedy records they're still going to put an asterisk next your name right but not
only that but there are so many great comedy champs out there that don't jizz like bobcat goldthwait
he's oh yeah he was a staunch anti-jizzer right you could make the argument that that jerry
seinfeld retired from comedy decades ago right and uh and he's still out there never jizzed you
can't no way has he never jizzed julia louise drivers was telling me that she tried to get him
to yeah and he just shut her down and then canceled the show he was like i'm sick of the
pressure and he canceled it but we're not canceling this show we're gonna move right on
let's uh let's get our first question up in the mix this one comes to us from uh uh i would i
would also point out we never actually introduced ourselves but i mean at this point people come on
i'm justin i'm i'm i'm travis i'm gonna say griffin you wanna switch i've been fucked up
you wanna switch for the show good up yeah i'm griffin okay fuck it i'm travis somebody hand me
an everything bagel with a ham with a ham hock on it i'm greg okay the footballer the football
loves touchdown yeah i love tds guys i feel like shit what's wrong i drank too much alcohol what
happened i did uh we did did these shots that i learned from epic meal time called the gordon
bombay where you take a shot of bombay gin and then have everyone call you gordon for the rest
of the night fuck those guys are funny they are jizzing they are jizzing to the fucking max and
like i am worried about where like their health is i hope that they come maybe they'll come to max
funcon someday and just like eat but that would be bad because it's in an isolated environment
it'll become like a like a doner party kind of thing yeah right they'll eat all the food and
then they're just like a meal time cannibalism yeah turn into hunger games um uh i left my
college town a couple years ago the old gang is slowly starting to break up one member of the
gang is the one who got away and i never confessed the fact that i've been crazy for him since we
met several years ago i've already moved away from our college town and only go back to visit
he'll be moving away within the year should i risk our remaining long distance friendship to
get it off my chest i know 20 does was the year getting it but i'm not sure what to do in 20
bakers does um how could we be from gmail any fucking clearer about what you're supposed to do
do in 20 dirt 20 dirt dig it up dig this shit up this is dirt this is dirty this is dirty dirt
get out the shovel scoop it and poop it get it out there you you this relationship
is a long distance relationship which is to say it's not one right yeah you might as well like
the first uh three quarters of of that question was just like it's dissolving it's dissolving
it's dissolving it's dissolving what do i do fuck it fuck it check take a shot maybe he
feels the same way is it too late to change the name of the year to 20 fuck yeah it is it really
rick really really is ricky is it ricky is the year of dj can i learn dj with my mouth i i say
i say just do it now there are two different ways to do it option a is you know the the
confessing of your love and say hey i've always option b is to say hey confetti
option a confetti i always loved you
just rip taylor him right let's have rip taylor go do some toupee humor
then option he'll get it he'll get it he'll know what's up and then option b is to say
i just matter of fact like hey devon by the way i've always dug you all right see you later side
note sorry quick addendum editors editor's note asterisk nobody's ever loved anyone named devon
man anytime we goof on a day there's always one guy is like
ah that's me i i'm really worried that there's a devon out there is like you got me
i am alone that one is good i am alone that is a good one you guys got me um
um yeah i mean you know it's it's long this this i know this feeling i know this feeling
of like everyone's starting to move away in a friend group starting to to bifurcate and perhaps
even trifurcate uh but but that's a great time to shore up some of the ones that matter to you the
most and if this is uh a guy that you care about then i mean why not i'm always gonna we're always
gonna tell you to to to go for it and stuff like this i mean friendships are nice but especially
long distance friendships it's a perfect situation you never have to see the guy right if it doesn't
work out you're never gonna see this fucko he's gone i mean honestly the worst the worst that
is probably no the worst that could happen is like an asteroid falls from the sky but like
the worst that's probably going to happen is if he doesn't reciprocate the feelings
it may be awkward for like a month or two but i mean you guys have known each other for a while
now and it's long distance so it's not like you have to awkwardly see each other that is that is
not it'll be fine again that is not how that's gonna go down it's he's not gonna say no he's
gonna also see the plate tectonics shifting the two of you away from each other this is
at any given point in your life there are like 10 people who this is your last chance to fuck them
oh you're painting a can't hardly wait situation i don't know what the fuck you're talking about
okay i'm saying that it look around look around you really look around you this only works if
you're like outside but look around you because the only thing in this room is uh my cat and my
sensi okay i might pretend that this is out of 30 rock okay have you hugged your mug today okay
well you guys can make pretend to do this with these things but i'm saying like you're on a bus
and you just got to the diversity stop and there goes six people just got off the bus you are never
going to have another chance to fuck those six people again or that sensi candle or that have
you hugged a mug today mug so they're like the six feet maybe there'll be the six people you
fucking heaven that's possible it's hard to say but i'm assuming you ride the bus a lot and
therefore come in contact with this situation thousands of times in your lifetime so it's more
like like the 650 000 people that you i actually have a i not a joke uh i i actually do think this
way on occasion not about sex though but about uh like if i'm in a in a place i've never been
in a place i've never been before and i'm moving through it you know like say an airport or
something like that as i'm passing those those people it is almost certainly the only time i'm
ever gonna see them it is intoxicating right basically well no what because the way i think
about it is that basically as soon as i avert my eyes from those people they're dead basically
like they're dead that's actually how i operate in just everyday life just when i don't see my
friends they're dead whenever i'm not talking to you guys you're dead so it's my world that
only exists within a six-foot circle around so like when babies start to figure out like
spatial understanding uh-huh that's just like no object permanent you just skip that one we
tried to play peekaboo with travis it just screams it just screams wildly where are you
what the fuck just there was a man there was a man named clint this sounds like a pretty good
liam neeson movie exactly where did you go it's taken three and he's playing peekaboo with his
daughter return my daughter to me um well i mean i'm just behind this washcloth dad
dad i'm behind a washcloth i have a particular set of skills i'm up i'm upstairs i'm you hear
the vacuum cleaner i'm upstairs please fix your object permanence i have a particular set of
skills object permanence is not one of them but i have learned all my shapes let me draw you a
circle 10 i have 10 fingers 10 toes this is like a muppet baby's version of taking babies oh god
i make peepee in the potty who's the big boy you're about to find out if you don't return my
daughter dad i'm right here just turn around slightly to the side you swear you wouldn't do
this at my wedding i'll lift the veil is that what you want i'll lift it fuck you guys want
to answer yeah yeah god i hope liam neeson doesn't hear that bit of all the like shit talk we talk
about so yeah you'll talk about anybody but not leo yeah uh this one was sent in by surprise
surprise ira ray thank you ira ray are you ira ray who wants to know i i like that ira ray has
contributed enough now that he gets like some sting music you know yeah yeah uh thank you ira
it's by yahoo answers user ben who asks oh this is a fucking rhyming to send you this picture of
ben this kid is so full um who asks what a 20 year old girl like a gps with my voice recorded as a
gift i kind of like her but she has no idea would giving a gps garmin with my voice recorded four
directions be a good gift if not any other suggestions well if you don't do a gps with
your own voice in it i don't know what other suggestions what else is there right yeah what
other yeah it's either that or darth vader uh yeah i have uh something that sounds like my wife
that always tells me how to drive it's called my wife am i right fellas everybody loves justin
um uh i would i would go so far as to say first bin that doesn't exist no it does yeah you can
you can get a garment and then just record yourself saying every single direction that
could ever happen yeah sure oh my god i think that you know i would get i would get uh i wonder
if sandra bullock would do it but like shout i always feel like i'm in speed speed up it's like
i'm in a school zone sandy chill on it um it depends entirely on what this kid's voice sounds
like doesn't it oh he's got like a smooth billy d thing going on yeah damn girl pump the brakes
you're coming up to a stop sign what you gonna do you see that barn turn left at the bar like
that's that would be good but if it's like um go straight for 200 meters next stop my heart
my heart you're gonna go to the flower store and i'm gonna buy you flowers tod hey todd here turn
left can you imagine as the voice of your car what if you could get william daniels but wait
a minute here's the here's the twist he's not kit he's mr feeny are you kidding me imagine it mr
mcroy turn left i kind of i don't know i'm kind of into this idea now there's lots who would you
who in your life who in your life would you would you most like to to have coming out of
your speakers does it have to be like someone we know or like a celebrity someone living or dead
but only dead william daniels yeah you kind of kind of blew it already it's like the best possible
one so we'll strike him because i don't think he's dead okay you know don adams would be good
quit i don't know who that is or do i mean don knots fuck is this is that a good that is a weird
gift it's a weird it's a weird way to tell someone that you like them how do you do how do you do it
do you like you slip it in subliminally that's what it has like turn left on love street
it's like what i don't see love street i meant canadie boulevard well that would get fucking
annoying because like this is a this is a woman on the go you know i feel like the whole present
is fucking annoying i mean it's thoughtful if the if the woman doesn't have gps and she gets lost
you know but what's less thoughtful is if you get it for for that purpose but then you instead of
saying you just take out the word turn right and you replace it with i love you susan will you be
mine love love todd there's a nerdy person named todd that's true travis i didn't think about that
every todd has to be a like some sort of sportsman let's go with gilbert oh that's much much much
better gill oh sorry gilbert sorry the sorry the gilbert that listens to this show we sincerely
apologize listen is it appropriate to chime in when someone's getting heavy praise for something
you did most of the work on or are you supposed to catch the praise giver in private and then let
them know the real deal or are you supposed to just let it go that's from feeling gypped in japan
that's okay i don't know why we got a good question that's offensive that's an offensive
name but anyway feeling traveler in japan i think they prefer travelers feeling romanied
feeling romanied nomadic fortune tellers okay that might be that might be racist hold on i think we
crossed backwards secret werewolf curse lingered here's the problem is it's it's like a lose lose
lose situation it really really wicked is that's why the dude is supposed to say like hey i that
it wasn't just me this is a this is not a one-man team yeah i think that's i think that's fourth
option is you confront the the praise given later and be like hey uh what the fuck um all you did
was get the coffee and i did 16 hours of work you got you got a logic trap this guy like while
everyone's praising and be like oh great do it again right now in front of all of us let's see it
here are the twigs do it what what possible thing could someone be praised for with twigs
shitty birdhouse okay that's called a nest you dumb ass build a nest again bird i did that that
bird didn't build that nest i did check the nest that's my saliva holding those twigs twigs when i
am a dad the one i will tell my children everything the truth about everything but the one thing i
will tell them that is not true is that i made every nest so they see a nest of the tree i made
it their dear old dad was the guy when they asked what you do for a living like well every day i
take my briefcase full of twigs and i go out for eight hours a day and make nests the city pays me
to do it those uh those grackles really do look comfortable you're right daddy did that daddy did
that for those grackles you could call people who own birdhouses slumlords my dad's building
organic housing so here's the issue with this option one you interrupt and say um excuse me uh
boss man i did all the work that's the worst you look shitty that's the worst one don't do that
unless no way benefits unless unless you do it in a fun way like when he's like i put this
presentation together and everyone's clapping and you go and i helped like like the shake and bake
ads like the old shake and bake advertisements and people will get a real kick out of it and then
the boss will turn to to michael's and be like michael's is this true and he'll be like oh yeah
yeah johnson's johnson's definitely helped your last name is johnson your last name is plural
my father founded the big johnson's t-shirt company
i'll be damned if i let it sit and follow the likes of you uh listen uh the the these are all
bad yeah i think the only one don't talk to the person in private because then like that looks
really really bad because it looks so shady and like underhanded but like hey um i didn't want
to say anything earlier right oh but he didn't do all the work i did the i i mean i don't think
it's a terrible idea to go to the to the person and say like listen we've both worked on this it
would mean a lot to me if you but then he'd be like oh oh oh what about this you go to him and
say hey i really appreciated all the things and the nice things you said about the project we
work really hard on it i didn't get a chance to earlier but i just wanted to say thank you i
really appreciated the acknowledgement oh no that's like a crazy thing but i kind of that's
really manipulative yeah you act as though dude also called you out and then he's like uh could
i yeah congratulations that's a pr i like that travis i'm actually into that could i do that for
anything though sorry like if i go to like a live theater show and like everybody's clapping and be
like guys thank thank you guys thank you so much for just acknowledging all of our hard work up
there we get up there every day just trying to make you laugh trying to make you cry trying to
make you clap you can always pretend to be the director no one knows no we're the writer who
knows who wrote a play really well unless you're unless it's like a shakespeare show which went
good luck that was me every time i see shakespeare when everybody's clapping i i like they shout
and i shout like they shout like bravo i'm i'm shouting like author author because i hope one
time he's like what shakespeare you're saying yeah you hope one time that one out of out of
let's say the 30 times you've seen a shakespeare show he arrives he arrives just in time he he
splits up through the floorboards very spooky goes to shakespeare and he's like you did a good
job with my play okay and and the reason he comes is because you just imagine i have shakily
supported his art form maybe 20 or 30 times i'm so glad i was able to reach one special boy in this
room only one person appreciated my play and then what if later that night you're watching
along came polly on dvd at home and he pops out of the tv like i did this one too like i don't
think you did really this one's based on othello is it is it really you know if you hung out with
shakespeare's ghost he would try to claim everything is some permutation oh yes the
incredible mr limpin it's very much like hamlet think about it really shakespeare it kind of
seems you know what is like mine is oedipus rex i'll hold on there because you that one is definitely
not you but wouldn't it be great to be hanging out with him in like 10 things i hate about you
come on and he's like this was come on they got it they improved it they nailed it i thought
i was gonna make a joke about i always get confused if that woman's name is elisa
olenik or larissa olenik can anyone come it's larissa the one thing i know is that the secret
world of alex mack was based on two gentlemen of verona think about it because the one gentleman
can dissolve into a pool of water it's not water griffin sorry it's it's ectoplasm she's a ghost
how about a yahoo can i keep talking about shakespeare's ghost i'm really into it do you
think he asked everyone if they have boz lerman's number so you can call him and tell him he's a
dick i did i did like leonardo de caprio but everything else was just leo leo was great and
that john leguizamo don't get me started what a delightful hispanic hold on hold on shakespeare
i like the movie about the more who teaches keanu how to fight
do you mean the matrix and did you just say the more could you not it's laurence fishburne
shakespeare you know he would claim to make up most words too anytime you used an impressive word
he would have to slip in there you know i i coined that in hamlet eight hamlet eight hamlet the eight
hamlet eight that was it was never produced i just finished the manuscript when i died i can
show you where i hid it if you want oh no okay it's just it's just an empty castle for two and
a half hours and then somehow is a good day to hamlet i don't know i don't think it was a good
name uh uh okay griffin now you can thank you i think i'm done talking about shakespeare's ghost
cool i went to stratford upon avon uh for our honeymoon and uh i got a big kick out of when
we got back pretending that there were more places named after shakespeare's plays in the uh in the
restaurant areas than there were because there was really no i i wanted steakspeares there were no
tie-ins what no tie-ins no tie-ins no no oh you know a subway would be great but they call it
as you like it you can just get the sandwich however you want okay griffin now i'm really
done i don't think i don't think i can trust you anymore i promise all right um this yahoo answer
was sent in by ryan lowen thank you ryan it's by yahoo answers user friendly zombie who asks
is it legal to smoke weed in space if an astronaut is out of any country would
nasa have any legal recourse if you smoked a bowl in the space shuttle i think it's the
kind of thing that they say not to do but everybody does it oh yeah i think the bigger problem is
less the smoking than the fire i think that you do get into some issues i think they'd probably
be okay with the weed if it wasn't for the you know open flame in a thing made of explosions
i think is less than ideal that's actually what happened in apollo 13 dude sparked a bowl
and they had a problem man that sounded so natural try this when you just said sparked a bowl
i could tell you griffin i've been practicing you sounded like a real grade eight chief chiefer
um you know you could just you can make this easier on yourself don't go to space to spark a
bowl go go to the south pole no country oh that's true that's a fact you just go to the south pole
and get like fucking lit just build a big like build the gazuntite institute down there at the
south pole and everybody can just like get high and patch adams can can fix people up and there's
no lawyers cops or toes because they all fell off your fucking foot because you're on the south
goddamn pole what are you treated the gazuntite institute you know what a lot a lot of any
anything related to freezing to death i have like probably the best at gangrene right now
like if you get gangrene don't even trip because i i do have that under control i have a better
place okay you're fucking attic or anywhere anywhere nobody's ever glow in the dark stars
post them up on the ceiling you're in space all of a sudden you're in space you don't need to
fucking nobody's ever gotten busted for doing weed fact fact because every time a cop catches
someone kept doing weed they're like ah kids you do getting it you guys having fun being young
enjoying it enjoying get out of here you're right get out of there enjoy that don't smoke it again
but if you do it's fine we've had a lot of fun here today but i do think we need to clarify that
i don't think this question asker was desperate to find a place he can smoke pot and space was his
last refuge like there's there are many other steps i think to before you you you like resort
to in a cave right you could always smoke in a cave underneath a camel why i mean why not it's
easier to get to you than space it's just a place on the earth is what you're saying yeah i'm just
i'm just thinking of places i could have said under a table but that's not as fun if the president
united states of america sparked up a j uh-huh in the oval office you know he does why do i know
he does what because he legalized it legalized it i don't he didn't though he's actually been
cracking down he said he was gonna legalize it he put a big old check mark on that bill
i yeah he was like approved approval what's the opposite of a veto is it an approval it's an
approval but i think you may be um confusing legalized marijuana with unmanned drone strikes
again i think you got it twisted maybe he gets high off unmanned drones oh that's the fucking
stuff what was that a wedding awesome uh fuck shoot it into my veins and also into them all of
them's shoot them's oh man getting political a little bit of fire edgy let's get paid
so
fat sacks fat sacks coming to us from emily to sam travis just read it get it out there
this message is for my asynchronous twin my brother sam for his 30th birthday we both love
mbbam which always gives us something to talk about while we try to bond over our 4 000 mile
separation happy birthday sam and then apparently she would like us to do a goof about i'm utilization
jesus jesus we can turn this heartwarming message into something that will make him
and then she trails off um cry sick hard sad i'm gonna go with hard because i think sam's a
total weird beard um hey weird sam i'm not gonna goof about fucking if you want to get your rocks
off over i'm relation go watch event horizon but get that out of here get that bad stuff out of
here oh what's the nation for this twin i think it's just people who are close so it's like a
brother come on but i mean but it's like hey listen it's can we not do this on sam's birthday
please okay i'm sorry i'm sorry sam emily i'm sorry can you not make a scene so happy birthday
sam i'm so happy you lived who's this message this next message is for sarah winters from abby
van van van den berg who's her sister van van den berg it's van den berg there's three vans
and then her name you have to really take a run abby van van van den berg uh my baron von van
den berg my sister sarah von kinder snoot introduced me to your show and we are both
big fans i won't be with my sister for her bday this year since we live in different cities
please brothers mcroy wish her in the creepiest wispiest voices you can muster a happy 33rd
birthday for me happy 33rd birthday can you can you make yourself sound like
the french baby ghost from your favorite youtube video
let me get the stamp of approval un-listenable thank you wonderful wunderbar
we finally nailed the exact right way to make a podcast no one enjoys listening to
oh man we went the distance i made it sonically sonically unpleasant and infringed one day whenever
we retire this podcast that good come and get a day um we are just going to do an hour of that
and that's how you will know that we are done that is how you will know that's how you will
know that we have come to the end of the road this final message is to john baltisberger from
philip prochaska wishing john baltisberger a happy birthday now that is all that come from
philip prochaska that does come from philip prochaska wishing john a happy birthday and also
he wants to tell him and announce in a very public manner that he is promoting him to treasurer of
the hard to say last names club i knew i own your friend abby vandenberg recommended you abby van
van vandenberg said that we should uh she she cried second to my nomination um they do not
say which birthday this is for mr baltisberger but i am going to guess eighth so happy eighth
birthday to john baltisberger from your 45 year old friend philip prochaska and it looks here
there's uh eight quotation marks around friend so that is an upsetting that is an upsetting and a
winky face like we get it the quotes the quotes so got it okay uh also i do want to talk about
a stream restraints.com extreme restraints.com is your number one source for things you can put in
holes in your body if you want to put it in there don't waste time with a q-tip that's child's play
why don't just skip right to a ribbed anal douche if you want something inside you but that's man's
play that's man's play a ribbon illusion is great because it'll put something in you and take more
out and it's also great because you can just say a bunch of syllables and it sounds like something
like justin has been doing yeah right pleasurable uh anal douche it's designed out of latex and
rubber first off make sure you get the pleasurable one if you get the uncomfortable sad one
there's like that's extreme restraints.com there's probably a like a completely unpleasant ribbed
anal douche uh but this one looks great looks like modern art you could put this on a shelf
looks like modern family looks like the dyson back it's like that baby from modern family
you know that fat 12 year old baby on modern family manny i love that show love that baby
is there a coupon code that you can tell us about now please middle list is the coupon code that's
going to save you 20 percent on your purchases there and listen that's enough to go get yourself
another anal douche because if you're anything like me your friends see the anal douche and you
send them home with it you loan them you forget who you loan them to and uh and and you just end
up needing more so go on and get a few a lot of people hear the word i feel like uh dane cook
has taken the word douche and turned it into something oh i thought you're gonna say that
people hear the phrase anal douche and they think of think of dane cook well i feel like i feel like
people have take co-opted the word douche or anal douche although that's less popular um i'm turning
into like a bad thing but i don't think that we should i don't think we should do that for a
pleasurable and what if what if we rebrand and we go with douche hmm it sounds it sounds international
which i do like i mean it probably is international in origin i i think that's probably there is
probably some sort of european country that discovered that there is a lot of detritus
up there yeah but since it's a tool for cleanliness we can assume it wasn't france
jerry lewis
christ yeah he's popular there he had a public did you guys know there's like a pub it was kind of a
a public um it was a big deal that he got kicked out of the the whole jerry's kids mda
thing it's like a it was like a a very public uh ousting of the jarrister so long story short
visit extreme restraints.com and use the code and ponder ponder a man's life achievements
squandered squandered reduced to ash only do charity if they're going to appreciate it
that's all i'm saying i've been with my girlfriend for a little over two years and i want to ask her
to marry me my only problem is that her sister five years older if that matters got engaged
recently and her wedding will be this summer getting engaged was kind of a big deal for her
and i'd feel a little guilty distracting from her wedding with excitement of another engagement
should i wait till after the wedding to propose or just not worry and go for it before and that's
from griffin mackerel weird oh fuck listen listen got it it's actually from prudent pros prudent
proposer good work prudent proposer follow your heart you know you can't let so you can't let
the yolk counterpoint or yolk of your big brother draw you down into the muck of mediocrity vis-a-vis
marriage well it just once again confirms that everything in life is a competition
and you just have to accept that the the older sister's wedding will probably be better and
everyone will like it better let's go let's go down the line of the shit that we're going to
have at our weddings and do this competition sorry guys i don't know why this is about you
i think it's about oh no let's talk about things that you could hypothetically have at your wedding
that will make it better than your younger siblings okay okay hypothetically hypothetically speaking
chocolate fountain i had that okay so that's that's old school yeah i want the new school shit
okay but i had it so you got if you're gonna beat me you gotta have two chocolate fountains or have
one that shoots something better than chocolate and yes i am talking about bull semen um uh petting
a petting zoo okay uh i'm gonna have mine professionally lighting design and sound
design ah fuck i had this idea of what if you at the wedding also serve dinner to your guests
nice so they're actually gonna steal that but make it a picnic they fuck that's way better i know
no um i oh i like i like really love my fiance
so she's gonna be there so she'll be there
so like that's but like our i guess our love is like the big like one of the big
my fiance and i we're gonna do separate ceremonies do the groom ceremony and the bride ceremony
in different rooms i kind of like that and you can get on skype you can skype each other i just
said i do like we're 15 minutes behind and my dress is big there's a lot it's a satellite
relay thing from one room to the other um it slows down i just can't wait for you guys to
check out sex i hear it's so great i lose your mind we've been doing these extreme restraints
i feel it's a lot these are a while now and i am just geared up full of bullseye i heard
uh on yahoo answers that it's like when you put on a pair of jeans just out of the dryer and
they're still warm and the zipper is like really hot is it like is it like that yeah it's just
like that good if you got another yahoo i feel like i could use it i use a yahoo i can do that
yeah i showed this one was sent in by nick k it was or key uh it's by yahoo answers user patrick
read 50 who asks how do i get diapers without my parents finding out oh good oh diapers
it's been a recur a kind of a fun fun theme lately diapers just said somebody set a google news alert
on yahoo answers for the word diapers and just then send me that hyperlink that rss feed uh i
am 16 and i am what you would consider an adult teen baby yes okay i nobody would consider anyone
to be that because it's just three different words three completely different i wouldn't call
anyone an adult teen let alone an adult flavor in there adding my neapolitan ice cream flavor
of adult teen adult teen baby grandpa here's the thing i have the baby uh the body of a teen and
the heart of a baby and i fuck like a grown man so get over here debra i really debra i really
need to get some diapers but i don't know how to buy them without my parents finding out please
help me so i can get my inner baby out i okay i'm trying to be cool because everything's fine as
long as you're not hurting somebody so if you want to be an adult teen baby that's cool by me
but just go to the store i guess and look like one of the people on team mom just sound like
trying to do right trying to do right by my baby mama okay that's a great plan dani ocean but how
do you get those fucking diapies back into the house how do you get that you've never have you
ever bought diapies they come in an enormous almost novelty size package have you ever seen
supermarkets sleep they're trying to get the diapers into the cart right you get like one
package at most the thing is you gotta put all of them on at once why do you have to do that
that's the best way to sneak them into the house and then put your like big put your like a big
dog sweatpants on your starter jacket and your starter jacket fluffy i don't think i oh you know
you should do say your extreme couponing and that you got these you got you bought three you buy
first of all once you pull this heist then you never have to do it again because you bring home
360 different diapers now they are going to be they are going to be adult teen baby diapers so
you may have to explain your way around that you could just say you're planning on having a big
baby someday and then you got these diapers for like four dollars why don't you bring him horrified
i have to ask this and i'm horrified to do so do they use the diapers of course they do why wouldn't
they use that if it's an adult teen baby do you think they just fucking look at them hey guys i
know i thought they put them on but do they use they shouldn't oh i have a spoiler alert for you
i'm not an adult teen baby and if i was wearing a diaper and had to use the bathroom i would not be
standing up right now i would not be moving away from the microphone i would just pee and poop
in the diaper because i already had it on i don't know why i put it on i'm continent but if i was
wearing one would you got okay no would you guys let me hey how about no let me ask you this okay
would you know hey listen i got one other question uh-huh would you
um oh man you know what the only time i could ever see myself doing it i shouldn't be saying this
the tonys you don't want to miss a second no but like what if mandy patinkin comes on stage how
about you're at times square new year's eve people actually do that do you know that when you look at
the time screen news when you look at dick clark's rocking new year's eve and you look out in that
crowd and then you think about somebody in that heat that has to do it that has to learn what
doing it has to let go they have a diaper on and they're doing it somebody told me that i was at a
party they were like yeah we were there we were in full dipe we were in full dipe we were in full
diaper galea letting it go you know you're a teen just buy a bunch of diapers and then tell your
parents that you're lazy i don't know mom and dad i want to play ever quest all the time focus on
two things and it's either homework or shitting yeah which one you want me to do listen listen
you want me to hit the books you want me to hit the body and you wanted to make your choice moms
hey mom start this diaper away for me thanks it's up to you had a traveler in the car had to uh had
to have one for the ride home i decided uh to use cloth if you could sign us up for like a service
or something but this isn't the diaper genie mom buy us a diaper genie we don't have one what is
a diaper genie a diaper genie is a is a hole that you put diapers into and then it compresses them
basically to make less room for diapies don't think about it oh man i can't
listen i'm seriously i'm gonna fucking throw up can we move on please can i ask that
i need some advice i want to know why this 16 year old is infatuated you were a baby last year
why are you so tied up in this i get it you want me that you want to be young again hi welcome to
every day your god damn life guess what you were gonna feel like that for the next god willing in
the creek don't rise like 80 years fucking don't get started on it there's gonna be plenty there
will be plenty of time to sew your creepy seats don't get started when you're when you have your
own house you can fill with diapers hey maybe it's a good sign if you're like well i can't sink this
past my parents then don't fucking do it till you can yeah yeah just wait till you're in the
privacy of your own listen i get it adult teen babies you're having the you're having the
realization that things were better when you were a kid people took care of you like yeah we all
feel that way you're not weird you're just weak be stronger resistance impulses i have impulses
every day to put on a diaper but let me tell you let me let me just give you this room i mean i'm
strong let me give you this reminder adult teen baby because you don't remember this from when
you were a baby but having your own poopy on your butt sucks that's so a trade-off with adulthood
it's sort of like a benjamin button is that when you poopy in your diaper it's going to be on your
butt you're going to hate it and let me also say this as a person a lot of my friends are having
kids and i'm kind of surrounded by babies and kids now babies are awesome and people like to
take care of them and and and baby them until they don't anymore until the kids start screaming
until it becomes a thing it's not that awesome to be a baby hey listen i need some advice
i work long hard days and when i get home i just need some time with myself i'm married and have
one son as much as i absolutely love them i just need me some me time the only way i can get away
is in the shower here's my question how can i spice up shower time once in a while i have a
shower beer oh no are there other ways to treat myself that shower guy from the southern gulf
islands and he sounds awesome he sounds like what about a full-on shower wet bar i don't know
shower wet bar i feel like i should be asking him for advice yeah why stop at a shower beer
have yourself a shower manhattan okay that's nice that's good because the actual recipe
for the manhattan is i believe uh a tablespoon of bitters and then uh sweet vermouth and then
two and a half cups of lukewarm shower water delicious and then you just drink that right up
there is a cocktail you could make with shower water i mean by definition anything's a cocktail
if you're drunk after but you you could make a cup come up with a cocktail that uses shower water
and that's like the height of luxury i mean it mixes it right you know you put on like a hard
spray and mix your cocktail that's what you call the drink the hard spray hard spray i love it
you could uh put it on the a massaging shower head on there and that's hours of fun what do
you mean you can put on your butt it feels real clean after because you spray your butt out when
did this when did this happen it happens it happens i don't remember it happening
i did you like the shower at my house uh i did yeah yeah oh no oh yes i'm an adult teen dirty boy
and that's what for wise at the end by the way yeah i mean have you considered just like
leaving your house for a bit
turn out oh my god turn up turn the shower rope ladder your fucking
so your dad has been in the bathroom for four hours i think i think dad has ocd string up
when you you climb back in you come out of the bathroom and your wife's like honey how was your
shower and why do you have a ticket so for the hobbit i need you to do this okay
question asker load up you're an inflatable clown load up balloon two fuck god damn it fuck fuck
fuck couldn't let me have it huh couldn't let me have it one thing couldn't let me have it
you just scooped it and poached that right away didn't you chop bye out of you seagulling griffin's
joke asshole listen i'll tell the boss it was both of us so you don't have to worry about it
listen uh jesse when griffin uh when jess made that joke it was griffin's griffin you have been
down on your goof quota this month well let me explain insert let me explain you said nothing
to indicate that they would be the inflatable clown i was just trying to prove to you how deep
our connection goes how strong our bond is okay cool well i'm gonna rob your house and then but
it's because we're so deeply connected leave my shower head it's the only thing i like oh you know
oh you know anything that has been in that zone hey listen thank you so much again for tuning
in to our our our show i'm really sorry about poaching griffin's joke earlier no you're not i'm
i am sorry i'm sorry um and but i'm not sorry that people are tweeting about our show like
jan villa rosa love actuary uh roger steve simmons lizzie cross mr paul 64 ambi whoa craig wilson
left walker ragged and uh everybody zanjara thank you so much to everyone who tweets with the mb
mba of hashtag if you want to get somebody started with our show there's no better place than our
sampler bit.ly forward slash it's my bim bam we desperately desperately need to update that can
we say this week get on the max fun forums and if you have like a bit preferably like a pretty
concise one that we could throw into a compilation that you like from any point in the show then uh
get on the forums and let us know because right now the sampler only covers like the first like
40 episodes or so and that was not our primo shit uh and while you're on maximum fun.org make sure
to check out all the other wonderful max fun shows uh throwing shade congratulations well they do uh
they won for best lgbt uh podcast why didn't we win that because we were mostly mean not to
everybody though it's equal but congratulations to them so make sure you check them out check out
jordan jesse go bullseye judge john honjman uh risk uh memory palace all the other ones um did
we win any not to my knowledge we won for best spirituality podcast good good good uh i want to
thank john roger and the long winters for the use of our theme song instead of departure off the
off the album putting the days to bed which sandwiches our show like two delicious delicious
you know i just listened to that album again this week god it's so fucking good yeah hey
preaching the choir hey listen if you want to uh if you want to uh check us out on facebook we have
a social presence uh if you if you go to facebook and search for mb mb am uh there there's a group
there that you can like and there's also i think it's a different actually different group the one
that is my brother my brother and me shouldn't splinter them should bring those two together
i don't know how that happened but well you got like rival we got a moses hit uh and and also i
want to tell you guys that um while i was going to facebook to check out uh uh how to how to get to
our page i did want to tell you that i discovered i'm friends with a woman who has only one like
and it is for arby's so sounds about right and also we haven't mentioned in a while but if you
uh would like to get like a personal message for somebody or for yourself i guess or a message for
your business or something like that on the show just go to maximum fun.org forward slash jumbotron
and you can get it all set up there yeah uh it's finally yahoo answer is sitting by ira ray thank
you ira it's by yahoo answers user aaron who asks what are some good songs against illuminati without
cussing i'm just mcgroy i'm travis i'm griffin mcgroy this has been my brother my brother me
kiss your dad square on the lips