The McElroy brothers are not experts and their advice should never be
followed. Oh Travis insists he's a sexpert but if there's a degree on his
wall balcony I haven't seen it. Also this show isn't for kids which I mentioned
only so the babies out there know how cool they are for listening. What's up
you cool baby!
It's better, it's better with you. My life. It's better, it's better with you. This is true. It's better, it's better with you. My life. It's better with you.
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother and me an advice show for the
modern era. I'm your oldest brother Justin Tyler McElroy. I'm your middlest
brother Travis Tyler McElroy. And I'm Xavier dark mime Xavier shadow Raven
and I'm a I am a sorcerer. You know it's Griffin say never talk about this in the
books but like 90% of being a sorcerer is just having the confidence to call
yourself a sorcerer. This is Griffin's second night wearing a tuxedo. I will
say I will say the cape is new the cape is for you Portland. Well it's not new
Griffin borrowed it from our tour manager Amanda. Our business manager
Amanda thank you and I will say that the fit is as such that it does make me look
like mr. Potter from it's a wonderful life. And it's also impressive because I
don't know how he's done this like physically the cape is on the outside
then jacket but the cape is connected to the vest underneath the jacket. Sorcerer.
Everybody looks great. I don't know I didn't see dad until right before we
came out. I do not know. He doesn't run any of that bias by management. It used
to be that dad would buy a t-shirt or something at the airport that had like
the name of the city we were on and now he's gone. I don't know yeah my favorite
part of his intro was when he suggested that he is paid for his services. I saw
dad and Travis standing next to each other backstage and it occurred to me it
looked like if there was a new Sherlock Holmes movie and you turn it on and then
five minutes in they come on the screen and you're like no I don't think so no
Did he just say his name is Maury Farty? That's not it. That's not it.
Anyway this is an advice show. We're so thrilled to be back here in Portland
Oregon. We ordered um we uh how can I how can I you know that spicy lettuce you
guys like yeah you should have we haven't consumed any yeah yeah act two
suited and zooted is no no no no don't work cowards there's no way you could
have seen us tittering like schoolchildren backstage as we legally
purchase recreational drugs it's just me and Travis like look this one's called
Obamacare that's pretty good that's hilarious I like anything that sounds
like the name of a cream song you know it's just like soda pop dreams and I'm
like yeah that's my thing I want to go to sleep ten minutes after the show's
done it's it couldn't possibly be harder to choose like I'm looking at them and
they're like this one's fucking chock full of resin and I'm like yeah yes yes
good and then I start thinking like is that too much resin for me can I handle
that level of resin it's resin like wax what's resin it's demoralizing on
purpose to keep the squares out I I purchased weed in Texas a few times
which I can say now cuz I don't live there anymore yeah good luck getting
them now Ted Cruz and I would be like um excuse me sir how much of it can I get
for this many I'd be like you gotta have I've got the newest I've got cheetah
piss it's the newest strain from the backpack boys like yes okay I love it
Justin and I were also like those friends at a restaurant where someone's
like I think I'll get some fries like well if you're gonna have fries we're
gonna was like yeah just like well if you're gonna if you're gonna let me let
me just look at the menu we're real bad boys doing this thing you all do twice a
day and we're cool we're cool dads and hopefully did it before this cuz it will
be better I guarantee and we won't we did have a brief discussion about guys
maybe this is the one where we just second act come out bombed out of our
mind listen stop you think you'd think right at least one third of us though by
which I mean me would be so paranoid and weird I would say something and you guys
would laugh and I'd be like why are you laughing what did I do this is an advice
show and we have emerged here in Portland like our friends the Chilean
miners who dug their way out of the ground with their own bare hands and
they don't talk about that enough when they tell that story they burrowed out
of the ground with their own bare hands yeah and then they saw their shadows
that went back and it was six more weeks of winter to this we're gonna help you
now are you ready to be helped we're gonna fix this town may I so many of you
I really hate it very nice um may I please unbutton the vest please yeah
let's take a vote oh wait yes
erotic erotic there we go let it breathe okay today I saw my pups breeder on an
episode of judge Judy I learned I knew that the breeder was having issues with
another breeder around dog ownership I mean I didn't think they're arguing
over the rights to the matrix assumed but I didn't know the details how can I
casually bring up that I saw the episode and would love to know more I grew up
watching judge Judy with my mom and would love to get some details about the
judge we all grew up watching just Judy with our mom that goes without saying it
seems a little insensitive to ask the episode was from last year and the
ruling was a little bit of a mixed result that's from pondering pup owner
in Portland are you here all right I love welcome the concern that it's
insensitive to talk about the private matter of them being well it sounds it
sounds like they got their ass beat no it's a mixed it's a mixed result which
is always what you want in court I am I listen I say this at 80% of my cases
both sides were in the wrong let's just come together now get out of here
daddy kids I can make sure to stop in front of the camera on your way out I
can settle one thing for you conclusively I guarantee that your dog
breeder saw judge Judy for the exact same number of seconds as you saw judge
Judy on television I guarantee judge Judy had five episodes of film that day
I guarantee Judy's not coming out beforehand like so how's everybody doing
yeah they give me all the pretzels I want come on back we can have some
pretzels I got store-brand Lacroix trailer if you guys want anything it's
not lemon lime it's just like lemon or lime but we warm into a big glass it's a
bit warm yeah you know I bet we could find some ice if you want it hey can we
get I know I sorry guys guys I'm yeah I heard just Judy does five minutes of
warm-up stand up yeah I want to show you all some paintings I made earlier
today hey tell me this look like a dog yeah I do shadow puppet stuff you guys
like that not your thing okay I'll just get up on of course the person wants to
be asked about their time on judge Judy yeah you guys know hey this will be a
very specific reference but I bet there's a few you guys know anybody
terrible in jeopardy okay do they want to talk about anything else because the
people I know they've been on jeopardy make sure you know they've been on
jeopardy yeah the idea that you would ask like hey I saw your episode of judge
you didn't they beg oh and I had can't I can't there's an you weren't there you
don't understand I signed an NDA for the thing they aired on television and also
I love this because it encouraged me hearing the thing of like how often we
get asked how to casually ask something like you beg hey so saw you won you know
like just say like I saw the episode of judge Judy you don't have to be casual
be excited yeah I don't believe judge Judy has the power of subpoena yeah I
don't think you can I don't think you can involuntarily be on judge Judy give
me five minutes with him I'll get him to talk yeah Judy methods we can't condone
this turn the cameras off I'll break you I thought this was just normal court
what's with all the cameras they put makeup on me for normal court oh no it's
her did you guys you guys know this is unrelated sort of but I accidentally
watched an episode of dr. Phil twice I accidentally watched two episodes of dr.
Phil because it wait the first one's an accident Justin no I accidentally watched
two episodes of dr. Phil because it was connected to a podcast I was listening
to at the time where that episode was referenced so I was watching that so on
purpose was it thought out the episode of dr. Phil you're a subscriber to fill
me in which is no but do you know doctor doctor give me the Phil no but do you
know that that do you know that he has an was it his own podcast podcast no no
no no he's not on the podcast but he has his own podcast and the podcast that
they were promoting in this episode is called anatomy of a murder with dr. Phil
and it's just dr. Phil like I I don't want to go this is how I did it this is
how I would have done it this is a heartbreak murders I don't think I want
that from you wait hold on so you listen to a podcast they reference an episode
of dr. Phil you watch the episode of dr. Phil and on that he promoted his
podcast and then you listen to that no I did podcasts are over do you know he
does have one called like fill in the blanks though hell yeah he does yeah he
does you wanna do another question uh-huh okay I've recently started
tucking in my shirt I'm in my 30s so I guess I've never thought about it before
but do you think when we start reading these questions at live shows someone in
the audience goes start talking in my shirt that's me I'm the shirt Tucker I
love when they dub over Samuel Jackson when he's like you sure
thanks get these shirts off this mother tucking plane I recently started tucking
in my shirt I'm in my 30s so I guess it was just time yes however I work in
construction and all the bending down and moving around pulls my shirt out of
my pants constantly you doing backflips in order to retuck my shirt I have to
loosen my belt and stick my hands down my pants yeah which is a weird look when
people catch me with my pants undone while I'm working on their kitchen
countertops or whatever oh cuz it's like you're enjoying your genitals you could
have found a more tasteful place to fix yourself to get yourself you step over
into a corner you face the corner and you do your business and hope no one
sees but if they do they'll think at least he's politely masturbating is
there anything I can say to people when I'm elbow deep in my car hearts not that
though well I was elbow deep in my car hearts on a Friday night looking for
loving my car hearts on the banks of the Chattahoochee in the back of my truck
bed with my hands in my car hearts but they weren't the only hands if you know
what I mean yes ghost hands like in Ghostbusters one you guys ever seen that
it's weird am I right how could they make a new Ghostbusters and not have
Slimer in it come on guys Slimer doesn't get anybody off
are you ready for some football it'd be cool if that ghost kept calling him
through the whole movie like hey I just never heard from you and that's where
the term ghosted comes from yeah so that deserved better no it did guys crushed it
is there anything I could say to people when I'm elbow deep in my car hearts to
justify or gloss over the situation just saying I'm tucking in my shirt
feels a little if your voice breaks I'm almost finished I'm 41 years old I don't
know I'm Greg Brady in every okay just saying I'm tucking in my shirt feels a
little he doth protest too much that's from tucking troubles into Portland and
it says here alliteration is not my strong suit are neither it seems is
discretion what are you are you here God bless you I got it you ready for
this yeah you're gonna need to sew your shirt into your underpants excellent
that's really good so your shirt to your underpants and make a velcro front so
you can just rip it up there you go and then every time you reach up to install
a countertop hinge or whatever you'd be like I'm ripping myself at half no
surprise hugs that is as far as I can hug right now suits are not made for a
hugging this is why business dads are so distant the dad in Mary Poppins was a
great dad mr. Banks can't physically hug his children so he makes up all these
excuses that he has to hire someone in petticoats to hug his children that's
how restrictive his tuxedo is he's sewn into it sewn into it every morning did I
mean a bet belt a belt doesn't hold the shirt and holds the pants up now it just
gets in your way when you need to fix it maybe what about like an elastic belt
where there's some tension there great okay that and then what about longer
shirt what about really really really long shirt oh yeah Scrooge that shit
yeah Scrooge it up and then at night with sleepy time you light your candle
you have a bit of potato soup loving it you learn a lot about love put on your
tassel cap and slip on off to dreamland it'd be beautiful I have great news for
you anytime anyone has ever been in my home to do any work whatsoever impressing
them is my number one priority I I've actually not letting them know how
ignorant I am of what they're doing and making them I can't think of another
word other than proud of me yeah I've been meaning to ask you both do you do
this thing when someone comes into your house to fix something do you ratchet up
your West Virginia accent yeah I do say like yeah man I don't know I don't know
what's happening yeah I also checked that yeah to build on Justin's point I
think the answer is whenever you are caught adjusting yourself and if they
have the audacity to say something along the lines of like what are you doing
just look back at them and be like this is part of it do you do you want these
countertops installed or do you want to hinges on these counters or not how are
you gonna get to the sink if I don't put hinges on these counters when is a good
time to tell this girl I've been talking to that I've released an acapella album
what's the right time track for don't get oh you're liking this I'm enjoying
this a well surprise check this out oh that's right
you made an acapella track but you just did the backing yeah I couldn't find
anybody else to sing with me but you get like how the rest of it would go I do
all the what don't get me wrong I love when that member of Rockapella went on a
solo career don't get me wrong acapella is pretty cool thus the album yeah but
telling someone about it nah nah nah that's more abrasive than selling your
saying you're a SoundCloud rapping career when if at all should I tell her
that's from Connor are you should are you here Connor all right
that's perfect what was that like a bee for sure you
definitely should at some point yeah oh man it'll come out at Connor Connor
Connor Connor Connor be honest is it good hell yeah yeah says Connor I actually
I actually have a little bit of life experience with this many years ago we
were in Portland here and we got high on drugs and decide we're gonna get into
trolls too in part of the recording of that podcast we would frequently feature
our toughest nails means mean mean guy in a different time period gangster yeah
he's like a really mean guy and his name is Joel Begleiter and he's our agent
you know he's not mean he's just a tough guy and we found this just tougher than
us and he's got he did he was in an acapella group in college called the
Brown Derby's right and we found down Easter Alexa by the Brown Derby's if you
could find that on Spotify in which he was the lead soloist he was the lead
soloist and we were so jazzed to find this because we were like we fucking got
a crack in the armor we finally got a crack in Joel's armor and then we were
like Joel guess what dog we got you and he was like did you listen to it we're
like yeah and he was like it's pretty good right we're like yeah it's like
yeah so it's pretty cool that I did that I guess we were a great group and I was
like yeah I guess it was pretty yeah Joel you got us and that's you wait you
got to listen listen here Joel's gonna sue us now right so good it's
infuriatingly good does everyone shut up
thank you Paul thank you God it's good I think if you lay down some sick shit
like that yeah play it next time she gets in the car I think you do have to
play it first because if someone told me I made an acapella album and now I'm
gonna play it for you oh boy I would need a fucking Texas Instruments
graphing calculator to figure out my facial expression I could not no way no
how could I have the right face for listening to that but if you're already
listening to it you're like this is good yeah I like this Connor here's my advice
you're gonna walk into this backwards you're going to be like whatever the
conversation is if it's about like you know projects you've worked on hobbies
you've had whatever you can say like well yeah I one time you know I put
together an acapella album and they're like you did and I get pretty good they
are inevitably going to ask to listen to it and you're like I mean I guess we
could which at that point it's great but if you went into it saying I'm going to
play this but you can't do that no no the next few seconds between that
announcement until you press the play button are going to be the worst seconds
of their life and here's the thing trust me from experience please don't try to
stream it because I guarantee oh god it will play two seconds and just wait
hold on it's just buffering hold on one second oh no I think oh there's some
gonna hold on wait the Bluetooth isn't it it's only coming through the left so
you're only getting hold on let me go get my big speakers hold on I swear I
charge this beforehand Paul was oh Paul wanted us to mention that he used to be
in an acapella group called da Vinci's notebook if you've never heard their
shoehorn with well they're selling it they just don't get together anymore you
don't leave an acapella band you've probably heard them because you
downloaded a line wire or Kazaa version of shoehorn with teeth that said it was
by moxie fruvis and it turned out it was actually by Paul yeah so that's where
what a pleasant surprise yeah what a treat for you another question
we got a haunted doll watch okay okay no sorry
ironically I was watching Ghostbusters afterlife backstage let me just move
over to crowns Travis watches movies so that he can tell you how he doesn't like
them yeah a lot guys I've heard Travis Travis has been watching Ghostbusters
afterlife for four days and I have I have ADHD yeah I've heard four
different reviews of the film based on how much he has watched yeah so he's
like so I watched the first 20 minutes of this movie and it's like let me tell
you what I think and then he has done that to me three other times like so
I'm 75 minutes in and here's where I'm at yeah I didn't want to hear about it
at all my experience changes as the movie goes on boy you are seriously
looking like something on your phone yeah it's got me really worried no don't
worry about it don't worry about it okay so I this is my version upon a doll and
whenever I do a bit I like to gamify it so I like to call this the doll is right
okay okay so here's what's gonna happen I will describe the dog and you'll see
the pictures and then you guys are gonna guess the price of the dog good Paul
please bring up the first doll spirit of sky
Hanukkah spirit of sky giggles laughter loving can we get any more information
yes we can welcome may I present sky she is the fairy spirit she is quite
charming she can be silly funny then very serious she surprises me all the
time she will give you vivid dreams always come to me during meditation whoa
the scale is so different from what I thought it was the first couple looked
like a doll and now it's on some firm gully shit and is very responsive to
any way you would like to communicate I don't need that she can be very
mischievous and likes to be spoiled her favorite thing is to hide small items no
worries I have always been able to find whatever she is hidden because she
didn't hide them because she's a doll yeah I will send a candle herbs from my
garden and a stone for you to welcome her into your home the doll vessel is in
a sitting position with her swing about myself I've been doing 20 years and
then there's a whole nother paragraph but it does continue is my favorite line
my mentor was my late great-aunt Maude some say she was a witch I believe she
was ahead of her time she preferred to say healer she did not like to conform
to words a lot of images of this end of description so I'll start with Griffin
on this one Griffin I feel by the way like I'm going to get it to the penny
okay how much driven 1399 Justin 39 99 Paul reveal 99 cents whoa that's a
starting bid that's different from the shipping is 814 well there's a stone in
the box what do you want the guy weighs 11 pounds guys it's tour manager Paul
just to let you know I'm following this along live right now in the time this
has been up on the screen the bidding price has gone up to $66 somebody make
that 69 bid real quick come on okay ball next doll active what that's not the
name haunted demonic doll active found while digging paranormal scary creepy
the blue sensor bar is so fucking long
I've never had people this close and being able to see people recoil in
terror from the dolls is really something else I purchased and rehome
haunted dolls and items from all over the world the paranormal covering my
wiener with a cross the paranormal has been part of our lives forever wait a
minute they they took a picture of themselves breaking ground like I bet
there's a fucking scary doll under here my dowsing rods are going wild this time
we brought our metal detector and struck gold how creepy is this wow
amazing the doll is sold by itself oh my god it's wrapped in plastic we can clean
it up for you or just leave it as is you fucking freak you'll never see my wiener
I died on Ash Wednesday all right this is on price Justin we'll begin with you
wow okay I'm gonna I'm gonna hit you with this $80 okay Griffin a hundred
and thirty one dollars reveal 217 American dollars you all rack that one
up yeah probably not huh that one's probably going unsold tonight next the
doll oh my god show the picture ball this is a simple description for this
one Todd is a beautiful artist made doll he is 19 is long and does great with an
SLS camera and outings on paranormal investigations he is one-of-a-kind I'll
say okay Griffin your guess I'm going to say I'm gonna say a hundred and seventy
dollars Justin I mean to a Jim Gaffigan collector this would be huge but you're
gonna have to find the right audience for it to a common person this might not
stoke their interest but it you know it's everything's worth what we're
willing to pay for it so what's the number just the number for me is gonna
be $39.99 the buy it now price is $295 I love how it says condition used you
tell me this isn't fresh off the shelves at American girl extra doll we have two
more oh my god Travis oh I like him this is fun this is haunted paranormal a
handmade four and a half inch thread doll three oh ill intent excuse me ill
intent please read we purchased this aggressive man at online auction from
Wyoming have you seen this aggressive man it was listed as a handmade talisman
used for ill intent and misfortune that's a shame rude please note some
have questioned a spirit not interacting with them in items they have purchased
from other sellers spirits have their own personalities sometimes it does take
them a day or two or even longer to adjust their new surroundings they don't
do parlor tricks and if they choose to hold off on interaction thing it is
their right to do so 0.2 doesn't seem especially haunted but that but it is
red I guess that is red let's you know it's pretty haunted Justin your guess
I'm gonna say travel on this one $39.99 Justin or Griffin I said 39 I'm going to
say $39.98 reveal yeah 13 bucks 13 bucks I mean to be fair it does say it's bad
they said this is made for bad reasons not a nice doll one more handy haunted
raggedy-andy doll active paranormal demonic voodoo ritual spirit just looks
like a raggedy-andy doll oh I want you guys to keep in mind there are two
prices here the bid price and the buy it now okay which one is higher the buy it
now price okay yeah it would be weird if they were like starting bid is higher
than if you just want to buy it away but okay um dark energy attached keep it
away from kids bring into your house with caution ebay wants description
sure why that ebay wants description short when it comes to paranormal or
supernatural any questions please message or discover your answers by
buying item and asking vessel yourself then one of the most poetic lines I've
ever read not everyone has a connection to the spirit world and that is okay
what salsa is hot for some may be mild for others that is not relevant to the
topic at hand Justin let's start with the starting bid price my starting bid
on this one is gonna be 39 I'm gonna say I'm gonna say one ninety nine ninety
nine okay and then Griffin yeah the buy it now price I'm going to say $1,000
okay Justin two hundred and twenty dollars Paul reveal Griffin once again
say your two bids please one ninety nine ninety nine and the buy it now price is
$1,000
for Macaroy for those of you at home the starting bid was $200 the buy it now was
$1,000 we're gonna be back for at two in a second have a great intermission we
can't stop that
hi everybody Travis here Griffin is still moving but it's going well he
should have his internet all set up soon and then we'll be able to get back to
recording episodes but in the meantime we sure hope you are enjoying these live
shows and we hope you are well in all things but right now I want to tell you
about stamps calm having to drop what you're doing to make a run to the post
office is a major pain not like the movie major pain that's a different
thing that's probably too dated right do people still talk about major pain I
don't know maybe maybe it's time for a major pain comeback doesn't matter
stamps calm is your 24 7 post office that you can access from anywhere whether
you're an office sending invoices an Etsy shop sending your products or a
warehouse shipping out orders stamps calm makes mailing and shipping a breeze
all you need is your regular computer and printer no special supplies or
equipment and you get discounts you can't find these discounts anywhere else
like up to 30% off USPS rates and 86% off UPS that's like almost the whole
thing if we were rounding up right that's almost the whole thing that's
incredible so don't mail and ship the hard way sign up with stamps calm today
sign up with promo code my brother all one word for a special offer that
includes a four-week trial plus free postage and a digital scale no long-term
commitments or contracts just go to stamps calm click the microphone at the
top of the page and enter code my brother I also want to tell you about
Bombas wearing Bombas right now I'm wearing three different articles of
Bombas right now bombas mission is simple make the most comfortable clothes
ever and match every item sold with an equal item donated so when you buy
Bombas you are also giving to someone in need
bombas designs their socks shirts and underwear to be the clothes you can't
wait to put on every day this is true everything they make is soft seamless
tagless and has a cozy feel also true Bombas no-show socks are designed for
comfort while being especially engineered to never fall down so let
your ankles be free to soak up the sunlight my friend prove that your
ankles aren't vampires let them soak in the Sun go to bombas.com slash my
brother and get 20% off your first purchase that's BOMBAS.com slash my
brother for 20% off your first purchase bombas.com slash my brother and just a
few announcements before we get back to the episode first of all if you haven't
gone to check out this month's merch you are missing out we've got a Garo plushy
that is so cute I'm gonna say the talk of the town it's the talk of the town
and we've got our if God's not dead how do you explain these gain shirt designed
by Lucas has been hide who is at mostly based on Twitter 10% of all merch
proceeds this month will go to the Center for reproductive rights the
Center for reproductive rights uses the power of law to advance reproductive
rights as fundamental human rights around the world you can find all of
that at McElroy merch calm also we have an ad survey running right now through
the end of the month it's our annual survey that helps us try to make sure
our advertisers are well matched with our audience if you go to maximum fun
org slash survey you can find it there it really helps us out thank you so much
the pre-orders for Taz 11th hour open now that's gonna come out in February
of 2023 you can go to the adventure zone comic comm to pre-order and we still
have a couple shows in the 20 rendezvous fancy takes flight tour you can find all
of those shows and buy the tickets and everything at bitch dot L Y slash
McElroy tours the November shows are in Washington DC Detroit and Cincinnati
mask and proof of full vaccination or negative kovat tests within 72 hours of
event start is required thank you so much and now back to the show
hey it's John Moe host of depression mode a podcast about people's mental
health journeys guess who we got guess who it's Jamie Lee Curtis I look at
life now as the game of guess who which is simply the process of elimination I
know what I don't like that's how I found out who I am
Jamie Lee Curtis on addiction show business and fooling people all on
depression mode from maximum fun wherever you get your podcasts
well Manolo we have a show to promote it's called after game show it's a
family-friendly podcast where listeners submit games and we play them with
callers from around the world no sounds good new episodes happen every other
Wednesday on maximum fun org it's a it's a fast and loose oasis of absurd
innocence and naivete and you're writing a poem no and just saying things from my
memory and it's a nice break from reality is that are we allowed to say
that I don't know it sounds bad it comes with a 100% happiness guarantee it does
not come for the games and stay for the chaos
I want to munch want to munch that's the hardest poles ever worked out amazing
good job Paul welcome to much squad it's a podcast within a podcast profiling the
latest and greatest in brand eating and today we got the meats because we're
talking about Arby's baby Arby's heads in the house some Arby's heads in the
house I don't can blame you this is legitimately the why I mean I don't want
to hype it up too much but this is the wildest thing I've ever seen all right
are you ready I don't know okay old spice wait and Arby's team up for high
stakes collaboration I don't want it to smell like Arby's or taste like old
spice well good news neither those is happening
whoa because to get oh man it's a collaboration to conquer the meat sweats
with a limited edition meat sweat defense kit drop oh my god oh shit oh
wait it actually says meat sweat defense on it old spice and Arby's have joined
forces to tackle the meat sweats Arby's is really taking a beating in this brand
right like this had to be old spices idea right for sure we're thinking is
like you know how your gross people eat your gross food we'll fix it remember
how your food so busted it makes people a sweaty pile of mess yeah we'll put a
sweaty sandwich with a sweaty pack of sweaty sauce on the bottom you want to
fix our stink dogs yes please no longer with the long-lasting sweat
protection of old spice sweat defense dry spray no longer will you live in
fear of that treacherous moment halfway through a delicious Arby's half pound
roast beef sandwich when the dreaded meat sweats strike with a vengeance okay
what the okay fuck live in fear hey you know what I was thinking we could have
always French no no not again not after what happened
Dylan's baptism is it for this our foods delicious but halfway through it you
might get so yucked that it makes you sweaty from it and the people around you
want to barf the Arby's they just ate and listen I know you person reading
this you're the worst it's ever been to defeat it it's gotta be right it can't
be this bad for everyone can it no just you to defeat it once and for all you
know you need the later to close off your pores we're gonna cauterize your
pores the limited edition meat sweat defense kit now available at Arby's shop
calm don't waste your time I bought them all the key's gonna you're gonna come
home from tourism and be like you smell like not beef what'd you do first time
in forever you've been opening my mail the key defense against the meat sweats
is drumroll please anti-meat the old spice defense dry spray with its 24-7
sweat and odor protection hey I don't want to quibble but if I have the meat
sweats I sure the fuck hope I don't need 24-7 it actually I'm looking at maybe
just a nice cool 30 minutes right like both the stick and the spray say 48
hour sandwiches fuck you up no Griffin breakfast breakfast lunch and
dinner my dude yeah yes the half pounder with roast beef sandwich which I have to
say is not depicted in that image there's no way that is not a real roast
beef it might be a big Montana or something but it's not anyway each meat
sweats defense kit is equipped with two dry sprays in popular sense that protect
guys and let's be honest it's just guys with this product protect guys from the
meat sweating potential of the half pound roast beef sandwich they are they
are naming names this specific sandwich is notorious for meat sweats that's not
all notorious notorious that's not all alongside the dry spray will be a
one-of-a-kind viral worthy roast beef pattern meat sweats sweatshirt and sweat
pant with a white with a co-branded towel and headband Paul Seborin let's
see it baby no no no no for those who can't get their hands on the limited
edition kits Old Spice and Arby's legendary commercial creative minds came
together to create an iconic new advertising spot featuring the old
why does it define defense on the box it has the definition of defense Paul if
you can find that that Old Spice guy Arby's commercial that was directed by
rug rug rats no Riggs Howard and produced by Whedon
Kennedy and Fallon fans everywhere will be able to check it out on YouTube
Facebook Instagram and tik-tok quote a collaboration between Old Spice and
Arby's makes all the sense in the world oh you can say whatever the fuck you
want it doesn't make it true oh I thought it I thought it was saying makes
all the sense in the world I'm on beef good smell this is the spectrum it makes
all the sense in the world the hell what's that sorry Arby's just hired you
Griffin yeah something something smells like a like lavender on a hot dog yes it
makes all the sense in the world to hilariously solve the age-old problem of
the notorious meat so they also define sweat listen it's very you imagine
buying this kit and not knowing what meat sweats is I'm just a big old twice
head I'm really glad there's a clock on the stage right now because I feel like
I've been thinking about Arby's for about an hour and a half okay it makes
all the sense of the world to hilariously solve the age-old problem of
the notorious meat sweats that we've all faced at some point in our lives yeah we
all remember the first time we faced meat sweats in our life that's from all
sweat is meat sweat if you think about it oh my god that's deep grip old spice
continues to find unique ways to surprise and delight fans with signature
humor and unexpected partnerships that remind them of the importance of
long-lasting protection even if they've just eaten a half pound roast beef do
you think at some point the roast beef say the half pound roast beef sandwich
is like okay I love all those for sure this is all so funny if we can pick
other sandwiches the highlight that also provide the meat sweats that would be so
choice for me like if you say all of our products then it just sounds you're
having a bit of fun this sounds accusatory targeted at me a sandwich the
mountainous half pound roast beef sandwich isn't the only place the old
spice has been lately what beef tastic brouhaha began this past week when the
old spice guy made his presence known on the streets of New York handing out sweat
defense dry sprays Arby's gift cards and these meat sweat defense kits it's like
if someone handed you an antidote and then was like and also here is poison
decked out in an old spice and Arby's SUV which I assume will be in my
driveway at some point through hooker through crook the old spice guy even
ended up in the meatpacking district to tell them that Arby's has the meats and
they said no you don't actually we know we pack them here and send it to you
you have some of the meats what you can't claim all the meats whether you
are eating a meat mountain or a half pound roast beef sandwich or just a
nasty boy Arby's is thrilled that our guests have access to this innovative
solution that helps them fully enjoy the meats while avoiding the sweats we are
big fans of old spice products and creativity and it was a no-brainer to
have a little fun with them on this program if I'm Jim Taylor Arby's
president if I'm gonna be so bold maybe next time let's try at least a half
brainer or at least a three-quarter brainer you can buy a meat sweat defense
kit at Arby shop.com slash meat hyphen sweat hyphen defense hyphen kit for $60
they're all gone I don't know why I read that and you could get one of these kids
maybe check the bay cuz they aren't on our BZ more so check eBay and maybe
they're there anyway that's the meat sweat defense get that was a journey can
you imagine a brand like deep like absolutely annihilating themselves to
that extent what would it would be like McDonald's started selling you a
co-branded partnership with empty that lets you capture all your farts in a bag
all your everyone knows about McDonald's farts and now you can put them in a bag
every quote from Arby's in that article did sound like it was written at gunpoint
so maybe okay credible hey we we have some questions from you all that we have
chosen to address we will we will call you down the microphone is right here
center stage behind these two people don't mind backup if you need help
hello hello hi who are you I'm Nathan hi I just started a new job teaching
hackers yeah yeah I teach an online Academy for hackers and I don't know
what the appropriate dress attire is oh thank you Nathan thank you Nathan for
this gift thank you you're teaching an online hacker class dangerous yeah is
that if they show up and had to pay tuition are you like you already fucking
yeah the end of the class and present my social security number I mean first
obvious question if I'm gonna play an outfit for you white hat or black hat
officially dark web black hat hacker class let's say white cuz I've been
wearing a wire this whole got you Nathan well first of all I assume you're
already like hot gluing glow sticks like to your jacket that's important
function yeah bandolier oh yeah absolutely what I'm realizing now is a
lot of my references are from the movie hackers and the TV show reboot yeah and
that one episode of Ghost Rider yeah what do you normally wear well I own a
lot of shirts that are themed after breweries okay yeah if I yeah I could
see that on a hacker I say this to your fucking face okay here's you need to get
a t-shirt that says typing noise typing noise typing noise I'm in that's good
can you wear like part of a keyboard on your chest and just occasionally be like
just when they're not really paying attention that could be cool I could
probably get away with it yeah maybe a power glove oh shit and you're like
here you're not making any progress to the ice give me a second do you have and
I hope you realize now this is gonna be the whole bit do you have or know
someone who can get you access to a katana is that I know lots of people he
wears brewery t-shirts and teaches hacking classes any other you have to go
to the dark web for those yeah okay what are their other hacker teachers
teachers yes it's a code anyway I imagine it runs the gamut yes well the
other teacher is like 55 so like okay I don't know what they're bringing okay
Nathan you ready for this when someone whoever performs like the worst on a
test or whatever the next day wear a t-shirt with all their information
printed oh my god
said co-teacher actually did hand out his credit card information yesterday as
a dare okay not a great dare get a shirt with your social security number on it
that would be so cool what an amazing just have it say good luck find me yeah
oh what's that I'm broke oh man does that help that helps hold on I'm not
done oh thanks Obamacare you have it just be like a word jumble that says the
word internet and the first student that gets it right be like that's an A-plus
right there everybody else fails you sold my jumble you made me stop for that
does that help Nathan just walk away I can't be responsible for him less so now
but yes we actually anti hello hi my name is Zaza hi Zaza I was the one with
the Shrek and Godfather yeah you did let's hear it so it is my partner's
sense of pride that he has never watched the movie Shrek and it is my point of
pride that I have never watched the movie the Godfather why don't you all
want to watch good movies sorry sorry Travis let's just say exactly well why
doesn't he want to watch Shrek Shrek is a good movie it's a good yeah sure yeah
basically the same as Godfather they're both good movies so you're saying you want to do
like a movie swap except you don't have to watch the Godfather in the exchange
okay yeah yeah no usually if someone says as a point of pride it's like I've
never sharted or something I do like as a point of pride I refuse to watch like
a film that now everyone's trying to emulate in cartoons or film that
everyone's trying hey you know it's fucked up I bet you there's I bet you
everyone on earth has either seen Shrek or the Godfather yeah I bet you there's
not okay obviously quick poll and be serious no everybody hands up no no
okay okay everybody put your hands up okay no no sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry no not in the cool way yeah no one hand up one hand up now drop your
hand if you have seen the God and don't fucking lie if you've never seen the
thought wait no if you have seen the Godfather put your hand down if you've
seen whoa okay if you've seen the movie Shrek yeah put your hand down there's
like there's like four four four soon-to-be best friends
oh it's a taunting the last person to watch either or the Godfather or die
it's all about it hey listen here's what you do you fuck you'd send him
tick-tocks from the movie Shrek until you've sent him every scene the yeah
legally if he's seen 51% of Shrek he sees Shrek right I get up if I go to
the bathroom during a movie I still say I've seen the movie I got up three times
during top gun maverick cuz I was bored it's not whoa it's not it's not the
movie it's me I sat down ten minutes and like oh that's my fault I went and saw
anyway if you say no no Justin please continue on with your full review of top
gun maverick you send him enough tick-tocks to where he's seen 50.0001
percentage but don't spoil the ending oh that's right the twist then he's seen
it was donkey the whole time neither of us have tick-tock what oh okay you
should have warned me about that what is there other places with videos YouTube I
guess you could send him YouTube videos of Shrek until he's probably seen over
half oh you could take notice starting find find check on YouTube and started
with like you got to watch this hilarious video you could you probably
would only need to clear 47 minutes or so if you need that grift go on for 40
you could take Nathan's hacker class and then just drop clips of it in okay does
that does that yeah just every time your partner tries to call their mom it's
right are you do you are you serious about getting out of this because I have
a 100% foolproof way oh yeah watch the godfather part 2 are you serious oh the
part 2 where's the direct watch part 2 and then tell him hey I watch the
godfather part 2 I didn't really get it I guess I don't really they'll be so
furious but they will drop the entire enterprise I guarantee you can also do
this like start godfather I'm like oh no actually I think I have seen that it's
like with the whole mafia thing yeah yeah he's that reference a leave the
canola oh leave the cannoli leave the cannoli you we just did a murder leave
the cannoli right there why would he leave the murder weapon
yeah so which one is he leaving he leaves the murder weapon he leaves the
murder weapon at the scene of the crime yeah cuz what's he gonna do leave
cannoli no I'm going somewhere else and I don't think I've seen godfather listen
here's what you do you watch five minutes of Shrek five minutes of
godfather five minutes of Shrek five minutes of godfather this is how it's
one movie it's one movie you're watching it on two screens can you watch him at
the same time yes get like a no one TV 50% opacity god
channel Shrek right channel got a dual screen moment okay yes no one
I'm starting to feel like this is our greatest live show ever all right I
want Amanda just said no thank you man okay hello hi we're a podcast what's
your deal um so I'm Kate I sent in the question okay I'm Kate hands in the
audience I send in the question about rabbit okay so I and also let this be a
lesson to you if you ever come to another live show you know like I think
my question will get answered this is the new baron like this is the okay no
pressure Kate oh yeah for sure um so I volunteer at a 4-h county fair every
year I'm the rabbit superintendent and and this year I got to attend and as the
rabbit judge and you were the super attendant and
the problem is is that today was the breed class and I had to judge all these
today yeah so I had to pose them all and you have to go through every animal in
the barn and there was a problem that arose because when you're handling all
of the female rabbits and all of the male rabbits the male rabbits smell the
female rabbit and they start sort of just going to town on your hands arms
body and you hey you've showered since then right yes very very very much I mean
I don't have dirt all over me so you can also tell from that so sorry that you
had to say that actually from now on if you're at if you're at one of our live
shows I would like everyone to just mention I don't have dirt all over me
anyway it's an audio medium if you're listening to this later I do not have
turtle so what I mean the rabbits are getting down is it the problem yeah so
they do completion if I remember they go into completion yes multiple times
throughout the show wait multiple times per rabbit okay it's what rabbits are
known for is how many jizzes they like carrots they like carrots they give me
eggs on Easter there's a lot of clarifying so a lot of other things I
know about rabbit rabbits other than they like to jizz a bunch yeah so
basically I mean there's a whole show circuit and there's like people who do
like judging and stuff I thought you're about to say there's people who walk
them off he can't he can't show right now no one's whacked him off yeah give
me a second hey okay I'm sorry to ask this question I have to know yeah
deeded duck points will that happens or do you add bonus I did I did give all
the rabbits that finished I did end up giving them all blue ribbons I didn't
it's how it worked I didn't deduct points they were all good rabbits what
can I say I hope you were locking this in your memories and amber because no
one will hear it again oh god okay okay so my big question of course I thought
yeah how do I stop the rabbits from jizzing on me yeah for sure for sure
but hold on is there a is there is there a how high does the bunny hop contest
that's not not as a part of this no that's it that's that 4h after hours
that's where the bedding began alley what are the can you give me one of the
other criteria that they are judged by it's like a dog breed show so like you
know the good the shape the density okay how do I how dense is the like you like
a you like a thick boy it just you know the body okay not yeah the rabbit the
rabbit if there was a people by the way if you're listening this later there
are people close to us who have physically turned their bodies yeah they
are recoiling they're no longer oriented towards us performing they're oriented
away from us to other directions that's good I love that if there was a how high
can the bunny hop contest do you think there would be a judge stopping the
bunnies from hopping so high and saying don't hop so high bunnies well of course
not this is a sorry y'all invented what is essentially a jizzing contest you
cannot we have to stop talking about rabbit jizz now hey hey next time judge
the boy bunnies first does that help hey does that help though sure yeah okay
thanks everyone big hand for Kate hello hello I'm Owen hi Owen how are you oh
all right um I sent in a question about getting permabanned yeah yeah all right
from the 4-h rabbit show I guess chanting is not oh and how did you get
first what's the name of the bar it's space room it's over on Hawthorne well
hold your horses yeah hold on a second you don't know this tale of what oh and
what happened my birthday was Wednesday and so so I went out and drank with some
of my friends cool ended up at the space room end of the night comes around last
call happens my friend Charlie decides to whip his pants down in the middle of
the bar wait no it's not as bad as you think gone super bad and I end up
getting super fucking and oh and you have to finish with like they mooned you
not just whip their pants down yeah there's two sides okay dumbed it out on
like in front of our table pressed ham mooning okay no this is this is very
jumpy now could also I'm just saying this is like a tasteful mooning this is
not the first time he's done this okay yeah this happens in a lot of bars no
he's okay cuz I'm gonna say some mean stuff about wait but that got you
perma-banned the target not perma-banned not you I'm perma-banned
this is what I'm saying that's messed up that's not fair you didn't do anything
I don't hold on did you did you did you laugh though oh of course I did now I
also think the context that it was last call actually should provide some
leniency because that happens at 930 p.m. right that's a perfect 230 in the
morning like yeah we love it I mean did this bar did this bar serve Charlie yes
you could make the argument then that they are culpable right like you gave
this person so much boost that they're mooning people you got a kind of you
provided windows right I how do you get perma-banned have you tried to just walk
back yeah all of the bartenders know me I used to live like two blocks no it's
the not fun apparently they don't know you well enough to know you're not a
butt weirdo your friend have you tried wearing a mask that says like not about
weirdo it's important it's a mask for some reason otherwise it's just written
on your face Griffin you could you could bring a tray of my mom's world-famous
chest bars oh that's gonna get that would be nice bring a nice baked good in
and then you're like I'm sorry about all that no what are you gonna write on the
card sorry my friend showed me his butt and you kicked me out of here forever
that's fair if that was a stranger who mooned you that they're not gonna kick
you out so it's a friend I was just joking about
just Judy I'm starting to think it's the yeah I think it might be the
appropriate venue she would love to get her hands on this one yeah all right so
let me get this straight hold on let me put down my pretzels let me get this
straight so you're telling me this isn't a custody battle they didn't like paint
your car weird thank you Christ
I don't know why our judge Judy sound like so we're so shitty sounding like
judge Judy Owen do you like the bar I do okay sounds like a cool bar the way
everybody cheered at it wait a minute there are definitely worse things that
have happened there too can this be one of these times where we abuse our power
as tastemakers and so if you go into this bar just be like you should really
let Owen back in it was not Owen's fault that Owen got mooned tonight
I'm just saying not tonight cuz I don't want to be associated I want to be in
San Diego California when you lead a Les Miserables style revolution down the
streets of Portland do you hear the people moon singing the songs of angry
men oh and does that help yeah all right
hey right off the bat I want to say thank you to Tyler Reed for the
beautiful poster yes thank you to the incredible Rachel Jacobs for making the
trip all the way out here to record us thank you Rachel is covering her mouth
in a I might throw up kind of way thank you to Emily and Michael RASL
interpreter wait hold on sorry what does that sign I love it
what's that's applause trap applause yeah thanks to Paul Saborin thanks to
our dad our dad bill from True Blood
thank you to Amanda for managing our business and cleaning the microphone and
letting me borrow this a great cape
hey you know what thank you to Montaigne yes my life is better with you and
Griffin real quick and thanks to the Arlene Schnitzer concert hall real quick
Griffin we always close with a celebrity impression I would just love
to hear your impression of a rat jizzing one rat wait hold on you a rabbit that
was my favorite part of ratatouille I miss what is this a mushroom a rabbit
no hold on more of that no no I want to hear rabbit let's hear a rabbit jizz do
I what's up Travis don't help him
the show doesn't end until you make a rabbit just come on Griffin one noise
baby come on bring it home for him okay shh quiet silence son Griffin in the
show oh yeah Justin McElroy drama Zachary McElroy my brother my brother
brother me kiss your dad's where are the lips it's better it's better it's
true maximum fun org comedy and culture artist-owned audience supported