The McElroy brothers are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there
will know how cool they are for listening. What's up, you cool baby?
Hello everybody and welcome to my brother my brother me an advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy. I'm your middlest brother Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother 30 under 30 media luminary Griffin McElroy.
I got a soundboard yeah so that's gonna be a new thing that the ruins or maybe
finalizes the sort of concept of this show okay you know people have said what what i wish
i wish that my brother my brother and me was more like an early 2000s like morning drive
to a radio show and we have the pest in there too now oh that's a lot of the pest i would love
i would actually prefer these to be like short sort of uh yelps or barks and not extended clips
of the past not the entirety of not the entirety of that you don't have a button map to the entirety
of the pest i'm hoping okay okay so you do have a button map to the entirety of yeah that's the
entirety of the pest just for that and what did you when you knew a newer program by the way
special thanks to roman marsden and i'm pretending visible for sabotaging our show by showing justin
how to do this um i'm assuming that's where you gleaned this particular yeah yeah when you were
programming in your board and you put in the entirety of the pest intro the hit john leguizamo
feature film um what did you think the use case for that was going to be like what did you think
was going to be the time of the show like if we started talking about it and i could just like
start playing it but then wow that's remember to stop playing it isn't it justin an order boris
yeah where it's like you started playing it so that we would talk about the enter and then
you're like oh the intro you mean this so it's kind of like a john leguizamo causal loop is what
you've established now i did put inspired by you last night griffin i did put something on here
that i kind of thought you would oh please talk about please i thought you would talk about it
what okay do you want the intro or no intro just hit no no intro i put my hand inside a toilet
oh thank you justin what
yeah you you heard it maybe one more i put my hand inside a toilet oh it's so good what is this
i mean this show is going to be please just explain i'm going to stop it now explain to
travis what he's just heard i mean i don't think it's the kind of thing that plays just by hearing
it but it made me personally very happy there's a company called brainpower media that makes a
bunch of really great films as far as i can tell including best friend from heaven in which chris
christopherson voices a dog who dies but then comes back from the dead to help his owners plan
a wedding um and then there's a movie called a witch's ball in which a man gets on stage and
sings a beautiful song about how he put his hand inside a toilet and so all of that is yeah like
that like that what does it sound like because i was talking over i put my hand inside a toilet
yes so that's the song i put me okay and then stop it because it's so loud it's very loud
and uh this show's not going to be a thing people can consume for entertainment anymore
i think maybe like it's becoming more avant-garde in a way which maybe more experimental yeah so
maybe we'll get talked talked about on all the big art blogs every frame of painting is going
to come out of retirement i don't know much about the beatles but this is probably like our revolver
or our sergeant pepper period the macros have changed what it means to podcast because podcasting
used to be a thing that people could enjoy yeah and it is yeah no the macroy brothers are
challenging you to just try to enjoy their show just try it and it's a lot like revolver in that
it feels like we are trying to shoot our listeners ears off with like a gun made of bad audio like a
bad audio experience so a love gun made of bad audio just to tie back in the kiss connection
so maybe we put the soundboard inside a toilet uh-huh okay and flush it down to sewer hell
so we kind of want to do some old school my bim bam without the soundboard yeah we got a lot of
stuff for you tonight you don't mind if we go way back to old school kids do you okay so there is
some now i get and now i'm starting to turn around on the soundboard because there is some topical
stuff on there so topical humor yeah okay i'm done well oh you must adjust in your elbow
i brushed a button on there okay so i'm gonna need you to set the soundboard that was a lot of fart
noise what's sad justin now we've used up all our whole fart noise budget i don't know how we're
gonna get through a show yeah we actually have to dip into our 2018 fart noise budget uh so this is
my brother my brother and me we it's advice show for the modern era uh we're kind of out of the
advice thing and more sort of focused on this soundboard currently so uh but we're definitely
gonna to help some people because that's what we're here before we started to think griffin
did you want to share your you had an idea for the next year slogan that i really liked yes i got a
letter in the mail uh and the letter in the mail had a suggestion for a slogan for 2018 and i wanted
to pitch it here i feel good about enough about this one by the way that i am i'm almost ready
to forego the usual pitch sesh we should talk about it we should you're right we should talk
about it but it's something to stew on because i don't know if it's the healthiest i'm all about
the health anyway uh landon and justin suggested 20 slates clean 20 slates clean and now let's
talk about it because i worry the possessive i worry i'm not sure we need that 20 slate clean
could be good i worry that people are going to think that we are there have been a lot of full
blown creeps and freaks creepazoids and freakazoids been coming out of the woodworks this year
and i don't want 20 slate clean to sound like we are um we are we are forgiving and forgetting
in any way but i worry that people could interpret 20 slate clean to mean that i just ah yes
i know our freakazoids we're still down we're so happy to have you on the show creepazoids
you're right creepazoids to the back please you know what creepazoids please go ahead and go
you can go ahead and go you're excused get the fuck out now freakazoids don't you move a muscle
yeah because y'all are here y'all are here with us scoot up it's got that jam on it and it's got
the nasty jam that you like freakazoids um but i think i'm also not sure about 20 slate clean
because i don't know that i want to uh establish a motto that is as sort of centered around like
boy this was a bad year next year's the one because i feel like maybe we thought 2016 was
like oh boy well at least 2016's over and then 2017 was sort of a bad sequel in a way you know
what i mean so i don't want to be like leave it behind i want it to be like fucking mount like
regulators mount up what what's so messed up is that it turned out that 2017 what turned out to
be 2013 dig it up yeah so like we just got the year off by like three years this year we dug
up a lot of dirt we there's a lot of dirty dirt just when you thought you'd hit bedrock you'd
hit it again and it was just more hard crumbly dirt yeah you thought it was bedrock but it was
actually new kinds of terrible dirt just that hadn't even been invented yet so i like the
phonetically 20 slate clean it sounds great i just don't know i i don't want to i'm not settled on
it because i don't know that it's necessarily yeah i was taking it more of like a personal
starting fresh you know not like forgive and forget but for yourself like allow yourself
this period of phoenix like but that's a good year titled should not need a uh a parenthetical
yeah all of us have had parenthetical and also 20 serpentine zag on them uh that was a sub
2013 dig it up like that was a subtitle to him to increase the power of it not to codify
that it doesn't apply it also i don't want a fresh start for everybody because i feel like
if one good thing came out of 2017 is that we got fucking hard like we got you you had to get
hard to get through 2017 and i'm not i'm not ready to get i it would be bad for us to give
up that chitin that we've developed after the waves of fucking garbage have crashed against our
shores for you know two calendar years now i i i feel like tough something about like
just fucking polish that armor we need a rhyme that rhymes with like something that represents
no surrender like 20 20 20 blade 20 blade teen and it's just like get
strapped with a big sharp sword maybe this is maybe this is the year that we all become
sword people listen we got another we're still in the candlelight spirit we do not we have plenty
of time to think about what the theme for next year is going to be true true there's probably
something with skating we just have to figure it out um skating uh but uh right now we're
going to get into the questions uh and i have to use the bathroom over here oh well how are we
going to do the questions if and could you at least press some buttons on the soundboard to
uh he's gone on griffin we should just uh pitch other like subtitles and let people come up with
the rhymes for us like i like mount up mount up if we mount up makes me psyched right if we can
find some kind of rhyme that's like 20 something something mount up 20 plate teen and it's like
plate armor this is nothing no 20 let's go to rhymezone.com yes checkmate team checkmate teen
no doesn't it doesn't quite go 20 weight teen be poised to strike 20 weight teen 20 weight teen
poised to strike oh i like that and it just means like keep your fucking head on the swivel
mount up mm-hmm what about 20 don't weight teen and it's like no day but today 20 weight teen
don't wait for you for your chance to to strike um what about have you guys done 20 freight teen
unstoppable like a freight like a freight train let's do some questions so a few days ago right
after my parents had gotten home from what i don't know we're in media res uh two guys in a
truck drove to up to our house and asked us if our neighbors christmas lights were public i didn't
think much of it at first but my mother's convinced this is a tactic they were using to scout our
house after thinking about it i myself also now believe we are going to be burgled are we that's
from worried in west virginia what on god's green earth does that mean okay so as i understand that
okay so this is based on my uh annual watching of um the american scream which is the the movie
about uh it's a documentary about people who decorate their houses for halloween it's extremely
good if you have not seen it it's extremely good it's maybe the best halloween movie right behind
a witch's ball but but one of the characters in there does a map of christmas lights sorry halloween
decorations in the area and so he goes and asks people like is it okay if they have a big display
he adds them to this map but he asked them like for permission before he adds them to the halloween
lights map the halloween decoration map right i do like the idea of halloween like yeah it's
beautiful um like just beautiful black lights um everybody walks down the street like going jogging
it's like is that come i see it in the halloween black lights okay good just but what i what i'm
saying is that he is suggesting like is it it is a wild distinction to make but is is it is your
light for you can i look at these can i look at these bad boys but he's asking that these these
these two people are asking a neighbor like hey do you think it's cool if we add your neighbors
well who better they can't approach the house travis with the christmas lights on it without
looking at the ding dang thing and they're not they don't want to do that if it's not for public
and what are you hey you get away from here this is for my kids what they what they're asking is
when you look at your neighbor's christmas lights how do they react yeah do they shoo you away and
throw a big sheet over it it's not for you it's for little dylan to make his christmas magical
you're using up all the magic with your foul eyes do you guys ever think about when you watch home
alone like how in our now modern age how home alone could like never happen in basically every
way start to finish oh yeah um yeah oh yeah yeah yeah for sure for sure like i put up a video
doorbell and i was like okay yeah this would stop him right there also how would kevin make
this doorbell electrocute people it's just a video thing yeah or you know kevin kevin pesci
jesus christ we cannot record this podcast this early in the morning anymore because i just said
kevin pesci out loud and i don't know who that is joe pesci's brother you've just docked someone
he's a doctor uh perfectly real kevin pesci from spokane kevin pesci hacks your nest cams sees all
the damn traps and then that's that's it that's all there is to it it's like facetime kevin from
france or wherever and you're just like hey sorry we left you there you cool all right bye um be
cool kid so i mean the alternative is that they were casing the joint oh absolutely you gotta
be constantly every time the the fedex comes and delivers my blue apron box i know they're also
like as long as i'm here i'm gonna see where the valuables are which is why i'm always every time
anybody steps near my house i gotta rearrange where my valuables are and i gotta rearrange
where all the traps are yep so annoying and it's so annoying because i don't remember where the
damn traps are and i gotta send rachel the map and then you know henry's play zone i sometimes
a trap ends up there and we have to figure that out and it gets very complicated because he loves
the traps because they look very fun like fun toys uh one of them is made out of a balloon but the
balloon's full of horrible you know human dissolving acid um and so we gotta balloon
preserving human dissolving gas right and so we have humans and balloons are made out of different
stuff just yeah read one book and so gotta remember which ones are the death balloons
and which ones are fun balloons for babies let's see here's the thing griffin people will say that
you're being too cautious but you've never been robbed so never been robbed because of all my
they i put up a sign also in front of my house that says great traps inside move them around
constantly so don't even try bother to case the joint kevin pesci i feel like occam's razor if
they were casing um houses they would probably come up with a a patter that is less uh baffling
they would probably have sort of a straight line like do you need us to clean your gutters or
something that is not like inventing this whole idea of public christmas or like hey here's a
here's your blue apron box and you say thanks you take it inside you set down in the kitchen
you go to use the john or the lou and then joe pesci pops out of the blue apron box steals all
of your things where'd my xbox one go damn it joe and also where's all my pre-portioned ingredients
i can use to make home-cooked meals damn it i got double robbed i don't have an xbox to play
crash bandicoot and all of my food from the blue aprons gone what am i gonna make sure what am i
gonna eat when i don't play crash bandicoot you gotta make sure that your blue apron box does not
contain any live joe pesci's every time i get a blue apron box i run my sword through it you got
yeah just to make sure because he's gonna eat all your ding dang fresh cilantro first yeah and that's
irritating you gotta go to sort of replace that daniel stern don't even take the food out he just
rubs his nasty body all over it and so you don't you're like my xbox is gone but at least my food's
here cook it up yum yum eat it wait a minute this tastes like daniel stern's nasty body shit
daniel stern's hair post the events of home alone one is is i think oh i just thought about tasting
daniel stern's hair i just thought about getting a big mouthful of that dude's head and i oh gosh
blue apron almost never has daniel stern's hair stern's hair in it almost never that's a blue
apron almost guarantee statistically speaking i've never gotten daniel stern's hair in my
in my blue apron box right down the box 99.999999% free of daniel stern's hair now we do want to be
clear it's mostly for blue apron we're not talking about a single strand of blue of of
daniel stern's hair it's a lot of it would be a lot of hair to get it to register on the on the
their sensors it needs to be a considerable amount of that warning on there but then one box showed
up just completely full of nothing but daniel stern's hair if you're portioning out goat cheese
you gotta assume some of daniel stern's hair it's gonna get in there i mean that's just
the reality of everything like everything you buy from the store uh when you get a soda mcdonald's
peanut butter all of it has some amount stern take a deep breath there's some daniel stern in there
right i think it was carl sagan who said we are all made of stern stuff yes
how about a yahoo i'd love that i'd love that it felt like we had reached the logical conclusion
of the daniel stern jokes abigail love it sent this one and thank you abigail to yahoo answers
user conquer the king who asked can i just say just a side note it always makes you really happy
when there's a new name of someone who likes senate like i don't think i've ever heard abigail's name
before and it's nice to know that there's like new yahoo soldiers listen i'm very thankful for
the great yahoo's that everybody sends in week to week and i hope nobody takes takes the uh recurring
people it's a who send them in like getting on the show all the time it is an art form it is an art
form to find these uh trash bags but not just trash bags trash bags that perfectly sort of fit
the the tone and nature of our show but abigail love it has done some great work here because
conquer the king asks why is paul mccartney stingy by stingy i mean why is he so greedy
with his music to the point that he isn't letting people play the beatles songs on youtube i know
he has a right to his music just like all artists however being that the songs are a beloved classic
that is over 40 years old he shouldn't be greedy that people love his music so much they are willing
to want to listen to it yeah he should be like other artists do which is be grateful that people
listen to his music and stop being so stingy paul mccartney yeah and this is not something i believe
and i need to go ahead and say that out loud because the streaming music industry has pretty
much decimated the music industry as far as i understand it and that's no good and people
artists are completely entitled to receiving compensation for the hard work that they do
and pay an artist quit expecting them to do everything for free but i i don't know why paul
mccartney won't let the great beatles music be on youtube let it be you know just let it be you
know eight days a week let me listen to it help i'm not i'm not saying all artists i have a problem
with them just paul mccartney just paul mccartney is every time excuse me i you try to hide it right
and it's like here's a fun clip of my family barbecue but really paperback writers in there
and paul mccartney somehow no matter how hard you try to bury the beatles music his music
these are my songs he knows and at this point it's just like paul can't you just be happy that
people like like what are you trying to do make money off of your music the songs are so old paul
and beloved people like them isn't that enough for you can you use that they're so old paul come
paul's just like paul's just sitting on his throne made of money and i'm trying to listen to these
i can't stress this enough super old songs you're lucky that i'm even listening to your old music
because i should be listening to new hot top 40 jams but instead i'm listening to your ancient
scrawlings paul it was record that was recorded with like a bird pecking on stone oh yeah i know
and and and like edison thomas edison like looked up from the you know gramophone and gave him a
thumbs up it's like coming out great paul every time i listen to a song that's older than 10 years
old which at this point encompasses a lot of the black eyed peas body of work i get this dusty taste
in my mouth and the beatles music so old that i listen to you know back in the ussr and i'm just
like oh god it's so old you're lucky about a place that doesn't even exist anymore you're lucky i'm
listening to your old music i bought a beatles album and i immediately of course opened it up
and upturned it to see all the web exclusive content behind the scenes footage that was gonna
fall out of it and do you know how much did fall out of this record none what yeah i was like i was
like scouring it looking for some sort of twitter handle on it that i could use to like thank them
for the music and complain about the price and there wasn't a single one like do you want like
where is the hashtag do you want me to tweet about this record or not because i'm not going to just
make one up justin how many youtubers were like partnered with them on certain songs and like
featuring like some 12 year old youtuber like there was a lot of that though right here's the
thing trap is gonna bug you out but um uh unless ellenor rigby is like some hot tuber that i have
not heard of before i don't think it had like any youtube people wait at all yeah you heard how do
they get people listen i don't know i mean i felt like it was kind of an act of charity on my behalf
yeah like reinforcing i went the narrative i went to a record store which is basically like a
retirement home for music if you really think about it and i picked up um paul's album the fun
title one that's like dr pepper's fun time jamboree took it home to put it in my record
player open it up two bats flew out of it old this old music guys it's and now it's a dangerous
public health hazard because the bats the bats fly into my traps and then they're deactivated
and now i have now i have holes in the in the reinforcements that the the you know the blue
apron thieves are absolutely gonna know about like we don't pay shakespeare when you do shakespeare
shows shakespeare's not like getting on youtube like let me see who's quoting hamlet and they're
like product trying videos come on paul mccartney you're basically shakespeare you're both british
i think come on yeah the beatles paul mccartney who you think you are shakespeare uh it's a bit
of a stretch you're a little full of yourself a little high on the horse a little bit paul
paul paul i did like your halo song the song you did for the halo game that wasn't quite halo was
great but paul very good and again artists should be paid for i feel like i have to say this like
10 times artists should be paid for their time and energy yes absolutely 100 all of them don't
steal stuff pay people to do designs for you pay people to do music for you just not paul mccartney
can be a little stingy sometimes when uh the beatles great music and by great i mean like
really old but good and like the old way where you're like you know you watch an old movie or
hear old songs like i see what you're going for if there needs to be like a christmas carol where
like three ghosts appear to paul mccartney and they're like hey just let people use your music
paul and old music is good when you only view it or listen to it through the lens of like well
clearly it's not like black eyed peas good but black eyed peas have 40 years of like extra
learnings that they use to make their great music and so i think the number one lesson that black
eyed peas taught us was don't put a year number in your song right because then maybe 10 years
later 2008 won't be so new and fresh and impressive sort of like the rubin stuttered hit
this is my sorry for 2004 uh don't you think rubin kicks himself right in the shorts for
not waiting 13 years on that one gosh darn it um how about another question yes
i just got paid artists for the time i just got hired just not paul mccartney i just got hired
at a law firm next summer uh for next summer and the head partner invited me to a holiday dinner
party with the rest of the firm's employees the problem is i have to order my meal in advance
my choices of protein are crab cakes chicken or filet mignon with sizes sweet potato fries
scallop potatoes or green beans how is this at all a problem this sounds dope how is this at all an
issue this will let me finish okay listen all right listen god uh this will be my first interaction
with the firm and i'm worried that picking the filet will come off too pretentious what should
i choose the steaks thank you i've never been hired oh my god okay griffin look at this though
right wait oh all right that's from perplexed in the clean plate club wow overtalk's gonna get way
better on this show if justin has a punishment button which is paul stanley yelling at us to
listen what we've got here toronto well that one's not applicable justin so i hit the wrong button
okay we've got a logic puzzle here right you have three protein options and you have to get
them across the river but you only have one raft the crab cakes will eat the filet mignon and you
have three side options and there is a right combination that will get you promoted before you
even start working oh shit right but if you say crab cakes and green beans are like crab cakes
this is a young man uh who dreams of the sea he's not going to focus on his job and you're like oh
i want chicken and scallop potatoes and it's like ah he thinks he's a simple man with simple desires
he has no he has no dreams he has no aspirations and if you're like i want flame mignon and sweet
potato fries and it's like oh la dee da look at mr high and mighty filet mignon over here
right i yeah you must like the minion movies he's a child right it's bad all around i would
like to suggest okay let's all have our ideal combination here oh i've got it out here's what
i would like to suggest um green beans and then right in at the bottom i will bring my own meat
because that's somebody who is worried about the bottom line has sort of like culinary prowess
because they they are willing to like cook their own food and bring it along and it's somebody who
uh uh never you know never wants to do things by the company line they want to think outside the
bun thank you travis none of these foods have buns well all of these all of these foods are outside
of the bun now justin that only works if you can if your dish you bring and you lift the little
metal cover off of it and it is more impressively cooked and plated than what has been served oh
shit fucking uh yeah i didn't i didn't uh choose my own meal because i brought my own gordo and
then gordon ramsay's like i wish you wouldn't call me that and you're like i can call you with a
fuck i want to call you gordon ramsay that's maybe the biggest power play that you have available to
you and you yell at gordon ramsay till he cries if you can make gordon ramsay cry at this christmas
party first of all gordon wants to be back in in the uk with his family during christmas time so
you know that you're gonna impress them because they're like wow what's he got on gordon ramsay
that he is able to pull him away from his beautiful family um my suggestion is this you get
the flight you get the filet mignon with a side of filet mignon oh and then you say two things i'm
hungry for advancement you don't say that second part but they'll know and then you also say i'm
eating two filet mignons because i'm gonna work twice as hard as any of these other bastards
you say all that you do say all that part out loud this actually goes along with what
my kobayashi maru which was you just check all of them okay i will have the filet mignon with
crab cakes and chicken on top and a side of sweet potato fries mixed with scalloped potatoes
mixed with green beans thank you very much oh yeah or because the summer is a long time away
and you might not even get that job but you'll have eaten the equivalent of three free meals
oh i see it's sort of a grift situation could mark them all and then right at the bottom
please donate mine to hungry orphans and they'll be like oh wow wow that's a big play or
you bring your own big bowl and you mush them all up into just one big nasty mess
and then you eat that with your hands and then the boss is like i like his style i'll have that too
yeah pretty soon can i have some of your nasty mess only if you make me the boss okay yes right
just write a little note on the card please provide table blender yeah because you'll want
definitely want that oh just write in dealer's choice that is the worst choice right back on
them that is the dealer's choice will be no food you get nothing because they are not going to
bother with that that's true don't mark a protein but next to green beans right seven and see if
you can get a seven times huge green beans x7 people are gonna remember that guy you should
call your boss and say a quick question what are green beans are these beans that you have dyed
green in some way um mark mark sweet potato fries and steak but next to green beans put a question
mark green beans and then their boss will be like well green beans are these fun little pods full of
these small weird nasty beans and you say okay i've learned that and now you've shown that you
are quick to learn ready for advancement ready to go i i maybe just mark out the green on green
beans and then mark that so i want some beans of a different whatever sort of variety you can you
can dig up in the kitchen yeah and write it mark it out and then write in uh scalloped sweet beans
scallop sweet beans with chicken with chicken cakes you figure it out i'm a fussy dude and i
need chicken cakes or else i'm gonna cry at the party turn it into sort of a logic flow so next
to chicken right if tenders yes if no proceed to next option and then you just have like a
sort of a flow chart to really make it as complicated as possible but that shows what
frosting yeah right with butter butter cream please uh could you just say i'll i'll pick
to find out what your boss is getting this is actually a great thing find out what your boss
is getting and get the exact same thing or get something different and then at the party you
sit down next to your boss this is so important and you say splitsies yeah oh yeah split wanted
all those options he definitely has also struggled with this and then insist on paying half the check
for the whole table and they'll keep saying like no this is the whole the business is paying for it
and you keep saying like are you sure because i'll i'll cover it this one could be on me it's like
you haven't even started working here you're like okay but you like really keep being insistent but
if at any point there is a ripcord here if at any point the boss is like okay cool you're like no
i was lying i don't have i guess i don't i don't get the job that's a lot that's far too much money
don't mark any food but at the bottom make an option for lots of overdue paperwork and so when
everybody else is eating and just like the beef juice is dribbling down their chin you'll be like
hammering it away at all the shit kathy left for the new year and you're gonna be the one making
everybody else look lazy and you'll be the one digging the company out of the red and hoisting
them by yourself into the black um is that good it's red is bad no one quite knows man i'm fucking
hungry should we treat ourselves to a visit to the money zone to fill our our our wallet bellies
yeah yeah i mean i don't eat money but sure i mean i do
first up this week is bowl and branch do you like to sleep like how you said that thanks
trav i tried to put a good positive energy behind it bowl and branch branch uh if you like to sleep
and i bet you do um you don't need to spend a fortune to get that beloved slumber uh you can uh
you can check out bowl and branch they're crafted from uh their sheets should start there yeah thank
you uh they're crafted from 100 organic cotton and they feel incredible and look amazing uh the the
new york times and forbes rave about them and three u.s presidents have them so depending on
which ones that's referring to that could be really great or try or quite or quite bad if
it's one of the nasty prezies or maybe not something you want to brag about uh they're
in their coffins uh try them for 30 nights and see for yourself if you're not impressed you can
return them for a full refund johnson can i ask you a question anything is bowling branch just
sheets um no travis they have other shit whoa so go to bowling branch.com today and you'll get
50 off your first set of sheets plus free shipping when you use the promo code my brother that's 50
dollars off plus free shipping right now at bowling branch.com they make great gifts they
make great gifts they make great sheets spelled b-o-l-l and branch.com promo code my brother
and uh go go get that for yourself because you deserve it bowling branch promo code bowling
branch.com promo code my brother i also want to tell you about blue apron we talked about him a
lot and we've had a lot of fun here but odds are like heavily in your favor that joe pesci
and daniel stern aren't gonna hop out of a blue apron box and steal your xbox and if they do if
they do blue apron will will buy you a new xbox it doesn't say that in the bullet points but i
have to believe that just standard human decency will sort of step in here um but they deliver
fresh pre-portioned ingredients and step-by-step recipes right to your door that and all those
meals can be cooked in under 45 minutes and the menu changes every week based on what's in season
and it's designed by blue aprons in-house culinary team i'm a big fan of blue apron because i uh when
i moved to austin i like literally basically had never cooked anything that wasn't frozen um and
blue apron taught me how to cook and it's a it's a very valuable life skill that i am very grateful
for um all the ingredients are high quality they send only non-gmo ingredients and meat with no
added hormones and right now blue aprons treating my brother my brother my brother my brother what's
our podcast my brother my brother and me listeners to their first three meals a 30 value with your
first order if you visit blue apron.com slash my brother so check out this week's menu and get 30
bucks off with free shipping at blue apron.com slash my brother blue apron a better way to cook
trap you want to read this uh message i sure do garth brooks is the number two selling artist in
the u.s but do you know anyone who's listened to a whole garth album insane clown posley has
dedicated fans but do you know anyone who's heard a single icp song join cameron and nathan and
listening to artists that many people dismiss it's a podcast called think outside the box set
equal parts investigative journalism cultural criticism and dick jokes well i mean it's a
podcast so yeah check out boxset.website it's a real url or search for us on podcast uh okay
or your preferred podcatcher i think ipod i what did it apple i have a picture of an apple here oh
see just as a picture of an apple tell me about the picture of apple we just got a box it's a
little black apple on mine oh that's fine podcast or your preferred podcatcher it's called think
outside the box set sounds like a lot of fun sounds like a hoot and a half sounds like a real
cool shindig for hip people this next one i can't tell what's going on with the for and from
um i don't know if it's a secret message or just like the coolest name i've ever seen somebody
may have gotten confused when they were filling out sort of the metadata of the message because
it says who's this message for and what they've put here is where like w h e r e who's this
message from where so it's possible they saw these questions were like where do you want me to put
this data where do you where do you where is this supposed to go where they did find the box they
did so what's the message trough are you fucking done yet no i no that's the message are you fucking
done yet sigh probably not keep at it though books don't just make themselves just watch out
for a hundred dolls as you print those bastards will get you thanks bros for keeping me laughing
late into the work night you guys are the best hugs um and they wanted that message in 2017
so some important stuff in here a lot actually they they said that their preferred time frame
is whatever's latest i mean this message is applicable until at least 2018 so they definitely
like have a large window here i think this is a message for themselves from themselves to
encourage themselves to finish the book they're writing i love that a lot of people though are i
don't know that book printers are some of the most like haunted buildings oh god yes we're doing the
taz graphic novel uh and they were like do you want to come by and see the magic of books getting
printed and i said nice try because once i step inside my spirit will never leave because of the
grudge yeah well i mean i'm pretty sure that only ghosts work in the print industry anymore
oh yeah what does that even mean trap uh well uh got something what's it mean do you have a thing
well like print is dying i think i don't know but that's not what that means what
yeah books are crushing it books are doing great good yeah but i'm pretty sure books are back books
are back wow hey good job books well you can't really walk away from the thing you said good job
books i've always been a fan are stacks of unread books taking over your apartment do you constantly
miss your train stop because you're caught up in reading i'm bria grant and i'm mallory o'mara we
party hard and by party hard we mean read books so join us every thursday on reading glasses a
maximum fun podcast about reading and book culture get more out of your reading life we'll help you
conquer your to be read pile get out of that book slump and squeeze more reading time into your busy
day learn how to read better wow that was good
oh maybe paul can help out with this one
oh
it's a podcast within a podcast um this one is a little different from our our normal but we want
to expand the scope for the show as we head into 2018 this one is a sweet frog you know no sweet
frog it's a frozen yogurt literally never heard of it sweet frog brings back deck the halls christmas
spectacle sweet frog frozen yogurt is gonna put on a real christmas spectacle throughout the holiday
season with a deck the halls benefit night nights plural that's important to keep in mind hosted by
participating locations from coast to coast okay so here's the promotion and i want you to really
as i'm setting the stage for this i want you to really like sort of envision it church and school
choirs throughout the country have partnered with local sweet frog shops to host benefit night
fundraisers these choirs will perform all the holiday favorites to help them raise much needed
funds for local initiatives to make these events even more special sweet frog will produce a video
christmas card using a montage of local choirs performing all over the country that video
christmas card will then be posted on all sweet frog social media outlets so basically you go in
everybody who's in the choir gets a free frozen yogurt nice count it and all the sales from that
night a portion 25 of all the sales go to uh the um the charity while the choir is performing wow
25 can you imagine all of us at sweet frog love this annual event that gets us in the christmas
spirit says their ceo patrick gallagher uh it's a wonderful time of community fellowship as people
come together to celebrate christmas what better way to do that than enjoying the sounds of the
season sung by local choirs we are proud to showcase great local talent and support local
churches and schools while helping our sweet frog owners generate some serious winter foot traffic
okay yeah i have two problems the first one is can i just eat my fucking frozen yogurt
please it is i am sad it is the holidays i am alone and i came in to eat some frozen yogurt
and just try to like fucking chill have you ever ever been in a frozen yogurt shop the size of
which you thought this is a place i would love to get blasted by jingle bells being screamed at me
by 40 people never ever ever never the the other thing yeah the other thing is 25 that is so nice
let me just real quick run the margins on frozen yogurt oh that's right it's 98
percent you literally take cow stuff and add some sugar and then you sell it for a hundred
dollars as somebody who's worked in the yogurt industry i can confirm justin's justin's math on
on this one um this is also like as somebody who's worked in the yogurt industry yes the cold months
are not necessarily the hottest time for a sweet frog or a yogurt land or the country's best yogurt
and so this this feels like you're just trying to trying to get us in the trying to get us in the
door my main concern is that you know with the introduction of local church choirs it ain't just
gonna be jingle bells it's there's going it's gonna get there's gonna be some jay-su in the mix
and there's gotta be you know there's an important separation between church and yogurt and i'm
worried that this is blurring the line so you know what though i think it sounds maybe a little nice
okay well here's holly sylvias who is of charlestown west virginia oh hey thank you
hey hello um and holly is going to be uh putting on a a deck the halls event in her store and here's
the quote we invited a local school choir fourth and fifth graders to perform good good love this
yogurt because it's kids i'm anticipating a huge crowd which is great children really shine when
they have a chance to perform in front of an audience so i want to pack the place out we'll
move tables out of the way to make more room if needed so she's really just like in this press
release kind of thinking through the logistics of this event and also so okay so i'm just gonna
enjoy my frozen yogurt while standing up well i'll stay i'll just stand then so i'll just stand
i paid nine dollars for this frozen yogurt but i'll go ahead and stand in a corner could you
excuse me little kid could you scoot over i'm trying to get to the yogurt i just please just
let me get my yogurt and when was the last time anybody bought yogurt and said oh i can't wait
to sit down and enjoy this here at the yogurt place um as somebody worked in the yogurt industry
they'll do they'll do that and it's just it's like when you turn in a test at school and the
teacher grades it right there in front of you because it's like oh boy i hope they enjoy the
work i've done there sometimes they'll look over at you and be like too much crushed up heath bar
i'll be like i'm sorry i'll do better next time here's your money back praise jesus love love it
love his stuff i think this sounds nice i like a good carol and i like carolers and i don't know
that this would necessarily make me want to go get cold cream in the cold cold harsh winter texas
months um but i think it sounds sweet and i think that justin was mean for no fun of it let me side
with justin here because i think were i unprepared for this site to await me and my frozen yogurt
shop and i opened the door just wanting to grab a quick frozen treat on my way home from a hard
day at the office and i opened the door and there was like an army of children singing about jesus i
don't think i'd think oh awesome now imagine instead travis you walked in and there was a
man dressed in halloween clothing standing alone on a stage while you enjoyed frozen yogurt and he
opened his mouth and i put my hand inside a toilet yeah that would rule yeah we're all very i mean if
we wanted to do a winter promotion um i feel like what would be dope is like hey this is griffin
for sweet frog i've changed i've jumped over like the can you hear me now guy and i'm a trader to
the country's best yogurt and there's a lot of shit you don't know about that brand but anyway
i'm excited to announce for the cold winter months you gotta have your frozen yogurt fixed
and that's why i've invented hot yogurt and it's the new jam that you are just gonna love and come
hey get out oh baby it's cold outside enjoy this hot yogurt it's the new thing i've developed and
it burns the mouth so so bad you have to it'll be like an hour before you can really enjoy it
and don't put any toppings in it because the toppings will be destroyed in this molten hot
yogurt this steaming plasma of yogurt um but it's better people are serving you yogurt that has
living things in it and our yogurt is served at a temperature in which no living these cultures will
be obliterated there is no sort of gastrointestinal sort of benefits to be gleaned from this very very
very very hot burning fiery yogurt and in fact why the opposite you will regret in you regret
consuming it yes because it'll burn all your insides out it'll burn a hole right through you
and if that don't get you the asbestos cup is definitely not going to be good for the health
it's made of fiberglass basically and it's going to get in the hot yogurt and there's nothing we
talked to the scientists and there's nothing we can do about it how about a yahoo yeah please
merit palmer sent this one in thank you merit it's from an anonymous yahoo user i'm gonna call
him the guy from the i put my hand inside toilet video asks how many horses would it take to pull
a horse trailer full of horses oh shit i'm so excited to get into this question with you boys
because we're gonna say a bunch of dumb math stuff but how many horses would it take to pull a horse
trailer that is just chocoblock full of horses wow it can't just be one to one right so here's
the question if let's here's what we need to establish first we need to what's the word tear
the scale a little bit is that how you pronounce that we're gonna tear we gotta tear it right so
how many horses does a horse trailer weigh i'm gonna say probably about six horses you're saying
sans horses empty horse trailer i think is about six horses worth of weight horses okay and you
can probably get like a decent sized horse trailer maybe five more horses in it so that's 11 horses
okay okay okay can one dude you need 11 horses to pull 11 horses worth of weight or does the term
horsepower refer to the amount of joules of force required to pull one horse against its will well
here's here's the question and i think we have to remove this factor or else this will be here all
day and everyone's gonna say like well with wheels on it that simple machine makes it easier okay
cool remove remove the wheel we are in a paralogic scenario here where there is no wheel or like
sled or we factor out the wheels and say the wheels will get you about two horses worth off
so now we're talking about nine horses and that's a very i just punched the numbers into siri and
she told me the wheels will counteract the weight of about two horses so now nine horses do we then
need nine horses pulling santa's sleigh tonight and bringing all the good boys and girls uh gift
of horses or is that not how any of this works well let's take okay griffin we've calculated this
the the the weight of the trailer right uh so now let's imagine 11 horses and each horse is riding
on the back of another horse right so you would need one horse per horse this is a lot what you've
just entered into the equation which is horse stacking yeah but you couldn't put two horses on
one horse it wouldn't fit this is gonna trick about that this is gonna trip you all out okay
i'm here to complicate things i did a quick google just to provide a little science okay
this is this is complicated but a single draft horse i don't know what that means
can pull a load up to 8000 pounds what draft horse is when you get on tap instead of in a bottle
right okay so get one horse out of a bottle it can pull 8000 pounds how much a horse way probably
about 4000 pounds so travis can google that while i'm reading these facts how much horseway don't
you don't have to say it don't use like your speech how much horseway just go ahead and type
it all fine siri so much horseway so griffin if i told you one draft horse can pull uh a load up
to 8000 pounds yeah how much would two horses be able to pull 16 000 pounds no wrong two draft
horses can i guess together and i guess yes 12 000 pounds no can i guess can i guess can i guess
yes 20 000 pounds of raw horse material no that's incorrect can i guess can i guess can i guess yeah
yeah 45 000 pounds 45 pounds 45 pounds all right listen what they can actually pull and there's a
lesson in this and we're gonna find it what they can pull working together is not 16 000 pounds
or double they can pull 24 000 pounds they could pull three times whoa they're usual by working
working together holy shit think about yeah because they build up momentum every action has
an equal opposite reaction except for two horses as the great law says from the 10 commandments
and so then we shit okay so now we got 11 horses right 11 horses worth take off the wheels that's
nine horses if it's a factor of tripling every time you add another horse then three horses
can then pull let me run the numbers on this real quick 72 000 pounds the three horses only so
they're dragging like a building behind them they can definitely if we get 10 horses and strap them
to the earth we can counteract the rotation of the earth and destroy everything here is where it gets
it gets worse guys it gets more complicated two horses that have worked together for a long time
buddies get out pals that like long-time collaborators can pull actually pull 32 000
pounds wait as heavy as they even can pull by themselves so now we have to factor in like
partnership drift these fucking horses are in the drift and they can pull the earth out of orbit
so you're telling me two horses we're in a like a buddy cop scenario here we're like two horses
at first they're both loose cannons this horse is by the books and this book this horse is out
there trying new shit and at first they're maybe maybe on a good day pulling 22 000 pounds right
but then they start to see within each other like you know we're not so different you and i and over
the years they just get it well enough that suddenly they are 8 000 pounds stronger it's
amazing you're trying but that a ton a u.s short ton is 2 000 pounds you're telling me that these
two horses can pull 16 tons of raw horse meat 16 tons what do you get it's just two horses
two horses friends two best like best friend horses how do you as a horse owner and owner of
the most buckwild freight company ever make these horses become best friends so that your margins
on no how do you stop them that's this is terrifying you can't stop them can't stop
i guarantee farmers look out of their windows and they see two horses like you know we gotta
destroy our house which right like and we gotta go break that up we can't okay a horse an adult
horse i looked this up siri told me an adult horse weighs between 840 to 2200 pounds so let's call
it let's call it 16 as an average 1600 pounds so if these two horses are pulling 32 000 pounds
and we use 1600 as an average we're talking about imagine looking out your window and seeing two
two brutal best friend horses pulling 20 fucking horses behind them oh no it's okay guys we've got
it we are longtime friends and we are going to pull all 20 of you in this trailer and then the
horse is like fucking high five because they also figured out how to do that because they're best
best friends now wait a minute i did not factor in what did we say six horses worth of weight in a
in a usual trailer minus two for the wheels so that's 16 horses 16 horses still 16 horses that's
a mate that is it is so you're telling me yes it is more cost effective for two horses to pull 16
horses than to just have all 18 horses walk all right let me add one can i also add by the way
that we have now like completely completely obliterated any value to the term horsepower
because it is not it is not a i mean are they uh you know 400 horsepower is that 400 horses
400 horsepower would destroy the galaxy yeah are they best friends are they are really like have
they worked together for a long time like there's so many factors in this horsepower also why are
we talking about this as clean energy because two horses apparently it all compounds just have like
six horses and you can power all of america why are we fucking with cars like why are we even
messing around with it i'll i'll talk about hey elon i'll hop on two horses i'll get to san
francisco in like an hour and a half right why aren't horses pulling my goddamn car
yeah why are we doing engines and gas and stuff so if i griffin am best friends with my horse
which i am take real good care make a big sweater for it with four leg holes love my horse
if me and my horse try to pull a trailer how much weight can we do because i think the horse gets
the breath the the best friend buff uh-huh the best friend strength buff and i obviously am it's
going to be carrying most of the weight literally in this situation does it still get the extra
strength from me the horse's best friend how much can you pull griffin probably about 4500 pounds
okay if i really if i if i'm wearing my cleats and i can really dig in there okay so griffin
can pull 4500 pounds and the horse by itself can pull 8000 but it gets the best friend buff
so it gets the best friend buff i'm gonna say you can pull a together 18 000 pounds and that will
i absolutely can't keep up with my best friend the horse and i will be obliterated by this 18 000
joules of force horse trailer you'll be ripped in half i'll all be destroyed at some point though
at some point though can't the best friend buff start to work against you like if one horse is
having an off day do you think there's a chance his partner horse because they are such close
friends would be like we're gonna take a little slower today like there are some days where it's
actually worse than typical horse performance because they do want to slow it down for their
friend or they want to enjoy they haven't caught up for a while so they slow it down like no reason
to rush chester yeah well you have to be careful because if like if one of your horses is sick and
you partner the other one with a new horse and then the sick horse sees that he's like i thought
we were best friends and like now oh good point yeah now there's an issue of like well i don't
want to partner with you anymore well that's what blinders are for to keep the horses from
seeing when the other horses are becoming other best friends with other horses man there's a lot
that goes into this you're in the horse trailer and the horse trailer is just not moving like
what the fuck's up and you listen to the two horses in front it's like that's my wife derrick
and it's like oh shit all right so i guess the answer to this is two pretty much anything you
want to haul yeah two good best friend horses can pretty much do it and that's a good lesson for us
if we all we don't just all need to work together we need to start working together now so our load
will steadily increase that we can haul together as a people then how can we get that gang gang
2018 stronger together oh that's not bad holy shit that's really good because that was both
was like romantic but also mates in the way of like friends but also like yeah yeah all working
yeah i was thinking about it platonically 2018 stronger together we can we you can do you can do
a lot by yourself and you should and you got to try but with another person you can pull 3600
pounds we like a lot of themes recently have celebrated self-interest yeah this one 30 30
3018 for the for the year 3018 2018 just find a bud or something because it's positive but it also
goes along with that like mount up ride or die we're all in this together fight together i do
wonder if you we this needs a particularly large coda too and that we're not incur like
we're not trying to repopulate the earth and increase mating amongst peoples well what if
we say it with like a british affectation so every time you say it yeah it's got to be like
2019 2019 and i don't know how we write that out yeah yeah um lot in there okay uh folks that is
going to do it for us thank you so much for listening to our program i'm ready to throw i'm
ready to throw my hat for 2018 we have we've got to have the conversation we can't just like leap
into it we were that was the conversation it's a whole thing that we have to do can i give you
this we haven't even given people a chance to submit submit yet how can i we can't what about
this subtitle though 2018 two horses can pull 32 000 pounds together their best friends okay
there's something there thank you for listening uh wanted to give uh another plug to mb mb am
angels uh which is trying to raise money to buy people in the tri-state area gifts here is an
astounding update for you so far but is it and you still need to get in on this because there's
still time you can uh send donations to donate at mbmbamangels.com uh so far through the amazing
astounding listeners of my brother my brother me and the volunteers who are organizing this charity
they have been able to purchase 23 beds four sofas three dressers a table with six chairs and there's
there are 23 kids that are not going to be sleeping on the floor because of you
you thank you so much um every year you all do this and um it honestly means the world so uh you
can keep donating donate at mbmbamangels.com we try to thank everybody but honestly there's
not thanks enough to to be able to um to to thank you for everything you've done on this
joyous candlelight season um 100 of the stockings have been claimed but you can uh still donate uh
these organizations in our area are never not in need of uh your generosity so thank you so
much for anything that you can do the fact that you all have done all of this for our hometown
means like more than i think we will ever be able like generosity is is good and pure and amazing
and we celebrate it in all its forms but the fact that like um because our podcast listeners are so
incredible like people in our hometown are are receive this incredible gift it is it is uh it
is beautiful beyond sort of description so thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank
you um thank you also to john roderick and the long winters for the use of our theme song it's
a departure off the album putting the days to bed very good song we're so thankful for that as well
and to maximum fun for having us on the network you can go to maximum fun org and check out all
the great podcasts there shows like the beef and dairy network and lady to lady and if you haven't
been paying attention max fun has added a lot of new shows and like the last six months new shows
go fact yourself switchblade sisters story break there's uh heat rocks there's all kinds of new
shows on there that you need to go check out uh he rocks is good y'all checked out yeah it's a
good one check out it's you have somebody on there to just tell their their jam what's their jam it's
great it's great um also since uh san francisco sketch fest is coming up uh i january 14th
schmaners is going to be there me and my wife teresa do a show called schmaners uh we are going
to be performing january 14th at sketch fest uh and if you've never been to san francisco sketch
fest it's amazing it's like in one weekend you can see more shows than you would see like all
year it's incredible uh and you can find that at sfsketchfest.com um and also schmaners is going to
be on the joko cruise uh and i think there's still a few cabins available um if you want to come out
and hang out on a boat for a week and see some awesome performers and hang out with awesome
people you can find out about that at jokocruise.com j-o-c-o cruise.com uh y'all want that final hit me
it was sent in by brig wultgen fantastic name thank you brig it's yahoo answer it's another
anonymous user i'm gonna call this one also the guy from the i put my hands on a toilet video
asks if i get my life saved by a frog will i turn into a frog my name is justin mccoroy i'm
travis mccoroy i'm griffin mccoroy this has been my brother my brother and me kiss your dad square
on the lips maximum fun.org comedy and culture artist owned listener supported i'm allegra ringo
and i'm renee colbert and we host a podcast called can i pet your dog renee can i tell you
about a dog i met this week i wish that you would in turn though can i tell you about a dog hero
may i tell you about a dog breed in a segment i like to call mutt minute i would love that
could we maybe talk about some dog tech could we have some cool guests on like lin-manuel
miranda nicole beyer and ann weaton i mean yeah absolutely i'm in you're on board what do you
say we uh we do all of this and put it into a podcast yeah okay you think all right uh should
we call it like i don't know can i pet your dog sure all right uh what do you what do you say we
put it on every tuesday on maximum fun or on itunes sounds good to me meeting's over