Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool babies?
Familiar, but not too familiar, but not too not familiar.
It's a new craze, hey good girls, do you want it? Just say, hey I wanna. Just say, hey I wanna.
John Rodger, John Rodger, John Rodger.
Oh shit.
I'm going to be, I'm going to be, I'm going to be worthless this whole show after that.
John Rodger, one more time for John Rodger.
He was like, do you want me to play the whole song? And we're like, let's remember who's on the marquee.
Hey, hey.
Calm down.
Seattle, are you ready for a psychosexual journey with us?
My name.
We're all going to come through the other end together.
Yeah, we, yeah, this is my brother, my brother and me, it's an advice show for the modern era and I'm your oldest brother Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle is brother Travis McElroy.
And I'm your sweet baby brother Flop Sweat Magoo.
I apologize for my shininess, but you see, I'm fucking terrified.
This is great though because the lighting allows me to only see the first 10 people, which feels right.
Yeah, it feels like an intimate coffee shop show. Super attractive, super duper attractive.
Hey baby, I hear the blues are calling, toss salad and scrambled eggs.
Now wait, now hold on.
We had a fucking screaming argument about that.
I mainly did that to irritate Griffin.
Hold on, I want to jump in. Griffin's big argument against us referencing Frasier was, no, hold on, his problem was, oh, everyone does that.
And he was just now, he was afraid that he literally said every comic act that comes to the net.
I'm saying fucking U2 comes here and plays at Bugaboo.
What's the, what's the thing that they do?
Bugaboo?
What's the thing that they do at the Bumber shoot?
Is that here?
You two plays at Bumber shoot and they're like, all right, here we go.
Uno, dos, tres, catorce.
Hey baby, I hear the blues.
Get it you fucks.
That was you guys.
You guys were Frasier.
This is a true story I heard that the dog from Frasier was notorious for killing cats at the studio.
There was a wrangler who had to stop him from killing cats on studio grounds.
I like to think if a dog reaches a certain level of celebrity, they can fucking kill as many cats as they want.
Better question, why were there so many cats at that studio?
Seemed like he was doing a service.
That dog had Alf's rider.
Just like, I only need six cats.
What did you put?
Nice.
So this is an advice show.
Are there any people?
I'm just going to try to see.
Are there any people, please raise your hands if they haven't listened to My Brother, My Brother and Me before?
And we'll try to hear the sounds of your fucking hands going up because we definitely can't see you.
Yeah, I can see you.
I heard some armpits deploy.
This is, if you are familiar with Dear Abby, it's basically like that.
It's an advice show and that's.
With an irreverent twist.
With an irreverent, we bring our own twisted view, our own skewed perspective to every, anyway.
I have green eyes and stranger always compliment them.
They'll say something like, your eyes are so pretty.
And then they'll say, you must get that a lot.
I never know how to respond.
Just saying, thank you or I do get that a lot.
Sounds conceited.
How do I respond to these compliments?
Do I compliment them back?
And that's from Gmail.
Justin, I want to say first that I really enjoyed your wistful reading of, you have such nice eyes.
Like the rest of the sentence is, my eyes are so bad.
Would it kill you to shoot some of that our way from time to time?
We've known each other for a while now.
You haven't said word one about these peepers.
Wait, look at me grooving?
Dreamy.
Thank you.
Justin?
They're fine.
I'll just be here.
They're functional.
Oh, sorry.
Super good.
Thank you.
Are you here, green eyes person?
That's a lie.
That's a lie, isn't it?
That took way too long.
Was that a pity woo?
I don't want them to be awkward.
Somebody out there has green eyes and they're like, this is my moment.
Did I get super drunk and right into an advice podcast?
Was that me?
Can I just say, I personally love the move of going, thanks, I get that a lot.
That's a power move.
You have great eyes.
I know.
So do you at seeing my great eyes.
How observant of you to notice those must be fully functional peepers you got because
they have definitely observed the masterpiece that I have going on here between brow and
nose.
There's got to be like just a reusable phrase you can use for like, well, thanks.
I've been growing them.
No, here's the joke.
This is the joke that I use when I get any compliment, like nice hair, which I get a
lot.
This fucking whoa, we're not deep enough into this show.
Sexy.
Wow.
This is the response.
Thanks.
I've been working out, but you have to say it like this.
I didn't say it right.
Hold on.
Let me do the delivery better.
But like more natural than that.
You put a little Mike Myers stink face on it.
I know it's funny too.
And then by that time, hopefully the elevators opened and you can escape.
Yeah, sure.
Holy shit.
Quick sidebar.
Can we talk about that number one dude we met in the elevator last night?
We were on the first floor of our hotel last night in Portland and we're first floor and
we were going up some Portland people that came up to this show.
That's like 70% of the fucking audience.
No one actually lives in Seattle.
They just like apparently truck in.
I commute for my comedy podcast.
We're on the first floor.
We had just gotten back from the show last night.
Super late.
We were all super tired.
The door opens up and we're going to the sixth floor and there's a dude just in it.
And we were like, hey, he's like, this is going down.
It was like, I assure you we're on the bottom of this building.
There's no more building.
So then the door closes.
The door closes because we're all very like passive people.
And then opens again.
It opens again.
He's like, oh, I guess it's going up now.
Like, yeah, we fucking hacked it.
Up, up, down, down, up, down, up.
And then you can change the direction of the elevator.
He did not say, I guess it's going up now.
He said it's going up now as if we ruined it.
Like he was trying to play it off as, oh, no, no.
I did go downstairs.
Made no mistake.
I took care of what I needed to take care of.
I did that downstairs and now I'm going up.
You lost track of time.
And then he got off the elevator.
Where were you going?
What was in the basement for you, sir?
I've got a boiler I'm excited about.
There was a woman when Teresa and I got there and we got on the elevator to go to her room.
We got there in our bags and this woman, apropos like we press the button, it's silent.
She just turns to us and goes, consider this your Portland welcome.
And then turn back.
And then we got off the elevator and said, thanks.
I feel so welcome now.
Do you remember what the dude's shirt said?
Because that was the best part.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it was professional sports?
It was professional championship.
Professional championship.
Two words.
She's like, cool.
Okay, wait.
Imagine in your mind a man in a shirt.
Do you have it?
We'll give you a moment.
Imagine his shirt has two words on it.
They are in this order, professional championship.
Okay?
That's someone who's hedging their bets.
It's so kind of something.
Because sports or business are both sports business.
I think we answered the question.
Calculate off.
I think we helped as best we could.
Yeah.
Does anybody here want a Yahoo answer?
Good.
If you're new to the show, sometimes people, I was going to say we'll get Yahoo answers
to the show, but that's just not true.
People get them for us.
Like Rachel Sperling, game recognized game.
Rachel Sperling, are you here?
Yeah, it would be concerning if you weren't.
Because you told us you were going to be, yeah.
Recognize the game.
This is Rachel's like seventh live show with us.
And she just knows to stand up and wave because we'll make her do it if she does.
Recognize that game.
Griffin, what's the Yahoo?
Just got a nice text from my wife.
What's it say?
No, don't worry about it.
Travis Stone, it's private.
Rachel Sperling sent this in.
Thank you.
There's a thousand people here.
It's by Yahoo answers user, Happy Equine, who asks.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're doing that.
This is one of them.
Happy Equine asks, desensitization, balloons?
Go ahead.
Desensitization, balloons?
So, this is longer than our usual fare.
Buckle up.
So I wanted to start desensitizing my horse.
I brought out a bag of potentially scary things to see what we would need to work on throughout the next few weeks.
There was a shiny banner that he was great with.
I could cover his eyes and wrap it around him, toss it, run around with it so it flapped, etc.
Then I moved on to a large plastic flag.
He was pretty nervous, but after about 15 minutes, I was able to rub it on him, put it on his face, etc.
You need some more, Dennis.
By the end of the day, I was even riding with it, WTC.
What does that mean?
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
One person.
Walk, chalk, cancer.
Holy fucking shit.
We got a couple of horse heads in the audience.
Well, they're probably not called horse heads.
Okay, wait.
Hang on after the show because I've got a lot of questions.
I've been talking a lot of horse bullshit for a while.
I need to know, is that so common a thing that you had to shorten it to save what?
That's, yeah.
You've got a lot.
Listen, you're a horse trainer.
WTC saves one syllable.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll talk after the show.
Okay, listen.
We'll exchange business cards.
Yeah.
Mine says my brother, my brother, and me.
Right.
Okay, listen.
We know jack shit about horses, but we talk about them.
If you're a horse trainer, and I cannot imagine there are so many different levels that walk,
chalk, canter is just like, that's just step one.
That's like 5% of it.
What else is this horse doing?
I know horses.
They just don't bite you, and then they walk, chalk, canter.
That's it, right?
That's like the whole thing.
I almost said triage, but I know that's not it.
Dressage?
What the fuck?
There it is.
Okay, all right.
I knew it wasn't triage.
I want that on the record.
Horses are good at knowing who would die first in a horrible accident.
Will he survive?
Nay.
Please finish the question.
Okay, this woman rubbed a fucking flag on a horse for a while.
A lot of this question is about rubbing flags on horses.
Then came the scary thing, balloons.
I was slowly introducing it to him.
My horse spooks mostly at sounds, so I was practicing with noises.
I would simply let out the air, and he went crazy.
After no improvement, which he had quickly had with the other objects,
I tried different sounds with the balloon.
Everyone made him so scared, just very scared, so I stopped,
not wanting to scare the bad gibbies out of him.
Sorry, I fucked that up.
Without wanting to scare the bad gibbies out of my poor boy.
Anyways, how can I get him used to these noises without terrifying him?
I will only do a little bit at a time so I don't overwhelm him,
but what are some of your ideas?
It does not sound like that is the case at all.
Yeah, it sounds like you put this horse through a gauntlet,
a day-long gauntlet of error.
You're a fucking Marquis de Sade of order.
What about these?
He's French.
Yeah, sure.
Most Marquis are.
I'd wager, maybe.
I don't know.
Anything.
How important is it that when you're training a horse,
how important is it that it be completely without fear?
Is that the ideal?
If you're on it, probably pretty important.
Super important.
That's what they're teaching.
They're not working on anything other than,
I want this horse to be the horse without fear.
No, I like this idea, though.
Like you got a horse.
That's good.
Pretty good.
You should keep doing that one for the rest of the day.
Nice.
That was a peach of a joke.
In tandem.
Here's the thing.
I guess what's most confusing to me is this idea of a fixer-upper horse.
If you get the horse and it's not immediately good
at whatever you need it to be good at,
and you're like, but I'll desensitize it.
How about you just don't make that horse do that thing?
Like it's not good around balloons.
That's how the horses cross the bear.
Yeah.
When God made horses, he was like, these things are perfect.
I got to do at least one.
Hey, hey, come in here.
Check out this horse.
Check out this awesome thing I made.
Nailed it, right?
Yeah, it's pretty good, right?
All sinewy and perfect and perfect.
Super good.
This is my day.
This is really good.
I should make it like super afraid of one thing.
How about balloons?
They won't have to deal with it for, I don't know, like 3,000 years.
How long have horses been around?
200 years.
Trainers?
Oh, got you there.
Where are horses and balloons even interacting?
They're not allowed at Times Square during the ball drop.
Where they drop balloons?
Never mind.
Maybe like a cart that delivers balloons to someplace.
You show up to like a Flaming Lips concert with a horse,
they're like, nope, turn around.
Others are very upset.
No one was more excited about the invention of the automobile
than balloon salesmen.
Finally, a calm drive.
Finally, a way to get these from A to B
without it being a whole thing.
So many balloon salesmen died from going over cliffs
in runaway carts.
Slow down, Brutus.
I am actively labeled as the hipster
in any of the various friend groups that I have.
My friends expect me to only appreciate bands
that they've never heard of.
While yes, I do have some obscure tastes.
I also have a pretty profound love for some modern pop artists.
When my friends or acquaintances hear me getting down
with the latest club banger,
they assume I'm listening to it ironically and mock me for it.
How do I convince my friends to stop throwing shade?
That's from subpar Seattle hipster, are you there?
Hey, word up.
I was hoping you'd be like, eh.
Can I give you some advice?
That's why you're here.
Stop using phrases.
Like modern pop artists?
Don't say that.
If you call it the latest club banger,
you are indeed listening to it ironically.
I don't know how to break it to you.
Here's a list of people who can use the term club banger
unironically.
Pitbull.
Holy shit!
Whoa!
Well, that's going to do it.
Travis, if you'd done that shit too, we could retire.
I'll do it now, we'll edit it in.
Pitbull.
The joke was that there wasn't another name after Pitbull.
That's it.
Even if Chingy was like, club banger, you're like, Chingy.
Chingy?
Stop it.
This is one of those problems where someone says,
hey, everyone thinks this about me, but they're wrong.
The problem, sorry to call you out,
but you're putting out something that makes everyone think that.
Maybe they know something, you don't.
Maybe you are listening to it ironically, so ironically,
even you don't know.
The deepest level of irony.
Yeah, you've crossed the Rubicon of irony.
Time to look in that deep, dark, truthful mirror and say,
do I really enjoy the new Carly Rae Jepsen album, Emotion?
Yeah, let's talk about Carly Rae Jepsen.
Indeed I do.
No, let's not.
I have heard that album straight through six times today.
We measured our J.
I asked Griffin, who was driving the whole way,
how far we were away when we were driving to Seattle today,
and he said, we're about one and a half Carly Rae Jepsen's emotions away,
because that's all we listened to the entire drive.
Our booking agent was backstage like, is that album really good,
or it's like people feel that way about me.
No, it was real good.
Making the most of the night, that was a good tune.
Run Away With Me is another really good Carly Rae Jepsen song.
Name one more really good Carly Rae Jepsen song.
Fucking Emotion, Favorite Color.
Yes, a bunch of favorite color fans out there.
I'm getting really sweaty again.
Yeah.
Do you guys want to Yahoo?
I feel like we didn't answer that question at all.
We didn't answer that question really.
Oh, man, but it's this question.
I'm very excited about it.
Okay.
Send in by Level9000.
Yeah, Drew Drew at Drew Davenport.
I'm so excited.
I read this one like a while ago.
I was like, no, we're saving this one for Seattle because they've earned it.
Because if anyone's going to get it, it's you freaks.
Seattle audiences are the best audiences in the world.
I've always heard that, Justin.
I've always heard that.
You know who told me that?
John Roderick.
Nobody rocks like Seattle.
Griffin, do you have a fucking question?
Please, we can't stall any longer.
Why were you on, please?
I've been a Yahoo diver for so long now that I know how the system works.
This person's name who asked this is anonymous, which means they're not anonymous.
They put anonymous into the name field.
It is anonymous, the group.
This is by the hacktivist group anonymous.
The hacktivist, the black hat hacktivist group anonymous asks,
if butterflies could speak for 24 hours, what do you think we could learn in those 24 hours?
We must know.
It's the only way.
Snowden leaning over his computer.
Ah, shit.
What if butterflies...
Oh, no.
What have I done?
I've been flying all day.
That's Amelie.
More or less.
Wait, no, I haven't said any fucking asses.
I've been visiting blossoms.
You know what I found inside your blossoms?
Secrets.
So Justin doesn't really...
I put the blossoms outside your house, Mr. President.
I've been out there with anonymous.
Fucking Snowden is Amelie.
Yeah, dude.
I just realized that.
I made Snowden small and shrunk him down the size of a butterfly.
He was Amelie.
He became Amelie, yeah.
That'd be a great movie.
You know...
Whoa.
Anyway, if butterflies could talk for 24 hours, what could we learn in those 24 hours?
Probably a lot of like B racial slurs.
Like ones we don't even know.
Like cool ones we're not even aware of.
All those honey butts.
Honey butts?
I didn't say they were nice or clever.
Can I just say that typically I don't use them, but racial slurs, typically not adorable.
This is from butterflies.
That's true.
Pollen suckers.
Is that good?
That's pretty good.
Well, butterflies pollinate, too, so that'd be...
Well, okay.
No one asked your opinion, fucking Bear Grylls.
Keep it to yourself.
Keep it to yourself, Jack Hanna.
Maybe butterflies should talk about how great it is to pollinate plants.
Oh, God.
I was all up in that daisy.
That daisy over there.
I got deep in her stamen.
Crush that stamen, that pistol.
Daisy's juicy.
God.
That's gross.
Those are bad two words.
I always like the assumption that if animals could talk, what would they say?
This idea of, like, they've got so much wisdom that I think most butterflies would just be going...
It's insane to think...
Okay, it's so human-centric to think that butterflies, could they talk?
Could really add anything to the human experience.
Like, they've probably got a lot of knowledge that's very specific to butterflies.
Oh, what's it all about?
Oh, man, I've been waiting to tell you.
Yeah, like, it's basically about I was a worm for a while, and then I squinched around,
and then my butt felt weird, and then I was in a coffin, and I was this.
I was like some soup in a coffin, I guess.
Yeah, some soup in a coffin, I don't know.
And I can't wait to see what's next.
What do I transform into next?
I don't know.
What's next for me?
I see big furry things walking around.
Really excited to try that out.
You big pink fucks, I would love to take a stab at one of you.
Whatever you tall people with glasses are.
That would be dope.
What if they only spoke Portuguese?
I have nothing for you, butterfly.
I do not speak Portuguese.
But it's that way, you got one day to get there, maybe catch a plane.
You can probably sneak onto a plane.
I'll take you in my bag.
Come with me.
I'll take it in my bag.
I'll fly to Portugal.
Be free.
Talk to you.
I bet butterflies.
Now hold on.
I want to live in the world in which a butterfly is just stable in the air in Griffin's carry-on
for the entire flight.
Just going, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Over there.
Portugal.
My home.
While I was in your backpack, I caught some Pokemon for you.
Remind me to turn my street pass on when we go back up stage, because I bet, yeah, my
fucking 3DS will just melt.
I bet butterflies, after they've transformed, are just insufferable.
Yeah.
They just think their king should have fucked down, I bet.
Oh, yeah.
You realize I was a piece of shit worm like a day ago.
Listen, baby.
I remember what it was like just being a worm, scooting around without looking at me.
I'm up here zooming around, soaring with the clouds.
I've got stained glass wings and a proboscis.
Why is Robert Evans a butterfly?
I remember when my wings first unfurled, and I thought, are these wings small?
But then I thought, it's how you flap them.
I'll tell you who loves wings.
Miss Judy Garland.
She was such a big fan.
She loved Two Things Booze and these beautiful flappers behind me.
Kept looking for a project to do together, never could work it out.
I only lived for 24 hours.
Well, I think they lived for a long time.
Super busy.
Okay.
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
You did not prepare us for this.
I just looked over at your computer and it was zoomed in and terrifying.
Ladies and gentlemen, this just in.
It's a haunted doll watch.
Boo.
This is hot across the wire.
This is coming in fast.
I'm just trying to get these details together as I can.
I just want you people in the audience to know and people at home, I will be spending
the entire time Justin is talking, trying to figure out which celebrity this doll reminds
me of.
It's a powerful witch named Ava.
It's a spirit vessel, EMV, EMP, very active, very powerful.
EMV and EMP?
Both of them, Griffin.
Yes, I'm just trying to get the details together.
We've got a description here.
Welcome, for your consideration, is a beautiful porcelain doll.
For the Academy Award for best spookiest doll goes to.
Best spookiest.
A spirit vessel and what an active spirit she is.
Ava is very independent.
She does things her own way.
Do not try to tie this haunted doll down.
She calls herself a wild woman, a witch, untamable as the wind.
This doll ghost, she inspires that aspect of our nature, reminding women to be strong.
Whoa!
To love ourselves.
No, that's fucking no, no, no, no, no.
That's fucking awesome.
That's awesome, right?
No, no, no.
Picture a woman looking at a haunted doll and going, you know what, you're right.
Yes.
I've been waiting for the, yes.
You know how I write.
You know what it is?
It's like, who's your inspirations woman?
Sally Radegas?
Who's yours?
A doll that lives in my house.
I did figure out who this doll looks like to me, by the way.
Excellent.
I bet on pins and fucking needles.
It's Geena Davis in Beetlejuice.
Yeah.
Yeah, I could see that actually.
For sure.
Anyway, she inspires that aspect of our nature to love ourselves.
She will not tolerate misogyny or bigotry.
It's a fucking cool doll.
She is a fierce protector, a healer, and she will bless your home with strength and protection.
She says it's time for her to move on, to grace another home with her presence and her magic.
That's with a K.
Who am I to argue?
That's the best part.
I'd love for you to kick it here for a while, but if you say so.
Steve, it's time for me to move on.
I've got to go inspire some other lady.
You know what, you're right.
You're right.
Yeah.
Maybe she doesn't want to go.
You have to punch her in the face like in Harriet and Henderson's.
What?
You weren't down here.
She is a fierce protector, a healer, who will bless your home.
Okay, who might argue, but I will miss her terribly.
Are you the one she's looking for?
Okay, I will miss her terribly.
There is a buy it now price at $59.99.
This is all I'm saying.
Listen, the new Call of Duty is coming out in a couple months.
I'm a little low on cash.
I've got to make my peace with the market forces.
I would love to trade my feminist power totem.
This doll is also shot literally like it looks like they held a flashlight under her chin.
She's super great.
And they take these pictures that have this like weird gold band across the front.
Like maybe that's a spirit.
I don't know.
I just think that's $60 real bad.
I feel it is time to find new homes for some of the spirit vessels I've collected.
This is the greatest short story I've ever heard in my life.
I feel like I do not have enough time to devote to working with all of them.
And it isn't fair to just keep them on the shelf.
This, okay, this guy or girl.
Yeah, you're just assuming.
This person.
Maybe it's a doll too.
Inception 2.
But their calling is to work with these vessels and they just got in over their head.
I've just got too many.
They don't have the time.
I need to cut Ava.
Sorry, Ava.
Your first quarter performance is a little disappointing.
Yeah, I don't know why she is stuck on JV and has to get sold on eBay.
Feel free to ask any questions you have.
I can provide additional pictures if you would like.
I will be listing other dolls soon if you would like to look at them as well.
As per eBay guidelines, I must say that this is for entertainment purposes only.
Oh, God.
eBay, can you not fucking give us like a minute of fantasy from this shit ass world?
You know what?
Seriously though, fuck eBay.
No, but seriously, fuck eBay because do you know what it says about their perception of you?
That they're like, listen, you have to clarify that you're not selling a literal ghost.
Like no fucking shit, eBay.
It's a ghost.
That's a crazy assumption for you to make because implicit in eBay's requirement for you to say this is for entertainment purposes only is a tacit endorsement of the existence of ghosts by eBay.
And not that your ability to buy and sell them.
Not even that.
That if ghosts do exist, they like to kick it in dolls.
They'll go where the doll goes.
Very easy.
I'm a ghost, okay?
When am I going to have it?
Wait, what?
I'm a ghost.
Am I going to have it like a stationary fake little human or like a bitch in Bugatti?
Wait, hold on.
We haven't checked haunted Bugatti watch.
Yeah, it's so sad Griffin died.
Yeah, it's pretty sad.
But he's inhabiting a Bugatti right now.
So he's actually pretty cool.
He's worth more now.
He's on the Pacific Coast Highway.
You can't catch him.
He's a very fast car now.
I believe it's time for audience.
That's what Tracy Chapman wrote that song about.
The song Fast Car, she had a friend, became a ghost, became a Bugatti in like 1980.
And we were driving, driving in my U.
I was in you, driving.
This is how fast car goes.
Good job, us in the past.
Good job, past us.
Boy, I wish present us were that good.
Feel a little off my game, traveling a little road hard and put down wet.
You know what'll help with that Griffin?
What's that?
It'll be Belgian waffles.
We should mention, Justin's not here.
We just got back from the tour that you're listening to now.
And it was a rough day of travel for most of us.
Yeah, a lot going on there.
A lot of slip ups, a lot of goof em ups.
We're home and in one piece, but that is why the episode is so late.
We're very sorry.
As long as we're busting out the bad news.
If you were really looking forward to hearing the energy that we could bring to a room in Portland.
Then, shitty news.
Because you won't.
That audio did not turn out great.
Didn't turn out great.
Well, two thirds of it did.
Two thirds of it turned out super good.
Somehow Travis's audio didn't come through at all.
Maybe we'll release that as like a really bad bonus episode.
Not for donors.
You deserve better than that.
But it's just like, hey, if you want to consume every bit of garbage and errata that we can put out there.
Then here, enjoy an episode where it sounds like Justin and I are talking to each other.
And also a ghost.
Now Griffin, you know what will help if people are sad about not being able to hear the Portland show.
They should do what I do.
Eat mini Belgian waffles?
Eat your feelings away.
Then you want to go to naturebox.com.
Naturebox offers lots of snack choices.
Like the mini Belgian waffles that I mentioned earlier.
Strawberry lemonade fruit stars.
Sweet and salty nut medley.
The Asiago cheese crisps.
Which are in fact my favorite.
There's all kinds of stuff.
And it's full of flavor.
But you won't find any junk in that box.
No junk in that trunk.
You know what I mean?
No junk.
No podcast episodes where you can't hear one third of the hosts.
I thought I was over it.
But apparently not entirely over it.
I had forgotten about it until you mentioned it.
Cool day.
If you would like to enjoy your first box of Naturebox snacks for free.
You just have to go to naturebox.com slash my brother.
And you get to try a box of their favorite snacks.
And then you're going to fall in love with it.
And just start ordering it from them.
So go to naturebox.com slash my brother.
And make that happen.
And after you've fallen in love with Naturebox.
You're also going to fall asleep.
You're not going to wake up from having a big bear tummy full of food.
Time to hibernate.
And the best way to do that is on a mattress.
Yep.
That is historically the best way for humans to get sleep.
I've got a mattress recommendation for everyone.
And it's Casper.
Who just so happens is our sponsor this week.
I sleep on Casper.
It's amazing.
I got it in the mail.
It came in a relatively small box.
Then you open it up.
And like some kind of future tech.
It turned into a mattress.
It went from a weird rolled up plastic thing to a mattress.
It was amazing.
You put three drops of water on it.
You said a little wish.
A little prayer.
And then your energy.
It expanded it.
Anyway, I want to tell you about Casper.
You go online. You buy it. They send it to you.
Like Travis said.
It's real little. And then it gets big.
And then it gets really comfy.
If you're unsold on this whole concept.
It's free delivery and painless returns.
After 99 days you say, you know what?
No.
Casper was a ghost.
And I find that a little too spooky to include in the bedroom.
I've got to get rid of it.
You can do that. You have 100 days to decide.
Right now you can get $50 towards any mattress purchase.
Because you listen to our show.
Just go to Casper.com slash my brother.
And use the promo code my brother.
All one word at checkout.
Terms and conditions do apply on that.
Not sure what that means.
But I do know as a hell of a mattress man.
We also want to say a special message to Lucretia.
This is from Maurice.
Maurice says,
Happy birthday to my wonderful girlfriend Lucretia.
You are 100% the best thing that has happened to me.
I love you.
Also, having a name like Lucretia spawns a lot of nicknames.
So, since she loves when you guys goof on a list.
Here are some of her nicknames.
Cretia.
Krish.
Lucky.
Lulu.
Lucretia.
And The Sugar.
I'm not sure why the list continued after Luda.
Or why there was anything that preceded Luda.
Because it's not even accurate, right?
Her name is not Luderisha.
Her name is...
I like The Sugar.
Because it sounds like a deceptively sweet assassin.
Yeah.
Her name is also spelled L-U-C-R-E-T-I-Z.
And...
And that's pronounced Lucretia.
Maurice has informed us.
I don't...
It seems like you can just sort of have your way with that though, right?
If that's my name.
If that's how I spell my name.
It's Lucretiz.
Oh, that's a really great, like, DJ name.
Hell yeah, it is.
You know what else is?
What?
Luda.
Got another message here that was sent in for Nazneen and Ian.
Or is that a lowercase L?
Maybe it's Lane.
Let's stick with Ian.
All right, Ian and Nazneen.
It's from Courtney and Kyle who say,
Congrats on your wedding, which we know we definitely had fun at.
You two are the greatest humans,
and what better way to tell you
than by letting the McElroy brothers do it for us.
The wedding was so great.
Yeah, I'm assuming they bought this message far in advance.
Which, by the way,
if you want to get up on our show and tag it,
then you gotta go to
jumbomfun.org forward slash jumbotron
and get your message in early.
Because we're booked up pretty
deep in advance, and
it's unfortunate, but that is
why Courtney and Kyle kind of had to roll the dice
on this one.
But happy wedding. I bet it was beautiful,
and I bet Courtney got a little too drunk.
Maybe, like, said some things
into the video camera.
No, no, no, no, no. Courtney locked it down.
Yeah? Do you think she started the dancing?
I think she started the dancing.
I think she was stone cold sober when she did it.
I think she was in full, like,
sound mind and body.
Just, like, got up there and nae nae'd all the night long.
Just nae nae'd
and whipped?
Nope. Nobody whips anymore.
Everybody just nae nae's, and she nae nae'd
all night long. Even during the slow songs.
Even during the father-daughter dance.
Excuse me, Courtney.
Could you just take a quick break?
Just a two minute? No? Okay, that's fine.
Put the breaks on it.
What other shit do we have to talk about?
Oh, big, big, big, big thanks to John Roderick.
John Roderick, you're the coolest dude ever
for doing our intro.
Just every week,
but also at the Seattle live show specifically.
That was a real treat for us.
We also want to remind everybody
that we have another live show coming up.
If you're listening to this and thinking,
oh, I wish I could have been there.
I wish I could see them live.
We're doing a live show for My Brother, My Brother, Me
and the Adventure Zone at LA PodFest.
You're probably listening to this and thinking,
but I'm nowhere near Los Angeles,
and I don't want to go to that dump city.
Well, that's mean.
It's very mean of you, but that's fine.
We love it.
I love LA.
If you go to LAPodFest.com
and click on live stream,
the thing is, we're going to be live streaming
all the shows from LAPodFest.
You can watch them live.
You can watch us do My Brother, My Brother, Me
and the Adventure Zone live from anywhere.
LAPodFest.com, click on live stream,
use the coupon code BROTHER or ZONE
and you can watch them along with all the other shows.
The greatest thing is this,
you don't even have to be at your computer
at the time when the shows happen.
They're going to archive it for a month.
You have 30 days to catch it.
It's a great deal.
Use the coupon code BROTHER and ZONE.
It saves you $5 and it helps support our show.
We love it.
Hi, I'm Lisa Hanawalt.
And I'm Emily Heller.
And if you're not listening to our podcast Baby Geniuses,
you're missing out on stuff like...
Who's like, would you ever go to a friend
and you're like, hey, could you
lick all these envelopes for me?
You'd be like, you're a serial killer.
Definitely, I'm leaving right now.
It was just a great moment of like,
oh no, I'm here, boys.
I'm on this side of the bench.
Just feel like they're always in character.
Like, they're always in character
as like, cool hipster girl.
And I just want to
break through that barrier.
Plus, every week we explore a new Wikipedia page
and talk to a crazy expert in the field of nonsense.
Well, any hack
can make you not have a boner.
I mean, it's about how you do it.
And we're the only podcast
with regular updates about Martha Stewart's pony
or your money back.
We're not going to give them their money back, are we?
No. Let's keep it.
Listen to our show every other Monday
on Maximum Fun.
Yay!
Should we throw it to the audience
for questions?
I believe we should.
So, from time to time in our live shows,
we throw it to the audience to get some questions
from you.
Can we get house lights?
There is one rule.
I don't know what that rule is.
No bummers!
That's correct. No bummers.
You can't all yell it at once.
Just you, horse trainer.
She doesn't know the rule. It's no bummers.
It's actually emblazoned.
If you forget, actually we have a helpful
mnemonic device.
Our friends at Ear Trumpet Labs in Portland
made us a microphone.
It's a Josephine model mic you can see before you.
It is emblazoned with the words
no bummers.
It's actually engraved on there
in case you forget.
Should we get a little bit more house?
Super duper can't see.
Who feels
that they have a great question
short,
fun, no bummers?
Breezy? Right here.
Right there.
Yes, you. Stand up.
Right there. Yes, you.
Come on down.
We pointed
at somebody last night in Portland
and three people started to walk down
like no. We almost left the stage.
You can do it. Oh shit, we didn't think
about this. Just scooch. Scooch.
These two kind people right here
are going to let you pass. It's like a whole
thing. Scooch.
Perfect. Come on down to Josephine.
Our mic. I'm not scooching.
Okay. Hi. Hi.
Hi. Yeah, go ahead and move that out. Yeah,
it's good. I like your initiative. Thank you.
What's your name? Summer.
Hi, Summer. What's up? Well, I'm here.
Is that good
or bad? You said it ain't no bad.
It's pretty good so far.
Nice. Well, I like that you left
the window open in case we tank at the end.
So far, I don't
want to say.
Okay, so my question is I'm
babysitting my dog up at college right now
while my parents are moving.
And I'm wondering... Your dog's
just dog sitting.
Dog sitting. Yeah, he's my family's dog.
Cool. His name is Jack.
That doesn't matter. It does to me.
Hold on. We don't know what matters yet.
You haven't finished the question.
Your question could be what do you think of his
name?
So I'm wondering if I have
like a guy over, is it okay
to engage in
intercourse in front of my dog? What?
This is a family show.
You know what I love about the summer, can I say?
What I love about this
is how much you
narrowed it down to that one factor.
Like it's a binary
decision. The dog's there.
Does that change things?
It doesn't
sound to me like it does.
I feel like we need to know everything
about this dog.
Yeah, my first question is can this
dog chill or what?
He's chill. He's a German
Shepherd.
He's only four years old.
Well, hold on.
Hold on. Dog years, he's at least
24, maybe 28.
I think right now he's about 32.
Oh man, if he doesn't know about this then.
He's seen some shit.
Please, Travis.
Tell me the age at which it's cool
for your dog to watch you fuck.
Please tell me that
number.
Three.
That sounds bad.
That sounds so bad. There's not an age
where it's like, oh, he's a 27
year old? Then by all means
have him watch or have sex.
If he's old enough to drive away and go do
something else.
He's a dog. Can you explain? That's his
fault. Yeah.
Lot of variables.
What's the layer? Is it a studio
apartment?
Does he have another room to go to if he doesn't
feel comfortable? Yeah.
I'm going to be in the basement
summer. He's in the
bedroom. Why?
Close the damn door.
Is this a fucking Frank Lloyd Wright
house in which there are no walls and doors?
Because if so, you have an issue.
If not, simple solution.
I think he's asleep.
This is my new house.
Summer.
The issue you're asking is, is it okay
if I like the fact that my dog watches me
have sex? Yeah, that's the real question.
Is there more house?
Is he a
raptor from Jurassic Park and he's figured out
how to open doors?
Is he smart? He's too damn smart.
He's kind of dumb.
Okay. Cool.
Then put on cartoons in the living
room. Let him have a great
time. I just don't want to leave him
unsupervised.
That's fair, yeah. Because you're setting
such a good example so far.
Travis!
Love it. Listen.
Love making is...
Or just fucking whatever it is.
It's beautiful no matter what.
Just some good old natural fucking.
You know what? I say go
for it. And then point
at him and do this.
No. Travis is now pointing
at his eyes and pointing
and I'm assuming what is
the dog's eyes.
Now, Travis, that is equally upsetting
if you're saying, hey dog, I'm watching you
or hey dog, watch this.
That's a good one.
Let me show you how it's done.
I'm sorry Summer, but thank you so much for coming
out. Thank you.
Alright, let's see.
Let's see.
Who else has got a slam dunk question?
Let's go right to it.
You in the glasses.
Yes, yes, with the yes.
Yes.
I see there that you're holding a poster.
Or you were holding a poster.
It's this poster here.
I hope it's our poster.
It was made by Emily Carroll and it's beautiful
and amazing and it's my favorite thing ever.
And it's affordably priced.
Hey, what's up?
What's your name?
My name is Rosh.
What's up?
You know.
Are you enjoying the show?
You know it's rough?
I do know, dude.
The show is great.
Top notch.
Is it the best show you've ever seen?
Shut up.
Are we doing all shows?
Podcasts?
So I have an etiquette question.
We're good at that.
So I have this pet peeve when people say
excuse me, but you're nowhere near them.
You know what happens all the time?
People are just like, oh, excuse me.
You're standing outside the bathroom, but you're not in the way.
And they're like, excuse me.
And then they just walk by.
And it's like, why the fuck did you say excuse me?
I'm not even in your way.
And I find it insinuating as if I'm just loitering outside.
So do I say no?
Or do I say yes?
No, now, Rosh,
can I tell you right now? I do that.
And the reason is, excuse me,
as a placeholder for this, I'm awkward
just being around people.
Just like, oh, I didn't think
a human would be here. Excuse me.
And all you have to say is, I get it.
Yeah.
There's a, I think,
when this happens, those people are using
excuse me
in the Japanese style.
Because the Japanese sumimasen
could be used for
literally anything.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Good morning. Happy birthday.
Welcome home.
Excuse me. Happy birthday. I'm sorry.
It's a
it's a power word.
And I think that might just be how I
It's a power word? Like a Fremen power word?
Like a Tovahkiin
shout.
Should I say it back then to assert dominance?
Excuse me.
No, excuse me.
You are excused.
I don't know.
Is this the thing? Am I crazy?
No, it definitely happens.
Well, hold on. Two aren't mutually excusable.
It is a thing.
I don't know if you're crazy. We just met.
Fair enough.
Maybe just say excuse me
longer than they did and louder.
Just say excuse me right back.
Excuse me.
What if you just said okay.
Silence.
No, Rosh. Silence.
Let it hang there.
Let them take the next step.
What's their follow up play?
What else they got in the tank?
Excuse me. I beg of you.
Please.
I need this.
I can't die until you excuse me.
I've been trapped in this loop for a hundred years.
Please, my spirit, Rosh.
Excuse me.
Does that answer your question?
Perfect.
I hope I could help.
You.
Yeah.
Hey, what's up?
I'm going to regret this.
Oh, cool.
What a start.
Sounds like we might also.
Proposal.
What's your name?
Casey.
Casey, you know the rule, right?
It's like on the mic.
It is.
And that's going to fit your question, right?
Yes.
It's happened a couple times.
Okay.
I've classically conditioned myself
to have to go to the bathroom at certain locations.
Nice.
For example, I was hired at a new job
every day for six months since then.
I had to go to the bathroom when I entered
because I smelled it and I had to go to the bathroom.
What?
That's why human bodies work?
It happened at Target and it happened at the library
at my university.
How can I not do this?
Let me understand this.
Your sense memory.
I told you I would regret this.
Your sense memory
of Target
is so powerful
that when you walk into Target,
your body must shit.
Number two.
You see that commercial
with the weird old lady and the Jack Russell Terry
and you're like, excuse me.
I'm afraid I must excuse.
I must wait to the loo.
I told you I would regret this.
You see people shooting arrows
at Targets and you're like,
pardon me for a moment, if you will.
If that were a toilet.
You said Target work
at the library.
Is that an Isaac Mizrahi?
Excuse me for a moment.
I will be back in exactly 37 seconds.
How can I not?
You said you were conditioned.
No, I'm sorry. It's going to be one of those questions.
It seems like classic conditioning.
Were you given a candy every time you left the bat?
Good job, Casey.
I don't know.
Open your mouth.
Did you get yourself to an icy at the Target Cafe?
It was probably
popcorn and a hot dog. Let's be real.
Wait, you say a hug or hot dog?
Hot dog.
Okay, much different than what I thought was happening.
Casey, there's only one way.
You got to eventually just once go to Target
and not shoot a duke.
Psychologically, shoot a duke at Target
and then punish yourself.
You start to associate it as a negative.
You shoot a duke and then go like,
Bad Casey.
Can I just stop?
Shoot yourself with a spray bottle.
I want to stop the world real quick because
take a shit at a Target and then punish yourself
is definitely the craziest
advice we've ever given anyone.
100.
This is what, like 268?
Yeah, we broke the world.
Definitely.
Go shit at a Target
and then hurt yourself
100% the craziest
thing anyone's ever told anyone to do.
I'm going to need to trade you advice
for a poster.
51 shades of gray
go shit at that Target
and then hurt yourself.
Are you
going to be there? Nope.
Just chain yourself to a wall
as soon as you walk in Target.
I can't be trusted.
You take this key no matter how much I beg.
You to please let me shit
your toes, but no matter
what I say, I'm going to be a wild animal
and I'm going to try to trick you with manipulation.
You can't listen to me.
Just please don't let me use the bathroom.
Oh, by the way, you have to leave here overnight.
Could you put
Harry Potter on all the screens or something?
The whole series,
please. I can't just have two hours
of entertainment.
Are you doing okay?
We've been going
all the hog up here.
Just tell me we helped.
Thank you.
Let's get one more.
Casey, your question made me lightheaded.
It was so good.
I already picked one.
All right.
Let's go back on the left.
You shaking your hand the most vigorously.
Nope. To the right. To the right.
You're not going to stand up.
It's the guy standing up then.
No.
While the shape in the back
makes their way down, we'll do your question.
Keep coming up.
We can knock yours out in 10 seconds.
This is going to be an easy one.
I feel it.
Go and go.
What's your name? My name is Noah.
Noah?
You better hurry, Noah.
He's coming.
Here comes the wind to go.
Just wait.
Walk super slow. Noah, hit me.
Last year, my wife and I had our first child.
This doesn't feel like it's going to be a breezy one.
No, it's going to take forever.
I love her to pieces.
She's smart. She's cute.
The child.
My wife also, but yes, my child.
We're talking about a second kid.
Honestly, I'm concerned that my first one
is my absolute favorite.
I will never love anybody more than her.
Is it worth it to
one and done, we get a score, hold on one,
or go for the second and see if we can...
Hey, future Noah,
you're listening to this episode with your kids,
who are now seven and five.
Maybe turn it off 30 seconds ago.
Yeah, Noah,
if you were wondering whether or not
you can have a second kid, you have just
sealed that deal for yourself, and the answer is
no, you can't, because we will put this
on the internet and they will hear it.
And the internet is forever.
The internet is forever, we hope.
Is that all there, kid? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure you will.
Listen, I'm no scientist, but yeah.
The chances of you going, you're not as good
as whatever first baby's name is,
hopefully you know what it is, but
you're not going to do that,
maybe in your dark times,
maybe in your quiet times,
but you're not going to do it actively all the time.
Just go for it?
Yeah, dude, go for it.
Have that baby.
That is the second time
we've done a live show, we have created
a human being by giving somebody
permission to have a child. Hey, what is up?
Am I good?
Because that guy's question was for real.
Well, how good is your question?
I love my two kids
so, so much.
I hate the third.
The fourth is okay, but fuck the fifth.
But the sixth one though?
Anyway, what's up? What's your name?
My name is Sam. Hi, Sam.
My question cannot possibly compare.
Yeah, great. Probably.
Mine is probably one of the more Seattle questions.
Cool beans. You've come to the right place.
Hello, Seattle!
Yeah! Scramble bags!
All over my face.
So, recently
I have moved into a home
where I am living with my brother-in-law.
Cool, cool.
And this guy has the hook up to some dank
kush.
Oh, cool, cool, cool!
Now that is marijuana?
Right. Yeah.
So, here's the thing. I'm a man of loyalty.
Cool. Okay.
For four or five years or so, I've been going to the same guy.
What's his name?
We're good. We're good here.
Let's just call him Weed Josh.
I'm a cop.
That's all I needed.
Best weed name ever. Go ahead.
We got him.
Kicking Weed Josh's door.
And what would you say are your greatest strengths, Weed Josh?
Low prices.
You're hired!
I like how comfortable you're getting with that microphone, Sam.
I'm making myself a home.
You're making love to it.
If your question is
I have too much access to weed,
I'm going to John Cena dive off
this stage and tackle you.
I can't imagine
what a cross that is to bear.
Get the John Cena music ready
because we might need it.
But what's your question for real, though?
So, I guess for real, it's like
how do I let Weed Josh know, like
I don't need his dank.
I don't need to drive fifty miles to get it.
Is it the distance?
That's a big factor.
That fools fifty miles from you?
I played baseball with this guy.
We grew up together.
He gives me the deals, but
But you have to drive to fucking Olympia to get your
Is your worry,
Sam, is your worry that Weed Josh
will see you smoking and go,
but I haven't seen him in three...
Hey.
That's not my purple
strain of sticky.
I thought we were bugs.
Weed Josh is
very clever.
Weed Josh sounds awesome.
Weed Josh is on his shit.
Let me ask you a question.
Is Weed Josh like a real friend?
You know, we've been around.
No, he's not.
He's not going to be like one of my like
groomsmen or something.
Not with that attitude.
How did you meet
Joshua? Well,
you know how high I am
right now.
It's because of that. He did that for me.
I, um...
Okay.
Earlier in the show,
we told a lady to shit at a target
and beat herself.
Now, keeping that in mind,
you saying
that someone who sells drugs
is going to have a hard time finding
other people to buy drugs
is the craziest thing I've ever
heard on this show.
To be fair... What am I going to do with
all these? But I got all these
extra drugs lying around.
They're just going to
spoil. They're going to go rotten.
Had to throw
them out.
Am I too nice? Yeah, bro.
You smoke that much weed? Like, what's going
on? Is it the dankness or is it the distance
that's really throwing you off? Wait a minute.
What if I have a solution?
I fix this for you. Smoke twice
as much weed.
Oh, hey.
Thank you, Sam. Yeah, we crushed it.
Hey, listen. Seattle, you've been
super-duper nice to us. Thank you so much.
Yeah, this has been a fucking good show. Thank you very much.
I'm not scared anymore.
Can I also just say... I'm not
scared anymore.
People at the back,
at the very back of the top of the
balcony, I think I love you most of all.
We want
to say a huge thanks to the Moore
Theater. It's been super nice being here.
Yeah, super, super cool. Peter's amazing.
Definitely, definitely haunted.
They got us some really good seafood, and it was delicious.
Thank you to Billions, which is our
booking company. They put this together for us. Our guide
Josh is here. He drove
all the way. We literally
would not be here if it weren't for Josh.
We wouldn't be a lot of places.
Thank you to Ear Trumpet Labs that made
our Josephine model microphone down
there. The No Bummer special.
Big thanks to Saw Bones
for getting things started real right.
I don't know that we've ever mentioned
it before, but John Roderick does our
theme song.
Too true,
Travis. Too true.
We really appreciate him and
the long wind. We've got posters
by Emily Carroll. They're special for
this tour. They're gorgeous.
They're out in the lobby. They're 10 bucks.
This one. It's really pretty.
Her signature's actually in the smoke.
It's a detail you may have missed.
That's our seasonal.
We're a member of the Maximum Fun Podcast Network
without whom none of this
would ever have happened to us. We're super thankful to them.
Maximumfun.org
is the place to find the best podcasts in the world.
Finally, I want to say a big
thank you, and you may not have seen this coming,
to you.
You've been
so nice to us.
I think that's it. Thank you to everybody who came out
to the Pacific Northwest shows.
Is Vancouver the Pacific Northwest?
It's not. They call it Pacific Southwest.
Do they really? They do.
We want to say thanks again
to NatureBox, where you can order
hundreds of great-tasting healthy snacks.
You can go to naturebox.com slash my brother to sign up
for a free sampler box of great-tasting healthy
snacks. We also want to say thank you
to Ear Trumpet Labs.
They provided some really
amazing microphones for the tour,
including a beautiful...
We talk about it in the show, but a beautiful
audience mic that is emblazoned
with the words, no bummers.
We really, really appreciate it, and we wanted
to say thank you. Yeah, thank y'all.
I think that's it. Let's throw it back to
us to wrap shit up.
Next week will probably be a regular
episode, I imagine. We'll save the Vancouver
show for when we're traveling to
LA, I guess.
We'll talk to y'all soon.
I think Griffin has
one more Yahoo that we're going to think about
and answer next week. Shit.
What do you got for us?
...
It's by Yahoo
answers user, Delta.
Who has a zero percent score?
No best answers. He's trying
his best.
He's new. He only started
June 15th. I got this.
No hits so far,
Delta. Going
a little long talking about
Delta.
Delta asks,
I like space
and dinosaurs?
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy. I'm Griffin McElroy.
This has been my brother and brother. Make kids are damn
square on the left.
...