The McElroy brothers are not experts,
and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert,
but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only
so the babies out there will know
how cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
It's the start of something beautiful.
A small acquaintance has blossomed,
it's ripened into a precious friendship.
I could have never seen what was coming for me.
Hangs at the skate park, hangs by the beach.
My life, it feels like
Life, ah, it's better, it's better with you
My life, ah, it's better, it's better with you
This is true, ah, it's better, it's better with two
My life, ah, it's better with you
This is my clear chair.
Let's talk about the chairs for one second.
We have, everyone agrees, the most visually boring show
that you could possibly go see,
and someone took the agency to give us some artistic chairs.
This is a first.
We have these beautiful clear chairs.
They're beautiful, and it has spiced up the show visually.
Hi, very welcome, my brother.
My brother, me and my show for the modern era.
I would say Cold Lucite.
And I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
And I'm your middle brother, Travis McElroy.
Et cetera.
And I'm your sweet, were you really?
Were you really about to start this show after your introduction?
Feels on brand, doesn't it?
It does a little bit.
I'm your sweet baby brother in 30 Under 30 Media,
Luminary Griffin McElroy.
Paul, help, I'm not on the wifi, Paul.
You gotta help me.
Can you help me?
Help me, I'm not on the wifi, Travis.
Help me, bud.
I will admit, this is not the reception I was expecting.
Yeah, let's take a second to talk about it.
I would actually like to recognize our,
if we could actually get house lights on,
on the house lights, if those could come.
Not the balcony, though.
Not the balcony.
Turn the balcony off.
No, no, no, no, no.
You need to know about the balcony.
Yeah, it is them.
Continue the sort of like Kevin McCallister tableau
of human beings and the balcony sort of linked up
by strings and pulleys.
If you were at our previous Detroit show,
I would like you to please stand and be recognized
for your valor.
You have all given so much for your country.
This day of all days is important.
Wait, is there lightsabers?
Thank you, some lightsabers.
People repping the Star Wars show.
Bold.
Okay, make them go away.
We were talking.
Bye.
Too scary.
Keep going.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
See, we can send jokes out of the room for a second.
This is about the same number we had at that show.
I do think we have, I mean, I think you can say safely this way,
we have demonstrably reduced our audience draw
in the city of Detroit, Michigan.
Oh, honey, they're coming again.
Are we going to go see that show?
Oh, yeah.
Probably talk about Babylon 5 or some nerd shit, babe.
And so perhaps never more applicable than it is now,
like the Chilean miners, we've reemerged from that disaster
to be here with you.
Oh, maybe you're...
I still think of that as a good day
because I saw Endgame afterwards.
Yeah.
Or no, Infinity War.
Infinity War.
Yeah.
No, I saw Endgame after eating too much
at a Brazilian steakhouse.
Okay.
That's how I'll always remember it.
What do you think of Endgame?
Too full.
If you're a new fan of ours,
and maybe you don't know what we're talking about
with all this Star Wars stuff,
one time we came to Detroit to do a Star Wars show
and it kicked so much ass.
It was such a kickass show.
We definitely didn't bail out super quick on the bit.
Yeah.
Definitely one of us didn't bail out instantly
for which the other two of us were actually pretty angry
the next day.
Travis.
No, what?
What?
Yes, because I'm the one known for bailing
on a not funny thing.
It's been lost to history.
We published that episode.
Sorry, was my propensity for not doing things
that aren't funny just used against me as a criticism?
Justin, it was your original idea.
It was your fucking idea, dude.
You tweeted it without consulting anyone.
Okay.
What I'm saying is if the richest man in the world
can do a dumb thing that he doesn't think through,
I should be allowed to do it too, right?
Thank you.
Otherwise, it's classist.
It's rich dad, poor dad, podcaster.
You gotta have the mentality.
We were talking about this backstage
because that was also the first tour
that our business manager, Amanda,
who is really the backbone of this organization,
went on with us, and so we were like,
hey, welcome to the company.
We blew it.
We fucked up so bad.
And we were talking about the next morning
on our way to the airport, we took a Lyft,
and it was like a sedan.
So it was like driver, Amanda, all three of us together
like we were on a road trip with our parents.
What the fuck was wrong with you last night?
What was that?
And after that show,
we changed the way we did live shows forever.
We changed the format.
No more themes.
You know, we're having fun now,
but I do not wish on any of you
the feeling of sitting in front of 2,000 friends
and realize you're dying.
You're dying, and there's no force on earth
that is gonna make that timer go any quicker.
Not even the force, as it turns out.
I do, now that it's been four years,
I do just want to apologize to the people who were there.
You did not get a good show, but...
You got a great show.
You got a weird show.
For everyone else on the planet,
it's funny that that show happened to you.
But that show happened a long time ago
in a theater that was here, so that part doesn't work.
But we've grown.
We've grown.
Except in terms, again, as Justin demonstrably stated earlier,
of audience following.
Ability to sell tickets here in Detroit.
Don't look at the balcony.
Let's go. Let's do the damn thing.
Oh, yeah, so we actually decided
to do the best show we've ever done to make up for it.
And that's the power of marketing.
How do I stop my coworker from...
Oh, it's also not too late.
If you have friends in the area who aren't here...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll keep the doors open.
We'll cut them a good discount.
You say, you ever seen...
No, okay, yeah, Amanda says no.
No discount, but they are welcome.
Say, you ever seen a comedy podcast show
from up higher in the theater?
And farther back?
It's just three guys at a table,
so you'll have to squint to see them,
but you'll love it.
How do I stop my coworker
from using the communal kettle to make hard-boiled eggs?
I'm not a person to keep someone from enjoying a breakfast meal,
but I use that same kettle she boils eggs in to make my tea.
That's from Agoraphobic in Ontario.
Welcome to America.
That question is weird enough
that I don't know what parts are Canada weird
and which parts are America weird.
There might be some parts that are Canada normal in there,
like making eggs at work.
Is it the communal kettle that's the problem?
I think just to sort of skirt this whole thing in the future,
it's illegal to bring ingredients to work.
Yeah.
Gone food and cold food are the only two.
The time you spend poaching an egg in the cafeteria
is time theft, I believe.
Right.
You are cooking now.
I just also want to say,
what type of person is the type of person
to stop someone from enjoying breakfast food?
That seems like a very specific thing that someone's into,
like, it depends on what kind of burrito it is.
The thing that really upsets me the most about this question
is that they're better cold.
Hard-boiled eggs?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why is this person not making them at home?
It's so easy.
Oh, they make them for the next day.
Oh, I'm going to be enjoying these come lunchtime.
You wait.
That's really where the friction's coming from.
It's that they can never make tea
because those eggs are always in there.
I like to make 45-minute eggs.
Why would you bring...
We've agreed that there should be no ingredients at work.
Why would you bring an ingredient
where there's a high likelihood you get to work
and make the noise,
oh, man.
Oh, no, all the eggs, man.
Okay, wait.
Justin and Griffin, which one's weirder?
Bringing a whole carton of eggs
or bringing just enough to eat that day?
A whole carton of eggs.
That's so many eggs.
Okay, but you're thinking about it, right?
Yeah, I am thinking about it
because if I'm going to make all hard-boiled eggs,
I'm going to make six.
I love those guys.
Right, so the idea of I brought a raw...
Yeah, a raw egg.
Oh, this?
I'm either going to eat it for lunch
or see if I can build a parachute
that will safely land it from a second story.
I'm going to eat it for lunch
or keep it alive for a week
to teach you about being a parent.
Because it's basically one and one.
Take it from three parents, babies, eggs, same.
Yeah, as long as you're not dropping babies are fine.
I would actually, in many ways,
rather drop a baby, but...
The egg, that's interesting.
Huh, we don't need to go into it.
I don't understand how they're getting the eggs to work.
That's all I can think about.
It's got to be hand.
It's got to be one egg and a hand.
I don't know, I trust...
If I can't see egg, it has squished already.
I think that this is the point
where you can go to the boss of this company and say,
hey, I think you're requiring this person
to get to work too early.
They don't have time to boil an egg in the morning.
Because if it's breakfast food, then it's like,
get to work, first thing you do,
pop on the kettle and boil an egg.
I want to talk more about means of egg conveyance.
And the armpit is the safest and it might hatch.
I would say maybe they're door dashing it.
I don't know if they got that Canada.
It's where they bring you things.
Like an egg?
Like one egg?
No, they get them door dashed every week
and the guy's like, ah, floor 12.
Yeah, send me on up, I got the eggs.
Hi Valerie, I'm here with your weekly eggs.
Man, I'd love a hard boiled egg right now.
If I've ever seen an example of why HR exists,
it is that.
I'm just like, hey, I don't mean to be a pain,
but Debbie is boiling eggs in the teapot.
I go, yeah, that's an easy fix.
I'll take care of this.
This one's fixable.
This one's easy.
There are some way more complex things we've had to deal with.
Don't boil eggs in the teapot.
I've got this one.
Hey, next white elephant gift exchange you do,
just throw a teapot in the mix.
It will solve the problem no matter who it ends up with.
Ideally, it ends up with the egg pervert
and then they can do their stuff at home.
Maybe that's it.
They're embarrassed.
They don't know where to buy it.
How does the water get this hot at work?
Jesus Christ.
Anybody notice the water gets so much hotter here at work?
It makes bubbles like there's a little guy under there
blowing water.
This is weird.
Guys, guys, check this out.
I put a raw egg in.
Well, watch this.
Peel it.
It does a goosh everywhere.
Not goosh, not chicken, hard.
What?
This only happens at work.
Call the science guy person.
You know, whatever the Canadian version of Bill Nye is.
That brief pause was all three of us
trying to think of a funny version,
Canadian version of Bill Nye coming up with Zilcho
and moving on.
William Nye was the best I had, and that wasn't it.
That's nothing.
I know.
I'm glad you didn't say that out loud.
So let's raise, we're going to raise the cultural bar
a little bit here in Detroit, home of culture.
Fancy is taking flight.
And I thought that maybe we would make things
just a little more adult
and discuss some works of fart.
I hate the stinger.
I hate the stinger for this bit so bad.
Griffin, this is tour manager Paul.
So if you've never heard...
Hold on, wait, Travis.
I've got some alts on that opening if you'd like.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, if you don't mind,
if you have one that the bit rate on the fart MP3
is not like...
I don't think it was loud enough for these riffs to land,
so I'd love to hear it cranked again.
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone, listen.
All right.
This is my first new one,
which is actually the one I just played.
That sucks, Paul.
Paul, that sounds so bad, my man.
I love it.
Paul, you do make music.
So you know what it sounds like
when a sound is pleasing to the ears.
I don't know, if Paul wrote the music part,
that was pretty good.
Yeah, the music part was great.
Do you have any with a fart that doesn't sound like
it is coming through a payphone pulse, Warren?
That was a high quality...
Okay, wait.
I want fully lossless audio codec, please, Paul.
I need a quick pull to my ears.
That was a pretty high quality fart.
Are you fucking out of your mind?
You.
It seems you.
Oh, beyond.
Do you need comparison?
Here's the original cue that you use for always...
Don't play more of...
Original cue.
That's such fucking...
That is a JPEG of a fart.
All right, here's another alt.
Paul!
Try this one.
Third option, hold on.
Don't fucking clap for that.
This is what...
You guys deserve the fucking Star Wars show
if this is what you like.
The amount of hiss on the high end of that fart sound
sucks so bad, Paul.
And what drives me crazy is I know you know that.
I got one more.
Paul, don't!
Okay, wait.
One more, one more, one more.
Fart.
I honestly prefer it.
All right, here we go.
The way this works, I am going to describe the thing.
This is a dumb fucking podcast.
Go ahead.
And then Griffin and Justin are going to guess what it is.
So it might be a movie, might be a book.
I forgot we were doing work of fart for a second.
I was having a lot of fun with Paul over there.
And so I was like embarrassed that we played the fart sound so many times.
And then I was like, oh, good, that part's over.
And now we can get to work of fart.
A governess helps a single father raise his numerous children
by teaching them to harmonize their farts.
The sound of...
Sound of Pusick.
Yes, Justin gets it.
That's one point for Justin.
I was going to say the sound of Pusick, but that's not it, is it?
That's not it.
I'm slipping.
This Joseph Heller novel examines the absurdity of war in military life
while extolling the virtues of mutual pleasure.
Fucking...
Can you give me a hint of who the fuck that is?
Okay, can you read it one more time?
This Joseph Heller novel examines the absurdity of war in military life
while extolling the virtues of mutual pleasure.
Catch 20...
Catch 20 Goo?
What?
Listen, mutual pleasure.
Catch 69.
Yes, it's Catch 69.
No, no, no, someone in the audience said it.
That's no points.
Justin's still up.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
This 70s rock album was recorded in the aftermath of relationship breakups
among the band's members and heavy bathrooming,
both of which shaped the album's lyrics.
Poomers?
Poomers, yes, Justin.
You're getting a little predictable in your twilight years.
All right, all right, all right.
Oh, rumors, this is all rumors.
Okay, okay.
Perhaps Tolstoy's greatest work.
This novel focuses on Napoleon's Russian invasion
and features three main characters who pee on everything.
Warren Peas?
Close.
Warren Piss?
Warren Piss, yes, that is correct, Griffin.
Okay, it's down to the wire, it's two and two.
Everybody scoot back, you're on the edge of your seats.
This Joyce classic is the story of a day in the life of Leopold Bloom
as he travels Dublin and goes about his business.
Is it Pulisies?
Yes.
You didn't let me finish!
I didn't even get a...
Can I finish?
Yeah, please.
Just a lot of poo ones this time.
As he travels Dublin and goes about his business,
attending a funeral, buying soap, going to the library,
walking by the beach, going to the pub,
but mostly his six-hour epic long shitting session.
Pulisies.
Yes, Justin wins!
Oh, that was it?
Let's hear it for Justin.
If it's gotten to the point where we can just take any media
with a title that has the ooh sound in it.
Yes.
Right, that is the point we're at
and the point we've been at.
Yes.
Okay, cool.
I'll remember that for next time.
That's when I've got you.
I work at a pizza place delivering said...
No, you don't.
Please go ahead, Justin.
I work at a pizza place delivering said pizzas to people's homes.
I also moved out on my own recently, so money's been tight.
I make and deliver pizzas.
Thank you for coming.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
I make and deliver dozens of orders a day.
This is normally not a problem except for when I'm hungry.
Then the hunger comes
and I crave the greasy pie.
Brothers, is there a way for me to get free pizza from my job
without leaving my customers short of a slice?
That's from delivering in Detroit.
What I love about this is you phrased it in such a way,
but what you're asking about is can I take a piece of pizza
out of the box before I deliver it, right?
Yeah, Trav, clearly that was the context of the question.
Because you can get free food from a restaurant you work at.
That happens all the time.
You make the pizza wrong and then you get to eat it.
That's the rules at pizza.
But I don't think they want that.
There's something about it that gets your motor running
instead of eating somebody else's pizza.
The illicit pie.
The OPP, that's what it stands for.
Oh, is that what it stands for?
I've always wondered, yeah.
The whole time, that's what it stood for.
So here's my first pitch to you.
Bring, bring, welcome to Pac-Man's Pizza,
home of the famous Pac-Man pizza
where every pizza looks like Pac-Man.
Uh-huh, yeah, it's a promotion.
Uh-huh, yeah.
It's a promotion that we named our business after.
It's a promotion that was so successful
we named our business after it.
Do you want, for the little dots,
do you want red bites or pepperoni?
Sorry.
Waka, waka, waka, waka.
Pac-a-roni.
They make us call them Pac-a-roni,
but that's confusing because it sounds like macaroni.
Waka, waka, waka.
Welcome to Elijah's Pizza
where we leave a slice out for our boy.
Just a big stack of them at the end of the day,
but then when none of us are looking, they disappear.
Elijah loves fucking pizza, man.
Loves that stuff.
Why don't you give them their total?
You just say, and we have a way
for your order to be one-eighth cheaper.
Would you be interested in that promotion today?
Would you be interested in built-in tip?
Yes, welcome to Pac-Man's where you'd never have to tip
because we already took it out of the box on our way over.
I think there is a reality in which you could swing this
just based on facial expression,
based on just sort of like guilt, non-verbalized guilt.
Just like, yeah, and here's your pizza, man.
Oh, thank you. Thanks for the tip.
Oh, that looks really good.
Yeah, man.
You guys are going to love that.
It looks so gooey and delicious.
I wish I had pizza.
Damn, I wish I had just even a little bit of that pizza.
Wouldn't it be dope if they made it
so you could easily separate out a small little,
like a segment of the, a piece of the pizza that I could have?
Anyways, back to my car that smells like pizza
but doesn't taste like it.
Maybe you could try like, and whenever you're done,
just leave whatever you don't want on the porch.
I'll come back.
That's the service we are at Raccoon's Pizza.
We have these new Tupperware boxes, so it all keeps,
and I'll just come get it from you, no problem.
This is my number. Just text me when you're done.
Also, if you have any batteries you need to dispose of,
I'm happy to grab those too, as long as I'm here.
Even if it's just a couple pepperoni stuck to the box, man.
Just let me know.
Yeah, also like old paint.
I'll come get that.
Anything you got, bud.
Where are you needing me to get rid of?
I'm trying to think.
If you take a piece out, but then you get like a circle
out of the very center of the remainder of the pizza,
can you just squish it back together?
I don't think so.
No, you can't actually.
No, not that way.
Not that way.
No, wait, you could do.
You could take one piece out and make a cone.
You could take one rectangular slice.
Okay, wait.
Okay, hold on.
Try to push people into square cut pizza.
When you square cut their pizza,
take the column of squares from the center.
Yes.
And then smoosh the halves, the remaining halves back together.
I've seen two shows.
I saw the Star Wars one and the one where they were helpful.
It's amazing.
Those are the two I've seen.
Maybe you could do pizza origami and be like,
I can turn it into a beautiful fleur de lis.
One slice's worth of pizza will have to hit the cutting room floor
in order to make this complicated pattern happen.
An artistic cut.
Yeah.
Or like a pizza like Tesseract, right?
We all think of it in a circle.
Sure, sure.
But what if it was a series of triangles
forming a non-geometric shape?
That is what a Tesseract is for sure.
It's even better to think from a wrinkle in time.
It's both, yeah, for sure.
You got it.
Hey, could you take a slice and then fold the pizza in half?
And try to insist it's a calzone
and the missing slice is on the bottom.
The missing slice is inside.
Yeah, well, by the time they realize that you're gone,
maybe they'll never...
Well, that's the other thing.
Rarely have I ever had a pizza delivered
and I open it to check before they leave.
Okay, but I do do that because my kids like cheese and no sauce.
Yeah.
And then Cooper likes sausage and no cheese.
So I do have to look at them
because everyone assumes we're kidding.
No, they didn't mean it.
They didn't mean that.
Can you deliver the pizza,
take three pieces in the other direction,
and then turn around and be like,
my lord, wait, let me test the pizza.
There have been assassins.
The Assassin's Guild has been active lately, my liege.
No, not the anchovy.
Those are usually safe.
I want the good one.
Let me lay down mine life for you, my liege.
I would love you to just start trying.
When you drop the pizza off, just be like,
can I get a slice?
Yeah.
Hey, man.
I notice you open the door.
I look inside.
There's one chair face of the TV.
You're not going to finish this whole thing.
Let me get a slice.
I'm not going to come in or make it weird.
Just let me get a slice.
Any pizza you've ever gotten that would've worked on you.
Correct?
100% of the time, I'd be like, absolutely, get in there.
No, hold on.
Logically, yes, Justin.
Get in there.
Emotionally, no.
No.
Someone brings you a pizza and goes,
hold on, let me get a slice.
No.
I'd be like, I'm calling the police.
It would be a request.
Like, can I get a slice before I go?
Rebrand the entire business like,
Burgle Boys Pizza Factory.
And the promotion can be,
our pizza is so fucking delicious
that our own delivery people will try to,
sometimes our pizza is going to show up incomplete.
It's because our pizza is so goddamn delicious.
Let me throw this out.
Pizza and pal.
Where it's like, hey man,
you feel like playing Mario Kart?
Order a pizza.
They'll show up, eat the pizza with you
and play Mario Kart with you.
Yes, I cannot stress enough
how much there was a very narrow period of my life
where I would've wanted this very badly.
And then every other period of my life
where I would very much not want this very, very badly.
Give me a slice of pizza
or I'm gonna play Mario Kart with you.
Fucking, yeah, whatever you say, man.
It's a sustainable model.
It's just like weed delivery.
My friends and family hate how I eat fruit.
And here's our next question.
Primarily, how I eat kiwis,
like when we eat an apple.
Skin and all.
They also hate my, and now you're about to hate it,
scrape and lick method of eating banana.
I don't utilize either of those verbs
when I eat a banana traditionally.
It's where I scrape my top teeth along my banana
to collect and enjoy the sweet aerated banana goo.
Hey, you know, I just had a realization.
There is at least one person in this room
that can relate to what it feels like
to fill in this room full of people
that are disgusted by you.
And I'm so happy we could share that feeling with you.
How do I get them to see the right
and proper way to eat fruit?
That's from fruit muncher in Michigan.
Okay, okay.
Right and proper is a stretch.
Justifiable fringe option is the best you might get.
Hey, what's up?
Oh, right, Griffin.
Hey, I'm your friend.
You can trust me.
You came to my show.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
I'm your friend.
You got to cut this shit out because...
No, stop, hold on.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
You think, what's a few times eating a banana funny?
This...
I'm a complicated person with a lot of stuff going on.
I'm a New York Times bestselling author and yet...
Everyone knows me as the guy who ate a banana weird one time.
You...
It's...
Listen, we didn't say your Christian name.
It's not too late.
We are...
I am three ghosts of Christmas from different times.
Stop it.
This doesn't have to be you.
There was a time to back Griffin up where you did this the first time.
Yeah.
Maybe by accident.
Maybe you didn't know better.
I don't know.
And you did it and people reacted in horror.
They loved it.
And you made the decision of I'm going to buy into it.
Yeah.
And that decision was wrong.
It was a bad wrong decision.
Although, I think we can all agree, the best way to eat a banana, squeeze it from the bottom, let the banana pop out, you catch it in your mouth.
Yeah.
And then you smile at the bananas.
You swallow it.
You see a shape of the banana in your throat.
It's hilarious.
Do it 30 more times.
Hilarious.
Right in front of them in that one sitting.
We're kind of just ignoring the kiwi part, aren't we?
Because there's no justification for that.
That's beyond the pale.
That came from a different point in the audience.
No, listen.
That's the hairy part.
If you tell me any food stuff you eat with the hair on it, I will sit and I will listen to it.
Don't say peach.
That doesn't count.
You know it doesn't count.
You know it's different and you wanted to shout it anyway?
I'm not interested in what hairy foods you eat, Detroit.
Especially when, frankly, it's one or two voices of thousands.
You must know if everyone's not shouting something, you shouldn't shout.
Because if you're the only one shouting out the hairy food that everyone supposedly eats, they don't.
Stop it.
We're trying to save you.
I cannot imagine an axis that one would eat a banana upon where scraping it with your teeth is remotely acceptable.
There had to be at least a few times where you scrape too hard and break it and it falls on the floor.
Unless you only peel off one section of peel.
They scrape it with their teeth.
You peel off one of four sections and then you scrape down.
It's all bad.
No, it's not good.
I'm just saying.
My daughter breaks a banana in half like it's a strength contest.
That's great.
I like that.
She hit her banana and her daughter just goes.
If your problem is that the fruit you're eating isn't light and airy enough, don't eat a banana.
Famously, a thick fruit.
Most of them are just kind of water and like latex.
That's about what most fruits are.
Orange, like gone.
Bananas can't be that for you and it's weird that you want the banana to be that for you.
There are also plenty of fruits that are designed to be eaten weird.
Like we had to work at a pomegranate.
We all had to get on board with the way to harvest a pomegranate and agree it was worth the trouble.
Banana easy to eat.
Yeah, that one's got the whole system built right in.
It's like God in his infinite wisdom put a handle on it.
Here he goes again.
I would love to watch you eat a banana in front of Kirk Cameron and turn him into a stone cold atheist.
You're right.
It all makes sense.
I know what I said, but wow.
It is a broken system.
I've never cussed before, but holy shit.
If you're anything like me around this time of year, you typically find yourself saying,
wow, I really wish that I had just prepared even a little bit, just a little bit of advanced preparation.
This is earlier.
This is now.
You're in that moment and there is no better partner for that than stamps.com.
It'll make it so easy.
You'll want to get out ahead of your holiday shopping that you need to do.
Stamps.com is a one stop shop, not just USPS fine service that it is, but also UPS services need to run your holiday operation right from your computer.
You don't have to deal with the lines.
There's no traffic.
There's no hassle.
And with stamps.com switch and save feature, you can easily compare carriers and rates.
You know you're getting the best deal this holiday season.
Trade late nights for silent nights and get started with stamps.com today.
Sign up with promo code my brother for a special offer that includes a four week trial plus free postage and a free digital scale.
No long term commitments or contracts.
Just go to stamps.com.
Click the microphone at the top of the page and enter code my brother.
Hey, while I've got you here and you're doing this shopping, you got your stamps all covered.
Fantastic.
But how do you know that you're getting the best deal outside of the world of stamps?
Well, there, my friend, you're going to rely on Honey.
It's a really easy to install browser extension.
PayPal Honey makes it easy to see if you could save a little bit of money.
It takes, you know, a couple of clicks to install it in this free tool.
When you go to check out, it'll look for coupons for what you are purchasing.
And that is thrilling because you get to save some money that you didn't think you were going to save.
I mean, what better feeling is there than that?
Honey will look for a coupon and find something that works.
The price just drops just like that.
I've saved money on a lot of tools for woodworking.
I've gotten some headphones at a really nice discount.
Hachi machi.
You're just losing money to not install Honey.
You can save even more when you ask Honey to keep track of price drops on your holiday shopping list.
If the price drops in anything on your list, you instantly get an alert to let you know.
If you don't already have Honey, you're just missing out.
By getting it, you'll be doing yourself a solid and you're supporting our show.
You like our show, right?
Get PayPal Honey for free at joinhoney.com slash brother.
That's joinhoney.com slash brother.
And now, back to the show.
Hey, I'm Dan McCoy.
I'm Stuart Wellington.
And I'm Elliot Kalin.
Listen, you like podcasts, right?
Sure you do.
Don't try and lie to me.
You're listening to one right now.
So why not try a different one called our one, The Flophouse.
And on The Flophouse, we watch a movie and talk about it.
And then sometimes we also do other stuff.
It's all meant to be funny and fun, and we think you'll have a good time.
And just to be clear, the name of the podcast is not our one, The Flophouse.
It's just called The Flophouse.
I do a lot of correcting Dan.
The Flophouse, a lot of correcting Dan.
Hey, it's Jon Moe, inviting you to listen to Depressed Mode with Jon Moe,
where I talk about mental health and the lives we live with all kinds of people.
Famous writers.
David Sedaris, welcome to Depressed Mode.
Thanks so much for having me.
Movie stars.
Jamie Lee Curtis, welcome to Depressed Mode.
I am happy to be here.
Musicians.
I am in St. Paul, Minnesota.
I'm talking to Amy Mann.
Great to talk to you.
And song exploders.
Rishi K. Sherway, welcome to Depressed Mode.
Thanks so much for having me.
Everyone's opening up on Depressed Mode on Maximum Fun.
I want to munch.
Welcome to Munch Squad.
It's a podcast, then a podcast profile, the latest, greatest brand eating.
And I waited as long as I could because I got two different huge topics to cover.
And the first one, you know we're going to talk about it, Detroit.
I went to DoorDash.
A app my father is incapable of using without ordering from Georgia.
I've saved this, by the way.
He's told this story multiple times this evening.
There's a moment when you try to order from a different place where DoorDash goes.
You're pretty far away.
You seem pretty far away.
So you know, Dad went, never mind that.
Oh, well.
We'll figure it out.
Hey, guys, let's talk about the crypto grill.
If you go to DoorDash here, and I don't think it's a real place you can go to,
which makes it probably the wildest ghost restaurant I've ever heard of in my life.
Let's talk about the crypto grill.
I have no context for any of this, but they do have a lot of different crypto themed items like the NFT milk.
Like the crypto burger.
That's the best you've got?
Yeah, it gets worse, bud.
Loaded cyber fries.
But then also curly fries.
They got curly fries or loaded cyber fries.
If you order the curly fries from the crypto grill, fuck you.
Man, do you remember like two decades ago when if you called the place Crypto Grill,
it was about spooky stuff?
Yeah, that's why I clicked on it.
I thought I was going to get a Bigfoot burger.
No dice.
Damn it.
Cyber fries is good.
I will patronize them just for the cyber fries though.
Because what do they have in there that makes them cyber?
Chips.
There's the beef.
There's the beef dono.
The baldana.
The bytecoin.
The bytecoin is good.
The ethereparm sandwich.
That sucks.
It's so bad.
I will gladly write your new blockchain jokes for the blockchain burger.
Ethereum mixed drink with rum in it.
Yeah, there we go.
The litecoin.
And then they have brisket loaded waffle fries,
which I looked at for a while and then thought that's just that.
Yeah.
Then there's also an item on here called the Crypto Lettuce Surprise You Sauce.
I don't believe I will actually.
Thank you for asking.
Let us pick the best sauce for what you ordered.
What in our relationship lets you think I trust you with anything?
With anything.
I love the Crypto Sauce are the only words in there outside of quotation wise.
So it says Crypto Lettuce Surprise You Sauce.
So crypto has nothing to do with it whatsoever.
But they also have a Superman cheesecake,
which has nothing to do with crypto, but is a specific reference.
Don't be cowards.
By the time we come back here and perform in four more calendar years in Detroit, Michigan,
I expect them to have their act together.
Yeah.
I did want to talk about, you know, because we want to make this show special.
I want to do a Munch Squad about one that's just good.
Okay.
This is Burger King.
I was thinking about him recently.
Like, you don't hear about them getting the mix.
They don't get nasty so much.
They had that one foul up with the black burger bun that gave everybody weird poops.
And then they quit.
It was a pretty, it was a pretty big whoopsie they made.
I will say.
Yeah.
But like, you know, Burger King does one weird poop food and Taco Bell is like,
call me when you've mastered it.
I literally, I had a thought, they got to do something to get back in the game.
And then I found this press release from October 6th that said,
today Burger King unveils its brand new positioning and campaign,
kicking off with its modernized tagline, you rule.
The work is part of the change guests nationwide will experience
as the brand implements its reclaim the flame plan,
which means that no one likes Burger King.
Wait, now hold on. Listen.
Reclaim the flame as a slogan announced by, let's say,
many groups that exist within the US of A is a terrifying statement.
Yes.
It also could be like, Ashen One, you must travel across these blighted lands.
Reclaim the flame.
So reclaim.
Here's a skeleton horse or some shit.
So reclaim the flame is the superstructure.
And then this is part of the fuel the flame advertising co-investment
between Burger King and its franchisees.
It's the you rule.
Who's hungry?
Campaign.
It's a key part of their positioning that will impact every guest's touch point.
It's about.
My touch points.
It's about celebrating everyday royalty
and puts the guests at the forefront of everything the brand does.
I feel pampered in this Burger King tonight.
In a partnership, in a partnership with our new creative agency,
OKRP, it's OKRP.
We've developed a simple and meaningful articulation
of how Burger King celebrates our guests.
It embodies our purpose, embraces individuality,
and elevates have it your way.
Something our brand has always been known for.
OKRP is the review we get most often on Adventure Zone on iTunes.
It's fucking mean. Yeah.
Now, I know there's this.
Here's the quote.
Advertising at its best is this is most relevant.
I feel like Don Draper is click clicking through a slide.
Yeah.
So when you celebrate them first, not the brand.
And that's just what we love about you rule.
It invites people in with an approach that recognizes their world,
not just sell some stuff.
That's great.
Now, OK.
Now, we're given that this one's pretty rough.
We're giving them permission to feel like winners.
Holy shit.
So they know what they're doing because I was about to say
have it your way reflects on the eating experience.
But you rules just like, hey.
Hey, man.
We're we are giving them permission to feel like winners with Burger King
as just a small award that makes their day a bit better.
Hey, Burger King.
Congrats on the self-awareness.
That's a huge first step.
This is going to make your day.
Is it going to fix everything?
Nope. Nope. Nope.
We'll win, though.
Little W for the.
You know that this isn't a healthy, responsible choice.
This is the little win.
And let's face it.
The song is irresistible.
What the song is irresistible.
We're hoping it'll be the earworm.
You can't shake off.
And that's my gift to you, Detroit.
Paul, Bud, let's bump it.
I do things the way I want to do them.
Make my own rules and listen to them.
Won't let anyone go and rain on my parade.
I think I want a flame grill, classical whopper.
Sure does sound fantastic.
I tell them how I want to have it.
They say, OK.
You rule your seasons a day at BK.
Have it your way.
You rule.
If I want it special, we're just playing.
The choice I make is my domain.
With every order, I can reign and have them my way.
Tall burgers.
The BK menu makes sure my stomach prospers.
Onion rings, chicken fries, and whopper.
Any food I think is proper, I can have it my way.
Get off the table.
You rule your seasons a day at BK.
I just can't stop dancing, Justin.
Have it your way.
You rule.
All right.
Right?
It's good.
It's really good.
That's all.
I just like the song.
I thought you'd like to hear it.
And it speaks to the youth.
That's the important thing.
I think if I walk.
They love chicken fries.
If I walk into a fucking Burger King and I say,
I would like the chicken fries value combo special meal,
please.
And then they're like, that's $4.89.
And then I'm like, I am not going to pay.
Because I have very recently been informed I'm in charge.
I'm the Burger King now, dog.
I know what you're wondering.
Why did I walk inside of a Burger King?
And it's because I'm claiming this Burger King for myself now.
You should have to assassinate the Burger King
when you walk into every Burger King.
Yeah.
Why did you do that?
I rule now.
I rule.
I have something of my own.
Give me chicken fries until I tell you to stop.
I've had three of them.
Stop.
I'll ask the king.
The king is dead.
I'm your king.
I'm the king now.
That's your Munch Squad for this week.
Thank you so much.
Should we turn it to some audience questions?
Yes, we should.
We received some questions from the audience.
We are going to call you down and just approach the mic.
It's here.
Center stage.
It is facing us, but you don't have to use it that way.
Please turn it so you're looking at us.
Yeah, that would be fantastic, actually.
Hello.
Hi.
My name is Luke.
Hey, Luke.
Nice to see him.
Hi, Luke.
What's your question?
So I'm an OB doctor.
I deliver babies.
Yeah.
Nice.
Like the person who delivers pizzas.
We get it.
Right.
Yeah.
Very often babies are born that don't have names, and occasionally the parents will ask
me what my name is, and it's always a little awkward.
I don't know if I should say my real name or if I should give a fake name because I
don't want the baby to steal my name.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
The baby is like could be a Baba Yaga who's going to steal-
Thank you.
Then have power over you.
Does the parent say it like this?
I don't have a name.
What's your name?
Hey.
Like how do you breathe?
Like I don't understand.
That's a risky gambit because you could, I'll say this.
Luke, fantastic name, could have a really shitty name.
Like Griffin.
No, that's, Griffin's good.
I think it would be kind of cool to know that your name says wonder.
I bet I could make myself cry on stage right now.
I think it would be kind of cool to know that your namesake is out there wandering around.
Like sometime you might see them, just look them in the eye and say, Luke, I am your doctor.
Justin, that was, no, no, no, no, no.
You, you crept toward the line, the precipice and you peeked over it, which I applaud you
for.
It's very brave.
You did make a Star Wars joke on stage.
Right, but it's tasteful.
And that's why I'll say this gang.
He could have made that joke at any show and not, it wasn't just for your benefit.
It just happened to be right.
This is how recently I was talking with my daughters and they're both named after people.
And then BB said, who are you named after?
And I go, I don't know.
No one.
And like my parents threw a dart at a board and picked traffic.
I don't know.
I think the being named after someone, even if I think being named after the doctor, imagine
if in like 10 years, it's like the most popular kid name, Luke.
And it's because of you.
I don't know how many babies you're delivering in a given day.
Is it enough to move the needle statistics wise?
Start insisting.
Hey, do you have a baby name picked out?
Don't even answer.
It's Luke.
Next.
Nurse, write down Luke.
Nurse, you misspelled Luke.
Does that, does that help Luke?
Yeah.
Thank you, brothers.
You're very welcome.
Thank you for joining us.
Next approach the crucible.
So I am Phil.
What is your, your question?
How can we help?
So my wife's fire department is hiring and they've had a few too many recruits who have
shown up taking pictures in all the gear with all the equipment and then left.
Yeah.
That happened with us and the fourth brother.
No, I get it.
Yeah, I get it.
Yeah.
So how can she recruit new firefighters that are interested in more than just a few good
Instagram pictures?
Well, welcome to the biggest problem we have on earth.
Yeah.
How to fight off people.
It is.
I appreciate your help.
How to fight off Instagram influencer.
Yeah, it's firefighter stolen valor is probably our biggest issue.
I think they have to fight one before they can do a picture.
If it's your first one other firefighter.
Yeah.
You have to fight.
No, I'm a firefighter fighter.
If, listen, here's what I'm saying.
If I'm going to take it from one of the other ones, our volunteer and professional firefighters,
they're heroes, right?
If I'm going to get a picture of myself, I want one of me doing the fighting of a fire.
Like if I'm going to get one picture, I want it to look cool like I'm doing the fire stuff.
Otherwise, I was just really good at ordering costumes.
Yeah, right.
I want to get one.
One under the belt.
Yeah.
One where a fire is going.
I don't know how you guarantee that, though, without arson.
Well, okay.
I was going to say you could start fires anywhere, but then that's arson.
Yeah, it's fucked up, isn't it?
I hate that they-
That sucks.
That's illegal.
Hey, guys, let's grow up.
Arson is generally frowned upon, yeah.
Does she ever pressure you to join?
She does actually.
She doesn't want me to because that's her thing.
Yeah, but you do look like you have beat a fire's ass, Phil.
She's way tougher than I am.
Does she ever look at a picture of a fire in the paper and be like, dang, Phil, wish
somebody had gotten there, huh?
I want you to know, Phil, I don't want you to be a firefighter.
Yeah.
You seem very blas about it.
I'm just saying it's not a quality I look for in a firefighter.
I don't want firefighters like, yeah, okay.
You seem like you-
When pressed, you might actually join the fire.
It's making some good points.
Oh, no, this new firefighter recruit we got just became more fire.
Yeah, but I'm just saying, did you see some of the political signs that the House had?
That's the opposite of what we wanted.
The media has misrepresented the fire in a pretty major way, okay?
If you take the time-
That fire makes some good points on its Twitter.
Does that help, Phil?
We'll go with yes.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, yeah, thanks, Phil.
Thank you, brothers.
See you, bud.
Hello.
How's it going?
Hi, I'm Bell.
My pronouns are she, her.
Hi, Bell.
As per my email, I run a LARP-
Chill my last up my spine, Bell.
All right.
Sorry, Bell, go ahead.
I run a LARP chapter in Toledo.
I've been trying to get more people to join my part, but the Venn diagram of dorks who want to sword fight
and people who want to go out to a park on every afternoon of every Saturday, it's kind of slim.
Sure.
Right?
How do I get more people to join?
How many do you need?
I'll take as many as I can.
Yeah, I mean, Travis, the answer to that question is two.
Just have a bucket, just like nonstop.
Well, okay, you say sword fighting.
Yeah.
I think there's a lot of other things going on in a given village.
Sure.
That you could be like, hey, do you want to sleep but in old-timey clothes?
Yeah.
Yeah, or we teach a lot of craft stuff.
Alchemy.
Leatherworking, sewing, stuff like that.
Yes.
Alchemy, sure.
Rune crafting.
I say this as someone who is now 39 and I have no idea what the answer to this is.
Is that something that looks good on a college application?
Rune crafting?
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah, absolutely.
I know people at the park they started back in Texas that will actually have like, yeah,
I've organized all kinds of events like on their resume and it looks good because it
shows that you know how to like organize stuff.
For sure.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You don't need to recruit people.
You need to go to a busier park and then everyone there is here.
Yeah.
Listen, I will say this.
You hit someone enough times the foam sword, something's going to happen.
Yeah, that's great.
A battle will ensue.
That's great.
If you throw them a foam sword and then you start hitting them ferociously with a foam
sword, you have made a larper.
Yeah.
Been learned to defend thyself.
They may not stop when you blow the whistle or whatever it is.
The ocarina.
There will be a role that is being played in a live action setting.
So very true.
I mean, how many people?
How far is Toledo from here?
That's about an hour's drive.
How many people here?
Hold on.
How many people here live in Toledo?
I think your group probably expanded by at least one to two people tonight if I was
guessing.
How can they join the group?
I have a Facebook group called Bright River.
We meet on Wildwood every Saturday at two.
This is it.
We're turning this show into Craigslist.
I love it.
Thank you, Belle.
Does that help?
I know it helps.
That absolutely helps.
Thank you so much, brothers.
Thank you.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm Rebecca.
Hi, Rebecca.
First of all, Primo Merch.
Fantastic 100% podcast.
Thank you.
It's the funniest thing we will ever do.
It's the only T-shirt of our merch that my wife wears.
Yeah.
It's very good.
Okay.
Sorry.
What's your question?
So, I recently got an e-scooter.
Yes.
Nice.
I'm wondering when I see other people out in the world on their e-scooters how I should
greet them.
Yeah, sure.
When you say e-scooter, this isn't like, I'm sorry, lime or like that kind of thing.
Like you.
You own this shit.
I own it.
Yeah.
You customize it?
You put a hemi on that bad boy?
Or do you put just like streamers on the handlebars?
You all got those scooters around here?
Yeah.
I know how I'm getting home tonight.
Nice.
Real nice.
I know more than one person who has exploded their collarbone on an e-scooter.
But I don't know if that's a part of the culture or not.
But you like high-five collarbones in mid-air as you pass each other.
Or just like when you both sound the same but just go, oh, fuck.
My collarbone.
Yeah.
Anybody up here have any electric vehicles?
I have an electronic bicycle now.
How do you greet other people with an electronic bicycle?
Except for running into them.
I usually slow way down until they're out of line of sight.
Because I think they probably know what they're doing way better than me.
Okay.
Can I tell you guys?
So BB is dying to get a skateboard.
And I've started entertaining it and said, yeah, I'll look for one that's like good for
six-year-olds.
And then I realized I have zero percent information on how to ride a scooter.
I might have to hire somebody to teach you how to skateboard.
Please record it, Travis.
No.
To teach my daughter how to skateboard as I stand off to the side going, you're doing
great, champ.
Oh, man.
No.
You have to do it and also record that.
Because I don't want to see you be like, oh, I don't know, Christ hair.
What if I'm amazing at it?
What if you're really good?
Do you do many tricks?
Do you know many tricks?
How many tricks do you know?
Um, it, the scooter like fell out from under me the other day and I, I feel like I-
Half?
Well, no.
Okay.
But yeah, it's a scooter.
It's an electronic scooter.
That's what it, that's what they do.
But you're still here.
So, trick.
Yeah.
That's a trick.
Like I landed well, I think.
You defied death.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
How many times do you see someone on an electric?
Actually a lot.
Yeah.
And I feel like I try to like, be like, yeah, another scooter.
Wait, hold on.
No, no, no.
This is important.
What's your usual?
Give me, yeah.
I try, I try to be like, you know, like a little nod.
Okay.
Because the first thing you did for the people at home, the first thing you did when showing
it was like a deep court jester bow.
Yeah.
And that could work.
I, you're coming at this the wrong way because you're saying to us, when I see other people
on e-scooters, how can I ingratiate myself and form a human bond with them and not like,
how do I intimidate and scare every other person?
Who dares try to grind my block?
Get extremely territorial, Rebecca.
Yeah.
That's the first thing.
If you see anyone fucking scooting in your block.
You take their battery or whatever.
Take their battery or whatever it is that powers those things.
Wease their juice as it were.
Does that help?
Yeah, that's really good.
Thank you, Rebecca.
Thank you.
So this is when we wrap up, if we could bring down the lights, but first I want to say our
poster by Kaley Turvo.
Yes.
Really good.
And you can buy them in the lobby.
It's one of the best posters we've ever had.
Sure.
Upsetting in a fun, good way.
But that's my whole aesthetic.
Sure.
Yes.
So those are available.
You can buy those.
Limited time only.
Thank you so much to the Masonic Temple here for having us and they're beautiful.
You guys see these fixtures?
Oh my God.
Did you see these fixtures?
When the lights come up later, make sure you look.
I'm sure you've probably looked before.
Thank you for letting us back into your city.
Yeah.
I really appreciate it.
It was, there were some tense moments.
Yeah.
It was touch and go.
We're supposed to do another show here at some point and then gosh dang COVID happened,
I think.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Shook out.
Anybody else?
Thanks Montane.
Thank you to Amanda and Rachel and Paul and our dad and Sawbones.
Yeah.
All of whom we couldn't do the show without.
Thank you to Montane for the use of our theme song, My Life is Better with you.
Yes.
And thanks to you.
Thanks to you for coming, giving us a second chance.
I hope we didn't fucking blow it.
Griffin, do you have any final thoughts for everybody?
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
Don't say May the force be with you.
No, I won't say that.
But if you, hey, it's me, Griffin.
If you say you're going to do something, then do it.
Don't say you're going to try to do it.
What is Justin McElroy?
No, hold on, let Griffin keep going.
No, no.
Why not try?
Because you won't do it, man.
Yeah.
My name is Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
Griffin McElroy.
This has been My Brother, My Brother, My Kids, Your Dad score on the left!