are not experts, and their advice should never be followed.
Travis insists he's a sexpert, but if there's a degree on his wall, I haven't seen it.
Also, this show isn't for kids, which I mention only so the babies out there will know how
cool they are for listening.
What's up, you cool baby?
I wish I had more things to pull out of my pocket.
Seriously, serious question before I sit down.
Jacket on or off?
You know what that...
This is a no jacket required show, my friend.
Welcome to my brother...
Oh wait, like, uh...
Welcome to my brother, my brother and me...
Holy shit!
Okay, we're going to start again from the top.
You guys pretend we just came out and not too not familiar.
There's our sleeping baby.
By the way, Sidney's back there now, so don't worry about being quiet for the baby anymore.
I want you all wild out.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
That's a cool night for me, so I do appreciate it.
Welcome to my brother, my brother and me, an advice show for the modern era.
I'm your oldest brother, Justin McElroy.
I'm your middle-est brother, Travis McElroy.
I'm your sweet baby brother, Griffin McElroy.
Like Chilean miners emerging from the depths of the Twin Cities, here we are in Minneapolis.
Juicy Lucy, is that a thing?
What?
I didn't have a lot of preconceived notions about Minneapolis before I came, but then
I showed up and everybody here is so nice.
You know what, Justin?
I would say the greatest audiences in the world live here in Minneapolis.
No, I'm serious.
We are staying at the beautiful Courtyard Marriott.
Please don't come find us at Marriott.
I can't recommend it enough when we're not there.
Right next to our hotel, there's a place called Town Hall Brewery that we had some great cheese
curds.
Some really great local brews.
Some great local brews.
I'm traveling with a baby, as you know.
We had some great local babies.
Sydney was a bit worried about how she was going to get home.
She wanted to leave in the middle of the show if her baby turns into a disaster, which is
prone to happen.
Welcome to parenthood.
I said, you can just get an Uber home.
She said, and this is a few weeks ago I should mention, she said, well, what about that show
we saw where the guy was using people's Uber data and pretending to be an Uber driver and
then killing them?
I said, well, that's fair.
I don't want you to be killed, so I'll abandon that plan.
I was recounting this story to Travis yesterday, and I said, how did he do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
He said, well, he hacked into Uber's system, and at that point, I realized, wait a minute.
Are you talking about the first five minutes of that episode of CSI Cyber we watched?
Sorry, my dear wife, who's also a physician.
Do you remember the documentary?
Ripped from the headlines by Patricia Arquette.
Take that.
Thank you.
So that was fun.
Here's another fun thing that we had this morning, this is a 100% true Minneapolis story
for you.
We were having breakfast.
We tried to find someplace to have brunch, and then we're just like, ugh, it's cold.
We're just going to go down to, it's called the Bistro, but it's in the ground floor lobby
of a courtyard in Marriott, so it's not really a bistro.
I was a super dad, and I asked them to blend up some strawberries.
He's a super dad because he forgot to bring baby food.
When some lose some, I guess, and they blended up some strawberries with some Oolala super
food juice or something like that, and she got about three bites in.
I look to the right for a second, and she just grabs the cup right onto my lap.
Now this isn't a funny story.
It was sad because it was all over the table, and it was all over the crotch of the only
jeans I brought.
That, okay, that part.
We're on tour right now.
We're on a four-day tour, and you are a one-jeans packer.
I live my life one jeans at a time, but I- You live your life one jeans at a time.
The frequency of your jeans is not an issue because you just got the one.
So let me get the end of the story.
My dear sweet daughter, who I hope is listening to this sometime in 2030-
When podcasts are outlawed.
Dump a Bacchus.
And only outlaws have podcasts.
The front of my crotch is covered in red, and Griffin, without missing a beat, but also
not with any help whatsoever, looks at me and says, you know, I've got a Judy Blume
book you should read.
That's a pretty good bit.
That was a cool trap.
Let's do the thing where we do the advice, okay?
So if you haven't listened to our show before, we take your questions and turn them alchemy-like
into wisdom.
Has anybody not listened to the show before?
Cool.
Welcome.
I didn't do that during Sawbones.
That's always a good- Is there anybody who has listened to the show before?
Anyone here from Minneapolis?
Anybody here from South Dakota?
Yeah, what's up?
Not as me.
I was just surprisingly- I knew that because you bought us cookies.
Let's read a question.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now pump the brakes, South Dakota.
Trying to sound a little North Dakota- Holy shit.
Let's just name more states, Ohio, Indiana- Okay, I get it.
I have a problem.
I'm a fun-loving young man, but since I'm one of the more responsible people in my circle
of friends, I love to say the occasional lame pun, and I'm often labeled as the dad of the
group.
How can I ditch the dad persona and show my friends that I still know how to party?
And that's from Not Lame in Lakeville.
Are you here?
Yeah.
Great.
Hold on.
I'm getting some dad- Let me see.
I'm gonna do my dad's thinking- Okay.
You appear to be a very young man.
You look like one of Mumford's sons, not Mumford himself.
I don't wanna see them anymore.
Yeah.
Choice.
That was a perfect shameful fade.
Can you give us...
Can you just sort...
I know I'm putting you on the spot right now, and I apologize, and if you don't wanna do
anything, just remain quiet, and it'll be wicked uncomfortable, but can you bust us
out an example, a slice of your oeuvre?
Your lame puns is what he means.
Wait, hold on.
Just come on up.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on to the microphone.
There's a microphone right here.
Now, come on.
First...
No, he's too...
Come on.
Come on up.
Ride the snake.
Here we go.
There's a microphone there.
Oh, my God.
You are in the perfect exact middle of the aisle, too.
Right in the middle.
Good crowd control.
Anyone here from Minneapolis?
Oh, man.
I'm gonna ask that in Chicago, too.
Okay.
So, here he comes to the stage.
What's your name, pal?
Oh, no.
There we go.
Okay.
It's hot.
Say it again.
Travis.
Yeah.
Nice.
The middle-est, brother.
Pretty great.
I gave you a little...
I like that.
I gave you a little bit of stalling time.
What you got?
We have a hypothetical restaurant full of menu items with punny names.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Fleetwood Mac and Cheese.
Solid.
That's...
I mean, it's not on point, but that's what makes it, like, great.
It's what makes it really good.
Notorious BLT.
That's super good.
Pretty good.
That's pretty good.
I'd tell that one.
That's good.
Do you got one more?
That's Comedy Rule of Three's.
Ashley, any help here?
Come on, Ashley.
Ashley.
No, Ashley's not here.
Ashley's not here at all.
Ashley.
He needs you.
He's gasping.
Ashley wants no part of this, Dad.
Help.
I think...
No, you know what?
No, that's good.
Comedy Rule of Two's.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a new thing I'm working on where I just say two things, and I...
Listen, we're millennials.
We can't wait for a third thing.
Yeah.
Just come up...
After the show, we'll do a private pun session, and you can...
Where are you gonna get puns from, Griffin?
Okay.
Thank you very, very much.
I feel bad for you.
Everybody, Travis.
Go sit down, Travis.
Okay.
We were backstage.
We'll jump back to talking about your thing, Travis.
I swear to God, this was not planned.
We didn't pick this question because we found this wonderful artifact.
No, this is the great spirit.
There's a word of the day calendar backstage that I think somebody here at the theater
may be made because there's a picture of a person pointing at you, and it's full of amazing
puns.
Like...
Guys, no kidding.
These are so good.
These are best in class.
Whoever said it's a word of the day calendar, it's a pun of the day calendar.
Yeah.
Where do you learn to make ice cream?
Sunday school.
Which US president was least guilty?
Lincoln.
He was in assent.
We thought this would be funnier.
In our defense, we didn't think this would be funnier.
This one's the best.
This one's the best, in my opinion.
Oh, why?
Because I can cut a piece of wood just by looking at it.
It's true.
I saw it with my own eyes.
That shit's awesome.
I think lean into it, right, because now you can wear calculator watches, and that's a
cool look.
Travis, can I tell you something?
It's totally awesome to be the lamest person at the party.
It's so great.
It's like a ripcord when you're at parties that you don't want to be at anymore, like
lame.
No one has ever looked at the lamest person at the party leaving early and said, oh, no,
come on.
No one wants the cool dude to leave.
They're like, you got to stay, but when the dad of the party leaves, it's like, great.
Now we can get to some shit.
Listen, Travis, it's exhausting being a trendsetter.
Don't be like me.
I got to stay up with the latest looks.
I got to listen to the latest music.
You fucking ruined your jeans today, and in lieu of them, you wore black basketball shorts
with a nice sweater and your nice shoes with almost knee-high white socks on.
A fanny pack spontaneously sprung from you.
You were wearing a very bright salmon-colored Doctor Who shirt.
I remember every goddamn detail of your ensemble today.
Here's the worst part about that is that last night, Travis and I went down to the lobby
trying to secure some Johnson & Johnson's baby wash, dad of the year, and again, forgot
to pack it, but I guess dad of the year, et cetera, et cetera.
And they told us there was a gas station nearby, so I walked to a gas station that was not
nearby.
It was over an overpass about a quarter mile away wearing a salmon-colored Doctor Who Dalek
t-shirt.
Just took that one on a two-day ride, huh?
Navy blue huge basketball shorts and brown, like, dress shoes.
These bad boys that I'm wearing right now with shorts and white socks, and on the way,
two Chinese ladies laughed at me.
But this morning, Trendsetter saw those two same Chinese ladies wearing pink Doctor Who
shirts, so I don't know, what's your game, ladies?
Do you guys want a Yahoo?
Yes, please.
Listen, it's not a public question.
It's just the two of us.
It's for us.
This one was sent in by Ashley Shannon.
Thank you, Ashley.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Ariana Rose, who asks, is it possible to have a Disney character
with you all day on your birthday at Disneyland?
I'm going to Disneyland for my birthday for free, and I just wanted to know if it's possible
to have a Disney character with you all day.
Like, going on the rides with you and having food with you all day.
Can we all agree that there's such an age question to this question, where it's like
a weird bell curve, where if you're like six, that's totally fine to ask this question.
And if you're like 26 right now in our modern day and age, it's like, yeah, I get why you
asked that question.
I get it.
Basically, you're paying for companionship.
We can all agree that the number one best pick would be Gaston, because I bet that two
can't party.
Right, but-
That'd be annoying.
No one drinks like Gaston.
Sure.
No one spits like Gaston.
In a wrestling match, nobody bites like Gaston.
He's especially good at expectorating.
Everybody.
Oh, what a guy.
Gaston.
It's like a quarter million dollars that we have to pay to have that on the show.
Thank you.
I'm saying you won't get Gaston.
You're not going to get Gaston.
You had to show-
We don't get a Gaston.
You had to show up at 6 a.m. if you want a Gaston.
For all day, you can get fucking flotsam from the Little Mermaid.
You can have a shriveled up Moray eel, like, what's up, happy birthday.
You get the really racist guy from Pocahontas.
I just hope there are no savages.
Happy birthday, I guess.
Do you want to go to Mexico at Epcot?
You mean with the Aztecs?
No, I do not.
I will stay here at the World of Tomorrow.
Was that guy Foghorn Langhorne?
He was like, Foghorn Langhorne meets Tim Curry.
It was actually a perfect uggie boogie and you just didn't nail the landing.
I wish Tim Curry would go to the Disney World.
Justin, I know the best place for a nice cheese pizza.
It's in Italy, in Epcot, unsurprisingly.
We'll go on Spaceship Earth.
Let's go hang with my homie, the dream master.
Him and his little buggy figment.
God, it's an impeccable Tim Curry.
Why is that?
It's a family impression.
We all can feel it.
You do an amazing impression of what you think Tim Curry sounds like.
Our dad can't do a sick Tim Curry.
The only thing I can think is that our dear departed mother must be a bitchin' Tim Curry
that we never heard.
It's in our genes.
It's a recessive gene.
I've isolated it.
The Tim Curry impression gene, duplicate it.
Here's a secret to doing a Tim Curry, I'll give it to you guys right now.
The secret is-
Don't give away our family secrets.
The secret is to just do it and then go, awesome.
Nailed it.
Perfect.
I'm gonna say, that was Tim Curry when you finished.
You guys got that, right?
It's so key you identified it.
You just have to say cheese pizza.
Cheese pizza.
Will you please read another question?
Thank you for being so kind about our Tim Curry impression.
We live in a Truman show like Bubble in which our Tim Curry impressions are fantastic.
If one of you yelled, you're terrible, this stage would collapse.
Every time my coworker says cool beans, a part of my soul dies.
What should I do?
I like that.
In and out.
I'm a justice of the peace.
Who sent this question in?
Okay.
Can you give us an idea of the frequency?
Always.
Every where.
Cool beans, cool beans, cool beans.
That must be a horrible existence they live in.
Cool beans to you, sister.
I assume he's the pope.
Yeah.
Or a cult leader.
Is this a business, is this like a serious business place that you work at that-
It's a bank and she says it in a baby voice.
If you're at home listening, she just said, it's a bank and she says it in a baby voice.
Cool beans.
That's about as good as, you should get Charlie out here and see what she can do.
Yeah, she loves being up in front of people in front of hot lights.
Could you counteract it by using hot beans to describe a negative scenario?
Travis, can you give an example of how hot beans would be used negatively?
Oh yeah, Steve's funeral was this weekend, right?
I wasn't able to make it.
How was it?
It was pretty hot beans.
His widow couldn't stop crying and I was just like, oh man, hot beans.
I thought it was going to be like a really cool beans way to say goodbye to our friend.
At least lukewarm beans, at least.
Those beans were hot.
Did you guys see the new Lars von Trier film this weekend?
It was, I mean, I'm not going to admit it, it was hot beans.
It was hot beans.
It's bracing.
It was like he just got up and dumped hot beans everywhere.
What if every time she said cool beans, you adopted a fanciful hobo voice?
Like cool beans?
Why would anybody want cool beans?
You need to start a nice trash fire.
Get some hot beans.
Make you up a, whip you up a sterno oven and get those beans a going.
You can put your beans on a cheese pizza.
No way.
Hold on.
Every, okay, so we've done 13.
This is our 13th live show, which explains why it's so terrible.
I think everyone has had-
Is that what?
How many?
This is our 13th.
Whoa.
Yeah.
And every one, you guys do your fucking Tim Curry impression and it's, if you chart it,
it's like a black hole in the center of the show that the rest of it just gets sucked
back down in.
No, I think we all know what the black hole in the center of our live shows are.
Speaking of.
Oh no.
No.
Earlier, we were talking about doing some Minneapolis research and learning a little
bit about your lovely, lovely city.
Stop.
And so-
I wrote a little report about Minneapolis.
Let's get meta right now because Justin, you birthed this.
No, I tried to stop it.
I tweeted last night, 23 hours ago, exactly.
If this tweet gets 100 faves, I'll let Travis McElroy do a Sad Lives in Minneapolis tomorrow
night.
Please, all caps, do not fave this tweet.
That's a honeypot.
That's a fucking bait tweet.
10 minutes later, 150 faves on the tweet.
People who aren't going to be here at the fucking epicenter.
They catfished you, people.
I'm sorry.
There's 150 people that click.
Fuck you, Minneapolis.
For real, though.
Long story short, I said, well, I'm jacking it up to 500.
That way, we definitely won't have to see Sad Lives as of this exact moment.
That tweet has 718 faves.
You're all scum.
Raise your hand if you've faved that tweet.
It's on you.
I'm out.
Thank you.
I would like to read to you now.
Can we leave?
Are we allowed to-
The brief report I have written about Minneapolis.
Ahem.
Minneapolis, officially, the city of Minneapolis.
This is a fucking Wikipedia page.
You fucking chopped and screwed the Wikipedia page.
I'll start again.
You get paid to do this show.
Minneapolis, officially, the city of Minneapolis is the succulent seat of Hennepin County.
And larger of the twin wangs.
That's not how it originally reads.
Do you guys get it?
The 14th largest metropolitan grundle in the United States.
Containing approximately 3.8 million fannies.
As of 2013, Minneapolis is the largest Jabberwocky in the state of Minnesota.
And the 46th largest in the United States with 400,070 titty sprinkles.
Minneapolis and Mountain Doom anchor the second largest Fauntleroy Center in the American
Midwest behind Chicago.
Minneapolis lies on both banks of the Luda River.
Just north of the river's confluence with the Minnesota River.
And adjoins Funkadocious, the state's capital.
The city is abundantly rich in mangoes.
With 20 lakes and wienerschnitzel.
The Doug Funny River, creeks and aardvarks.
Many connected by picadillos in the chain of lakes.
And the Grand McGuffin National Scenic Byway.
It was once the world's anime capital.
And a hub for Blastoise.
And today is the primary onomatopoeia center between Chicago and John Cena.
With Minneapolis proper containing America's fifth highest concentration of fish titties.
As an integral link to the global economy, Minneapolis is categorized as crumbelievable.
Thank you.
I think Justin's just gone.
Oh, there he is.
We could just do like 30 of those and that could be the whole show.
Do you guys want that?
I have 29 more.
What's that podcast nobody listens to?
Oh, my brother and my brother, where they just do sad libs over and over again.
I hate that show.
Hey, everybody.
Sorry to break in, but we got to make money.
We did make money on the live episode that you're listening to already, but it's all
about diversifying your portfolio.
We owe a lot of people a lot of money and they won't take no for an answer.
Paint us a word picture, Justin, of why we sound so weird right now.
Because we're passing around a microphone and I'm in a robe and we're splitting a seat,
you and I, and I'm straddling the seat and you're sitting on the seat and that's not
a joke.
Who's hungry?
I am.
For NatureBox.
NatureBox is a snack service with zero artificial flavors or colors or sweeteners, no trans
fats, no high fructose corn syrup.
It's nutritious.
It's food you feel good about putting in your body.
Important to note that we're in a hotel because we're about to go to a live show.
This isn't like a thing that we do.
It's just like have buddy-buddy hotel nights every now and then.
Yeah.
Go to NatureBox.
You can get some stuff like sriracha roasted cashews, white truffle popcorn, peanut butter
nom-noms.
Yes, please.
Or personalize your favorites.
I think that's a note for us.
That's probably for us to do, but those actually are my favorites.
My favorites are the lemon almond tea biscuits.
They are delicious and buttery.
I like the sea biscuit.
Oh wait, I wasn't thinking my favorite snack box food, NatureBox snack box, I was thinking
my favorite VHS tape of Blockbuster.
If you go to NatureBox.com slash my brother, you can get a free trial box of their favorite
snacks.
So like that's an awesome deal.
NatureBox.com slash my brother, you get a free box.
Free snacks.
Certainly you're reading that wrong.
Free trial box of your favorite snacks.
So there will be a court involved and jury of your peers and then it's unanimous, yummy,
and that's how the movie The Judge ends with Robert Downey Jr.
It's not a very good flick.
Also if you want to make a website about how good this advertising break has been and who
can blame you, it's been great.
I would suggest you run, don't walk.
Run and then slow down because you're holding a computer.
Walk the rest away, you're going to get exhausted.
Guys is tonight's show going to be a fucking catastrophe?
Run till that to Squarespace.com.
It's an all in one website platform that makes it fast and easy to create your own professional
website.
They got beautiful templates.
There's integration with Google apps and getting images and there's a feature called cover
pages that is not described here.
I'm betting it's really going to change the game of websites.
You can get a free trial box of Squarespace.
Free trial box of internet, all the internet you want for free.
With no credit card required to start building your website today, go to Squarespace.com
and use the code MYBROTHER, all one word and you'll get 10% off your first purchase.
Again, that's Squarespace.com, use the code MYBROTHER.
Squarespace.
Build it.
Two, three.
Beautiful.
Sorry, the syncing is off.
Let me try it one more time.
Read this next message.
Who's this next message?
Who's this next message for?
Poppy and CJ McElroy?
Yeah, it's not what you think.
It's a completely different McElroy family.
There's more than one.
I'm not sure I feel about that.
I knew there was a guy who played on the Colts that was a McElroy, a Greg McElroy, I think
he was-
It's all for Joe McElroy, Corey McElroy.
This is from Mama and Papa.
Happy first birthday, you cool babies.
Your first year has been an adventure and everywhere we go, people love you.
We've learned how to say twins in three other languages and we're ready to learn a couple
more.
We love you.
That's the most precious thing and are we related to them and am I everybody in this
question's dad?
Justin, I'm getting texts and it's vibrating really close to your pizone.
Happy first birthday.
This is the most heartwarming message.
Confirm yes or no.
Check yes or no.
Am I everyone's dad in this message?
Thank you.
Who is this next message for Griffin?
It's for Chris Legue.
I really crushed the pronunciation because they provide it.
And who is it from?
Dan Aiyel.
Shit.
Dan Aiyel writes, I'm just kidding, it's Danielle, I can't see it because Travis has fucked
up the browser.
Thank you, Travis.
Dan Aiyel says to Chris Legue, Chris, please put your clean clothes in your drawers, not
back into the hampers.
Thank you from your loving wife, Danielle.
And also Sydney, please do that as well.
And then it says here, you toast.
It doesn't say that, but that's like an extra burn that I added for Danielle to you, Chris
Legue.
Check yourself.
You toast.
Now back to the show.
Do you guys want another Yahoo?
How about, oh man, there's so many good ones.
This one was sent in by Sarah Gorman.
Thank you, Sarah.
Yahoo answers user Skye who asks, can a ghost puke on you?
Weirdest thing happened to me.
One more time.
Can a ghost puke on you?
Weirdest thing happened to me, I woke up just now and realized that there was puke on me
and next to me.
Nobody in my house did it.
It wasn't my mom, my sister, my stepdad, or any of the animals.
It happened in the last three and a half hours because it wasn't warm.
It was my body temperature.
What the fuck CSI?
Don't touch anything.
This is a crime scene.
This was extremely gross.
Can anyone please help me?
It was the stepdad.
We can all agree it was the stepdad.
Or the stepdad's birds.
The stepdad's train.
Go.
What did you say?
Somebody puke on you?
I don't know.
Have you explored the occult?
I can feel a cold spot in your room.
I wasn't in there, but I heard.
Now, Darlene, I mean, to be fair, I did tell you to not play with the Ouija and you did.
Is that her stepdad, Barack Obama?
Travis, are you telling me that I do a perfect Barack Obama impression?
Because I can add that to the repertoire.
Now, what if Tim Curry and Barack Obama sat down?
I think it might sound a little bit like this.
Here's Johnny.
That's my Jack Nicholson.
We can't rule ghosts.
I mean, rule of thumb for just life.
We can't rule ghosts out.
No, but I guess my question is, why wouldn't you start with, did someone break into my
room from the outside, just completely straight up, puke on me, and say, my work here is done,
and leave?
I really had that coming.
Wait.
Let me check.
I'm going to see if this is...
Okay, so this is from October of 2010, not from April Fool's Day, because that'd be a
fucking great goof.
Just walking like...
Good morning.
Did you see the puke?
Yeah, that was me.
AFD.
Get it?
Did you get it?
It's a commentary on how politics made me sick.
Also, I hate you.
And I needed to yack, I don't know.
Those three things hit together.
She a night puker?
What?
Did I say night?
I'm sorry.
Hold on.
I literally...
One more time?
Can you give it to me again?
You know that REM song, Night Puker?
What I'm saying is maybe she's a night puker.
Night puker.
Perfect.
That's Bay Sleeper.
That's a two-sympath song, which, by the way, Michael Cypher, come on.
Do we have another really super good question?
I think I might have one here.
My husband, Jesse, has been growing his beard out for a year now.
It's large, unruly, catches everything he eats, along with somebody on...
Somebody named Jesse in the audience right now is like, fuck.
It's large, unruly, catches everything he eats.
I know which one it is.
Let me talk about Jesse first.
You don't have to point to him, I fucking see him.
Can I finish talking about Jesse for a second?
It's large...
It says here, he's also a really great guy with a kind soul.
It's large, unruly, catches everything he eats, along with the fact that he looks like
Harry from the 1990s show, Harry and the Hendersons.
His podcast network is going great, but Jesse Thorne joke for...
He's got a big beard now.
It's just nasty, et cetera, et cetera.
Here's the end of the question, which I do want to take a quick break.
The 1990s show, Harry and the Hendersons?
What we're talking about is the TV show, not the fucking great movie with John Lethgow.
The movie I cry hardest at in the entire world, other than Iron Giant.
Not the film.
Which has a lot of similarities, if you think about it.
Not the TV show, which is basically Alf, anyway.
Tall Alf is what...
The original TV show was Super Tall Alf.
This Sunday on Fox, Tall Alf, followed by Big Wonders.
I don't know.
We're throwing some spaghetti at the wall.
Listen.
Empty house.
I don't know.
Fuck it.
Whatever.
Reverse it.
There's an end to the question.
My question to you, I'm intimidated because there's nothing we're going to say that's
funnier than the end of this question.
What is the best way to auction off my husband's beard?
As from Kim.
Quick question.
What?
You...
Okay.
So, auctioning off a beard, that's complicated because you might get a guy come up to you
at the end of the auction when you get the clippers out, Jesse, and you're ready to shave
it off.
He's like, no.
Leave it on.
I own that beard.
Check the small print.
I own that beard exactly where you bought it.
What if he comes in when you're trying to eat some soup or some gazpacho and he covers
your beard with laminates and nothing happens to it because he owns it.
I own that beard.
It's possible.
Yeah.
Ghosts are puking on people.
Stranger things have happened.
I appreciate you jumping just straight into, we're going to auction the beard off.
Not how to convince him to shave it.
No, no, no.
And I like that because I think the three of us maybe could have gotten there on one
of our patented goof riffs that we like to go on, and you just saved us the trouble like
you guys were going to talk about auctioning the beard.
Right now.
We're starting at $5.
$5.
I got $5 right there.
$10.
$20.
$20 right there.
Do I have $50?
$50.
Don't buy it unless you mean it because you know we're going to make you pay cash right
now.
I got 50.
Can I see 50?
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you really have 50?
Who's 50?
Who has $50?
$50 for a beard.
Do I have $75 for a beard?
It's a great beard.
$75.
It's like Landland.
Like Landland.
50 going once.
This feels illegal.
50 going twice.
This is not binding at all.
Sold.
What are we doing?
Give Jesse $50.
You guys can't just fucking do shit.
Sell your beard to a man.
Give him your beard.
Sell your beard.
Let him build a nest.
We don't have a fucking structure in place for removal.
Paypal him the money.
After the show, you two settle up, which I mean shave your beard and give him $50.
Buy three and one-third posters and just give them to him.
Granddad, explain this back.
I like that.
I get a slice.
There we go.
Perfect.
That... Okay.
We were just handed the smallest pair of baby scissors.
He sold them from Baby Charlie.
This is Justin's baby scissors that we're going to use to cut...
It'll take us 16 hours.
We'll finish this just as we arrive in Chicago.
We just sold a man's beard.
We are golden gods.
I'm going to check in with you every 60 seconds just to see how you feel at that point in
time about your money-making decisions in life.
Wait, Hardy.
Why can't we afford to pay rent this month?
I don't know.
I bought a man's beard.
I got caught up in the magic.
I got some kindling for a soup-scented fire.
You remember how you said I should get a merkin?
Good news.
I'm finally investing our money, not wasting it.
I'm building a future for me and the kids and you.
Should we get some folks up here?
No, not yet.
Let me ask this one... Oh, I just called.
Is that a touch screen?
What'd you just do?
I just archived it.
Hold on.
Oh, shit.
Shut up.
Hold on.
Wait.
Here it comes.
How do we get my wife's family to stop giving us shit we don't need or even have any use
for?
We live in a small apartment with a tiny yet perfectly functional kitchen, and they've
given us things like electric griddles, dessert, coops.
What's that?
Coupes.
All right.
It's a fucking... It's a tiny... You went to culinary school.
It's a fucking rad drop-top car that you drive cakes around in.
And a giant plug-in roaster we've literally never used.
They've also dumped tons of crafty shit and clothes we don't need on us.
They're not rich.
They just like to express their love and affection through stuff.
Ah, fuck them.
As from too much stuff in the Twin Cities.
Now, Justin, it actually says too much shit in the Twin Cities.
Did we hit our limit on cursing?
Then you're like, oh, that's it.
We're done.
We hit our limit on cursing in 2012.
This was y'all who have the stuff problem.
Here's what you get to do.
This is awesome.
You get to be like adult to younger friend Santa Claus.
22-year-olds love crafty shit.
You're saying a 22-year-old's going to get a roaster and be like, yeah.
They won't even know what it does, but they won't have one already.
Just pour fiddle-faddle onto it while it's turning.
I don't...
Am this roasting?
You're right.
It's the flavor.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
This sucks.
I think...
Well, the obvious solution, of course, is to take all of it to Antiques Roadshow.
A lot of people do that.
Wait, wait.
No, wait.
Stop.
Antiques Roadshow?
Yeah.
They're not like, oh, crafty shit.
No, this is crafty shit from yesterday.
No, no, no.
I'm saying a lot of people do this, and it's like a Antiques Roadshow hack is...
I read about that on BuzzFeed.
Are you tired of enjoying Antiques Roadshow like all the plebs?
Well, now it's time to find the express lane.
If you plug your Antiques Roadshow into a watermelon, you'll never believe what happens.
Okay, tell me about your Antiques Roadshow hack.
You take all your garbage to Antiques Roadshow, and they'll give you a little lot, and you
stand there, and you put all your shit there.
And then they come back, and they're like, all right, Baker family, you're...
Hey, where'd you go?
Oh, no.
They left all their shit.
Another one.
And then that is their problem, and they have to deal with it.
It's a pretty circuitous...
Mark Wahlberg, take care of this garbage.
Are you...
Okay.
And they're like, oh, my God, wait, this was President Roosevelt's roaster.
It's engraved, yummy, yum, it's chicken time, President Roosevelt.
It says it right there.
He used this to win the Spanish-American War.
Is that a thing that he did?
I like the idea...
Shh.
There were two of them, so your odds are pretty good.
I like the idea that the Antiques Roadshow people will, even if it's not old, fake it.
Oh, this is old.
Yeah.
This bedazzled tea, well, might surprise you to learn.
Betsy Ross was big into bedazzling.
The original American flag was hyper color.
Not a lot of people know that.
A lot of people don't know that.
Let's get some people up here.
Does that help?
Okay.
Right here.
Now, here's the thing.
Come on up.
There is one rule when it comes to the questions.
No bombers.
Right.
They gotta be comedy.
If you are bombing, we will throw you off the stage.
Come on up.
You got any more Diet Coke in that can?
I didn't bring any mixers.
Just booze.
Nope.
All right, ma'am.
Hi.
Hello.
Hey, how's it going?
Good.
Great.
What's your name?
Really good.
We're in Minneapolis.
So am I.
Anyone here else from Minneapolis?
Just a quick question.
Anybody actually projecting tonight?
I'm not from here.
She's just in Minneapolis.
Okay.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
What's your name?
Katie.
I'm Katie.
Hi.
Hi, Katie.
To be fair, I'm not from Minneapolis.
No.
Easy, Katie.
Nice.
Listen, I'm not gonna...
It's the biggest of the twin wags.
This is a short mic.
Okay, what's the question, Katie?
I'm gonna crouch.
How can I help?
Yeah, this will help.
How can you help me?
One of my part-time jobs is really super related to pizza.
Okay.
Is that possibly at a pizza place?
No, it's not.
It's really adjacent.
It's really...
Do you describe what pizza looks like to blind people?
It's...
I got that out.
I eat it for them and then describe it.
Well, they can taste the fucking pizza.
Hold on.
Stop eating better than sighted people.
That's how that works.
I know.
Stop eating blind people's pizza.
I have not a job, Katie.
You're just a dick.
I don't even...
How's the pizza, Katie?
Money, please.
I don't even have a question.
I just wanted to point out what an asshole I am.
Okay.
Take care, Katie.
It's a nice cheese pizza.
I don't need to stand up like a human.
What's your pizza job?
Hey, so one of my part-time jobs is very pizza related, as I said, and as a consequence of
that, at least two to three times a day, I get people posting on my Facebook wall pizza
related things like, hey, look at this pizza decorated car.
Look at this three-tiered pizza wedding cake.
And almost every time, they're like, it's right up your alley, this pizza thing.
It's really hard to relate to this because we three brothers don't have anything that
we've publicly said we liked, or a Facebook group where people might post things about
that constantly.
Hey, I found some horses to try this.
To be fair, you did create the group.
You kind of asked for it.
That's true.
All the ghosts and horses are your fault.
I would love a horse dumpster that I just am the admin of.
I would like a well that people-
HorseDumpster.com.
HorseDumpster.horse.
I would love a well in my backyard that people just threw horses down all day.
All right.
So the problem is just people think you're the pizza person now, and you've left.
Yeah, so it's this.
Okay.
It's very job.
I don't really know why.
So there are people even that I haven't spoken to for 15 years that just by virtue of knowing
me on Facebook will post these pizza related things.
And I don't expect really to be able to get it to stop.
That's not going to happen.
But I'm out of responses.
Like I'm at the point now where I'm like, yeah.
Zombie.
Like.
I'm not just like, hi, cool.
That's like my response.
It starts to feel disingenuous.
Yeah.
For sure.
Okay.
I see your point.
Katie.
Yes.
I have two suggestions.
One, just Google commonly said words by the Ninja Turtles.
And every time somebody posts anything, just like, cowabunga.
I was going to say, I'm copy pasting cowabunga from here on out.
Just do that every time.
Secondly, I can tell you how to make it stop.
In your question, you stated that it's a lot of it is people who you haven't spoken to
in 15 years.
And the thing is, and this is real advice, you guys.
Stop chuckling.
Oh, man.
You know what I'm going to say.
You need to kill them.
No.
No, but what it is, is it's people who want to catch up to you, want to relate to you,
but they only know the one fact about you.
And that's the worst part of it.
I'm a very multidimensional person.
I like a lot of things.
Right.
So what Travis is saying is you got to.
I like Batman.
You got to start sharing.
Other things.
You got to start posting more on your Facebook.
Like really excited for this new Batman thing.
Go hard.
You got to be like, can't wait for that new Batman movie.
Also fuck pizza.
I'm done with that pizza week shit.
Also, I'm really glad I get that money for my pizza job.
But it ain't what I'm about.
Did y'all see Interstellar?
It was crazy.
I'm really into space now.
Not pizza so much.
My favorite thing about Interstellar was how little pizza there was in it.
There was like zero pizza.
Matt Damon woke up and said, oh, my God, another person.
Did you bring pizza?
That would have been a way better scene.
That would have been super good.
Thank you so much, Katie.
Thank you, Katie.
Katie!
Let's get somebody from this side.
Yes, you.
First hand, I saw go up.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do I have time to get more ginger ale?
Because I'm going to get top 10 drunk if I don't slow it down.
I'm asking you.
You're my brother.
Oh.
Do you want us to go get you ginger ale?
No.
Do I have time to go get ginger ale?
We're in the middle of the show.
Wait a minute.
Do you have time before he gets up here?
Is this the show?
I thought we were just getting them hot.
Getting them ready.
Getting you warmed up for the third podcast of the evening.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Night Vale.
Yeah!
Look at that fucking crushing it.
Just for those of you listening at home, ginger ale happened.
Hi, what's your name?
Hi.
My name is Mark with a C from the Twin Cities.
Oh, good, because I was going to say Mark really hard.
Mark, is your question a bummer?
No, it's not.
Okay, great.
No, no, no.
God!
Unless.
Unless you don't make it a bummer.
Well, don't put the onus on us, Mark.
It's up to you guys.
If your question leads us to a bummer, you're equally at fault.
I thought it was my brother, my brother, and me, not my brother, my brother, and a
guy named Mark, because then...
It's also not called throwing shade, Mark.
Mark, what is your question?
Yeah, so I have this thing where I never text my friends back in a promptly manner.
Cool.
It's not...
Someone just yelled the worst.
Katie, your time's done.
There's a real Greek choir thing happening in this audience right now.
It's a Minnesota thing.
Minnesota people speak out.
Yeah.
I like that about you all.
Don't ever change.
So I don't text people back in a timely manner, and it's gotten really bad to the point where
one of my friends started an Excel spreadsheet where they calculate how long it takes me
to respond back.
Cool.
Great.
Like over there.
Okay.
Go ahead.
And a lot of it, it's not like I don't want to respond.
It's more like...
It's usually questions like, can you hang out tonight?
Can you hang out this weekend?
A lot of it's like, I don't know yet, because I have a job that's very random and dynamic
and I work weird hours.
So I just don't text anything back.
And it's starting to feel like I'm the asshole in this situation, which is...
It's starting.
I am fixing to fix my hands.
Which is true and valid.
But it's more like, I don't know.
Is there a thing I should say?
Thanks, sound dude.
Okay.
Mark.
Is there a thing I should text?
Is there a thing I should do?
Do you just sometimes not respond?
I just don't respond.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hmm.
This is my favorite type of question, Mark.
Because the answer is...
It's a short answer.
The answer is, start texting them back.
Yeah.
Thank you.
No, no, but my point is like, I don't know what to say, right?
Because I don't know my schedule.
All they're looking for is recognition that you've received.
So all you gotta say is like, I'll let you know.
How about just a cordial gotcha?
Just like, yup.
You don't have to...
Or just send back animoticon.
Just a smiley face every time, so like, I don't know what that means, but clearly he
got it.
He said, dog, dog, pizza, pizza, and then the poop one.
So I think that might be a yes.
I think he might be right.
Yeah.
Just text them back.
Has anyone checked on Mark lately?
He's lost his mind.
He's very into...
For now, Mark, if you don't...
Sometimes you don't know what to say.
Just text him a link in bmbam.com.
What?
TeenGoogle.com.
TeenGoogle.com for all your teen...
No, just tell them...
GriffinSpaceJam.com.
I feel you.
I really do feel you.
I really do.
But you got to tell them about your absence of information that you have that you can't
plan shit yet.
I want to do that.
Let me see if I can make it work.
Mark, next time you get a text and you don't respond, I want you to imagine staring the
person dead eyes.
Just staring them dead...
Staring their persona in the eye.
Just staring them dead in the eyes and not saying anything.
Just imagine that's your text response to them just...
You have to say...
If you were in your real life, in RL, you would say, a something.
You take that and you just type it, and then you're good.
We fixed your life, Mark.
Thank you.
You actually really helped.
That genuinely helped.
Travis, do you want to pick one?
You haven't picked one yet.
Oh, okay.
Let's see.
Who else has picked one?
Oh, okay, let's see, who else has one?
She's reaching really hard and she's far in the back.
Yeah, come on up.
Come on up.
There's a center aisle.
If you can get to it.
Oh, Sunday school.
I just got it.
Cause ice cream.
Yeah.
Sunday school.
That was like bad joke inception.
The best punch line for that is, French class.
It's classic.
Honey, I shrunk the kids.
Any honey?
I shrunk the kids.
Holy shit.
You...
Get up here faster, please.
Jesus, I'm dead.
Well, in three days.
All right.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, wait a minute.
We forgot to make the joke.
Travis just made a really...
Hold on.
Travis just made the worst Good Friday goof in the goddamn history of speech.
We were going to make a great goof about how this is our Good Friday.
No way.
We were going to make a great Friday.
No, but that's gone now.
Now that's gone.
Hi, what's your name?
My name is Lauren.
Hi, Lauren.
Hello, Lauren.
Hi.
So I have a couple of roommates in the house that me and my fiance live in.
Okay.
And one of them cooks quite a bit.
Is your fiance here?
Yeah.
He's right there.
Long hair.
Hey, how's it going?
Hello.
Okay.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
And basically she cooks a lot.
Makes a lot of dishes.
We're cool with that.
We can sometimes eat it.
Or we do...
We sometimes eat it.
She leaves the stuff out on the countertop, usually overnight, and open in the fridge
for days.
No!
How?
Is she an animal?
Like gonzo?
Is she a beast?
Did you allow a wolverine into your home?
Maybe.
That's the worst thing I've ever heard.
Right?
And I read the newspaper.
So braggy.
Also, it's highlights.
But go ahead.
What do we do?
Okay.
Yell at her.
Yell at her really, really...
Like this.
What are you doing?
That volume is the...
If you do it any less, she's not gonna get the...
What are you doing?
You're ruining everything.
This isn't what George Washington in The Founding Fathers did.
What if she's watching TV, she's enjoying some Dance Moms, and you just walk over with
an open container of rigatoni and just dump it on her lap?
Peel the fucking skin off everything and then weave it into a fucking jacket and give it
to her for Christmas with a note card that says, fuck you, on it.
You're the worst.
I have one...
I have a clarification question.
When she cooks this stuff, is she cooking it under the auspices of like, I am cooking
for you, I'm cooking for the house, or is she cooking and she makes too much so everybody
gets to eat the leftovers?
Great question, Trav.
Thanks.
So her name is Hannah.
She's super sweet.
She just...
Fuck you, Hannah.
Go ahead.
Come on.
She's not here.
Hey, will you play that for her?
Is she listening?
No.
Play that for her.
Okay.
I will.
I think we might have libeled her, but go ahead.
I want this human to know where she's at with me.
So she loves to cook, and anybody who loves to cook just cooks for an army.
What you're describing is she likes to start to cook and then not complete what I would
call the most important step, finishing.
Yeah.
Somebody just yelled cleaning up.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You got there ahead of me, but you're right.
Wait, wait.
He's talking about cleaning up.
I'm going to nail this.
In case he forgets the words at the last second, I'm going to give him those words, and I'll
appreciate that.
What's it called when you have the shit out and it's dirty?
It's like, it's dirty, and you need to do something about it to make it not dirty.
God damn it.
Cleaning down.
Oh, shit.
Dirty up.
Nope.
Fuck.
I'll get there.
I clean up as I could.
I put stuff away as soon as I serve the plate.
I put it away.
Brag.
Brag, brag, brag.
It bothers me if something sits out.
Are you reading the newspaper like, no, polish, polish, polish.
Do you have a house spirit?
Because that might be...
Wait, but you have other roommates, right?
This is one of a couple.
So it's me and my fiance.
He owns the house.
We have one roommate who is also here.
Corey.
Hi.
A victor.
The winner of the...
Hey, out there.
A victor.
You're going to need to nail a board list with house rules up on the door.
It's just like, one rule, clean up.
You're the Martin Luther of rigatoni cleanup.
You are going to need to get a Martin Luther costume.
Do you have one already?
Okay.
No home should be without.
For sale over there, posters and Martin Luther costumes.
Has any of this been good?
Huh?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
You weren't even paying attention.
All right.
Yeah, yeah.
Something like that.
There you go.
Thank you, and I love your nail polish.
What's that?
I love Travis's nail polish.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
How sweet.
Nobody ever says anything about it.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
Quick, quick, quick.
It's almost over, but let me holler at you just one last time.
Thanks to naturebox.com where you can order hundreds of great tasting healthy snacks.
Go to naturebox.com slash my brother to sign up for your free sample box of great tasting
healthy snacks.
Let's close out.
I'm excited to get to the final Yahoo because it's so fucking transcendent.
Okay.
So, Minneapolis, thank you so much.
It's been great.
It's been a super good show.
You guys are like the most fun ever.
Don't forget about the posters.
They're really, really incredible.
Please, listen, I do not know what we will do with posters that say Minneapolis on them.
If you don't buy all of them, we're fucked.
So grab them.
Thanks to John Roderick and the Long Winters for using our theme song, It's a Departure
Off the Album, Putting the Days to Bed.
Is he here?
No?
Okay.
Somebody just went, hey.
Hey.
Oh, shit.
I almost forgot about John Roderick.
I know this part.
Thank you to Sawbones for doing an amazing job opening for us.
Thank you to everybody here at the Cedar Cultural Center.
This is like, this is a pretty fucking rad venue.
You guys didn't get to go back in the green room, but it's pretty cool.
There's a baby back there and everything.
It's a fully stocked green room.
Yeah, everybody's been really, really nice.
Yeah, this has been tremendous.
Thank you guys so much.
Yeah, Minneapolis, you've been super, super, super nice to us.
Finally, I...
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna read...
Okay, buckle up.
It's gonna go for a while.
Every episode of My Brother, My Brother, Me, we have one final Yahoo Answers question that
we will ponder over the next week.
And then...
This one's meaty.
This one's gonna have...
You're gonna be chewing on this one for a while.
So as always, stick with us.
We return to it next week and we talk about it.
Every time.
Don't.
We've always done this.
And Griffin, do you have one to close this out this week?
I do.
I wanna read the actual question, and this is unprecedented, I'm gonna read the additional
details to you.
So...
This is really fucking good.
Stick with it.
A ton of people sent this in, including John Jarzymski, David Jackson, Zoe Kinski, and
probably a bunch of other people.
Thank you all so much.
It's by Yahoo Answers user Frankie, who asks, can I get my dad arrested for not letting
me drop out of school to become Zane Malick's replacement in One Direction?
That's nothing.
Okay.
So, I want to drop out of school forever, because I am tired of this teacher bullying
me.
Today he said I smelled like a whore's handbag.
WTF is he even talking about?
I was smelling like aftershave, a nice one.
So I drew up a plan to show my dad I am very serious about this.
It goes, one, leave school, two, be a zookeeper.
But then I heard about Zane, so I'm willing to take that vacancy.
Cool trajectory.
I have got better at faking English accent, and I would like lots of girlfriends.
He didn't even look at my plan.
He just got mad, saying for the last time, I'm not leaving school.
Said next time I mention it, I will automatically get a slap.
This is a democracy.
I'm tired of him saying no to everything.
Can I get a parrot?
No.
Can I go to Manchester with my friend?
Can I have one more beer?
No.
Can I have some money?
So I started saying no to everything he says to me, and he had the audacity to get mad
at me and yell, you don't tell me no.
I am the dad.
I do this for you.
I do that for you, blah, blah, blah.
I am a massive dickhead, blah, blah.
Please arrest him, and I will have fun.
Fun.
I'm Justin McElroy.
I'm Travis McElroy.
I'm Griffin McElroy.
It's been my brother Robby, kiss your dad's square on the lips.
I'm Travis McElroy.